This week the media learns of the thrilling concept of
simulations being a fantastic way to teach and prepare someone for a new
situation the gaming generation are now parents and able to make this point
that's just one story join us for the rest of the week's gaming news starting
right now on the show where every gamer has a voice orange lounge radio hello my
friends out there on the internet welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice it is orange lounge radio live tonight with
episode number 786 of our show for this July the 28th of 2019 my name is Rob
Roberts joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games gaming
culture and the gamer lifestyle with my co-hosts in studio not on camera cuz she
doesn't want to be even though her new hair is a really rad color here I mean
it's not like new hair she's not like she's oh there you go so so so once in a
while she wants to be on camera the shadow route orange you there she is
DarkSakura or Jamie Summers hi is orange orange orange you glad you're here at
OLR tonight yes you could have so happy to be on the show you could have still
been playing all sorts of pinball and classic arcade games in San Jose but
you're here with us no I couldn't cuz Dan wanted to come home oh what a like
I'm tired I was toddler tired what a party pooper yeah all right anyway we do
tape live of course every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific 9 o'clock Eastern
right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at twitch TV twitch.tv slash vog network and
I'm saying that because I'm reading some comments from chat where stu 100 Matt
says orange hair radio and Spyro Jonathan says heck yeah orange hair
radio so did you dye your hair orange because you are that devoted to this
show as if 17 years of your life wasn't enough bitch I might be I'm actually not
gonna be bleaching my roots anymore because you know it's bad for your hair
to over bleach I wouldn't know I don't I don't have hair anymore well so why do
you think I wear hats those on the camera can see it's dark up here I'm
gonna be going really red and growing out this orange part to wear when my
hair's long it's gonna be like flame point I'm thinking ahead this is gonna
be like a three-year endeavor it looks worse on cam that it really is like I
sort it like it looks like it's just like completely bald on top but I do
have some hair it looks worse on cam I think but not but bald is beautiful so
I don't give a fuck so whatever it gives you an excuse to have interesting hats
too yeah it is I'd like the hats are a good accessory why not you you ladies
get to pick your purses that match well not that gender roles should define
anything but the majority of you know American culture is that you pick a
purse to go with your outfit why should I say queens yeah exactly right but if I
wanted to pick take a purse then god damn it I'm gonna take a purse exactly
all right bring back the murse all right anyway I had a murse we talked about
that another time all right anyway hello I don't mean to ignore Loki techmaster
Loki over there that's fine but you're equal number one I'm thinking you don't
have a lot to contribute to the purse discussion no and I can clearly see
you're over there catching Pokemon yes because apparently my house is a how hot
bed of Pokemon no just because I haven't done it in a while and because I don't
know yeah I'm out of the loop so you know to that guy that reviewed us on
iTunes saying they talk about nothing but Pokemon go those days are numbered I
haven't played some review I shouldn't even acknowledge the negative reviews
but it is what it is yeah yeah but you can always leave a positive review if
you want to offset that stuff for the record there's jack shit at your house
what they had a thing where you get you hatched or you get a dratini and then
you have to take a picture of it and then that picture got me one of those
smear goal things and so I had to catch that oh I didn't do that I caught a
dratini but I didn't take a picture of it yeah I've kind of fallen off the
wagon on this quest like I guess today was the in here we are talking about
anyway today was like that Team Rocket type of my game well they keep doing it
on Sunday night well I can hit it though before when I leave the house to come
here I can hit the pokestop by my house so here's the weird thing like so
Pokemon go gave my phone a new background I don't know why like it
changed my wallpaper did you tell it it could no it just did it like it crashed
the wallpaper is it a cute Pikachu no it's just like it's just like some pink
like looks like like a mountain range or something I had like weird it's supposed
to be a simulation of earth with like the lighting and everything and the
cloud cover is supposed to match with what the weather satellites are because
that's kind of cool and now it's gone all right whatever background on y'all's
phone I have a picture of mr. smoosh on my well you can't see it right now
because I have apparently Twitter alerts that are in the way oh because that's a
good thing because y'all are promoting the show tonight because I barely did
but I have a picture of mr. smoosh is the background of my phone you guys
probably can't even see it from that far away but that's what I have I try to
take a picture of a dratini to see if that would count and it doesn't you can
turn off the AR thing and and it's a lot easier to do pictures and so I wanted to
take the AR because I did it on top of my macbook and it's got your knee in the
picture oh my sexy knee I'm sure I'm I'm being a little bit of a that neither
tonight by showing off my knees that knee uh-huh all right anyway it's hot
today I can't how could I not wear shorts everybody's wearing shorts
because it's 106 today here in lovely Sacramento where we're based the ambient
temperature coming off of my car when I got in it was 115 Wow right well all
right anyway let's let's talk about the weather more talk about games and dark
soccer you braved the weather this weekend because you went on a road trip
off to San Jose right I didn't brave the weather I left it but so tell us a was
like it didn't get any hotter than like 88 you know that's that's typical Bay
Area but anyway tell us about California extreme it was the thing I go to every
year basically in a nutshell California extreme is a big gaming Expo where they
have like a huge ballroom full of pinball classic games music games and
they've got a big candy cab section now the Japanese style cabinets and then
they have like a whole other room now that's just like a big meeting room
that's also full of games and then they have a vendor room upstairs with a stage
to do rock band kind of how allowed did their thing and then you know classic
consoles also set up up there so it was really good it goes on for two days I
forgot what time it opens I think it opens at like 9 or 10 but it goes to 2
in the morning on Saturday and then Sunday all day and people you know bring
their own machines some people sell them there Stern has a big presence and I
twice ran into Steve Ritchie and he's like oh hi cuz you know we're Facebook
buddies it's funny yeah and he was I was like let's get a picture together he's
like I got to go take my pills I'm like okay Steve he's not a chicken of the
spring anymore but he's he's just a good guy he and his wife are the nicest
people you'll ever meet but they had all kinds of really good games which I could
go ahead and do now and get my gaming week out of the way for everything I
played yeah well I was hoping there might be stuff outside of for that but
oh sorry well no I hardly played anything outside of California stream
except for the usual we'll get into a little bit of what you what you played a
California stream then okay so I played Black Knight Sword of Rage which was
amazing as always and if you were ever gonna buy a Black Knight Sword of Rage
get premium don't get the pro the premium that brand new table yeah maybe
three months old they had the miss pac-man mini like the cabinet that's
like like a two-thirds my height but there's like those arcade one-up
machines yeah I think that's what they were interesting I didn't I'm surprised
that those are kind of yeah those have an interesting place in this day and age
right because like I would think in some ways those might be frowned on because
they're not authentic miss pac-man's but they sure do give a fairly authentic
experience with the screens the screens really a big difference like you can
really notice the screens on those arcade one-ups are not the same thing
you remember playing oh really and then they had an even smaller one that didn't
look like it was in the same thing so it could have been custom but it was an
ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 so that's some interesting ones ones there they didn't
have any of like I mean those are almost like the junior size one but they didn't
have the junior size Neo Geo you know I bet that arcade one-up company was
probably like advertising there actually they probably had some type of deal to
have their machines there because that is the perfect crowd to be selling the
those things to you know classic arcade game fans with disposable income that is
like that is their crowd so I wouldn't be surprised if those machines were
there because like arcade one-up kind of wanted them there and they did have from
what I could notice fewer of the pinball and arcade board vendors and more of the
classic video game vendors although I tried to find Saturn and turbo graphic
stuff and they were very sparse they still the place that I buy from tiny
potato I really like those guys I hang you know hang out and chat with them
every year but they have a copy of cotton for PlayStation that I would
really like to buy but it's 90 bucks I keep waffling on it you know but I mean
it was really a fun time all the vendors were really nice everyone was really
friendly and chatty and one of the vendors watched me open a couple of
blind boxes cuz he went in I said he's like can I predict him first I'm like
sure so he shakes the two of them I grabbed like the dig dug blind set which
you could get one of three characters so you know he had two out of three choice
like this one is a puka and this one is the I always forget the name of the
dragon the fry gar fry gar is like this one's a fry I wanted to say that's a
video game cuz the game rygar yeah I was thinking rygar and I was like so he
shook him is like this one's a fry gar this one's a puka so when I opened them
one was a fry gar one was a puka I wouldn't have minded a dig-dug but I
like having the baddies so they're cool and pukas are cute but at any rate I
they really they were missing some stuff this year just some things that I
expected to be there this year that were not there were lots of panels Steve
Ritchie did a panel about developing Black Knight there was one about DJ max
oh wow yeah 730 and I I didn't go to it cuz I was hanging out with melody but
Mel went to it which by the way preview preview we may have Mel on yeah yeah I
heard yeah he was thinking about is he gonna come up here we doing something
awesome I would love to have love to have him back on the show talk about the
have a DDR night infinity stage yeah that he's gonna be working with but you
know there was a pretty decent music game section but they didn't I was
looking for a couple of things they didn't have it although they did have
that nostalgia game by Konami that looks kind of like a keyboard but not really a
keyboard I think I know what you're talking about it's it's a newer game
right yeah yeah I think Musica which I finally got to play it was fun they had
my my do you know what my my is uh yeah circle that's got the button yeah
pattern I played that and it had an oppa oppa song so I was very happy I'm not
great at it you know it's just my first time playing it but I think I did okay
so as they had a bunch of DJ max though they had some you beat they had a couple
of the bishi bashi so that was pretty fun they had a real prop cycle another
prop cycle Adams family they did had an Adams family though but you know there
was there were certain the blastroids that used to belong to us was there so
it was pretty funny dance like I'm gonna go see our blastroids but anyway so what
I played there was I played Black Knight Sword of Rage I played the Miss Pac-man
mini I played Pac-man and chomp chomp which is a very weird little more recent
Pac-man game JJ squawkers which thought I played Sonic the fighters I played
azumanga daioh puzzle bobble so it's basically puzzle bobble with the girls
from azumanga daioh in it so easy peasy I played my my I played virtual on
oratorio tangram which was really fun they were in the Japanese cabinets and
they were back-to-back and I was just trying to play through you know the
story mode and this one person just keeps challenging challenging chill I'm
like I was just so stubborn I was like I just want to beat you and be done and
you kept doing over and over and like six games and I'm like okay I'm done and
I just let him win you know I just ran in with the sword and it's like if you
can beat me at close range then you win and so I walked around and just poked
him on the shoulder I was like good game dude and he's like it's a girl you know
like the total it's a girl look like a girl speaks to me pretty much like the
ending of Metroid for the very first time yeah but I played Dodon Pachi I
played Big Bang bar so they had a Big Bang bar but it was I think it was a
repro because the glass on it they played Musica I played some regular old
pac-man but it wasn't one of those I forgot what they're called like the
marquee cabinets the the narrower ones with a smaller screen yeah I know what
you're talking about but I don't know the name call them something and I
remember did if you bring up pac-man did they have my all-time fave baby pac-man
I didn't see baby pac-man I would have played the shit out of it I saying for
those of you that go Google baby pac-man if you don't know it cuz baby pac-man
the reason why I love that game so much I remembered as a kid it is half like
pac-man arcade game but then there's a point where when you go out the tunnels
you don't like warp to yet well you do when you go out the side when you go
there's tunnels in the bottom and when you go out the bottom tunnels you drop
into a pinball board and so it's half pac-man half pinball and it's so cool I
didn't play journey either because apparently the joystick was a little
messed up but I also played you know crazy auto which was a kind of backwards
retheme of miss pac-man because miss pac-man started life as a pac-man like
expansion yeah I was like a pac-man plus and they were gonna release it under the
name crazy auto with a walking character and everything and then you know Namco
and shit happened and miss pac-man I also played a Beatlemania pinball and I
played the Sega Tetris that's got the big fat blocks like you only have like
ten block spaces to work with it's kind of hard but it was really fun I really
enjoyed it and there was also you know there was a few others a bunch of cave
shooters like mushihime sama and and what was battle garega
what else did I play no it was do don pachi that I played because I love that
game but yeah they just had all kinds of neat stuff I mean there were there were
a bunch of you know the street fighter ones like starting from third impact all
the way up through five they had an arcade machine for five and they had
multi blood you know just all kinds of neat import games over in that area so
it was it was really neat you know just a fun time and hanging out with my
friends and you know ran into Bradley like you do and I played with the
toddler what kind of like vendors were there cuz aren't there usually like
around the edges of the rooms there's like some vendors selling like classic
arcade things like what did you see there was like one DIY vendor outside
doing like etched glass and there was another one inside also doing etched
glass like for mugs and shot pint glasses and shot glasses and then you
know I said there weren't so many we pinball part vendors like there were in
previous years Marco pinball of course is one of the sponsors with Stern for
bringing in a lot of the because they have it that big stern section that had
like Black Knight Deadpool all of that and so they were selling parts and stuff
from Marco there was the shirt vendors for California extreme there were just a
lot of like kitschy knick-knack II stuff for for the video game merch like the
blind boxes and Mario mugs and there was a doormat that I wanted one that says
welcome to Peach's castle it was kind of cute and they had like throws and
everything like blankets and this is nothing super exciting maybe you know if
I was trying to decorate my teenage bedroom that might be something or if
you know we start getting into decorating the game room or something it
was it was all nice stuff you know I got my two little things to put on my desk
at work and I got patches actually I got an Atari patch I got a mass link shield
the Hyrule shield patch and I got a a super mushroom because I'm gonna make a
patch jacket so fun you need to get some of those old-school Activision
achievement patches for your jacket I'll see I would love that I would look so
many issues reprose there's got to be reprose of that I would love to get an
awesome jacket with like all the Activision badges I think that would be
cool yeah that's got to be like an Etsy or something one of those things I wish
Activision themselves would do it though you know because they as much love or
hate Activision in their current state today for those of us that were you know
cool kid Atari 2600 folks like you know it would be it would be nice to you know
get our get our hands on some of that type of merch right oh so I did buy a
few things though oh yeah I bought the compact old-school Game Boy case it's
this well they can on the podcast anyway so anyway it's it's actually honestly
about the length of this microphone okay and it has enough space for they can see
mine it has enough room in it for a Game Boy on one side and then maybe like
four games total on the other I think I used to have one of those cases it's a
hard case and I was like I don't have a Game Boy to put in it we don't have an
old-school Game Boy anymore but I could make like a purse or something out of it
it'd be fun or you know like a first aid kit yeah you know I thought it would be
neat I only paid five bucks for it and then I got the Game Gear magnifier I
mean he wanted eight bucks for it but I actually got the two items together for
ten bucks you know cuz you haggle you haggle when you go to the classic gaming
table and then I got a game called air adventures for Saturn that I never
played but like they this one guy traded it in with a stack of other games and
when the fellow was looking it up it's like it was only worth the dollar I was
like I'll give you two bucks for it okay so I took it sight unseen two bucks
because it's another Saturn game and I thought it'd be fun to try something new
you know that hadn't played before and yeah I didn't really do like a whole
bunch of shopping in it my knee t-shirts you know but they had some fun little
stuff and I love blind boxes so I now have my poop puka and fry car you need
to you start a YouTube channel opening blind boxes do you know like how popular
those types of videos are yeah but these aren't it these are different than like
those little blind boxes the gift blind boxes it's people like order like the
Amazon returns or the blind boxes on Etsy or not Etsy but eBay you know those
are the ones that get money or the people who buy the storage units I know
let me ask you one more thing about California stream and then we'll get on
into the rest of our gaming weeks the type of stuff we've been playing but you
know you've been going to the convention for several years now what was your
favorite thing about the convention this year and well let's start there what was
your favorite thing about the convention this year um I don't know
just I guess more seeing my friends the people yeah that's fair that they
hanging out with nerds hanging out with nerds heck yeah that's one of my
favorite actually Dragon Con mag fest any kind of into the two things that I
heard the most that made me happy was one I like your hair and number two I
like your shirt I was wearing my crazy red shirt for Animal Crossing that says
seems legit oh I was gonna wear my chica shirt and I was like you know I'm
gonna wear crazy red it's a little a little bit bigger it's a little more
comfortable and everyone's like oh my god you're sure let me take let me take
a picture of your shirt okay and then I think probably the obvious follow-up to
that would be what would be one thing that you would want to see them do next
year that they haven't done yet I want or they're not doing I would like a
whole room of nothing but I'd like them to put the candy cabs and the Bahmani
the music games in their own room that sounds like a get you go you'd like so
much noise pollution though and that but I guess I guess if you set up barriers
the right way if you kind of thought it through there'd probably be a way to
make it a little more tolerable and the other there's actually one other thing
because I was when I was talking to tiny potato guys there they said that they
weren't given any lighting where they were so people couldn't they had to go
to Target and buy lamps and I was like you really need to take better care of
your vendors you know don't put people in dark little corners with no lighting
that's not fair to them if you were gonna have the vendors be in a place
other than where they usually are you need to make sure you have sufficient
lighting so that people can see those items and they're not wasting money
renting the space okay that's good feedback I think that's exactly the type
of thing I think would be good for them to hear but I think that next year
though I actually want to officially try to go as press next year I want to go
period because I've missed it so many years in a row but this is also you know
in generally like personally this is also a hard weekend so it's like you
know it's just just a bad time of year for it you know yeah but I'm gonna put
in for press next year you should so that we can go in and interview people
and do panels good panels yeah I get some of the get some of them for some
some break segments get some interviews that'd be awesome maybe we should even
like petition to do a panel you never know I mean at this point we would be a
classic podcast don't you think classic podcast they have games from 2002 in
there that are classic games I think there was there was also another game in
there I forgot the name of it but it was like the super field goal football
baseball mixture game it was kind of weird yeah Bobby and Chad is saying I'd
love to go to probably won't be able to swing it yeah I think him and I are in
similar predicaments as to why he can't come out here for California extreme and
why I can't go out there for the southern fried gaming expo which is
really it's really their equivalent is what that that show is so yeah but I
mean it's really it's really fun you know I had a great time like like I
said earlier I was toddler tired when I was done because I didn't want to stop
playing but I was tired was it that super slam-dunk yeah yeah we had that
guy on the show a long time because they were at gamer X yeah second or third
year yeah we had them remembered it but everyone in dance pinball group was like
oh it's so much fun yeah it's a fun game they had a killer be there it's been out
a while now that a killer be a killer Queen that was it which I still haven't
played that game but everyone says it's really fun so Bobby and Chad says yeah
the toddler tired thing is why I got a hotel room at southern fried so I didn't
have to drive home at night and yeah I think that's why I like a lot of people
like kind of even if the convention is like right by you you know a lot of
people if they have the income I mean certainly you know how much money you do
or don't have and are able to spend on that type of stuff plays a factor but if
you're fortunate enough to be able to swing it like I think a lot of people
are just like I'm just gonna plan to stay on site they're doing a big ingress
thing in downtown Sacramento on October 12th I'm considering getting a hotel
room in downtown Sacramento because of the whole toddler tired thing yeah I
need to get in on that information yeah you do you do come join us anyway all
right let's talk about the rest of our gaming weeks outside of the convention
of California extreme which I really do hope to attend next year and
congratulate those guys on their success because everybody I talked to that goes
loves it and I just it's just it's always like a bad like timing conflict I
think one year speaking of gamer X and the the game there I think one year it
was the same weekend as gamer X and that was an issue I think it was the year
gamer X was up in San Francisco tell me stream was like the same weekend I seem
to remember that was the thing that happened yeah yeah anyway um did you
want to add anything else to your gaming week our soccer outside of the
convention the usual phone games mm-hmm so that's it yeah and Pokemon go first
my phone today no it needs to stop doing that probably so many people getting in
on that event I guess which sadly I've just lost track of Loki how about you
how was your gaming week I didn't play a lot of games this week I played just a
little bit Pokemon go okay but you did something video game adjacent I know
because you invited me and I couldn't go so I played more laser tag again
actually so I went last night I tried to get a meetup group of people to go play
some laser tag I did have one of my friends show up with his kids so we
played for a little bit and that was kind of fun so he played that for a
while at the local place here then today I went to a not quite local place a
little further away to try out their arena and system stuff to see if it's
something I would like I was hesitant to go there because it's twice as much it's
very far away and I don't know I just had kind of a bad feeling about it and
when we got there and played it it was kind of jank a little bit the arena is
nice and I like how some of the features that they have are kind of remind me of
cues are but it's the guns themselves were really tiny and they force you to
push like two buttons on the side in order for you to actually be able to
fire the gun so you have to hold the two buttons on the side because they always
want to make sure they using two hands whereas the place I play over here they
have an optical sensor so you put your hand on the bottom and it detects it's
there you don't have to hold some stupid buttons so forcing to hold those tiny
buttons actually cramps the hell out of your hand and doing that even for just
20 minutes I was like fuck this place I'm not coming back here but I do want
to check out all the places in the area so I played most of them now but then
ended up driving back over here playing a couple games so it's fun I keep
playing in it and I tried to actually have some footage shot I got one of those
action cameras I just don't have the right settings on it right now so it
came out really grainy and dark because I have to adjust some of the settings on
the camera which is unfortunate because I had some pretty good games there but
it's hard to see what's going on and I had it mounted to my head instead of
like on my shoulder or something like that and it's just really hard to see
kind of what I was doing you kind of miss a lot of it so I'm gonna try it
again at some point I may actually pick up another camera to try to maybe mount
one to a gun mount one to my shoulder or something to get some footage because I
think that'd be really cool but yeah so I've been playing lots of laser tag so
I used to play a lot of laser tag way back in the day and it definitely still
shows I like that you're having like your midlife crisis where you're
rediscovering it all over again it's not that I have never like not like I know
wanted to if like if a Q's are were to open up tomorrow yeah I'd be playing
there all the time well you're going to this new place a lot which is pretty
cool and it's see it's like I'm so torn because that place like it has a decent
arena it has decent gear but the people that run it are just not great they
they're just like it's you can tell that they're minimum wage kids that just
don't care about being there and I get it you know it's a job I worked the job
at a laser tech place before so I understand what it's like but like they
don't know anything that's going on there like they have stuff that they
advertise the website like about like a membership that you can do so you get a
membership you give your own like call sign or whatever and you can scan it a
card on the mission on the actual gun and it'll pop up like your name instead
of the names that are on the guns normally and then also you like
accumulate points towards something that happens like I think you select like
exclusive weapons and stuff like that which is kind of cool so I thought oh
yeah I'll do that for myself and my kids because we've been playing here for a
few times and I go and ask them today about it because it is is literally one
of the tabs that's on their website is membership it says ask us when you come
in I'm like okay hey what about that membership thing how do I get and you
sign up on that they're like I don't know what you're talking about like okay
and in like the last week when we went to like we did they're like three hour
thing where they're supposed to have pizza they're like pizza didn't arrive
on time and they're like well we don't know where it is you can tell it's just
not very professional with the kids right but like I met the owner last
night and you know he obviously knows what's going on he has another arena in
San Francisco as well and he commutes up here to run it sometimes but like he was
dead it was dead on a Saturday night and that's not a good sign it's not a good
sign they don't have anything in their lobby like it's just empty they have
some ticket redemption games and like even today like when we were leaving
there was I don't know what it was it looked like a rehab group or something
like that but a bunch of old dudes and looks like some other people with like
uniforms on that like we're taking him in a van back somewhere I don't know but
okay I assumed it was like drug rehab or something like that and so they were
taking him back and they gave us like a big thing a big stack of tickets so here
you go you know your kids can get some of the prizes here and he had like
shitty-ass it's all like even like even all the tickets this is just shit it's
this absolute shit let me get some chat comments over at twitch.tv slash vogue
Network VG realness says if laser tag is dead on a Saturday night it won't be
around much longer yeah and I know and it's it's really comes down to location
and advertising I've been to places I know it's in a business park which is a
it's it's it's a business park but you can see it from the road so that's good
at least but I've been to another laser tag place that was also in a business
park and it just didn't last because nobody knows where it is and so look for
and there's no advertising they don't have much of a social media presence
there's no advertising whereas the other place I went to today definitely you
know a lot more popular lots of people there but they have they have their way
expensive they have more of an arcade they have like some bounce house shit
that's there that really I wouldn't pay any money for that and they have their
only cafe so they're definitely set up to kind of run a little bit better of an
operation but this place it's it's struggling and what they talk about like
let me get let me get some other comment sorry I asked you 100 mats is giving you
photo advice saying the camera will give you a lot of grainy footage in low light
but yeah if you mess with the aperture or shutter speed and the video noise it
will look better obviously more light would fix it but you can't really do
that in the laser tag arena yeah at night vision will look good but the
strobe lights mess it up Bobby is talking about the business park thing
saying most escape rooms are in a business park and they do fine around
here last night we just do one last night and it's way far back in a
business park and it was pretty hopping yeah those escape rooms everyone that
I've been to is in like a business park too but they advertise they get out
there they do stuff online and like they really they could utilize like print
advertising I think would really help them like a mailer or something like
that so people know they're there only reason I found them is because I was
searching for laser tech places in the area like I wonder you know where
haven't I been yet and I was like oh this one's I didn't even know this was
here you know and so I found it that way it ended up being pretty decent it's
just they need them they need to get in touch with an arcade vendor to put some
arcade games in that damn thing because they're pushing like on their birthday
packages oh yeah you can get like additional tokens and stuff like that
but to play what there's like literally nothing there like I I'm gonna at some
point film some stuff and like put it up I thought about like reviewing laser tag
places I thought that'd be kind of fun at some point so as soon as I get a
camera set up to do that because only we had a camera in our pockets that goes
with us everywhere we go well you know I do but like I'm talking about my action
project of it yeah so I do want to do that because if you it would be fun to
go out you know review a bunch of places and stuff just from a perspective of
someone that played a lot of laser tag and so yeah I'm having a lot of fun with
it I just wish I wish there's more people there because really on a
Saturday night there should be quite a few people or even like during the day
like when we went there last week there was birthday parties going through and
it was pretty good but like this week there there's no one there you know and
Kai's you know had made a funny comment earlier to saying you can play laser tag
in your house in VR on psvr rec room and VR laser tag is a good plan B when the
places are not popping true but it's just not the same thing it's like it's
like saying you know you can play a football game on your you know Xbox or
you can go play football for real it is and and I like you know I like the games
where it actually feels like their skill involved in it like the first one I play
the reason I was not really attracted to that game at all is because like I can
tell I can hit I'm a pretty good shot with hitting people in games I used to
bounce shots off walls and stuff like that and do all sorts of crazy shit
because I believe you know I've played several thousand games of laser tag and
I you know the place I play now it's just you know I can hit people just as
well as I could before and cues are this other place we went to today those guns
I swear to God fucking suck like I could not hit shit with those guns and
it's definitely the guns because like you're aiming straight on the person's
just like standing there and you just can't hit anything with it and it's just
the equipment it really sucks because it's good for like if you just have a
bunch of kids running around they don't give a shit you know then that's fine
but like for someone that actually wants to play it you know and actually get
good at it and play it with people that want to play competitively you can't
when it's just like it's fucking random that your shit's gonna work or not so
anyways that's enough talking about that that's fine moving on to my gaming week
so as you guys know after last week's show was a shorter show because I went
to Chicago on business for the week so I was out of town Monday through Friday
so that really kind of put a cramp or in my ability to do gaming but I did
play a shit ton of Mario maker 2 on the flight and you might wonder how do you
play Mario maker 2 and your RNA have played easy I was playing the single
player campaign pretty much the whole way I was yeah I mean I'm sure there's a
lot to play there yeah there is and I'm probably I'm still only probably about
like 50% of the way through because I'm very stubborn and I refuse to use the
tools that will help you get through like if like if you die twice then the
little Luigi bag comes up and says do you need help dummy like it doesn't say
it that way but that's kind of like fuck you Luigi I don't need your fucking help
so and as you know and I realize some people probably take full-on advantage
of it right away and that's fine play games how you want to play games but I'm
like no I'm gonna be a little more stubborn I really want to see because
you know I feel like I make progress every time yeah and there were some like
it's not just like you get this assortment of levels but then if you
kind of like explore around the castle there's like this dog that offers you
levels underdog or whatever offers you levels too and his levels can be really
hard so I feel like in some of those levels I like make a little bit of
progression every time so you know if I have four hours to kill on a flight I'm
fine with you know trying to make a little bit I wish they have like you
know advanced tutorials in those games it's a new dog all of the likes you
know advanced techniques like the shell jumps and stuff like that that you see
like speed runners and like kaizo runners dudes like yeah say how do I get
good at that stuff or let's not even let's let's step back let's not even go
to good how do I do that I would say I'm like half only halfway through the
campaign and I think I've had to play like 25 levels and then some to you know
so there's a lot of levels in there to play so yeah I was I was plenty fine
entertained with Mario maker 2 and single-player modes that was pretty much
like my flight I did I watched a movie as well but then on the way back the
frickin like the headphone jack and the little TV didn't work so I was gonna
watch another movie but it couldn't I couldn't do anything so I was like I
just played that and then I played bejeweled on this because that you know
how the airplane things seat backs have games on them I don't know I just played
bejeweled on the on the airplane so there was that because there's so few
cell phone games that'll work when it has to be an airplane mode you know so
so that put a cramp in my gaming week except of the survivor LARP I'm sure
you're all ready for updates on that right because I was able to play that
and that was very intense a lot's been going on so remember my game started
with 22 people so the 10th place person was just voted out tonight there's nine
people left and I'm one of them and they announced tonight that we are all the
finalists and the jury so there's so I've at least made the jury so for those
of you that watch or follow survivor you know that like that's a big like
accomplishment you're in every episode at that point that's yay so that's
that's kind of that's kind of good I mean obviously I can't again I don't
know who's watching so I can't talk a lot about the strategical stuff all I
can say was that today was like a big day so yeah it was a lot going on so you
know it's getting more and more intense do you want to see what we had to do
for the last immunity challenge our first individual immunity challenge
would you all like to see it sure last week you guys got to hear about the
talking thing right yes now I'm gonna show you a physical one so because this
is a physical one for the sake of the podcasters could you guys narrate what
I'm doing please yes okay all right so it's cup stacking you're doing cup
stacking okay stacking cups so he's gotten small end with the big end on top
and then big end so it looks like an hourglass and then he's taking it and
flipping it over sideways holding it together so he's holding it that way
how long did you hold it yeah without using glue it's it's it looks
deceptively easy doesn't it because the first time I know that's right they
explained it to us I practiced it and I was like this is much easier than the
last cup stacking thing we had to do this is fine but you know it's about the
small so I went for about 15 minutes and my understanding is the person who won
immunity went for about 28 minutes and basically what happens is that as you're
kind of holding it and because you have the again for the podcast listeners you
kind of like if you stack four cups but you do them inverted each time so you
have like a big and small and big and smallest so you kind of do it that way
and then you flip it over it is supposed to be inspired by an actual survivor
challenge that was on the Micronesia season season which was the last
immunity challenge which I believe is a similar thing they had to hold like a
stack of things horizontally that normally would be vertical that type of
thing so um and your forearms start to hurt after a while because what happens
is that if there's even the slightest movement in the cup which is what
happened to me about ten minutes in well I just had a movement I breathed wrong I
don't know one of my cups slipped just a little bit and so now you're pushing
together tighter because you're like shit they're not like the grip is kind
of gone so you have to move them together tighter and then that starts to
hurt your forearms faster and so it's very very interesting but I mean what an
easy what an easy little thing to do that kind of makes for an interesting
challenge but I think a lot of those type of online games have like minute to
win it I use it you remember that old game show minute to win it they have
those minute to win it style challenges so that was that was kind of what it was
so anyways SSG100Matt says is Rob gonna judge the fuck out of people
uh-huh especially if I get voted out uh-huh
Sia Tabiri says so are you gonna be the Thorgy who makes the right decision
absolutely I will make the right decision at the end of the game well
why y'all assuming I'm gonna be on the jury won't I be in the finals why are
you all quick to assume I'm getting voted yeah but no one trusts Thorgy
anyway cuz it's a what he's a white guy with dreads all right anyway so that's
that's the update on that so yeah that supposedly survivor is done in less than
two weeks I've been playing that game for a fucking month and I'm like I like
it's it's so like mentally draining like if I ever talk about that I do this type
of shit again and it's not like all-stars or something like that like
it's just like Oh Rob signed up for another game like you guys have
permission to just like push me and start smacking me with the microphones
over and over and beat some sense into me you have my permission so all right
but I am having fun and I'm meeting some really good people so that's cool all
right anyway um that was my gaming week let's talk a little bit about other
things going on in gaming news so Loki watch stars off some gaming news so we
talked a little bit about the joy con drift thing that was an issue last week
that people started pointing out a little bit more and there's a
class-action lawsuit so Nintendo is kind of addressed the issue by basically
repairing these joy cons for free now and so what they're gonna be doing is
allowing customers to be able to send them in they no longer have to request
to provide proof of purchase for the joy con repairs they just basically send
them in and it gets repaired and then if you did pay for repair previously
they're gonna refund your money that you spent on that so that's good I mean
they've taken advantage of this at some point and it sounds like they've kind of
been cornered into caving into some of the pressure because last week we were
talking about a class-action lawsuit showing up well I just wish they would
just fix the design on it just fix whatever the issue is and then re you
know release them with the new you know I don't know the new ones that come out
I guess well then cuz you know in chat says why not just mail everybody new
joy cons well obviously that's gonna be that's really expensive because
considering that the fix like the piece of the replacing is really minimal yeah
and so to mail out a brand new control that's kind of really and if your joy
cons aren't fucked up they don't want to just send you something that is gonna
set is gonna set them back on costs like you know again my joy cons are okay knock
on wood you know for now they're fine but it's probably because I don't use my
joy cons that much I play like I was a 90% of my switch gaming is on that pro
controller and the only time I use those joy cons is like traveling when I was
like on the plane I did of course I used the joy cons to play Mario maker 2
because getting out the pro controller and the switch on an airplane that's a
bit much but using the joy cons and all that was was a little bit more like you
know like like a Game Boy or something you know yeah really big Game Boy
basically so yeah so that's about the one time I really used to joy cons but
even then I'm still kind of using them attached to the system so I think it's
still a different type of wear and tear than when you you know have them and
you're you know waving them around or doing other stuff you don't have like
third-party joy cons yet I mean I get it that you know that it'd be limited but
like I'm imagining something that's like attached to this kind of a pro controller
type of controller or something like that I mean a little bit beefier that
you be able to that have different analog six or something would be kind
of nice now cuz you and chat says no no he's always clarifying what you're
saying saying I mean you call them up say it's jacked up and they mail you a
new one case by case like Xbox just sent everyone a refurb when it red-ringed oh
yes the coffins they would send you you have to send them your Xbox yeah so I
get but in a way that is kind of what because Nintendo is offering to fix
these right so but you're just not necessarily sending them you're taking
them in right yeah you'd sell the mail it to them I would think it's just like
the Xbox 360 I thought maybe they had like a network of approved fixers no no
one can do that in store even like GameStop has their own like remember in
the back of the PlayStation manual and it would say here's the approved Sony
like repair shops oh I don't be like you and all of Northern California yeah but
yeah no one really does that nowadays but yeah it's nice to see that they're
taking care of this but really you know it shouldn't take a class-action lawsuit
to finally get around to actually fixing an issue yeah it was a little bit
slow-moving I think in that regard but I mean it's it's good that they're at
least like stepping up and trying to fix it as opposed to just trying to shove it
under the rug you know and I think we kind of we kind of knew this it's a
better approach to take then what happened with the red ring where it's
like oh it's a small it's just a small amount of users that are affected by it
you know nip it in the ass now considering the price to fix it is
probably pretty minimal yeah yeah it would just be all those shipping costs
but a giant company like Nintendo gets you know buku contracts on on shipping
and stuff you know so I'm sure it's not you know bad so all right well let's
move on and talk about something that's going on with a Nintendo game I think a
lot of people were excited about Fire Emblem that came out over this weekend
right I think Fire Emblem was out on Friday so I know some people I saw some
people on Twitter talking about it I have to admit not a series I super get
into I'm not as into the tactical games unless it's Final Fantasy Tactics no
hate I understand why people like their fire emblem but it's just you know one
of those games I just don't get around to but a very interesting change
happening with file a fire emblem fire emblem three houses is going to be
getting it and that's the game that just came out it's going to be getting a
patch that will replace the male protagonists voice so Nintendo has
re-recorded the lines for male Blythe that is the name of the male
protagonist because the voice actor Chris Niosi has had some allegations
that have shown up against abusive behavior apparently he's also been
accused of having a tendency to break and da's he has been in other games
including Octopath Traveler Pokemon and Sailor Moon so he has been replaced by
Zack Aguilar from the games One Punch Man and Hunter x Hunter and he was in
the mobile game Fire Emblem Heroes so they're gonna basically do that so
Nintendo of America had mentioned in a statement after assessing the situation
we decided to re-record the characters voiceovers and Fire Emblem three houses
and Fire Emblem Heroes with another actor the voiceovers will be included in
a future patch the original voice actor Niosi put an apology on tumblr after an
ex-girlfriend called him out for emotional abuse and so forth and he has
admitted to horribly mistreating and abusing friends colleagues and even his
significant others so big yikes to all that but definitely sounds like somebody
Nintendo did not want to be associated with anymore I couldn't help but be
reminded of sorts of I feel like we just had a story like two three months ago
about Yakuza game right or yeah it was like Sega's Yakuza game it was a
different type of Yakuza game right where I was saying it was a spin-off no
no it well it was I think it was a spin-off but it was a Yakuza game okay
and they ended up replacing the guy in that who was alcoholism a relative no he
was like doing cocaine and drugs drugs are super yeah he's a actor in Japan
yeah because I think I've seen him before somewhere I remember he was like
a familiar-looking guy like was he like he must have been in some movie that
raises anyway so he was replaced in that and it was kind of like oop he just
vanished from the game but the interesting thing about patches is that
it's you know I and I'm not you know what this guy did is is pretty gross and
I understand why Nintendo doesn't want to be associated but you know there's
going to be those collector collectible people who are gonna be like well I want
to play the version that has the original guy in it because it's gonna be
the more rare version so if I take my switch offline I can hear that one even
though in this day and age of YouTube you would think well if you really just
want to hear the subtle differences between the two interpretations the
character there's gonna be YouTube's galore and things like that but it is it
does create this interesting like pre patch I guess space of trying to see
things before they were changed and I would think even in the case of the
Yakuza game that got flipped there's probably the same type of fascination I
suppose going on I think there's a good word for it fascination you know even if
you're like you know you understand with the reasons everything like that there's
still that that curiosity about I wonder what it sounded like originally if that
makes sense hmm interesting because Bobby brings up a completely different
type of situation with voice actor replacement talking about justice for
Peter Dinklage which you might remember he was the original voice actor in
destiny for the little shit I forgot that thing's name the ghost destiny
goes right so he was the original voice that little thing and he wasn't very
good no it wasn't it wasn't very it wasn't very well done so in one of the
later I think was expansions like just in the middle of the night Nolan North
came and replaced him like just came across the wall and replaced him as the
voice actor and Peter Dinklage was suddenly patched out and that's it but
that's an interesting scenario too because you know you kind of have to
download those patches because destiny isn't always online persistent type of
game yeah I don't think that's the case with something like fire emblems or you
know that Yakuza game we had a little while ago well nowadays it is I guess
remember they did some we had some similar sign into your network account
they haven't you I don't want to spoil what's coming up but you all know it's
they had a recall member of a little big planet remember that because the all
right because the music there was the music was in there and I had one of the
original versions that had like the license hadn't really cleared for it
the disc got out anyway yeah well it was you know wasn't that is because there
was language in there it was it was some foreign words that was offensive somehow
and so right and so that they had to take this on religion or religious
thing and they were that that can be shaky ground you know so but I did have
the original version of that which I had it in there before they pulled it because
they recalled all of them I didn't send my back um I think I ended up selling it
later on but yeah it was it was gonna cry and sell it for enough yeah
interest was patched out later too so yeah let's see going to chat over at a
twitch.tv slash bog network pistol pakas in chat says I mean if you have a cart
copy the patch isn't gonna overwrite that data right no I would imagine it
wouldn't so I mean all you would have to do is delete the local data for the game
from your switch and it's only gonna be I mean you may not be able to play
online you may not be able to do some of the things that because I believe if you
do not have the most current version of a Nintendo game it won't let you play
online until you patch it but you can play it offline and connect it to the
internet and that's how you know I imagine people would do it but most
people aren't gonna bat an eyelash or they they just put their switch on the
dock overnight and it's on their home network so the thing's just gonna update
whether you want it to or not and most people are never gonna know that this
voice actor was just suddenly replaced but yeah it's just it's just it's also
this interesting day and age that we live in where they can do that type of
stuff where they can remove music from Grand Theft Auto San Andreas because
they run out of the license runs out yeah patch it out of the game which is
annoying sg100 Matt reminds us of another case recently John Tron was
taken out of ukulele because there's you know controversy there as well so we'll
just leave it at that so there's what happens when you're a shit to people so
yeah well don't be a shit to people for one but yeah so anyway okay so better to
be the shit then be a shit okay so we kind of touched a little bit tangentially
there another issue that's all over the internet this week so dark Sakura tell
me a little bit about what's going on here Oh shenanigans oh sorry real quick
because quest buster with a great comment about this isn't just games in
this day and age quest buster says reminds me when Ridley Scott literally
reshot everything that had Kevin Spacey in it for his movie all the money in the
world replacing with Christopher Plummer that's right they do that in movies too
so obviously Kevin Spacey yikes so they reshot everything that was somebody else
and didn't I think that Christopher Plummer got an Oscar nomination for it
because I think in Hollywood you know they kind of you know Hollywood's a
weird it's almost like they kind of knew like he did that last minute until it so
he kind of got an Oscar nom for it was interesting anyway all right now we can
move on sorry I thought that was a very interesting comment like oh it's not
just games well okay so as a lot of people know the first three doom games
kind of had this mass release on consoles and mobile devices but it had
this Bethesda login requirement and remember playing doom on the PC back in
the day when you had to log into your Bethesda account in order to get
connected on doom 2 with your friends yeah exactly it's like login to be net
remember that Bina is battle net also like what is that about Bina is battle
net well it anyway they are patching that out it caused a lot of memes it was
great but they put out an announcement and I'll just read it directly this came
out on the 27th so this was yesterday update on our new classic doom releases
the Bethesda net login requirement was included for the Slayer's Club to reward
members for playing the classic doom games the login should be optional and
we're working on changing the requirement to optional now we're just
trying to help you know the best part about that is players club so like since
they got rid of the original versions they delisted those which had
multiplayer by the way and then these don't have the online multiplayer they
don't have the online multiplayer the whole point why the fuck else do you
play doom 2 for the story local multiplayer reading playboy for the
articles get the fuck out anyway honestly I'd never liked to play
multiplayer doom I like to multiplayer Duke Nukem but I didn't like to play
doom multiplayer I just like to play by myself I love to doom to multiplayer I
used to there was a BBS we would call into and it would help connect your doom
games and I was I think I was rocking my was it my 386 still didn't know what
could have it I think was my 486 for a 100 megahertz at the time and I would
play doom in a tiny ass window so that I could actually have the fluid motion
when I was playing online it was so fun like kids today wouldn't understand I
had black and white doom format classic that I would sneak and play during the
middle of my typing class in college at any rate you know the games are out now
doom and doom 2 or 499 and doom 3 is 999 and you can play them on iOS and Xbox
PlayStation for Xbox one Nintendo switch and Android so yeah none of them have
the multiplayer we don't really that is so stupid because I have the one on
Xbox 360 which they made backwards compatible with Xbox one so it's in your
Xbox one library and as far as I remember you can still play that one
online I don't know anybody else with ad listen to that so you can't sell so that
you can't get it again you can't buy it we'll just build some 486 and have some
land go on seriously we need to do we need to do a PC do night hell yeah or
Duke Nukem honestly Duke Nukem was the best at all I like the voice macros oh
yeah like Duke Nukem was like the the creme de la creme of those 90 shooters I
think because that's the one I remember playing in the college dorm we would be
yelling each other from down the hall like when we get killed that was those
were the days anyway so what were some of your favorite memes you guys saw of
course Bobby black ones Bobby black wolf in our chat he did a little thing on his
podcast I hit a little graphic that came up that said yet needed Bethesda
announcement can't counsel listen to podcast I'm sure somebody clipped it and
it's over on Twitch I'll be honest I didn't really see all that many he also
did one for his Tesla which is funny oh yeah the one he did for his Tesla was
funny yeah I saw Tesla being towed yesterday that wasn't Bobby's Tesla
Bobby did something on Twitter where I think there must be a drawing app or
something on those big screens and he put like you must log into your
Bethesda net account to turn on your car so that's something like that I'm
paraphrasing but yeah that was pretty funny yeah I thought there were I just
thought some of the classic 8-bit memes were great with the whole like you know
you must log into your Bethesda net account to find our princess in another
castle you know things like that just good stuff you got it you got to love
Twitter going crazy with the memes good stuff anyway it's always fun when
Bethesda is a joke which is all the time nowadays I just why would you put out
something again like I get the whole like oh we want to put doom on iOS and
and all that stuff why would you take out the multiplayer like just I'll take
I don't want to run the multiplayer servers for five thousand please I guess
I don't know I don't know what that's all about that's unfortunate isn't there
some reddit out there I swear to God I saw some reddit where it was like will
it run doom and it's them installing do because the doom source code was public
some time ago I think I think they made it for somebody so they get doom running
all these things because I remember recently there was some type of exploit
within it was either the Harry Potter game or Pokemon go game one of those
games you could launch a full-on web browser from within the game so somebody
had them playing doom within Pokemon go and like that's the type of shit you see
on reddit we're like you know running it's called like running doom or doom I
don't know but it's it's what what can you install doom on so it's it's weird
that this is so timed where it's like yay we got doom on iOS and all this
stuff but we fucking changed it it's a little silly no no just just played on
PC like you have a PC that runs I know if you have a PC you have a PC that runs
doom you sure do Bobby Blackwell says yeah you know this will open next year's
e3 presser you think they're gonna be that tongue-in-cheek enough to start
their e3 presser and then have a splash screen saying you must have your
Bethesda net account to continue I could see them phrasing it a different way to
poke fun at it they might say it like they might show a sample login screen
please log into your Bethesda account and then the person I would think that
they are not gonna do that and the reason because we're talking like
almost a year away I mean why bring that memes shelf why bring why bring that
back up why why remind people that you fucked up in a way because I'm sure
between now and June of next year they're gonna fuck up in it dozens of
ways that are gonna be far greater than what we have with just doom so honestly
think next year's e3 presser they just open with the theme from the Elder
Scrolls and then show show off Elder Scrolls 6 and it's just like this at
this point at this point they should just fucking mock the South Park I'm
sorry video and just have Todd Howard apologizing to be fair to the folks in
chat as 200 Matt says they were able to joke about themselves about fallout 76
they will rip themselves plenty oh yes and that worked out so well for them
they brought up fallout 76 stuff as soon her Matt says they made jokes about the
arrow to the knee stuff in the presser do you know like I've heard that joke
was in Mortal Kombat 11 oh yeah I heard that arrow to the knee stuff so fucking
much that when I was do you remember I randomly started playing Skyrim VR when
I was like getting in place in VR like I got to the point where the guy really
says that and I did I'm like is this guy being a meep oh no oh this is the
actual arrow to the knee part like I had that like whoa meta moment type of thing
going on like oh it's an arrow to the knee Joe oh wait no this this is the
arrow to the knee line I am it was great it's like you have those guards to say
that and then they run straight up to a dragon started hitting it with a sword
and get like torched by fire and they're like yeah I was actually watching like
all the intros on Mortal Kombat 11 to get the references and it's totally a
line even today yeah my favorite is the mod for Skyrim whenever they say that
line they get struck by lightning see a tiberian chat says it's like right in
front of my salad oh I still use that today in fact I was I think the last
time I used it was in one of these type of games I think it was like the
survivor II type games I think it was a different one that was going faster and
something happened that I didn't like and I said to the other person I was
like really right in front of my salad you're gonna do that so those those
memes oh you know so there was a gay porn that was shot and I don't know what
they're doing oh they're full-on like having sex in the kitchen but they're
doing it like the counter is up here so they're like down here and the girl who
I don't know if she's supposed to be somebody's girlfriend or she's like you
know the the fruit fly the flame dame type of thing or what but she's like
eating your salad and she's like she looks and she goes are you guys fucking
and she goes really right in front of my salad that's pretty great and honestly
that would be me it was I'd be like don't do that in the kitchen that's in
sanitary it was it was improved I think and now of course of course she is now
like famous you know she's making her coin off that whole thing I think they
put her in legit movies and stuff you know they made a sequel to a poor she's
not even a porn actress she was just like the salad chick but now she's
getting in all these porns because she's the salad girl she's the solid salad
tosser but honestly that would be I'd just be like that's unsanitary don't do
pixel pakka says that porn company has a weird thing about girls discovering the
screwing and Sia Tiberi says it's the girlfriend the one guy is pretending to
be an in-home cooking class thing for the boyfriend and then it went to like
sex okay I guess they thank you all for explaining the plot and for your later
brows all s 200 Matt has linked to these safe for work version on YouTube if you
wish to go look at that I'm going to assume that there's black bars because
it's on YouTube covering up the like I'm offended by I'm just offended by you
seen one you see them all I'm afraid that salad dressing oh yeah she's just
like it's also the way she says it she's like really anyway tall counter to me
baby oh it's a bar nevermind oh I see maybe this whole meme thing does have
weight cuz here we are talking about the salad chick and that was like two years
ago we are we that I'm saving that now so I can watch it when I get home okay
yeah yeah you got to do homework sure all right anyway let's move on all right
Loki then if you don't like this topic how about a new one we'll talk about
grand theft auto online and you know there's been an issue with blue boxes
being compared to gambling and you know that a lot of companies can get in
trouble because of in-game gambling mechanics might kind of run afoul of
some online gambling laws well take two said fuck all that let's put gambling in
our games so they opened up the diamond casino in Grand Theft Auto online so you
can actually go in there and buy chips and gamble and you win money and of
course because this is Grand Theft Auto online you can buy shark cards with real
money and get in-game money to gamble with and stuff like that so because of
that issue certain countries can actually purchase the in-game cards or
even do some of the gambling games in there because of different local laws so
for example Iceland Iran Peru and Vietnam are some of the countries that
you can't access most of the casino and also that certain things you can't you
can't buy the penthouse in the casino as well and you're not actually able to
virtually gamble in there so it's interesting that they have to go this
route to kind of get around the different laws but what happens when you
put actual gambling in your game granted yes you can't actually get real money
from this but you can pay real money for in someone with gambling tendencies
wants to win that in-game you know money to buy like some fake car in there they
may be tempted to drop real-world money to buy chips and so it's kind of an
issue no that's something fascinating that I wouldn't have thought about is
that you might have like this like real-world gambling you know issue and
that you kind of act out through online games because maybe it's less of a
problem because it's it's a fake game but in the same time yeah I mean you
could get like if someone has gambling tendencies and you're you're betting
like fake money you're still gonna have the same response like to that even
though you're not winning real money and because of that you're like oh man
no I'm down I just need to I only pay I'm gonna pay ten dollars and we get some
more money and then I'm gonna get back on top of him win that money back you
could have like that same kind of tendency and they fucking know what
they're doing they fucking know what they're doing they know people are gonna
there's some people out there they're gonna do that and they don't care
because they're making money off of it so it is what it is some people though
of course being the internet age are getting around these restrictions by
using VPNs because they can so even this won't necessarily stop them but that may
be illegal in your country if you do that interesting all right well let's
move on to another topic this is one that I think many of us have
unfortunately had to deal with when playing games and maybe you know earlier
we were kind of having a laugh about the doom online and the fact that it's been
removed but you know some of us maybe aren't playing games online the way we
used to and the reason why is because of assholes harassment is really what it
is and this week making its way around the gaming blogs is a new survey by the
Anti-Defamation League or ADL and as part of their report they reported that
as many as two-thirds of online gamers in the US have experienced it had
experienced what they called severe harassment half of the responders of the
survey said that their race religion ability gender sexual orientation or
ethnicity was something that made them a target and 30% claimed they've been
doxxed in an online game that one really that seems so high all they had to do is
ask a woman oh yeah no I would have told him it's no it's and don't like I'm
absolutely not going like wow I can't believe it's this rampant like don't get
me wrong like I'm it's absolutely it's this rampant and I'm sure but I'm just
the 30% docs I'm like that's Wow that's scary and a quarter of respondents said
that online they have been exposed to white supremacist ideology that also
being a part of the ADL report which obviously is a whole nother yikes and
you know just leave it at that but unfortunately I think those of us that
have been on a rando map online or something unfortunately yeah I've heard
all I've heard all that stupid shit when playing things like destiny and
halo and that type of stuff online with randos and it's why I really don't like
fucking playing with randos online anymore I don't fucking do it on Xbox
Live or this Xbox Live is for playing with my friends vog network people are
fine because I feel like if you are at the level enough where you want to come
hang with us in online clubs and things like that then you kind of know you
accept these rules of you're not gonna be a fucking asshole because you know
Bobby'll ban you if you do I want like though there to be team mute that you
vote and you mute somebody I want to say and I could be wrong I want to say
either halo or destiny did put something like that in that if enough people kind
of muted somebody that person would be muted but I don't quote me on that but I
want to say that is something that has been explored in the I want ostracism to
be a thing they have to be careful because some people could use that type
of voting system to gang up on an innocent person that's the problem is
that the bad guys are gonna use it for their own purposes too that's that's and
that's why I think you haven't seen that stuff if stuff implemented more
widespread I just really want like Jean Grey level psychic power so I can reach
across the country and smack them in the head because Nazis deserve to be punched
misogynists deserve to be punched metal mayhem and chat says not just gamers but
streamers too oh sure that's one reason where it's like you know olr we get
anywhere between what like 25 maybe 45 maybe 50 at our peak viewers that we get
live we have about 33 on right now if my little console is to be believed we have
more than that that listen on the podcast feed but you know we have a we
have a decently sized crowd that turns up here on Sunday nights and we're
really appreciative but I like that we're kind of like at that level where
we're pulling a respectable crowd here people people actually want to listen to
what we're doing and we appreciate that I love it and they want to participate
in the conversation that's wonderful too but we're not big enough where the
fucking haters are coming out or the people that are just there to get a
reaction are coming out like that's a problem that you're more twitch partners
and the people that have you know 200 people that watch one of their streams
that's the stuff they have to deal with so in a way like you know and I've been
asked kind of point-blank are you are you irritated that you're not more
famous and it's one of those things where it's like I don't know like then
I if we were bigger we'd have to deal with all that shit and I don't know how
I feel about that I kind of I feel like we're almost better off in a way not
having to deal with that so um guys you doing chat says I play online a lot and
no one ever talks once in a blue moon I think the missing word there I see some
nasty text in rocket League but most of the time people never use voice chat it
may also depend on what you're playing and I know I don't use voice chat
because I got sick of the things people were saying on voice chat so if I do
play games online I don't use it now it is worth saying I do play things like
Final Fantasy 14 World of Warcraft in the past I've played those types of MMOs
online but I think it's harder to be that much of an asshole in those games
because usually you're working together towards a common goal and if you're
gonna be that guy then you're not gonna get to the goal either and granted don't
get me wrong and I know full well know some people exist in in those things
only to troll and I've seen my fair share of them in World of Warcraft but
even the trolls will oftentimes end up they end up on block lists and then when
they want to do something for real later on they can't because they've pissed
everybody off on the server so anyway some other comments I wanted to read
about this report and then we can stew on it a little bit if we want online
harassment is getting worse and a similar ADL survey this according to
past studies that was conducted earlier in the year talked about that 37% of
Americans have experienced severe harassment online online gaming meant
when they kind of analyzed that the ADL survey said 65% of players experienced
severe harassment when it's the online gaming now just some things about the
survey ADL sampled about a thousand people and to be fair the gaming
community at large is trying to figure out what they can do about this for
example Phil Spencer from Xbox recently had that post about laying out things
for combating abuse saying that you know gaming is for everyone period
overwatch they put in the endorsement feature so that you you kind of reward
people as opposed to punishing people and they say that the endorsement
feature reduced toxic behavior by 40% so some things to consider but obviously
harassment is still a thing I don't know without going too deep what what
can we do about it what can us decent people do about harassment and I think
there's definitely like number one I think the obvious thing would be you
know call it out when you see it like if somebody's getting harassed you know as
much as you might not want to or something like that you have to kind of
stand up for the underdog a little bit right but I think the reality of the
situation is that most of us are just pulling out of these situations where
we even get to where the bullies are and like I said I just play with friends
done like this is why I don't get in these mixed situations so I don't know
thoughts yeah calling it out I think just reporting people that are you know
doing this kind of harassment and I mean I don't know just playing with friends
yeah guys you doing chat says anytime I hear a jerk picking on someone I fight
back as Jonah to Matt says the report did say the 88% of players who play
certain games like Warcraft had very positive experiences as voice chats and
you know I think especially like but in Wow and in Final Fantasy and those types
of games you find your guildies you kind of find your tribe you find your people
and you're on voice chat with those people and like people are gonna treat
each other with respect because again you're helping each other out you're all
get you're all getting epic purples or whatever the equivalent is in the game
you're playing you know pixel pockets and chat says any game I play I
immediately mute voice chat for all and I'm silent myself it only took a few
shitty people to make me decide it's not worth it with random people I'll just
chat with my friends and that's more fun anyway yeah I'm kind of right there with
you all right well anyhow let's move on and talk about other voice issues right
dark soccer what do you have well this one um I don't really know how I feel
about it but basically Microsoft is gonna be tweaking their Xbox one
dashboard again and this time they're removing Cortana I don't know it's still
on PC and Windows 10 right the Cortana interface I don't I believe Cortana
still on Windows 10 yeah but at any rate they are removing it and redesigning
things and it'll bring everything into one area where you can see it right away
so it's supposed to give you quicker access to your past titles mixer service
community and Microsoft Store and so they're just I guess in the long run
trying to make it a more efficient thing but Cortana is going bye-bye I guess they
do need to kind of clean up some of that extra stuff on Xbox one and I can't I
can't think of a time where I've been like Cortana take me to the store to buy
Castlevania or something you know it's just doesn't really happen but yeah the
big thing on here is that yeah you can no longer talk to her via your headset
you can still power on your Xbox one through Xbox skill for Cortana on iOS
Android or Windows so that's true because there might be for some people
that might be an accessibility thing so I don't just want to like say well it's
useless for me so fuck it because I could there could be a very big reason
why it could be an accessibility thing for Cortana to help you navigate there's
more they basically are refocusing Cortana for the business scenarios and
are working on conversation recognition but they did decouple her from the
Windows 10 for the May update and they are making Cortana a separate app hmm so
interesting well it's good that it's still there because I bet there are some
people that kind of need Cortana s2100 Matt and chat says Cortana was
initially used with your Kinect after they killed that off you could still do
it with your mic now it's gone Bobby Blackwell says I used Xbox record that a
lot but Cortana took it away and mental mayhem says to be honest when I first
got Windows 10 I tried Cortana just for the lulls but it got boring quick all
those comments from our chat room over at twitch TV slash vog network so there
you go Cortana will no longer be a part of the Xbox one after well unless you
use some workarounds and things like that after a future update let's move on
a few more stories for you guys then we're gonna get to the classic game of
the week Loki yes so this is kind of neat there's a brand new I don't know
spirit not really unauthorized spiritual successor I guess of Simon's quest so
there's a game that's coming out that someone's working on called Simon quest
Transylvania adventure and it's kind of homage or parody of Simon's quest and
it's like a indie game that hopefully won't get struck down by you know a DMC
a or something like that but it definitely is got the same type of stuff
that you would see in Simon's quest they said convoluted hints mansions and a
time system that doesn't make you wait and apparently they're working on a demo
so this is a the Twitter user program answer and looks pretty cool so far just
based on the little video that he posted definitely get the vibe of Castlevania a
little too much though I was gonna say I getting some cease-and-desist vibes on
yeah you know at what point does parody end and copycat yeah I don't get me
wrong like it looks great it looks really cool like I love the retro vibe
it's giving and you know and and just how much it kind of invokes Castlevania
but it's kind of this different thing obviously um and I understand that like
they're trying to like not use the Castlevania name but Simon quest yeah
maybe you should have renamed your protagonist maybe why don't they call
like castle quest or well I guess that was probably a name of the game
sometime at some point or like you know Simon adventure yes something something
to get it a little more distant from that so hmm it looks neat hope it comes
out Sia Tabiri suggests Trevor quest in our chat room Trevor quest yeah use one
of the other all right Belmont's why not yeah I don't know I'm definitely looking
forward to checking out if it actually ends up coming out apparently though
they were supposed to have a playable version of it at Con Bravo so I don't
know we'll see but I'm guessing there's I'm guessing Konami doesn't exactly have
the rush the rush between you know C and D versus it being out now it's that
stuff at the end of your project tears we're just like hey look I made this
game it's done now you can see India it's too late yeah pixel pocket suggests
the name no me's quest that's Simon backwards SSG 100 Matt suggests the
title love Simon quest I guess how about how about they they could just
change the protagonist Simone's quest Simone's quest own Raven Simone ace
quest let's not do that why not see a debris just Dracula scavenger hunt the
adventure all right anyway let's move on let's talk a little bit about something
that is going to be going away from the Wii U for those of you that are still
using your Wii U which there might be some of you out there I mean even though
I'm sure many of you have updated to the switch there might be some reasons to
keep your Wii U around but as of September 26th if you do use a Wii U to
watch Amazon Prime video you'll no longer be able to do that prime video
users are starting to get emails letting them know that they no longer to be able
to do that and this is kind of interesting a $25 credit towards buying
fire TV devices to help that feel a little less now I want to just fire up
my Wii U and open the no I'm not gonna get a fire team all right the email says
we are continually upgrading our service and this occasionally means we can no
longer support certain device models to help you continue streaming your
favorite content we're offering you a $25 credit towards select fire TV
devices which will allow you to continue to stream your favorites from prime
video so if you're using the Wii U for this you still have Netflix YouTube and
Hulu today but who knows how much longer that is going to be now it should
be pointed out Amazon Prime is not on the switch some of these you know I
think YouTube's on the switch at this point Hulu's on the switch but not
Slick's no not Netflix Netflix ain't on the switch and Amazon Prime isn't on the
switch so this isn't as easy as just going over to the switch and I will say
you know what I I have used I do remember downloading prime video onto
the Wii U and using it because my broadcast signal from the Wii U was
strong enough where if I had Amazon going on the Wii U I could take the
tablet into the bedroom and watch an episode of Drag Race or something from
the bedroom so you know they're there may be some uses why somebody wants to
take that tablet and watch it somewhere else their house a little portable
television so but I guess at the same time if I wanted to I could just use my
phone but the Wii U had that kind of bigger screen you know yeah I mean it's
nice but I understand that they don't need they want to support it but I'm not
gonna profess that I've like used it at all ever recently they probably figured
out that the numbers aren't really you know there as far as the number of users
and so it makes sense that they would probably retire mm-hmm let's see I
wanted to read some other comments in chat Bobby Blackwell points out twitch
also isn't on the switch no that's I mean I think we all understand be too
easy twitch on the switch well and we understand that the switch probably
isn't going to let you broadcast stuff because of you know the the parts that
are in it maybe when there's a pro maybe that's something I'm looking at for the
pro hmm who knows we'll just theorize on that oh I have the pros I have a pro
switch to do streaming services I bet that'll be a thing but anyway but it's
surprising that you don't at least just have the twitch like watch stuff client
that is a little weird I think yeah I don't know I'd love to be able to have
that so anyway as 200 Matt says most companies are like this is gone in blank
days if you have problems with this kick rocks yeah so it's it's kind of true
that you know they didn't have to offer the $25 incentive on the fire TV or
whatever but they are but I think Amazon probably discounted the price by 25 bucks
on Prime Day anyway if not more than that so I'm sure Amazon takes a loss I
mean because it's almost like game consoles the more fire TVs that are in
home the more people that are likely to buy stuff on the Amazon Prime video
thing so it kind of suits them to have that in as many places as possible so I
don't think this is just them being the nice guy if you will all right anyhow as
200 Matt says maybe it'll let you stream from the switch but only at 480 P let's
see your streams are gonna be crap quality all right let's move on to the
classic game of the week every week dark soccer steps in the gaming vault and
finds a game that she thinks hey you guys should be remembering this game
this week I'm kind of surprised you're doing this game this week this is a big
one and I thought you might have would save this for an anniversary show or
something yeah yeah I thought we'd already done this one too I also thought
we'd already done this one I think just with me being kind of in music game mode
it stuck out in my head it's fair and it's also one of those congratulations
this game is 10 years old type of moments actually right now it's 12 years
old all right so what is the game rock band there you go so I just want to
point out usually on the podcast we have a little bit of the game's audio in
the background um however tonight we have removed the audio just because we
don't want to risk a twitch muting for the copyright music so we only have the
visual writing on twitch you can get like something like Charlene I'm right
behind you or whatever like I just I didn't want to risk it even with the
freebie songs so it's fine if you yeah y'all probably you're already familiar
with rock band I imagine this crowd pretty familiar with rock band already
yeah anyway so rock band is a music game is developed by harmonix it was
published by MTV games and distributed by EA and we are talking about the first
game in the series it was out for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 released on
November 20th 2007 and there was a PlayStation 2 version it was released
December 18th 2007 so also a Wii version on June 22nd 2008 harmonix had
also developed the guitar hero series and then when the guitar hero was sent
off to never soft harmonix made the new game with multi-instrument gameplay so
sort of like having your guitar in one game instead of spread out amongst all
of the various you know I guess it actually was kind of like the guitar
you know by having the multiple instruments except you you know it grew
from there from just you know guitar and drum and mic and there have been like a
bajillion sequels you know of rock band so we won't even be getting into there
but basically you've got your different peripherals you have you know of course
your on-screen interface is what controls how you're supposed to do it
with the mic you have to sing to relative pitch to the original vocal so
I know some people who just may as well not fucking use the mic because they
can't you know hold a tune in a bag
there's nothing also by the way that will set off like my own self loathing
of my voice than playing ink on the mic in garage band just saying I hate
hearing myself out of key but you know you also have you know your guitar one
person can be bass and you've got your drum kit later on of course you know we
got the piano and the cymbals and all these other goodies so at any rate you
build up your score you get different multipliers and you have an overdrive
that lets you just you know apparently play really awesome and then you can use
like on the guitar you use your whammy bar for like using effectors for how
you're playing you know example you've got different difficulty levels easy
medium hard and expert and if you don't play well enough you get muted out of
the song so there you go um the PlayStation 2 and we version didn't have
any customizable options for your player but Xbox 360 and ps3 did so you could
change their physique their clothes tattoos the way they move all kinds of
stuff and then you know again we had a the guitar was based off the Fender
Stratocaster you had you know your your drum pedals you also have like your game
modes like band world tour where you could play in different venues and
unlock things and customize your character even more you also have like
solo play you have a solo tour and the soundtrack pretty massive so they
reached out to five record labels that provided most of the master recordings
including EMI Hollywood Records Sony BMG Universal Music and Warner Music well
actually for Warner Music specifically it was Rhino Entertainment you know you
know what I remember about Rhino Entertainment is that when I was young I
had a bunch of albums that had the old Rhino logo on it and that's how I always
remember Rhino Entertainment but they had you know the Wii version had five
additional songs by the way over some of the others they had Danny California
don't fear the Reaper understand man here it goes again
highway star and learn to fly oh and suffragette city and when I dead or
alive and won't get fooled again so those are bonus you could also get
downloaded you know track packs and single songs so like to date one thousand
four hundred and eighty downloadable songs are available that's a lot of
music but at any rate like I said it was developed by a harmonics post guitar
hero and red octane and made the the it looks like red octane was making the
peripherals but yeah we never soft took over development of guitar hero well
harmonics had to go somewhere I had to do something and so they started in
February 2006 working with different designers for prototyping the
instruments for developing an all-new hardware bringing in things like your
drum support and they just kept working on it from there and it ended up being
you know such a big hit like I said we've got so many so many other
peripherals and it's so many other releases that it just just really moved
right along they did have licensing fees for using some of the wireless
technology especially for Microsoft and if they had chosen to pay for it they
would have actually released the different versions at different costs
so they used wired technology to start off with it so so anyway yeah it's got
a massive online community at rock band calm and now I mean remember we used to
help out with them loud the charity event where you basically play rock band
on stage I used to do some of the graphics but it was I mean there's all
these like weird special editions too like there's Green Day and I think there
was Beatles rock band that was a big deal but you know as it came out you
know they also were learning that of course some of the guitars from other
games were incompatible for example the Gibson Les Paul guitar controller that
came with guitar hero 3 was not compatible with rock band even though
harmonics said that they had an open controller support but basically
harmonics and Activision we're just pointing fingers back and forth harmonics
put out a patch Activision blocked it so who's the bad guy here and then but
Activision then announced that guitar hero world tour would use the rock bands
instruments and just drama at any rate though rock band was very highly
received for most of the American reviewers you didn't get a score under a
nine on that scale or a five stars or an a so they were all very excellent won so
many awards best multiplayer experience innovation awards across the board best
music game and Xbox magazine said best reason to move to a bigger house award
this I mean this game really was like it was just so like like transformative I
mean between you really have to kind of co-credit this and like a tar hero and
just you know with the whole like plastic instrument revolution and sure
those of us that have been music game fans a little bit longer such as you
know us here at OLR and some of our longtime listeners obviously we remember
what was about guitar freaks and importing the stuff from Japan the beat
media 2dx controllers and things like that but Konami and you know we talked
about this ad nauseum in our first 180 episodes Konami was never willing to
really take that risk with the US audiences until it was too late the
Japanese arm of the company was too fucking stubborn even though the
American side was telling him do it do it do it they were too fucking stubborn
until I think it was really too late to hit the momentum on that and then by the
time they finally did get it on it it looked like a fucking knockoff of this
because it was rock revolution when Konami finally got it was just a bad
fucking version of this so you know it was it was really guitar hero 2 probably
in many ways I would say and then like this as a definitely follow-up with
charter 3 that really kind of like pushed that plastic instrument
revolution and just started music gaming in the u.s. well there also did have
effects on the actual music industry their Viacom was saying that it was
averaging the sale of 1 million downloadable songs every nine days and
for example Motley Crue's single Saints of Los Angeles debuted as a rock band
track the same time that the album released some of the tracks that were
specific to rock band actually ended up being later on we released for example
Rush's alternate working man only which one of my favorite songs ever we
actually like ran out of video and that was some guy playing a 10-minute song
but in any way the alternate version of working man that was released only for
rock band was so well loved that Rush released that version as a download
through iTunes and started making some of their albums available like moving
pictures was was released in the game two months after all this so I really
want to go back and play again on my Xbox one because I have rock band for on
Xbox one but like I remember I was having a lot of problems getting the
instruments connecting like weird shit was happening and I got so frustrated I
just stopped but for me the real peak of the rock band series for me was rock
band three because I love the keyboards I'm like the one person that loved the
keyboards that was so awesome and I wish I wish the keyboard thing had taken off
more mmm I was just reading about some of the litigation with Gibson guitar and
Konami's lawsuit and everything oh sure yeah but I mean basically a Viacom did
a counter suit against Konami saying that rock band improves on Konami's
original patent and that rock revolution used controllers are similar
to rock band so they both settled and there you go there you go I also want to
give a shout out for rock band blitz I wish they had made that one backwards
compatible 360 there's also mention of frets on fire oh yeah when the like a
computer yeah and then of course we had you know coming out of
that there was rock Smith to where you actually could play a real guitar that
was much different it was but I don't know how much laid off the concept yeah
I don't know how much I can say but I know somebody who worked on that game so
and so do you know yeah I'm saying that I don't know that it would be out oh
yes you're not for oh yeah definitely definitely like again it's all about
that risk right nobody would have taken a risk on a game like rock Smith if rock
band and guitar hero too hadn't like put it out there there was that and I'm
sure somebody asked that question well you know everybody's fake jam it why
don't we teach people how to play a real guitar why we do this for real maybe
there's a way and that's what rock Smith dead well and on top of that though in
the later releases of rock band you had the pro modes where they had the
guitars and the keyboard I love the cute because you really were playing the
keyboard parts if you played it in pro yeah it's pretty cool yeah it was
awesome but Bobby talking about rock band blitz they only had the music
licenses for a couple years for the songs they ended up delisting rock band
blitz it's I look Robin blitz was just it was all the DLC you already had for
rock band but then you played it in like an amplitude kind of game and I loved it
so cool so all right there it is your classic game of the week rock band one
of the greatest all-time classics really especially for us music game fans love
it that's the type of game that brought us all together and so I'm assuming were
they playing this a California extreme did it get you kind of thing oh yeah you
said they're playing on stage right yeah but I didn't play but you I saw it along
with it though yeah because they you know started singing the cure I also did
karaoke this last week cuz that's my fun stage I'm just singing it at the vendor
booth no but I did real karaoke I met up with some of my friends in Chicago we
went out to one of the bars for karaoke it was fun I was basically show me show
me show me how you do that song that's one of my favorites but I was singing it
over there and some kid was looking over just grinning it was pretty funny mm-hmm
you were singing classic rock all right let's move on let's get into some rapid
fire news and quickly travel around the world with some other headlines and
what's going on in gaming so Loki won't start us off all right so we've got a
couple things here so one it's a little bit of a preview of what we can expect
from gamescom which is just around the corner supposed to take place on August
20th through the 24th and thq Nordic is apparently gonna have some new games to
announce as well as showing off some additional things including their remake
for destroy all humans they also have a remake for spongebob squarepants battle
for bikini bottom a rehydrated and apparently the strategy game of
desperados 3 and Darksiders Genesis but they're supposed to be announcing also
new games as well during that time so I guess we'll have to wait and see what
that is thq Nordic I'm hoping that one of those is a no-saints program but you
know I'm I'm highly skeptical that gonna be something in the same universe ages
of mayhem 2 yes that game really was not terrible enough and we have to make a
sequel to make it even worse and then finally this is kind of cool grand theft
auto 3 Liberty City may remember that game that's pretty old but now you can
actually play in the Liberty City map from grand theft auto 3 in beam and G so
for those not aware of what beam and G is it is a physics based driving game
which basically you kind of do whatever you want in it but mostly it's to crash
your car in very unique ways but now you can crash your car in very unique
ways all over the map of grand theft auto 3 and it looks awesome and of
course it's not something that you can necessarily download and via the
official like mod repositories but there's a thread in their forum on beam
and g.com so go check it out there and it looks awesome I don't know if I don't
think I have beam ng but I've seen lots of videos of people playing it I do want
to probably pick it up now all right moving on to a hackers gonna hack story
because we love these around here at olr this has to do with somebody getting
Android running on the switch that's right XDA are the homebrew developers
that have just released an Android firmware for the Nintendo switch it's a
8-point Android 8.1 lineage OS 15.1 I don't I don't do enough Android no idea
what that is um but I'm assuming just one of the operating systems one of the
older ones probably not one of the newest ones and so compatible models
will do it there are of course it's buggy it's got battery life issues some
of the rotation some sensitive touchscreen input but everything in
there otherwise would work so basically it will turn your switch into an Android
tablet with a pair of controllers this is something you're basically flashing
the firmware on your switch to be this so you're losing your Nintendo switch so
you know only if you really really really are into fucking with your
hardware do you want to do something like this apparently it is based on
androids a division that works with the Nvidia shield TV so some things on the
Tegra like Borderlands and Half-Life 2 will actually run on this not to say
they run well but they run so very interesting with that that's a big big
console mod going on there so yeah again I would not do this for shits and
giggles unless you really know what you're doing with this type of modding
because you're likely gonna lose access to being able to play Mario maker and
things like that anyway let's talk about a story on Facebook instant games
because they are going to be kind of going away kind of not really so instant
games on Facebook started in the newsfeed and then they went to groups and
the light app and I believe they went into the messaging app you could play
games like pac-man and stuff with friends I know I've done that before
but not in a long time I think it was one of those things were like oh I
played pac-man with somebody on messenger okay I'll never need to do
that again in my entire life like I don't think I really got into the thing
in the Facebook gaming thing was also a little weird to me because like oh you
can play these things on an app in your phone and most of them are just apps you
can download on your phone and play there you know I mean if I wanted to
play pac-man I could just download the pac-man app for my phone right but for
whatever reason you know some people wanted to do the Facebook messenger
gaming because excuse me probably some more of the social features and things
like that well games are gonna be moving out of the messenger app they will be
moving into the Facebook gaming tab global director of games partnerships
Leo Aleb said quote starting later this summer instant games will no longer be
playable directly in the new version of messenger on iOS to ensure a smooth
transition players and messenger will continue to access games through thread
updates and chat bots while gameplay itself will app switch to Facebook quite
honestly this all sounds terrible so I just is there a Facebook game I'm
missing out on is there something I should be playing I don't know I blocked
all of those notifications so probably not
it's Farmville still a thing I don't know too I wonder if my ex is still
jamming to the Farmville soundtrack all these years later I have no idea I don't
know which one was this all right okay so and a pot of podcast listeners in
chat want me to correct on the Android story apparently you are running it off
a micro SD card you are not actually overriding your switch data I apologize
I must have misinterpreted because they were talking about that you may be kind
of screwing up your system to be able to play some of the other games later on
so I apologize if I misrepresented that but I I still would I still would
venture with this shit with caution if you really want to run an Android thing
how about you just buy an Android tablet they're not that expensive they're
cheaper than a switch but that's but I also the earlier in the day or earlier
in the show I said but isn't that reddit where everybody runs doom on all this
different shit hilarious so I get the appeal I do I do anyway back to the
Facebook story kaijuto says my ex loved that Facebook MMO game forgot the name
of it Oh Farmville she had me in her auction
room watching her watching her seller stuff it was fun metal man has them
metal mayhem says I don't give two shits about Facebook games to be honest if I
were to play a game it'd be one of my games from steam or good old games good
plug so I think it's it's safe to say pixel shits will not be coming to
Facebook Messenger or Facebook instant or whatever the fuck they're calling it
now anytime soon anyway who wants to play games on Facebook anyway you know
the only game I'm playing for a while mind games do you remember though that
Sims on Facebook yes I vaguely played there what's right there was like a Sim
and it was thing yeah like 2d and not 3d yeah no I totally remember it that thing
was nuts that was yeah okay and then like this pet game but that those weren't
like things within the app that was kind of the precursor that those games were
also on Google Plus games when that one and only game I played on Facebook that
I had to suffer through was a stupid goddamn garage sale game part of that
fucking ready player one challenge that is the only fucking game I ever played
on there and that was enough to sour me off of the whole fucking platform I
remember that dark to see you says I was kind of addicted to the civilization
port for a little while I remember that that's right there was like a
civilization game on Facebook I did words with friends a lot yeah yeah sim
social that was it pixel pockets anyway that's enough about that dark soccer
what do you have for rapid-fire news certainly not pixel shit right now sorry
why we are the original game that we got as monster rancher in Japan it was
monster farm is getting a re-release in Japan the there is a teaser website up
for it but koi Tecmo has released the thing on their Twitter and it's looking
kind of cute you know it's funny is that I almost picked up a monster farm
yesterday because I my I'd never played monster rancher so I was thinking about
getting it but I didn't but there's in the translation of this hold on let me
get the translation pulled up it says oh my god why is this being slow
basically it's saying that it's going to be released on an unannounced platform
in 2019 and they used the word high sheen which typically indicates a digital
release so it could either be it's a digital only console PC title or
smartphone so and then in other news that I don't know if this makes me
excited it could but Sega of Japan has filed a trademark for Knights dream wheel
thinking that it could be another game in the Knights franchise it would be
really nice if it did but it didn't spell Knights with a special spelling of
Knights so it could be something else but if it's a if it's a a new Knights
game I would be quite happy I'm surprised that isn't something they've
revisited recently why not we're getting a lot of the other stuff like we night
there was a wee night's game I remember that a wee little night's game but yes
there's that and then of course Panzer Dragoon I think is the other kind of big
one that I remember at e3 this year is pretty big deal so it'd be cool yeah
all right well let's move on and travel around the world and check out some
release dates and some video games coming out soon near you not a whole lot
this week we've got mutant year zero road to Eden deluxe edition on Nintendo
switch oxygen not included on PC Mac and Linux Madden 20 Madden NFL 20 on PC
PlayStation 4 and Xbox one the church in the darkness on PC Mac and Nintendo
switch PlayStation 4 and Xbox one that's it all right let's travel to Japan right
now get in the car let's go on the PlayStation 4 this week on August 1st we
have a game called labyrinth life sadly I don't believe this game stars stars
David Bowie I think it's probably an anime based game they talk about a faint
in agony flowering system interesting but it already know right yeah and I
guess it also does some rock-paper-scissors type of battle and oh
it looks like you can change the bus sizes on your characters well that oh
yeah I think yeah I've heard this was a game I think that was it's only wasn't
bringing over to the West because of they had like some of these I don't know
if this is the same game series but they had one where you basically have to
breed these like princesses or whatever they rescue or something like that
there's some weird shit now they all right well if labyrinth life is your
thing you enjoy that it's this week um also coming out of Japan this week crash
team racing nitro fueled gets its Japanese release I know we've had it
here for a little bit but is finally on its way out in Japan this week and if we
want to go over to the Nintendo switch Oh mega labyrinth life comes out on the
switch all right where you can make some Omega anyway also we've got a game
called the same crash team racing is also out in Japan and the air conflicts
collection gets a release on the switch this week and I feel like we just had
no this is okay no this is not like an arcade shooter this is a game with air
conflict secret wars and air conflicts Pacific carriers in one pack so if you
are you know cuz the airplane simulator games are pretty popular overseas so if
you want that you can have that dark Sakura how about the UK in the UK we
don't really have very many either what is coming out on the 29th which is I
guess already the 29th right now there is FIA European truck racing
championship and there's mutant year zero Road to Eden the deluxe edition and
then on August 1st is Madden NFL 20 so they go back to labyrinth life a little
bit I just I'm just I'm just gonna read this one I mean basically you kind of
get the gist of the game anyways but they said it apparently if you expand
your bus with every fallen foe mighty memories lead to great greater power
defeating foes builds up your Omega power in the chest increasing bus size
and parameters they go all the way to a Z cup this is a Nintendo switch game by
the way and apparently is coming out in the u.s. on August 1st so that is that
is another that is another game that is coming out is it really yes it is are
you gonna do a let's play a live stream no it's 60 bucks not paying for that but
Z cups Loki oh wow you know what what I think that that's so terrible that's not
even funny anymore when I know people who have had breast reductions for that
kind of pain that it would cause I don't think that a part of the body should be
fetished I really don't I'm just getting so sick of it we're not objects all right
I mean and I'm not saying it's right but are you really surprised I should be
surprised is the thing I really should be surprised I don't even know what I'm
looking at here we and I really don't want to know whether fictional or not
bodies need to be respected it's just fucking stupid I don't know what that is
not here to glorify your fucking hormones Bobby Black Wolf in chat says
Nintendo is kitty because you know Nintendo is a kids company they only put
out kids games we all know that's the case of course let's see yeah some folks
in chat saying excuse me Z cup yeah anyway podculture says there is such a
thing as too much of a good thing anyway let's move on can we please go to the
mailbag so every week you guys email us participate at orange lounge radio.com
and we read our favorite emails live on air did we get any emails this week um
yeah we actually got a really interesting little email that apparently
they recorded you masturbating Rob how does it go what important where you have
been recorded masturbating and the M is an upside down W so it's a spam message
this something yes okay been washed we have to reading wow I was
waster baiting I'm not even opening it and of course I'd tell you the the from
who is anonymous hacker okay anonymous hacker caught me waster baiting here
like here in the OLR studio or like somewhere else in the house like do they
like was it was it professor plum in the conservatory with the Crisco
I'm not gonna play this game anymore so that means since we got no real emails
it's drag race talk what is there to talk about drag race drag race isn't on
right now but I saw a funny meme okay this is every time a Republican is
caught with another man a drag queen gets her heels oh because there's yet
another one that got like was caught on Grindr or something yeah just today I
was seeing that going around yeah it's like why be so hateful unless you just
hate yourself mm-hmm just just get fucked in the ass you'll feel better no
I'm serious all these closeted Republican shitholes now now we're gonna
get another email about you beating off that Pikachu so please stop just hear me
out hear me out this is why we don't have a lot of yours no no just just hear
me out I don't think a man has to identify as gay to sometimes have gay
moments you know you can be bisexual there's no problem with it being bi is
valid but if you're this repressed you're this repressed because you've
been denying yourself or you're doing it and you hate yourself just get fucked in
the ass and be open about it stand up there and go you know what I like it I'm
not gonna say it cuz someone's gonna clip me saying it and I don't like any
of it but just say getting fucked in the ass is okay use your enema wear a condom
and get fucked in the ass do it safely people who matter will not think any
less of you for it welcome everybody to the voice of geeks Network where every
geek has a voice dark soccer has chosen to use hers for a significant purpose
tonight well honestly enough it's why I became a sister take the stigma out of
it the moment that no one gives a shit that you're getting fucked in the ass is
the moment that you don't have to hide I mean fucking a people I'm I'm in super
literally is what it is I'm just saying if people stopped having such a big
conniption fit over it and just I'm gonna stop explaining it shouldn't have
to be explained you if you like if you like it in the but you should be able to
have it just saying what what back that ass up just saying Rob do you need
another drink shall we all right so speaking of getting fucked in the ass
Nintendo has been really hard on people not being able to upload lots of
different levels for Mario maker 2 and so because of that now they're gonna be
increasing the cap from 32 to 64 and they said that also they're gonna be
increasing that upload limit one more time so we don't know when that's gonna
happen but sometime in the future you may be able to upload more than 64
levels which I don't understand why they're limiting everybody to do that
but just in case if you think that you know your levels being deleted because
you may be doing some exploits in the game are safe offline you are sorely
mistaken so apparently of course like the first Mario maker people have been
exploiting different glitches in the game to do all sorts of crazy stuff one
of these is actually how to create a black hole in Mario maker 2 which allows
you to put objects on top of each other that aren't supposed to be layered that
way so you can kind of create these really crazy fire bars and different
overlapping terrain including pipes and whatnot have the moon appearing in
daytime levels and all sorts of crazy stuff the game will know that you're
doing that of course and it will actually say that corrupt data has been
found in your course has been deleted or just won't let you save the game because
there's corrupt data as well and so unfortunately you know those crazy
levels that people might be able to make with these exploits aren't gonna be a
thing because they have patched in ways to detect those which is unfortunate but
hey you know the level caps gonna be up to 120 probably someday or more I don't
know why there's even a cap on the number of levels you can put out there
anyways who cares like you can't tell me people that would just upload
garbage but how are you gonna discover that garbage I guess it gets thrown into
your feet or whatever but like the level size the download of that I mean the
storage space has got to be so minimal I can't imagine why we would even limit
that stuff little big planet doesn't do that and you can do all sorts of crazy
shit in that why why even limit Mario maker I don't know that's the thing you
haven't picked up Mario maker too yet have you I have are you making any
levels um I haven't gotten to play it yet because my kids have been playing it
I haven't made any levels yet that's the one thing I'm missing so I should have
I should have tried like making a level one on the airplane but I just I
probably will at some point mm-hmm all right anyway Bobby with the clerk's
jokes in there we have 37 viewers in a row anyway
moving on maybe something you want to make in Mario maker is your own pole
position inspired level I don't know I had no other transition and I figure it
was better than the last one pole position somebody has remade this in 3d
yeah I saw that yeah and they Rob what's wrong because I was about to read the
name of it and you know it's called hmm PP engine yes pole position engine so
it's a it's a PP engine is a three-year Rob definitely needs an adult this
episode yeah you know Bobby said try not to
masturbate on your way to the car on my way to playing some PP engine which is
a 3d remake of the night it's a 3d remake of the 1982 game pole position
Rob can't even which is what your PP stands for but it actually reverse
engineers all of the games code so it's actually following basically what you
would expect the cars and the AI to do but it's modern high-definition graphics
as in crashing every time you get on a curve yeah yes and all the all the like
lame-looking billboards that go by and the little explosions and all of that
yeah Jonathan Thomas on reddit said I started back in 2013 my god that's six
years ago reverse some people do podcasts for 17 years some people spent
six years on their PP engine I started back in 2013 reverse engineering the
code from the original arcade ROM with the help of the main debugger and some
primitive self-made tools to analyze instruction traces and create assembly
source files that could be assembled back into the original arcade ROM
following this I worked through the assembly source file to produce a
portable c-based library containing the game logic for pole position this
library was used in two projects the one you see here and another project to
convert pole pole position to the Atari st a 16-bit computer that was released
in 1985 I mean this is like on one hand I'm like what a colossal waste of time
but on the other hand I'm like this is actually like really cool it's like the
most authentic way to remake like an old game but just like put new graphics
on it like they they didn't just like remake it with new programming languages
that emulated like I thought that they went in and like did it from the code so
that's that's pretty cool now you actually don't you have a pole position
cabinet or you did like that became your main cabinet or am I mixing it up with
something yeah we had a pole position and sure me moved into it remember mm-hmm
because it was missing the pedal so sure me decided it was her new cat mansion
mm-hmm but yeah we put a meme in that at one time and then I don't remember we
sold it and then did other things now Bobby Blackwell would like to point out
in our chat room at least he completed his racing game unlike some people well
took him six years to do it I got time all right anyway let's move on we have a
few more stories for you guys and then we're gonna get to our discord segment
which I think I accidentally left off the show role but we will get to
discord if you want to give us a call over at vog network or vognetwork.com
slash discord but first dark soccer I think you have another kind of like
video game study thing I do because I like to bring something about science
into this but there is a game called driving XC which you can find at
driving XC calm for $39 it's available also as a digital download for I guess
they mean Xbox one and ps4 but it's a game that helps new drivers learn how to
drive and on top of that in one of the interviews on here the father of the teen
says it's actually helped him become a better driver that after having pay
attention you know to watching his daughter play it that he started
becoming a more careful driver so basically it's drivers ed the game and
the guy behind it is named Bob Davis he was making the large-scale car
simulators like you did you ever have the simulators in your high school for
drivers ed no we had that use like a film strip to drive with and the
simulators were terrible this is like also like from the 60s it was pretty bad
but this guy's been making the simulator since 2005 and so his driving
essentials is to help be an interactive driving simulator for teens that they
could do on their own and so it's actually apparently been helping kids
learn to drive better as ten different lessons starting with the basics and
take you through different driving scenarios so that it gives you you know
it makes you more aware when you're ready for your driving test and there's
even a level where you have a phone and it forces you to look at it so you can
see what distracted right distracted driving can do is even if you're at a
stoplight looking at your phone can still cause an accident so just saying
it's really really good way to get people prepared and like I said her dad
said that it was really making him a more conscious driver too and you can
get this at driving X e.com interesting you think they're using video games and
more and more in the driver's ed type stuff I don't remember why we didn't do
that type of stuff I feel like I feel like we were all prepping to take a test
and it's like you took that test so that you could take like basically you take a
driver's ed course through a private thing at 15 and a half I think or some
like that was when you could do that the only thing is that it uses a standard
controller wheels and pedals are not supported but I think they should put in
driving wheel support you know because that's gonna just even add to the
experience I'm interesting perspective from dark Tetsuya in our chat room over
twitch TV slash vog network saying the doctors were convinced I shouldn't drive
so I've just been using video games to live vicariously very interesting
perspective there because you know some of us may not realize that oh yeah some
people aren't able to drive whether it's due to a medical issue a vision
issue you know whatever it is but when it comes to video games where you know
it's a it's a it's a controlled environment a fake environment not not
the real world you kind of get to you know experience that in a different way
and as much as we've been having a laugh at pole position and the acronyms later
or acronyms that come from it you know maybe that was the realistic simulator
in 1982 but certainly now today the technologies come so far that when you
play a game like a Gran Turismo or something it's it's so realistic you
know well I'll tell you I actually learned because I hadn't driven in a
while but I learned about over steering from playing Ridge Racer so just saying
you know I learned how to steer myself out of a drift in other games so you
know just applying some of the technique I mean yeah and I'd say you know
improving your hand-eye coordination too is also helpful so you know it's
funny Bobby Black Wolf I guess did some research into the pole position thing
turns out that game was either that little reimagine he hasn't been working
out for six years because that originally came out in January 2014 it's
just making its way around the gaming blogs again this week for whatever
reason whether it be to do a reddit post or something like that as these things
sometimes happen but you know here at OLR it's about what is out there in
gaming culture and if something gets rediscovered and is new all over again
it still qualifies so I mean I I had no idea it was a thing so it's still kind
of new maybe in 2019 they'll update it for VR who knows so anyhow let's move on
Loki story from you all right so it's another week so we have yet another
story of a epic epic game store exclusive so mech warrior 5 unfortunately
is being delayed it's now set for December of this year and it will be
epic game store exclusive as well so piranha games put out a press release
saying our partnership with epic game store allows piranha the opportunity to
make sure mech warrior 5 mercenaries meets our internal goal of creating the
best mech warrior game possible we want more money since we since we announced
the development of the first player mech war game in 17 years we have stated that
our goal was to deliver to fans mech warrior mercenaries experience with true
freedom of choice and being able to share that experience in a co-op setting
by true freedom of choice we do not mean storefronts of course so yeah it was
originally supposed to be coming out sooner and apparently though with that
if you had pre-ordered the game you will be able to request a full refund up
until September 1st hmm well so at least they're gonna do the refund thing that
as I'm sure some other recent controversies like Shenmue and all that
stuff the one that gets me though is the whole Tetris effect being exclusive on
the epic store but then if you want to play it in VR you have to have steam
because I don't think that is a requirement anymore for like the audience
Oculus version or something like that oh I thought it only went with the vibe and
so you had to have steam VR in order to be able to run yeah but yeah that is
funny this is kind of like one of those like this is it's really weird type of
thing yeah maybe it just also goes to show that you also maybe don't just
think of steam as a store I guess steam is I guess more than that at this point
now with the whole you know fact that there's maybe our drivers in it maybe it
shouldn't you know I don't know and Bobby says the oculus version runs steam
VR they didn't make it specifically for oculus last I checked steam VR runs on
oculus so they just did a one-size-fits-all hmm so yeah it's kind of
kind of interesting I mean I don't know like I kind of want to get Tetris effect
on PC but I I already have it on PlayStation I want to be able to play it
on like 4k though I think that seems like really cool but like I just feel
like nothing's gonna top the VR version I might wait for a sale I think that's
what I'll probably and ultimately end up doing but I do love Tetris effect that
game is so good if you guys haven't played it yet so good so but I just
don't see myself jumping into PC VR anytime soon I don't like I'm not the
level of enthusiasts that you know Bobby or even maybe Kai's you know or some
other of you guys that love your VR are at I'm kind of like I got PS VR it plays
enough it suits my needs I'm good for now I'm looking forward to the no man
sky thing which um you know cuz that's gonna get VR pretty soon I'm excited I
thought it already happened it's like any day now the beyond updates gonna be
out which I'm speaking what good timing hey Alan can I bug you to come on the
show please Alan is in this new pocket hi can you come on the show will you
come on the show yeah cuz I literally just brought something up that is kind
of like relevant to you and what you're doing um you've been playing a game a
lot recently we tell us the viewers a little bit about what you've been up to
I've been playing a lot of No Man's Sky I just wanted to see what the mod
community had done with it in addition to the updates that well apparently
unless this guy's completely full of shit was one mod that I'm using called
fantasy a lot of his work has actually been incorporated like he has a credit
in some of the patches because hello games has used his stuff he made a mod
to where you find a ruin and then if you use the thing that lets you dig into the
earth there's actually like like kind of like archaeology where you go under the
ground it's not just to find minerals but there's things you can find to sell
that are actually under that's a part of the base game now and he made a mod to
do that originally so I was out of town last week obviously on a business trip
so how many hours would you say you plants spent playing No Man's Sky where
I wouldn't be here to judge you I've started over a few times I would say
from the time you left I would say around 15 or 16 hours over the course of
the week so it's two or three hours a night I can't judge ask me how many
hours I've been on call for my larp so it's fine yeah well I still haven't
tried rez VR and you own that it's in the living room I just knew he'd been
playing No Man's Sky lately and it was kind of relevant so I didn't even think
about the modding community and what modding is probably done to that game on
PC I bet it's something so that's cool all right anyhow let's move on oh no I
want to say one more thing about the mech warrior thing so you're into like
the mech games is this something you're thinking about um yeah probably not
going to I used to play the like one of the mech warrior games a while back but
I've kind of got him out of it all right well you know I love these little mini
arcade cabinets that I have right in fact some of them are actually branded
the whole my arcade thing and I think there's one over there this burger time
one which isn't on cam but I'll go grab it here this burger time one is a my
arcade machine and they're actually putting out a new version of this so
there's gonna be something like this but I think it's gonna be a little bit
bigger and for those these are the ones that they have I think a target target
is where you can get these the my arcade things so actually and I should
try turning it on so you guys can really see what this looks like if I can
remember oh no the whole the whole bottom is the whole little like on
switch and then hopefully it'll come on here and mm-hmm so sorry I'm starting it
up here trying to show the folks on Twitch what it looks like but it's a
pretty it's a pretty faithful reinterpretation of like burger time a
lot of them are our console versions yeah they really are yeah so I think of
this like Coleco or I think it's probably a little beyond that actually I
know that the the Cubert one was very similar to the Coleco version with a
few little bit of graphical tweaks mm-hmm so this same company the my arcade
is going to be putting out a Namco museum mini player it's going to have
20 different games on it including you know you would expect pac-man pac-man 2
pac-mania but also some other interesting selections including dragon
spirit that one's pretty cool rolling thunder all three of them splatter house
both of those games so it's kind of interesting a little bit of a diverse
selection from Namco the screen on that it's going to be four and a quarter
inches so I think that's a bit larger it's probably twice the size of what I
just showed mm-hmm on the twitch stream so it's a lot larger and it has but it's
a more vertical screen so it will kind of be more like an iPhone type of shape
or an Android you know more like the vertical shape but at the four and a
quarter inches so it's gonna have 20 games in it and it's going to retail I
believe for $99.99 and it's on its way out right now you can get it on Amazon
and my arcade calm it is kind of expensive I mean well if you think about
that that little burger time thing I just showed on cam that was about 35 I
want to say maybe 30 no I think it was 30 and then the Walmart ones which is a
different series those are arcade classics those set me back about 20 a
pop so but I do think I do think that my arcade ones they're little you can see
they're a little fancier they're a little sturdier the screens a slight bit
bigger I think they're a slight better quality it's not that the arcade classic
ones are bad they're really not they're good too but I think the my arcade ones
are definitely like a better quality so it's interesting that they're kind of
taking this one step further with this Namco museum collection but you know
these things are these these retro collections and things are really
everywhere so now Tigerclaw points out some of the my arcade little cabinets
have a bunch of games on them and they're mostly ripoff games I think that
a stranger things thing we saw recently which had come up on the show yeah it's
one of those examples too and that one was a little bit cheap looking um metal
mayhem says is there any device out there where pac-man hasn't appeared on
by this point well if it wasn't on there voluntarily I'm sure somebody put it on
there for sure so anyway yeah so that's it my arcade of Namco museum I I'm
interested but I a hundred bucks is a lot of money especially for the retro
stuff but I want to get more of the little cabinets the single game
cabinets I love that there's stuff like wreck-it Ralph or I'm sorry fix-it Felix
is the game obviously wreck-it Ralph inspired I love that that is where he
needs his own game he does like along the lines of rampage mm-hmm and there's
another what there was another one that was like 70 bucks I saw a target that
had a bunch of stuff in it I think this might be the one Tigerclaws linking with
bad dudes and there's other stuff in there too that's it was like a Data East
collection yeah it's a Data East collection is exactly what it is and I
think bad dudes is kind of like the one that they put on the box because that's
one of the most recognizable games in it I still I still kind of want one of
those arcade 1up machines I still feel like that might be a thing I end up
getting myself for the holidays because I know one of our friends star soccer I
got one of those Star Wars ones over the weekend or at least ordered it and I
know they were talking in chat there might be other people interested in
getting the Star Wars one so yeah those things those things look really cool so
all right well at this point we are going to open up our discord for you
guys to give us a call and say hello if you want to join in the conversation you
can head on over to the green room on our discord server over at vog network
calm or vog network calm slash discord that'll get you an invite right into the
discord server if you are new to orange launch radio hey we would love to have
you on the show but tell us a little bit about what you want to call in tonight
in the orange lounge radio channel just so we know you're not troll okay we
wouldn't know you have a legit question that's all it's always just making sure
we're making sure none of that toxicity makes it here to our little program so
our best we can I'm sure we can't avoid everything completely anyway let's get
to it I see somebody just joined the green room and we haven't had a call in
a while so let's get to it hi you are on orange launch radio who's this hey
what's going on everyone it's wrong though hey Rama is great to hear from
you what's on your mind tonight not much is great to hear you guys to see you
guys every week well hello hello to what to what you want to talk about tonight
all right so it was a couple things I want to talk about but I could save that
for another time but anything I want to talk about in regards to Nintendo
patching out Kristin Aussie's voice in Fire Emblem yeah what about that well I
will say this I mean it's no secret that I've been part of the anime cosplay
fandom for about 20 years and several of those years I've gotten friendly with
various voice actors and the sad part is his actions it's sort of been like sort
of not documented but well known it's like people around him knew this and the
thing is it just takes something big for everybody to come out of the woodwork to
point fingers at him for his actions now I do not condone what he did but I do
respect him in the way that he is going to do his best to make amends I look at
it this way um if you if you make mistakes it's up to you to own up and
redeem yourself so others can see it you've become a better person yeah I
think part of you know fixing mistakes though is kind of like accepting the
punishment like you know you did the crime do the time sort of thing right so
I mean I and I think this whole removal and and and shaming and so forth is kind
of a part of that it's true and I said this may have killed his career but
given how he made this long apology now it's not the first time I've seen
something like this right now there's something big going on in a community
with a million dollar lawsuit we'll just leave that that but if he's being
sincere about his actions and you know what he's he should get a second chance
if he's just saying it just to cover himself and save faith then you know
what you're done right no I and I can I can be open to that you know if you know
kind of accept the consequences which it sounds like you know I'm not following
this guy probably as closely but if he is accepting the consequences and doing
that and trying to be better from it then you know the whole idea of
rehabilitation is the first place is to get better and do better so as long as
the actions show that a person is doing better then I think there's room to
forgive that I guess or you know except that a person can change absolutely it's
just sad that it things like this come out this way it's like you make it big
then somebody from your past reminds you of something shitty you've done and you
never owned up to it it's sort of like the whole James Gunn thing with Guardians
of the Galaxy that he's owned up to what he's done frequently and then it keeps
coming back and he end up losing his job now he has his job back you know one I
think a lot of that was about how he kind of played that out in the public
eye too you know and that's why he's kind of back doing the film again so
interesting it has is he a big and I'm sorry I might have missed this is he big
in that like anime scene does he do voices there too is that how you kind of
know a little more about this yeah one of the voices he's known for is he is
Helios in Sailor Moon supers which is produced by this interesting okay didn't
know that you might know him by his alternate name on YouTube kerboffer I
don't watch enough YouTube stuff to know he's done various voices and then been
in backgrounds and various like tracks and stuff like that so I swear I kind of
know him so interesting all right well before I let you go anything else you
want to talk about tonight if I'm looking at the couch correctly do I see
a reference to the Golden Girls between Loki and Pikachu you do this is actually
a calendar that Loki got for Christmas and if you've been watching if you've
been paying attention on the stream we have updated it every month with the
latest month that we're on so this is July's picture which is again for the
sake of the podcast listeners I'm describing it a little bit it is Sophia
cooking up a dish and Blanche is looking on at it and the quote says if this
sauce were a person I'd get naked and make love to it and that was a Sophia
quote there you go I watched every single episode of that show when it was
on the air it's great I know a lot of like bros who watch Golden Girls it's
it's it's funny for everybody yes yes cuz let's be real most was watched it
for be Arthur anyway I always loved Betty White even at a young age so but
yes of course of course be Arthur I mean they were all great in their own ways so
it's interesting though how much merchandise and shit there is now with
all that be Arthur I'm on my wine break yes one of my favorite try to bullshit
one of my favorite be Arthur moments was from the Golden Girls and I just
will never forget this one is that you know where I think it's Betty White says
and where are you going and she goes to get ice cream or commit a felony I'm
gonna decide in the car
Blanche about homophobia oh yeah there's that yeah condoms rose condoms
condoms condoms yeah it was amazing moment too I remember it Sicily Golden
Girls are great on a future episode of olr we were just going to act out scenes
from the Golden Girls so I don't know what part Loki's gonna play but we'll
figure that out I think I think Loki kind of would be the Dorothy in this
situation I really do I'm definitely the Blanche probably of this group I think
our soccer would be Sophia you know what just go to SDCC and cosplay as the
Golden Girls and I'll stand behind you with a boom box playing to sound playing
at the theme song you would dark soccer you would definitely the one be the one
that would be like picture it Namco arcade mobile 1996 and then not give a
shit yes I'd say the dry things absolutely all right anyway all right
I'm gonna let you go Rama so we can squeeze in another call but they walk
out with my with my Walker good to hear it was always my friend right back at
you all right bye all right let's get to another call here on the show hello
you're on orange launch radio who's this
hello no hello hey this is that deaf sorry I had my
mute on that's okay sometimes I know we surprise you when we drag and drop you
on air what's on your mind tonight well I want to talk about something that
happened Mexico this week involving eSports a little back of a little
backstory there's this Federation eSports Federation in Mexico that was
initiated back in February if I remember correctly so it's like okay a big deal
so we can have like national teams support for for the eSports community
here in Mexico all good fast forward to this week they're starting their their
tournaments they're starting out to scout for national team members and they
start charging the around 600 pesos which is around I think let me get my
calculations almost correctly like $30 which isn't much but right the thing is
they are affiliated with the National Sports Committee in Mexico so they are
a civil association they cannot profit of any tournament or anything an event
they they're doing so it's like a really really bad situation for them and in in
especially because one of the tournaments they were they are holding
is for clash of clans or one one of the mobile games and supercell the developer
came out on Twitter and told them hey hey guys you cannot charge any any
amount of money for any of the participants so it yeah it was a really
really big deal this week in Mexico because of that and and actually one of
the under of the people one of the heads of famous which was just called came out
and said that yeah they didn't like expected this to happen because they do
need the money they they do have to pay for the train training for the for the
participants if they get selected they have to pay the trips they have to pay
everything involved for for the making of these tournaments so it's
understandable but they should have like came out of upfront about it it's like
the many people here and including myself we're kind of disappointed on
that and how they handle it because it's like really really like shady stuff be
all behind all I have talked about already where they try to make I was
just saying were they trying to make a claim about where the money was going at
the start when they actually announced the tournaments and all that stuff they
just they just said you have to be affiliated with them with famous and you
have to pay the 600 pesos they didn't say why they didn't say like oh we need
this to pay for for all the events and in all that all the other stuff that is
needed which is understandable but again they weren't clear about it and it was
like until like a few days ago I think Friday that an article popped out in an
interview they they made what up with a website here in Mexico that actually
like explain all that but again it's like way too late and many people are
like actually mad legit mad about it so it's understand again it's understandable
why they did it but they should have like been clear about it from the
beginning yeah especially when like the developers are probably sitting here
thinking these folks that are completely unaffiliated with us are making money
off of our games using our games in the promotion using our games to attract
people and then they're charging this fee for them and even if the fee is you
know pretty nominal you know three bucks is not a whole lot of money it's cheaper
than a grande at Starbucks and all is said and done but it's it's the
principle yeah actually $30 I think but again not not that big of a deal with
with the money involved but it's the thing that yeah even they got in trouble
kind of in trouble with supercell which is again the developer they came out and
you cannot charge these official rules for any official tournament it's like
you cannot charge any participant at all even like even if there's like an an
entry fee for the venue you cannot charge them that yeah it's a free entry
for any participant and they're also involved with overwatch not necessarily
League but the World Cup and also other games like the League of Legends and
others other games that are going like they have a World Cup basically huh
interesting well I'll be curious to kind of see if there's more that develops on
this if more companies kind of come out against it or if you know these guys
kind of reverse course on that or give a little more clarity to where these this
money is why they're collecting it where it's going or if they suddenly
make a big charitable donation or I'll be curious to kind of see where this
ends up yeah me too actually because again it I actually want to for them to
like do do good do better actually yeah because they're trying to get like games
officially recognized by the the International Olympics Committee they're
working really hard on it and but like this this kind of stuff is like kind of
disappointing if anything for sure for sure all right my friend I'm gonna let
you go so we wrap up the show but thank you thank you for the news from a place
we are you know an area where we aren't always paying attention all the time so
it's nice to hear from news from around the world hey thanks for having me good
like always no problem take care my friend yeah all right well there you go
that that's gonna do it I think for the call tonight which means we are about
oops I almost closed OBS I'm going to close discord we are about to the end of
another episode of orange lounge radio not bad for a week of news that was a
little bit slower although I should check in make sure we're low-key there's
no last-minute stories there's just one last thing I was gonna mention so the
Epic Games Store put out some new free games for the month and one of those was
a game called moon lighter which apparently someone spotted that there
was the enable cloud save function and which they'd come in that on Twitter
and Tim Sweeney responded with we've actually enabled cloud saves for a
couple of games right now but they'll be rolling out more so it's another
enhancement that they're finally adding to their storefront that they really
should have tried it for a while yeah something to try to kind of maybe
justify a lot more of those exclusives they're snapping up when people don't
really want to use their store so interesting interesting we'll see what
develops of that all right well we are gonna wrap up for the night I'm gonna
say as I always do thank you for tuning in and spending your night with us here
at orange launch radio we appreciate all of the support if you like what you
heard here at orange launch radio please tell a friend or two about the show help
us spread the word because we are the word where every we are the show where
every gamer has a voice but if the voices aren't here to air then what are
we gonna do so please tell a friend or two about the show and you know a nice
five-star review on a place like iTunes goes an awful long way also you can do
these auto hosts of vog network over on your twitch channel and whether you have
a hundred followers or one follower that stuff goes a long way towards
discoverability so please consider putting us on your auto host list that
would be fantastic otherwise I think I think that's all I've got to say and I
think we're ready to go around and get everybody's final thoughts we will be
back in seven days to do this all over again Bobby black wolf who airs live
before us at a voice keys Network will not be live next week he is off to a
convention called Gen Con which is very big on the board games I know so I'm
hoping he will get some video even if it's board games I'm sure he'll bring
back some video and I would think somewhere in that building there's some
video game representation so he'll probably get a little bit of that so
yeah there's gonna be that and yeah we look forward to seeing you guys next
week we will still be here on orange lounge radio at that time so dark soccer
do you want to start us off tonight her with the orange hair do you have any
final thoughts for our listeners tonight um don't want to be a downer but stop
shooting people you twats oh yeah that thing you just sent me during the show
there's an active shooter right now at the Gilroy garlic festival and that you
know for Northern California that's a huge event and so like and the first
question I asked was you know our bling-blank wasn't there were they yeah
so she was there yesterday I almost went there this weekend but it's a hundred
some degrees outside and it's also like an hour yeah still still just you know
at any rate at any rate we need more than your thoughts and prayers keep them
to yourself but also though in more positive things just like don't be don't
don't be a douche just don't be an asshole if you are thinking crazy
asshole things see a therapist that's a lot better than killing people go go see
a therapist and maybe take it in the ass just say thanks my final thought tonight
is going to say because I forgot to mention this during my gaming week but I
was meeting up with some ingress buddies to kind of keep an eye on what was going
on in the myriad anomaly series so I just want to congratulate the
enlightened on winning the myriad anomaly series this weekend so that's my
final thought congrats to all that well-thought resistance polite clapping
wink all right Loki your final thought tonight my final thought is I'm hungry
and I didn't have no time to grab dinner today me too I'm like 1500 calories
under my budger and something drinks a stay hydrated Loki I'm saved I've
stayed hydrated I just need to actually eat food now all right all right well
that's gonna do it thank you guys again so much for being here live or on our
podcast feed however you decided to consume orange laundry oh thank you so
much for doing so we will see you in seven days to do it all again how does
that sound great I thought so goodnight you've been listening to Orange Lounge
Radio Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios to join us
for a live show tune in to fog network calm Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific 9
p.m. Eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not
necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or fog network
but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you