[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Allgames.com
[SPEAKER_09]: That's Thursday night at 11 p.m.
[SPEAKER_09]: Eastern, 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pacific.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they're going to have a pre-show as well, so just tune in at 6 Pacific and you'll be good.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're actually going to have performing at the show this Guitar Hero Band.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what they've done is they've actually gotten heroes of guitar playing to perform at this band, like
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to read the entire list here.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys can go to allgames.com to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But get this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lyle Workman, who's like a guitar player for Sting and Beck.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they have Daryl Anders, who's the bassist for Tower of Power and Bonnie Hayes.
[SPEAKER_09]: They also have Marcus Henderson, who's the guitar player for Drist and En Vogue.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they just have like all these standout stars there that are going to be performing in this band.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that should be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be airing that live over on All Games, our buddies over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, so let's get into some news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last segment we talked about Katamari Damacy ending, sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: We also talked about some big lies going around in the industry right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big stinky ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now we're going to talk about some big acquisitions and things of that nature.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, tis the season to buy a company smaller than yours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starting off here with THQ.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're acquiring Vigil Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: For those probably not very familiar with Vigil Games, they created both Marvel's Uncanny X-Men and Battle Chasers series.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's part of the studio system strategy, which is designed to foster a singular vision and unique culture at each of our studios, according to Jack Sorensen, the executive vice president of the worldwide studios at THQ.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's basically to inject more of that creativity into their games, I guess, where it may be lacking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, now that I think of it, THQ did create... I want to see the outfit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, that game was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, speaking of bigger fish in the pond, Sony, they've signed a deal with PlayLogic for future first-party games, and that should be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, unfortunately, they haven't said what the game was, but it is slated to come out on PSP PlayStation 2...
[SPEAKER_08]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: is purchasing Battlefield developer Digital Illusion CE
[SPEAKER_08]: Battlefield 2 Demo March 24 Xbox Live
[SPEAKER_09]: The demo is actually going to have up to 24 players being able to play online.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is kind of cool that a lot of the Xbox Live demos lately have been, you know, these big multiplayer things like the outfit and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So even though they're not my type of games, like I really tried, you guys, I tried to play Battlefield 2 because everybody was just raving about it, but it's just...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just not my type of game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I'll check it out on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell, if it's free, why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm going to suck, and I'm going to be a detriment to any team I'm on.
[SPEAKER_09]: But check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's coming out for the Xbox 360 in April.
[SPEAKER_09]: April 11th or 12th
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: and I haven't watched MTV in forever so I didn't even know they were making music videos in high def but I guess that makes sense just real quick the Xbox Live top 10 games of the week 10 needs first speed most wanted 9 the outfit demo 8 Battlefield 2 which is amazing because how is that
[SPEAKER_09]: Already there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it the old one?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm thinking the old one on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, and then seven, Project Gotham Racing 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Six, Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: Five, Perfect Dark Zero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Four, EA Sports Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three, Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two, Ghost Recon 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: And number one is still Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Should we start a betting pool on when Halo 2 will actually be dethroned?
[SPEAKER_09]: Halo 3, Gears of War
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the 24th was the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: You got 10 days.
[SPEAKER_09]: 10 days, Capcom, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get that stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, I want my achievement points for beating the game with Chun-Li 100%.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I heard that the reason why it wasn't out yet is because they're having trouble with lag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lots of lag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or that horrible lag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fine, if they have to spend extra time to make it work good, then that's fine, because we don't want them releasing it and just patching it later to make up for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's fine, but a status check would be nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, moving on to another completely different topic.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, we were talking about Silent Hill a little bit in Part A, but this is not about the movie, necessarily.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of, sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually a talk from 1UP stating that there's going to be a Silent Hill remake on the PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Konami's been all happy over the talk about the movie, so there's a
[SPEAKER_03]: A rumor that they are going to re-release the first game though with Harry Mason's wife, who is the heroine of the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it does have to do with the movie after all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's sort of a tie-in.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that that's a good idea, but, you know, they'd have to make some changes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'd have to be an alternate universe sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wouldn't that have to kind of come out, like, very soon, if they wanted it to promote the movie?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe they're going to wait for the DVD release?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait for the DVD release, because you want to see how well the movie does first before you go and make a game about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wouldn't that be a great combo pack, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: DVD and game?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they've tried it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sony does that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no, I'm thinking of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Sony did do that once.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did, oh, what was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stealth in the Wipeout Stealth, which, whoo!
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that didn't sell very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, stealth sucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this something you'd probably check out, Jamie, being a fan of Silent Hill?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, of course.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I think I would, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even though remakes can be a little ass sometimes, I mean, sometimes they're really good, and I think back to, of course, Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: All-Stars and the greatest remakes they ever did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Viva Piñata
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooray Pinatas!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a game which is going to have a cartoon based on it about a living island of pinatas.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what, may you ask, pinatas do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they have to fix this garden that has kind of gone awry and you have to lure your fellow pinatas to your garden.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's what that second to last VG Cats was about.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just all came together.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just dawned on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, it was so much fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what is this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Xbox's response to Animal Crossing, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is the easy way to put it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's...
[SPEAKER_08]: They're trying to make a Pokemon, and goddammit, they're going to be damned if it'll happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because aren't they supposed to do like a TV show in all night?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: A TV show.
[SPEAKER_09]: About pinatas.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I come into a town of Eva Pinata and start regulating with a baseball bat, will I get lots of candy?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the only way I would want this game to come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you could play a little kid who fucking goes around with a giant stick and beats the shit out of these stupid animals and steals their candy.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is the game I want.
[SPEAKER_09]: God damn it, Grand Theft Pinata.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to ask, why all this hate for Viva Pinata before you've even... Have you seen the website?
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, have you seen the website?
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw screenshots, I have not seen the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you seen the website?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I have not seen the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen screenshots of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The website is like some Shrek wannabe crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: These characters come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: They even, they're like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_08]: A game based on piñatas?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's seriously, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sounds like it could be innovative.
[SPEAKER_08]: with the way they're doing Xbox Live where you can communicate with other players and send your pinatas to their stuff to kind of make it like Animal Crossing type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But really, it looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have chatters that disagree.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xander C in our chatroom says, Viva Pinata looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it just because maybe this isn't your kind of thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Penny Arcade, not VGCats, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pinyarkade.
[SPEAKER_08]: Their comic was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, seriously, I have seen the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched the little flash video that they have where they're doing screen tests of this Viva Pinata thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like it's a bad Pixar movie gone awry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could come out of nowhere and make it cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is just going to be another failed attempt like Cameo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Cameo, to be honest, wasn't that great of a game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was supposed to be a Zelda killer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't quite a Zelda killer.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's not a Zelda killer.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an okay game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty much, if you're an adventure gamer person, it's pretty much your only choice right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just feels like it could have been done on the regular Xbox.
[SPEAKER_09]: It feels like there's really...
[SPEAKER_09]: Fable was almost just the same type of thing in many ways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Props are rare for at least trying something different.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only problem is I don't like the idea of how they're putting out this cartoon thing to go with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because all they're trying to do is like, well kids like cartoons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cartoons sold Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's... I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I applaud them for doing something different besides the usual Xbox fare, which turns a lot of people off to the system, which is sports, shooters, and all those types of games.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need some more variety in the Xbox lineup, so I'm happy they're trying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rare needs to just put out another goddamn Killer Instincts game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can they, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they can.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, fine, make something else that's similar.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just make another fighting game or something, or put out something really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously, go to the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you think I'm lying about how crappy this game is, go to the website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which most of our chatroom does disagree with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, and go to the website, watch the video, and tell me if you're not pissed off at this game after you watch the video.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want a piñata game like a first-person shooter, so you go around and shoot the piñatas, and then you have to go cut the candy.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you get candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, you ready to inject some rage into this episode of Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_09]: Shut up and play the music!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright. ...
[SPEAKER_03]: My FU of the week goes towards education.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I've been having to deal with, I dropped a class, and then I have a, she's such a smart lady, a great teacher, but she tells us there's this assignment due and the assignment's not on the assignment page, it's just for each chapter, so what do we do?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it just bugs me that there's this expectation that we don't have lives outside of class, that we are given just buttloads of homework to do, and some of us work full-time, so what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's, it's not a very big FU, but that's what's been on my mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your FU.
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU is the bad drivers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, get this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was driving down the freeway today, going to go check out Tux's for the wedding.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I see some dumbass pulling off to the side of the road.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's like, because he missed his intersection or turn or whatever off the freeway.
[SPEAKER_07]: The friggin' idiot starts backing up on the freeway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Backing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Flipped the goddamn thing in the reverse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who was driving?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, goddamn woman in a fucking SUV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was she on her phone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, she probably was, but I didn't bother to look because there was a giant trail of smoke from her skidding into the goddamn side of the road there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid people out there, and I see it daily.
[SPEAKER_09]: Curses.
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU would go to Weekends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or should I say actually the work week, because weekends aren't long enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really feel like I haven't done, I mean, don't get me wrong, I've actually done a lot, a lot of stuff this weekend, but not enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of wish there was more time in the weekend, because I really have had no time to just kind of lie on the couch and go, I'm just relaxing today.
[SPEAKER_09]: So F you to our society only allowing us two days on the weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we should work for two days in a week and get a five-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would rock.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, I'm just lazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm still on the topic of pinata, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: They still can't get over that pinata thing, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: We now have Grand Theft Pinata, Metal Gear Pinata, Katamari Pinata.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: They always take one gag a week and run with it, don't they, in chat?
[SPEAKER_09]: You did not just bring up the Viva Pinata website over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it does look like a Shrek ripoff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll check it out later.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's so funny!
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I want to get on to another topic here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kotaku.com has recently posted some images.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pinata Mamie, 2DX I thought you were laughing at Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, that's not very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're a respected site.
[SPEAKER_09]: Kotaku.com recently posted some pictures, you have to go back to March 15th though, of the Game Boy Advance SP in pretty pink, now with a brighter backlit screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or should I say, pearly pink is actually the color they're going for there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why do you think that they might be trying to release a pink Game Boy?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not getting enough female players.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because all females buy anything that's pink.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just, it's bred into their DNA.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know a lot of males that would be interested in the pink system.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're just, not the typical mindset that a lot of game companies cater to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: My Game Boy Advance, however, was pink.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did it just so that people couldn't pin me down to any one particular thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also have an afterburner in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, I really only brought that up so we could tie into our next story that's going to be brought to us by DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, it's actually our website of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, our website of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here we go then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's bring in the theme music.
[SPEAKER_09]: You like to surf the internet and find a great website for us every week, don't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, this one was linked to me by a friend of mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on The Escapist, and the article can be found at www.escapistmagazine.com slash issue slash 17 slash 27.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's, oh my god, girls don't exist on the interweb.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exclamation point one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'll go ahead and read off just the first paragraph.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's by somebody named...
[SPEAKER_03]: Whitney Butts.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am a girl on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I said it.
[SPEAKER_03]: A girl on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: There really are quite a few of us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can type.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can play games with the best of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you, my friend, are about to get owned by a girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically the story of somebody who's been playing World of Warcraft and no one believed that she was a girl or thought that she was like a girl speaking for her boyfriend on the chat or was like, you know, not.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a picture of her on the site.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's
[SPEAKER_09]: I read the article when you posted it on our secret place that we put all the stories up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I read it and I thought it was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: The IRC conversations that she posted in those chat logs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was like, I actually wanted to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We didn't have enough time to prepare it, but I actually wanted to do IRC theater.
[SPEAKER_09]: We were going to interact the dialogue here, but it's just amazing the, for lack of a better word, stupidity of people.
[SPEAKER_09]: My mother used to use this term a lot, and I hated it then, but it's the only way I can think of to describe this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hard-headedness of the youth that, OMG, she's a girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got it on Rock and Rock.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's either that or...
[SPEAKER_03]: I would get it every so often back when I was a moderator on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was either, oh my god, you're a girl, or oh my god, you're not Asian.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because that's a stereotype that only Asians play DDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, you're not an Asian boy!
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually got it when I played Tetranet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would actually, when I used to list my video game collection on places, people go, you can't have all that because you're a girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where is there some type of law that says I can't be good at video games and I can't enjoy video games because I have boobs and a uterus?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, where is that law?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to see it so that I can set it on fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what, it's interesting because there was also one of those IRC logs talked about where she responded that she said something about like, ooh, I really like Johnny Depp or something, and one of the people said, that's gay, what are you, gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I was kind of like, so what if it was a gay person?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, obviously as a gay gamer myself, I face sometimes a lot of these same types of issues that you're bringing up as well where people like go,
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my gosh, you're actually gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: And then they'll shut up for a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or sometimes I've gotten that where it's like, you're gay, you shouldn't be playing video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should be being in a musical and listening to Barbra Streisand.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me be the first to tell you, I fucking hate Barbra Streisand.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate her, I hate her music, I hate her movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate everything about Barbra Streisand.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's like butter.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, she's like shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like her at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: My mom likes her a lot, but that's my mom.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's those types of stereotypes I really hate.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, so what if I'm gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: I can play video games just like anybody else.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what if you're a girl?
[SPEAKER_09]: We've all got hands.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all you need to use a controller, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: And apologies to any of you guys who might have had amputation or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's devices for you too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've actually seen someone play with a joystick using their chin.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's also another thing I want to read on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, just because a girl plays video games doesn't necessarily mean she's going to instantly put her picture up on the internet for the male population to drool over because it's a woman that plays a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go ahead and quote her on this again, if nobody minds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Again, a girl who doesn't show her picture on the internet is not a girl, and the only girls on the internet are actually guys who are just trying to get free stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't get me wrong, I haven't gotten free stuff before.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I have gotten free stuff before, but I don't solicit it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like those, quote, girls who sit around dancing for tips and games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know who you are, and you know you're not a real girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: Real girls don't exist on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, FYI, guys, if you think every girl that you run into in an MMO is actually a girl, just like if you assume that every guy you run into on an MMO is actually a guy, you are an idiot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've played male characters before.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I've played female characters before.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not because I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_03]: On my Ragnarok account, I played a male so that I could play a bard.
[SPEAKER_09]: How many of you guys out there, how many of you straight men out there, have ever played Street Fighter 2 as Chun-Li?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did that make you gay?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the whole thing just really gets me because, and I have, you know, being a female gamer, it's even worse though being a female gamer with a voice in the community though.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, I've gotten some hate mail from people who have literally told me to get off the radio and get back in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_03]: What the fuck century is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_03]: What backwards-ass country did you grow up in where they still have Neanderthals in charge banging women on the head and dragging them around by their hair to make them go cook them dinner?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, seriously, DarkSakura is a pretty good cook.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will give her that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am an excellent cook, but then again, you know, that's not the point.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also don't clean house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I make my husband do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a house husband.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, for real.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but the thing is, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: Even my husband's friends are a bit surprised that I'll go in there every so often and play games with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And regularly own people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to say, when Tekken 3 was out, I was the goddess of Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I used to go in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so humble about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to go in there and smoke all the boys.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they'd be like, oh my god, I got beat by a girl.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is also Alabama, but still.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember going into Cyber Station one day, the same one I worked at.
[SPEAKER_03]: and we had the brand new Deluxe Tekken 3 there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these guys have been there since the store opened at 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_03]: I show up at 2 in the afternoon.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been doing nothing but playing King all day, doing the throw combos.
[SPEAKER_03]: I go in there with Jin and just knock him off the machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Didn't somebody actually tell you once, like, oh my god, it's the girl that plays Tekken?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like you're the girl, the only girl in the United States that's ever played Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went back to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: and ran into somebody at the arcade and I was like, yeah, I used to come in here all the time and play Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, you're that girl that plays Tekken!
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you're the only girl in the universe that's ever played Tekken.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently I had been talked about for a little bit after I left.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also was the one on campus who used to beat people on, because we had a Darkstalkers machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: That used to be my game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That and Killer Instinct.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it gets me that
[SPEAKER_03]: There's this whole thing that girls can't play games like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either that or the girls who are like the uber sluts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this ties into the next article that I'm going to bring up here, which I'm sure will piss you off a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's located at www.kimrom.info is the little blog.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's the blog post from March 8th.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it goes, Female Gaming My Ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think I get the point that they're trying to make in this article because they talk about like, you know, they show these pictures, especially like here it is, like a girl website, a girl gaming website.
[SPEAKER_09]: Quote, another great example of how female gaming attracts attention is a new team who calls themselves Can't Touch This.
[SPEAKER_09]: The image below is their new homepage design.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, it's totally an exploitation of women's site and it's pink and it shows like a girl in a bikini, a little butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think what's kind of amusing is that they put a response like if it was a guy site.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: and I can totally see where this would piss someone off.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's right.
[SPEAKER_09]: The sensationalism of girls playing video games just because they're girls and showing off the tits and everything and like OMG this is what a girl playing a game looks like and when you run into a girl team they're all going to be babes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's just that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's stupidity.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I agree with that portion of the article.
[SPEAKER_08]: How the hell are you going to operate the mouse if you're holding a gun?
[SPEAKER_08]: That doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: The article
[SPEAKER_09]: was written like, and this is my opinion here guys, but I think the article was written so trashy and so sensationalistic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me give you a way that the article opens up here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Men are better at computer games than women.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big surprise.
[SPEAKER_09]: We grow up playing games, we spend enormous amounts of time playing games, we consciously dedicate time to better ourselves, and we are competitive by nature.
[SPEAKER_09]: No wonder we're better gamers.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm thinking like, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've never seen a woman who's obsessed with soccer playing soccer, because those bitches are some of the most competitive women I've ever seen in my life.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, just these broad generalizations that the person's making here to open.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if they're doing this for shock value or something, but it just totally, like, when I read it and it opened up with that, it totally, like, I was like, okay, I don't even, even if there's a point in here somewhere, it's lost on me.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, I'm sure you felt similarly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did actually reply to this guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_03]: He actually replied to me too, but he was just saying more of the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: I listed an itemized bit, and actually what I first started off saying is I wasn't going to dignify this poor excuse for an editorial with a response, but perhaps I have a small responsibility to do so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nor were we going to talk about it on the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops!
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, I think that this guy's idiocy should be pointed out because...
[SPEAKER_03]: This is an attitude that's prevalent, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand wanting to see less of the, quote, hoochie gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's like I pointed out, he's basically going from his male ego.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all he was speaking from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's another quote.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the real problem with female gaming is that female gamers in general have the same ambitions as men, but they lack the dedication and drive to fulfill those ambitions.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let that quote speak for itself there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's just like, you know, I know plenty of women who are very high level.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, there was just an article that was floating the internet this week about one of the girls who was on season seven of Buffy, one of the other Slayers, is secretly a level 60 character in World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Girls can have that ambition and drive to succeed in a game just like any guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you can't ever say all girls and you can't ever say all men because you're going to be wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of my co-workers regularly talks to the guy in the cubicle across from me about her level, what, close to 70 character on World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: and she's been wanting me to pay for my accounts again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a friend who's like the C-Mode goddess in Phantasy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: She just goes in there and smokes people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why is it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why can't...
[SPEAKER_03]: Why do guys think this?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm not saying that all guys think this, but it does seem to be a pretty prevalent misconception among male gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, where did this... I honestly, and I hate to, I don't want to turn around the whole sexist thing myself, but I honestly think that a whole big chunk of it is male ego being threatened by women being able to do something.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, some of it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: As a guy, I would agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: But granted, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess my perspective on things is different.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it sounds to me – and I understand this guy's underlying point is that maybe there's a little bit of – he's a little –
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want her representative of my fellow female gamers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to go lay on this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, form your own opinions.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to bring it up because, like it or not, it is an article that's been circulating a lot of the big news sites this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: So check it out if you want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Camerom.info and blog for March 8th.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure some of you guys want to respond to that, so we are going to open up our Skype line at this time.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you guys want to give us a call, you can give us a call on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just go to interactwithus on www.orangeloungeradio.com, or you can actually give us a telephone call as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: The telephone number is 916-
[SPEAKER_09]: and 226-9067.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember that that could be a toll call, so please ask the permission of whoever runs the line before you actually give us a call because there might be charges incurred.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow, they're lighting up tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start off with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Raven's Dolphin Well, there's lots of games that come out for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There are a lot of games that come out for the PSP, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm going to be honest, there just hasn't been a whole lot that's really been that exciting to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's not to say that there isn't stuff coming up that's exciting to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Such as, well, the Mega Man games were just released, and I still need to check those out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But of course, me and my Katamari.
[SPEAKER_09]: Luminous, I named as my game of the year last year, was a PSP game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, there are things to like about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think that you can't...
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not existing just to be a game system.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're also trying to do a lot of other stuff with it, such as the built-in web stuff and the podcast downloads and the Flash being incorporated into it and the iToy and all that other stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Was there anything else you wanted to say about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought Mega Man, the two of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you think about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a little bit of lag, so just feel free to speak freely.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give your thoughts on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I loved them both.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought Powered Up was the best.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm definitely going to have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, you can download maps from it from their own servers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's kind of cool, and that's something, you know, that the DS doesn't do, is, like, the whole, like, I mean, it's just now starting to get into the online interactivity thing, so, you know, Nintendo still has a long way to grow in that department, but, of course, you know, Metroid Prime Hunters is exciting, but I like, you know, I like that idea of all the expansions and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, anyway, Raven's Dolphin, thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are going to have to go ahead and let you go, because we're getting a little too much lag there, but, and we got a lot of calls on the line tonight, so we want to go to another caller there, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, this is Speck.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Speck, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a little bit of lag, so just go ahead and get your question out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, sorry about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead and get your question out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I do want to say that the biggest April Fool's joke was probably the Nintendo On, if you guys ever heard about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us a little bit about this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I vaguely remember this, but tell us about this joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was someone had, right before E3, had put together this huge trailer saying what the revolution was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I think, I think, wasn't this like kind of last year that they did something like this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this is like, um, I think around Tokyo Game Show, something like that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, so what do you, what in your mind made this the greatest April Fool's prank in your opinion?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it made people actually believed it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: It did run on a lot of gaming sites, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's success if you're any joke.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the success of a joke, and one of many reasons why I hate April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, and also, Jamie, I just have,
[SPEAKER_04]: One of my friends wanted to say something to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega rocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't... Did... It was either DarkSakura rocks or fuck off.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't tell which one of the two it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said Sega rocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got a lot of lag there, but thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got some first-time callers tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, caller, are you there?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it says Sega Rocks.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's still cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, unfortunately I'm not hearing from this guy, so maybe your mic was down or something was going on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Nintendo Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo Maniac 64, what is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Sakura likes me or something, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's saying woohoo.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you're fairly cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're fans of you because you're fans of us.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why we cheer you when you come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, what's up, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um... Not much, except... Can I rant about this one friend of mine?
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it gaming-related?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm, kinda.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's... He's... Well, okay, he's a pretty big PS tool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, so tell us... Okay, get the rant out.
[SPEAKER_05]: He just, like, always...
[SPEAKER_05]: This is like Nintendo and Xbox, just like everyone else.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's not Sony, this is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, punch him in the face.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what else to tell you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Has he ever actually played Microsoft or Nintendo products?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, he played Pictochow, my dear.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that doesn't fucking count.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's not even like a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to sit that boy down and tell him, you know what, you need to try it, or you need to S-T-F-U.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you tell him that three boobs on the radio said that to him.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's another thing I want to rant about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, hurry up.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's basically a neo-Nazi.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hide is my dog, hide is my dog, hide is my dog.
[SPEAKER_09]: Isn't that a Bloomchen song?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we gotta let you both go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: And kick that guy in the balls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to one more call here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, hi there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Funny Dale.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Funny Dale.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to talk about the issue you had a few minutes ago about the female gamers.
[SPEAKER_11]: By all means, go for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the reason why you see these websites, the Frag Dolls and the PMS Clan all have these young supermodels is because, well, I hate to say this, but a good portion of the video game audience is a bunch of 15 year olds who, well, can't get laid.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they shouldn't really be looking at porn, so the Frag Dolls are probably the closest thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: And I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I totally agree with what you're saying, Funnydale, because it's apparent in what's happening with G4 TV as well, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it was supposed to be like a network for games, and it kind of turned into it's just geared at the young 15-year-old males and stuff who can't get laid, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the problem I see with that, is that if gaming truly wants to open its audience to everyone, as you see that Nintendo is trying to do very badly, and granted, Nintendo doesn't sponsor any of this stuff,
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm talking about the gamer community as a whole.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to be looked at as something other than a bunch of 15-year-old kids who can't get laid, this shit has to stop.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's what's really about, and I think that's why we're here kind of speaking out against it a little bit, is here to say, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Gamers come in all shapes, sizes, and types, and we like games, and we don't have to fit into these certain stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's just another sign of how stereotypes hurt society, and that goes in all facets of life.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why can't we go back to the wonderful flashback for me like 20 years ago, or maybe not even quite 20 years ago,
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go back to the time when gaming was real gaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're talking the Nintendo World Championships.
[SPEAKER_08]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why can't we go back to simpler times where it was based on skill and not whether you're a man or a woman.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's how well you're good at Super Mario Brothers, Rad Racer, and Tetris.
[SPEAKER_09]: And when the Power Glove was so bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Kali, you were trying to get a point in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, the problem with the argument is that game publishers are there to make money, and they make money doing that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just look at MTV.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good point, but also look at games like Tetris and Brain Training, and the PopCap games is another big one on the internet, PopCap.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those games and those types of things really reach to such a broader audience.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the publishers have to be willing to take a risk once in a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tetris is the exception
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, as long as it makes the money, they'll keep on doing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's unfortunate, but it's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_09]: But that's, you know, again, that's why I vote with my dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a point that came up in Part A, you know, vote with my dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to continue to support these games that are all about, you know, the TNA.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, well, maybe Dead or Alive, though, because that game's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: Spoiled Rotten Prisoners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, seriously, it's really interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now when you go to prison, you actually might be able to play video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Inmates in Oregon can purchase a plug-and-play console, kind of like a kiosk Nintendo, with 50 embedded games and are mounted to an LCD TV if they behave.
[SPEAKER_08]: Plus, I don't know, it's just,
[SPEAKER_08]: Really interesting that they're actually coming out with video games from inmates.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on, they're in there for... Unless, unless they're playing really crappy games like, you know, E.T.
[SPEAKER_08]: or something like that for the 2600.
[SPEAKER_09]: What I thought was funniest about that article was that some stupid prison had allowed games like Grand Theft Auto and games where you're killing cops to actually be played until they realized what was actually in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, I didn't realize there was cop killing in Cop Killer the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're tax dollars at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this a good thing, a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing is that I hear that this comes out to sort of combat prison riots.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's to try and de-stress the prisoners.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm kind of like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You've got to figure out a different way to break up prison riots.
[SPEAKER_07]: We shoot them with a shotgun to the face.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty simple.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now we're getting into pretty radical politics.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, you've got to think of other ways to combat prison riots.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to be rioting if they don't have a face.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't let them out of their cell if they're going to riot.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the running man, because Richard Dawson was a villain, and that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: One thing that's certainly villainous in its own way is spam on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know you guys hate getting spam mail.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you can get spam on your Xbox 360, thanks to Burnout Revenge, who encourages you to send in-game clips to your friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you even get achievement points when you do so, right, Loki, who spammed me last week with this?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, I think you guys need to be a little smarter when you're thinking of your achievement points, scales like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not an achievement in gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's an achievement in whoring.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to be honest, the replays are kind of retarded anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I've made some pretty cool ones, but nothing like, oh my god, you have to see this, except for the glitch that I saw, but I couldn't record that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, you got some hackin' and crackin' news, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first one, it's pretty major, actually, was that the Xbox 360 DVD firmware has been hacked.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's a video of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically, the way it works is all Xbox 360 games that come out there, of course, they're all encoded so that you can't reverse engineer them and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And plus, each single...
[SPEAKER_08]: Their file type, XEX, has a media flag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, the media flag tells the Xbox what type of media it's on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whether that be a CD-R, DVD-R, DVD Plus R, etc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or DVD, Xbox, DVD, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it knows what type of media it's on.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if, for example, I try to copy a game and I make a perfect copy and it's on a DVD-R, it's going to say, hey, this isn't a pressed CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what they did was they actually modified the DVD firmware not to make that check.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if I make an exact copy of the game, it'll run like nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, as with all these exploits, the hacking group behind it is not releasing the firmware because they don't endorse piracy, they only endorse hacking.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, it's not going to be released, but it can be done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's somebody else off to figure it out, I suppose, who doesn't endorse piracy, if that's what you're into.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, and here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I remember back in the heyday, when I used to import games, I used to get HK copies.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, these were mass-produced, pirated copies where they would be pressed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why aren't these floating around out there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, because if you can press an exact copy of the game, and it's on a DVD, I mean, shouldn't it work?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course some other cool stuff of course on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first one is this really strange stick minigame.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like with stick figures called Pointless Tormenting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like it already.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's basically you torment stick figures.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just really simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you're interested in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember Stick Fighter?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dick Fighter was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on PSP updates, so you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another kind of cool game is another homebrew game that's been, I think even on the Dreamcast, called Dragon Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like a Final Fantasy fighting game, almost.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has the really super deformed characters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, Dragon Fighter version 0.2 was released on the PSP, so you can check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think actually some of the graphics were used from RPG Maker is what they based a lot of this on.
[SPEAKER_08]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might be something interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on PSP Updates as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another one that I did find that was kind of neat was this game called Irkwan Masters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now if you remember way back in the day in DOS games, there was this game called Star Control, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was like a kind of a space shooter RPG type of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this is based on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's also based on another knockoff game called, of course, Irkon Masters.
[SPEAKER_08]: But check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have version 0.50 available.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's anything like Star Control or Star Control 2 was, really fun shooter game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're now going to go ahead and let DarkSakura dive in and open up our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you guys send us letters to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com, DarkSakura likes to dig through the mailbag and pick out a few favorites to make fun of here live on air.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm good at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's going to give some serious responses with our help here to this week's letters.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's open up the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who sent us some mail this week?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sipspon wrote in and said...
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got another suggestion for the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about making a question for the listener call-in section?
[SPEAKER_03]: As it seems to me now, the call-in part is really people just doing a shout-out or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: There doesn't seem to be any real structure.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you were to pose a question early in the show, listeners would have time to think about answers and could call in and discuss.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's okay to have random calls and shoutouts, but it's not very interesting unless you have something to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's a good idea, but I think I see a lot of other podcasts that kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although I don't see a whole lot that are interactive in that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of them do it through email and things like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I kind of always, at least my envision of the show, is that things be like an open format.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if somebody had a topic they wanted to bring to us, they could do that on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Call Echo 123 so we don't hear this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_03]: We keep one in the closet.
[SPEAKER_03]: WTF WTF WTF WTF
[SPEAKER_08]: but it's a cool game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It really is a cool game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a different art style.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like people going, what the hell happened to Link?
[SPEAKER_08]: He looks all cel-shaded and funky looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still a good game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, except for the fact that the world was flooded and then when you go to one spoiler part of this game when you see Hyrule's underwater, you're like, why couldn't it have been that game?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, where Hyrule's not underwater, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And more emails?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is an email from Lauren.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says, hey, I'm looking at full metal DDR pads on eBay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like you can buy one for between $100 to $500 plus, but I was wondering if you knew which manufacturers are the more dependable, Blade, Ion, etc.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of these ones is, I think it's the one that they were selling at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I've seen that pad before there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was broken when I used it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's the problem with it right there.
[SPEAKER_09]: You see how it says, what is this one we're looking at here?
[SPEAKER_09]: The eBay one?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who makes this one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Gus, I can't find the manufacturer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've bought a metal eBay pad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, the ones that are like an inch thick or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that sucker bent.
[SPEAKER_03]: The one that I was at E3, my...
[SPEAKER_03]: Iguana Girl got injured on.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know Guitar Hero is pretty rockin' and they do make some solid controllers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Honestly, the Afterburner is the place to be for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Their stuff has always been high quality.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except for one particular game.
[SPEAKER_09]: In my opinion, but other people feel differently, so that's just my opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or build your own.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have the last two emails are from our friend Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rockin'.
[SPEAKER_03]: To read this, a friend asked me to advise on streaming HDTV to his TV from his PC, so I looked it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you go to a Windows MCE route, there are two Microsoft devices they recommend, the Xbox 360 and Windows Media Extender.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Microsoft page for MCE, Windows Media Extender is downplayed almost completely in favor of the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: They really want to push those boxes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the other thing is actually a link from, I guess it's Gamasutra.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is an article here about ESA files to retrieve Illinois bill game legal costs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ah, yes, the legal, you know, I've got to admit, I've been trying to stay on what's going on with the bill.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Game Industry Trade Association with the Entertainment Software Association has filed a petition to the United States Department
[SPEAKER_03]: District Court asking it to order the state of Illinois to pay $644,545 in legal fees for its unsuccessful efforts to enact a law banning the sale of violent video games in the state.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pay them up, Illinois.
[SPEAKER_03]: You heard me.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you've got some emails you want to send along, mailbag at orangeloungeradar.com is the place to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all one word, mailbag.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on to some more news.
[SPEAKER_09]: And of course, you know I couldn't get through a show without bringing up something related to Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's new information coming out about Treasures of Ott, Oregon, thanks to the event that happened recently there.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was that in, I want to say Santa Cruz?
[SPEAKER_09]: I know it was somewhere in California.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had this big event, a live event.
[SPEAKER_09]: They showed the new trailer and everybody was cheering.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's some new information on what's coming with the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this sounds like it's going to be a much more thorough expansion than Chains of Promethea was.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chains of Promethea was like, new missions, new areas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_09]: But this is a whole lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Besieged mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is where the enemies are going to start taking over the towns.
[SPEAKER_09]: and you actually fight to keep over the town.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also going to be an assault mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is where if you're over level 50, you can just play for an hour or so and you don't have to assemble a giant party.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just go to take a huge quest.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a direct response to...
[SPEAKER_09]: It takes me too long to find a flippin' party.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to do something casually that doesn't take me all night long.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I think that's a good idea, except for the fact that it's limited to over level 50, because that kind of defeats the purpose in many ways, because it takes a while to get to level 50.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not even going to talk about breaking the 50 cap and how hard that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll wait and see how that turns out before we make our final decisions on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, we do know that there's going to be a brand new job class.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Puppet Master is going to be a new job class along with the previously announced Corsair, who you might as well call a pirate, and Blue Mage that were previously announced.
[SPEAKER_03]: Puppet Master?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember if it was Puppeteer or Puppet Master.
[SPEAKER_09]: Puppet Master.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it Puppet Master?
[SPEAKER_03]: That just now has me thinking of a person with little creepy puppets going around.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually what it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my, whoa, we got DarkSakura to say something complimentary about Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_09]: Someone note the date and time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop pointing at me.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're scary.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We've had village raids for years in Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but that's just the GMs playing tricks on you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, also, this is very cool as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chocobo racing is going to be incorporated into Final Fantasy XI along with breeding.
[SPEAKER_09]: So those of you guys that love to raise your own Chocobos in Final Fantasy VII, now it's going to be incorporated into Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've got to say my hat's off to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you get a black one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you get a gold one?
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: We won't know until it comes out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have to race them at the gold saucer?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Colosseum
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't really know what it's going to be yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: They just said a Colosseum.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they have PvP and Ballista, so we don't know if it's going to be PvP or if it's going to be like, think about Final Fantasy VI had a Colosseum, and you would kind of bet an item, and then depending on if you won, you would get something better.
[SPEAKER_09]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be a variety of things.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we shall see.
[SPEAKER_09]: So pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is an addition to new areas and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it sounds like Final Fantasy XI is learning from the poor reviews of Chains of Promethea and kind of adding a lot more oomph into this expansion.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to get some people back into the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here I come.
[SPEAKER_09]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's not the only thing Square's working on, though, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I should say Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're working on another MMO.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's just a brand new MMO.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not going to be Final Fantasy related.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dragon Quest Online.
[SPEAKER_08]: But other details beyond that, nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: They just know that they're working on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Final Fantasy XIII?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did remember hearing them.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were working on another game, and I do remember seeing something about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't remember what it was, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something that was at E3 last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: I seem to remember vaguely hearing something about this, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I wonder if this is related or if it's something completely different.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to move on here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, I know that I don't get a Website of the Week segment here on this show, but let's pretend for once that I did get a Website of the Week segment.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're just jealous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Scandal.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take a stand against politicians who come up with these harebrained bills about preventing the violent video games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once in a while, depending on the wording of the bill, it can be okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm talking about the cases where they compare the games to pornography and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, I've been saying throughout the past couple shows, vote with your dollars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, now here you can vote with your votes.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's basically a place to get people mobilized for action in the political world in the name of gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_09]: And here's a little quote from the website about what they're all about there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Video Game Voters Network
[SPEAKER_09]: Protect Your Games.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's www.videogamevoters.org.
[SPEAKER_09]: I urge you to sign up for this site.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if you don't agree with all of it, maybe you'll find that once you've read it, you don't agree with everything maybe that they're going to do, at least you're educated.
[SPEAKER_09]: And knowing is half the battle, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, Joe.
[SPEAKER_09]: So bravo to those guys for starting that up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's a good idea to get everybody together to take action against this stuff and speak up and say, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Gamers aren't a bunch of 15-year-old guys who can't get laid.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a lot of gamers over 18 who are voting you guys in office, and if you're going to continue to be ignorant about gaming, which is what a lot of this stuff ends up being, is ignorance about gaming, then we're going to remove you from office and put someone in there who's not as ignorant.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any last minute stories anyone wants to share?
[SPEAKER_09]: But of course!
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of on the same level as Half-Life 2, Survivor for the arcade, Global VR, developer of arcade machines, has announced a new title for conversion to the arcade play, and that would be Ubisoft's Far Cry Instincts, the console version for the Far Cry series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Crisis is coming to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have one for you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: About Sid Meier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: A new PC game that will allow you to build your very own rail network laying tracks and deciding routes and designing trains called Railroads!
[SPEAKER_03]: With an exclamation point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait, but there was Railroad Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_09]: It wasn't Sid Meier's Railroad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Railroads.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's titled Sid Meier's Railroads.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a click and drag system to lay tracks, bridges, tunnels, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can also, not only as your rail network grows, cities, industries, you organize cargo transport, provide passenger routes for commuters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fend off hobos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll need to basically watch the business side as you are also dealing with the technical side.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know who will like this game a lot?
[SPEAKER_09]: My dad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because he used to work for the railroad.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's retired now, but he worked for the railroad, so he loves these types of things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll share this with him.
[SPEAKER_03]: You also have the ability to make your own maps and scenarios and do your dream layout in train table mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you can also challenge historical figures like Cornelius Vanderbilt and J.P.
[SPEAKER_03]: Morgan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that's kind of interesting because it's like the civilization aspect there in railroading.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it has LAN or online play, competitive, cooperative.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's going to be pretty big.
[SPEAKER_09]: Railroad Tycoon is one of those great classic games that you should definitely check out if you're kind of younger or into gaming or whatever and haven't checked out a lot of old PC gaming titles that are just fabulous.
[SPEAKER_09]: Civilization, definitely check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: and Railroad Tycoon is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, this game looks very pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope it's easy to get into though.
[SPEAKER_09]: The problem with a lot of these PC sim type of games is that the learning curve is way too high.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hopefully this will be easy to get into.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Civilization, at least the original one, had a pretty good learning curve on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Civ 2 and 3 were pretty good too.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I have faith that this will be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's looking pretty awesome so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I probably wouldn't be too into playing it, but it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100 Matt
[SPEAKER_08]: One of them is
[SPEAKER_08]: This 15 year old student from Salem, Virginia recited 8,784 digits of pi from memory on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: His father promised to buy him an Xbox 360 if he succeeded his own personal goal, which was 10,790.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was actually trying to set the world record, which was...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: So he can't even download something off Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: He just gets a core.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ironically enough, $10,790 is how many systems that were actually sold in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: In the time it took him to learn to memorize that, the kid could have gone out and gotten a job and gotten the money to buy this Xbox 360, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's 15.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe he can't work.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get a work permit at that age, can't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get a job!
[SPEAKER_08]: Foname
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura will bake some pies since after all the emails do say you should be in the kitchen, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll bake arsenic pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might go down for a day.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to about wrap it up for tonight's program.
[SPEAKER_02]: And ribbons and bows.
[SPEAKER_09]: A few quick programming notes for you guys, for those of you guys that listen to Orange Lounge Radio 24-7.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just so you know, Pump Up the Volume will not be heard this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because of Comcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, I did get The Ultimate Geek as my tech, and he was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the guy who came to... He might be listening to the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: He actually did... Well, I wouldn't say he's like a geek geek, but he's into the same type of... He likes Monty Python and... That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And George Romero.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was really awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you were listening, I totally forgot what your name was because I actually do want to send a compliment to your boss.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if you are listening, email me at jamie at orangedownsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will totally write a letter of commendation to your boss.
[SPEAKER_09]: But also, he needs to fix your line.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not him.
[SPEAKER_03]: We found out what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, the tech who came over, the first thing he did was go in and pet Shermie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, you're cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've had nothing but good from Comcast lately, even though my service hasn't been great.
[SPEAKER_09]: When Loki and I lived together, we had a tech come over to the place that we were living at, and the guy walked into the room and saw the arcade machine that Loki had built, and was like, what do you guys do here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, I still get stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get, you know, people, like, I order pizza, and he's like, didn't you used to live on, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they recognize the arcade cabinet, and
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember when you guys were building that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would like to say, what happened is that in my neighborhood, someone cut the head line of a fiber optic cable, cost them $10,000 to repair it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a bunch of jerks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and so we were all out of service, and what's happening is that while they're effecting the repairs and putting everything back together, we've been having really erratic service.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I've been told to give it a week for it to clear up, so as a result, so that you guys don't have to put up with the crap that happened last week, I am not doing a show this Tuesday, I will be back the next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, but I will be on Wednesday night with the Rob Roberts show, so for some music and some geek chat and stuff, and, uh, you know, uh, whatever else...
[SPEAKER_09]: comes up.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll let you know about it on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: For now, let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts, starting off with Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I completely forgot something I wanted to talk about, and I'll make it really quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make it quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Supernova.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was at the ASI event that was going on, and there was some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing, of course, Betson, the manufacturer of this, said no upgrade units will be available.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all new hardware.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can buy it straight, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did show videos that were recorded at the event of the new songs, including Healing Division and also Chaos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chaos, which has four goddamn billion tempo changes and stops in it, including 164th stops, so it's
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have very conflicting emotions toward Comcast right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guitar Vader!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening to Orange Lounge Radio this week and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we'll see you next week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.OrangeLoungeRadio.com See you next week!