[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, March 19th, 2006, a barrage of updates on the PlayStation 3, we dispel April Fool's rumors already hitting the internet, and do we really have to say goodbye to Katamari Damacy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome everybody to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're here to give you the news that gamers really want to know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always, say hello to my awesome co-host, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Full.
[SPEAKER_02]: Full?
[SPEAKER_02]: You just ate before the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I had my usual burrito.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of doom.
[SPEAKER_02]: What makes it a burrito of doom?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it blessed by the Dark Lord Satan or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kidding, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, Satan decided not to bless my burrito.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also say hello to our tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_00]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_00]: I feel like a Got Milk commercial.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have all that chocolate from those brownie bites.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's like two weeks in a row that we've had those brownie bites here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I went to Starbucks to go buy them, but they only had two.
[SPEAKER_00]: They were also out of white mocha, which I don't really care because I don't drink coffee, but Nellie wanted a white mocha, so.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you had to hear all that complaining?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't like Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yay, brownie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, we're here on this episode number 177 for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: March 19th of 2006 and we got a lot of news to go into tonight so let's just start getting into the show we always started off talking about how our gaming week was the kinds of games we played this week little mini reviews on stuff we've looked into and just so you know that we're gamers too you know DarkSakura what you been doing this week
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, a lot of Animal Crossing again, just because it's what I can play at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rest of my time has been spent doing school stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, my husband has told me that I'm getting a PSP of my very own soon because of a certain case that will be associated with a certain game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: For me and my Katamari, apparently there's a case being released that's in the shape of the prince's head.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I think I saw a picture of that somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if it was a custom thing or the official one, but I know I've seen a picture of a PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's got to be official if it's being shipped to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I know, but I'm wondering if the picture I saw was the official one or a fan one, because you know fans probably did one, too, before that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Animal Crossing I noticed a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_02]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I think it's slightly harder, but then again, I've been playing it on the micro, where it's like really, really tiny.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that's why I won't get a micro, because my eyesight's borderline bad enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mine was a gift.
[SPEAKER_02]: Puzzle games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what puzzle game never really came out for a home console that kind of made me sad?
[SPEAKER_02]: They used to have this game at Golfland Local Arcade, the Battle Balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever play that with the marbles that you had to stack like four in a row?
[SPEAKER_04]: I never played that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was an import game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Isn't that a Capcom game?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about, oh shoot, what was that one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Magical Drop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Magical Drop kind of had like a resurgence.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can get that on your phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had Magical Drop on my cell phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got Magical Drop on an EOGO CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, that's the way to do it if you want to do it authentic.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm pretty sure Magical Drop also existed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say there was a version of it on Super Nintendo, but please don't quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that they did one actually for the Pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably because it was an SNK game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh wait, that's totally not true.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't send me gifts, but I got one in person.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a pretty big one in person not that long ago, so I can't say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also found a very interesting book.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was at Barnes & Noble last night, and there was a retro magazine that they did with the Super R-Type on the cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a gaming retro magazine?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also another book that was something about writing and poetry spawned from old video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of the end cap books in the fantasy section that made me laugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Haikus?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was a haiku book.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what we should have on OrangeSongsRadio.com is a haiku forum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, great video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: How I love thee so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I play you all day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was moved.
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually was right too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw your fingers tapping as you were talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you want to share about your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_00]: My week was okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing a lot of the Xbox stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bought The Outfit and I played that for about half an hour.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I haven't really gotten in the back.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been trying to finish up
[SPEAKER_00]: getting the rest of my achievements in full auto and I have one left and that's rank 10 online I just got my million or was it a million like was it a million points in just the game and then 100 no 1000 kills I got the achievement for that and I have rank 9 I just did and then I just have rank 10 online to do and then I'm done with the game
[SPEAKER_02]: What are achievement points to you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you an achievement point whore where you have to have as many as you possibly can?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes and no.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm kind of that way too.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, I just want to get done with the game because I'm not really playing it too much anymore and it's just...
[SPEAKER_00]: It's okay multiplayer, but it's not that fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I just want to get done with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So if I feel like selling it, I know that I've milked all the achievement points out of it that I could possibly get.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of yes and no on the achievement points.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I see, for instance, take...
[SPEAKER_02]: Take Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Geometry Wars has an achievement point that you get like 5 or 10 points, I don't remember, for what's called pacifism, where you don't get hit by anything for 60 seconds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was kind of like, okay, normally I wouldn't play the game like that, but okay, if I get 10 points out of it, I'll try it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it actually is kind of tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't get it my first try.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was actually a bit of a challenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I'll go out of my way for little things like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I know people that, like, there was an article on the internet, I don't remember if it was this week or last week, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: It was about how to get easily 6,000 gamer points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's all sports games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm kind of like, okay, no, that's not cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that's the way you're getting the gamers points, then that means nothing when you look at the score.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's unfortunate that the score doesn't really tell you right away how the points were gotten, but I still really like the system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's really kind of innovative.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's certainly different, but...
[SPEAKER_00]: I did play a little bit of Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_00]: I did get the Pacifist achievement, which was a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've only been able to get about 100,000, and then I get
[SPEAKER_02]: I really suck at Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's too much flashy shit on the screen.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been wondering if I should try it in retro mode, if that would make a difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your score won't rank.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a different mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a ranking mode for it, but it's not the same one that the achievements unlock on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just too flashy.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's too many particles in there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was actually reading an FAQ on the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was looking on forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I might have actually been on the official Xbox forums looking for hints on how to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people are saying like, oh, you should be able to breeze through the first 500k easily.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, okay, am I just old and my hand-eye coordination has gone way down or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I really have a hard time breaking...
[SPEAKER_02]: like 200k on a regular basis maybe I'm just like I read a tip that I thought was interesting in the tip suggested that like if you're having a hard time with it you focus on your ship and nothing but the ship like you don't allow anything else on the screen to distract you except your ship so that way you're dodging no matter what and that will help you get through like at least like if they say the first 500k or million or something like that but then after that you really do have to use your peripheral vision because I guess things just start bombarding you like crazy but
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll at least help you if you're struggling in the beginning like I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like you are.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then I was playing Feeding Frenzy.
[SPEAKER_00]: The thing I like about this and the fact the way the achievements are is it's a game where, say I beat 10 levels of it, I can start it back later and play starting from level 10 and keep going on.
[SPEAKER_00]: It makes achievements really simple on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Plus, it's a pretty simple game, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the one where you start off as a small fish and
[SPEAKER_02]: I've played a game exactly like that at Dave and Buster's except it gave you tickets and I have to say tickets are a little cooler than the achievement points because tickets I can trade in for stuffed animals which is cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm just waiting for when they come up with something on Xbox Live that you can only access it if you have X amount of achievement points or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that would be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't necessarily have to be a game, but something like a beta only open to hardcore players who got a certain amount of achievement points on something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe one of these deals.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the problem is...
[SPEAKER_02]: is that it's these articles like the How to Get 6,000 Gamers Points Easily that are going to kind of screw that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And unfortunately, some games, the achievement points are way easier to get than others.
[SPEAKER_02]: For instance, going with Xbox Live Arcade, Crystal Quest compared to Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Bejeweled, you have to play hardcore because all the achievements practically are like astronomical numbers of rounds and points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas Crystal Quest, if you get pretty good at it, you'll only have to play through one or two times to really unlock the bulk of achievement points.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, some of the time, you know, you have to spend time with it for the others.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, put the two games side by side and, you know, it's much easier to get it in the one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But other than that, I've been playing a little bit of Burnout, a little bit of Full Auto, of course, The Outfit, as I mentioned, and I think that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've just been kind of bouncing around from those, and a little bit of Grand Theft Auto, Liberty City Stories, of course, and God, I think there was another game in there, too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I actually played The Simpsons on my main cabinet for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I thought you had a thought, because you reached for your mic suddenly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was going to fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what it might be, is that you're getting ready to scold me for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh no, what'd you do?
[SPEAKER_02]: I spent the majority of my gaming week playing Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Addict, that's okay, I went back to Ragnarok online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Addict, alright, so we're even.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so I've been playing Fallout SE 11 starting over from scratch, and I think I mentioned on the last podcast I was going to do this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I've actually been in the habit of doing it this week and playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm already up to level 9, yes, and soon I'll be level 30 and be all ready for the expansion pack when it comes out, because the expansion pack
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely looks like it's going to be worth a try.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're incorporating elements of older Final Fantasies and stuff into it, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody pointed out to me in the trailer, you can see one of the judges from Final Fantasy Tactics and stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am interested in some of the new classes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm prepping my little Taru, because I reincarnated myself as a Taru.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said I'm doing an absolute clean start.
[SPEAKER_02]: New server, so I can't get any of the same help I had before.
[SPEAKER_02]: New character, new everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I reincarnated myself as a little Taru Taru.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I plan on being a blue mage.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the problem is that everybody's going to be a blue mage when that thing rolls out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember Lil' Kim.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lil' Kim was my mule on my old server, and she was a Taru as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll tell you the name of my new character off-air.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I will say I play on the Seraph server now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm watching you guys, the Seraph server.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll talk smack about you on the show if you wrong me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll tell you my character name off-air because it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't want to get...
[SPEAKER_04]: You actually reminded me that I did forget to say that I'm on a free server for Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever happened with the legality of that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that kind of a gray area?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Gravity cares anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as they're making money, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: The server that I'm playing on is super dedicated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's so much better than playing on IRO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never had any problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been really great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the rest of my gaming week, I also was playing quite a bit of Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: I checked out Jewel Quest.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually bought Jewel Quest because I knew it was kind of like Bejeweled, and I like Bejeweled, so I bought it.
[SPEAKER_02]: My problem with Jewel Quest is that it's too much like Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: For some reason, I just...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: The achievement points are certainly easier, but honestly, I'm not really considering that in my review of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I put the game side by side.
[SPEAKER_02]: I definitely prefer Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's got some more modes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's just more polished looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you consider that they're essentially the same game, I mean, not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jewel Quest is about not how many three in a row you connect, but where you get them on the board, and it kind of influences your strategy a little bit, but really...
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have Tetris Grandmaster that came out for the Japanese launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think this is true.
[SPEAKER_02]: maybe they own the exclusive rights for their own systems or something because you notice all the Tetris games that come out on Nintendo systems are Nintendo games like this new DS one that's coming out is a Nintendo game the old Game Boy one I don't know I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe somebody in the chat room knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on chat if you want to share some information with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, of course, you can always drop us an email as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into some gaming news for tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's start it off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of us might have something to contribute here with the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, they had that huge press conference earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably most of you guys on the internet have read it by now, but we have to talk about it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Certainly, we want to give our input.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, start us off with a summary.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did we find out about after this conference this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they announced a few things about both the PlayStation 3 and PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll start off with the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, it's going to be launched in November.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I think that was only news to Sony because everyone else figured that it was going to be November.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's nice to hear them actually confirm it because I think most of us were thinking it was going to be 2007 at this point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm not confirming it and saying that they're actually going to make it in November because, I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: After all, Microsoft did say they were going to ship 3 million units by the three-month mark, and that never happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: I credit Sony with a little bit more brains than Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's interesting is that I was reading a separate article this week that talked about the launch of the Sega Saturn, and when they launched that, it was like a surprise announcement at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was one of those things that was like, we're not telling you to wait until November.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on shelves today.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's kind of cool, but at the same time it also kind of killed the system because with the surprise announcement there wasn't enough time for all the developers to get the games out, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's kind of a double-edged sword there.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What killed the system, what killed the Saturn was Sega's whole marketing ploy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Saturn did very well in Japan, and it had much better games that we never saw, that never saw the light of day in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was very import-friendly.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's what killed the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, sorry, this isn't about Sega, it's about Sony.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, it's going to be released somewhere in the first 10, 11 days of November.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, so the early part of November there.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it's going to be including a 60 gigabyte hard drive pre-installed with Linux.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: They beat the... I think that's kind of funny is that they've kind of just given in to the fact that somebody's going to install Linux on this anyway, so here you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be us.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, so I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to have, what was it...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony's got to know better than that.
[SPEAKER_00]: They know that would be suicide.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you have to understand this.
[SPEAKER_00]: It might be $900 if you bought the system for what it's actually worth, but you know everyone sells systems at a loss.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sony's going to have to be prepared to take a hell of a loss on these.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got to lose money to make money.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I mean, the whole thing was with the Blu-ray drive, and that's what half the cost is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_00]: is going to be fully backwards compatible with all PlayStation and PlayStation 2 titles.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're going to basically upscale all of them like the 360 does with the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was one of the most exciting announcements to me, honestly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, they're going to be digitally distributing PlayStation 1 and PlayStation 2 games to the console.
[SPEAKER_02]: PlayStation Hub Service
[SPEAKER_00]: which is going to be for both the PlayStation Portable and the PS3 as well as they're going to be what's kind of neat about that is it will be free to play multiplayer games but there's going to be additional content on there that will cost money and they'll have subscription services for that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: The servers will not be a central server like Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_00]: They will be separate, each run by different companies but
[SPEAKER_00]: Spirit Snare says, I think they're probably aiming for 550-ish.
[SPEAKER_02]: 5.50 is a little more reasonable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, if I were to make a prediction, to compete with Microsoft, they've got to do one of two things.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really have to release this system for $399, just like the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to be less than $400.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but they're flat out saying it's not going to be less than $400.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm thinking that they're going to have to release, I think the price point will be $4.99 is my guess, and of course I don't know shit, but $4.99 is my guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're really going to emphasize Blu-ray, this will play movies in high def, and they're going to say you need this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're going to really emphasize those things that that system can do that Xbox 360 doesn't do.
[SPEAKER_00]: What they need to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're going to see them throw in a bonus movie like you remember when PSP came out they gave Spider-Man 2 free I bet you anything there's going to be a tie-in where the first few PlayStation Soul will come with a free Blu-ray movie whatever Sony's big summer picture is will be the tie-in movie
[SPEAKER_00]: What they need to do is they need to have this system.
[SPEAKER_00]: They need to emphasize the fact that you don't have to go out and buy all these additional peripherals and crap that you had to do with the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I got a system.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, wait, now I got controllers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, each one of those are $40 each.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I have to buy the right cables for my TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: By the way, those are also $40 each.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I didn't get a remote with mine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, guess what?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's $40 also.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it all adds up in the end.
[SPEAKER_00]: And by the way, those controllers, how much did it cost Microsoft to make them?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, it was like $10 or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting way to look at it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're making their money back in peripherals.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's where the money is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't Spider-Man 3 this summer?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Spider-Man 3 is next summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirty Thief just made a good point to give Advent Children as the free movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: But would they be able to do that when it's really Square's movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, certainly a lot of fanboys would love to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Square's in Sony's bed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Blu-ray version of it, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll be hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Certainly make it more attractive.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, the other things, of course, they were talking about was the PSP and some of the stuff that's not much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_00]: We knew that there was going to be an iToy peripheral coming, a webcam type thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's going to be coming, I believe, it was September was the announced date for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: and then, of course, GPS is coming on later in the year, probably in the third or fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then, of course, with the iToy type of peripheral on there, they're going to be adding video phone support in the fall.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of the other things that was kind of interesting, they did announce that there was going to be a core pack that's going to be a reduced price PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, you're just getting the bare-bones stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're not getting a case.
[SPEAKER_00]: No headphones, which to be honest, the case and headphones kind of sucked anyways, so save $50.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're going to be releasing a ceramic white PSP core pack as well, which is going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think that's Japan only though for the white one.
[SPEAKER_00]: What is interesting though is they're going to be offering an official PlayStation 1 emulator for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: and you'll be able to digitally download these straight off the internet to your PSP and I think this is where the 4GB NAND Flash PSP comes into play where you'll be able to store these on your memory stick and I don't understand how these aren't going to be pirated from memory sticks but I don't know they're going to find a way I'm sure interesting
[SPEAKER_00]: and of course with the next update the web browser will get full Flash 6.0 support.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it will be able to view most web pages.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have to put some on our PSP site.
[SPEAKER_00]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_00]: And also they're going to be able to record streaming audio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's interesting about the PSP to me is that they're really trying to think of things that the DS hasn't done yet to really sell the system more as not a game system but as a personal entertainment system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's put it that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like with the whole iToy support, being able to do the short videos and these exchanges over the internet and stuff with the old games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're really trying to think of the things, and the web support too, like things that the DS...
[SPEAKER_02]: Really hasn't done yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whereas most of the DS's innovations have been about the games itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, don't get me wrong, have been great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think PSP, you really see it trying to solidify itself as the more entertainment system as opposed to the game system.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, what's interesting with the GPS thing is it is going to be available.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of the first games it's going to use is a new Hot Shots game coming out, which I thought was interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: But apparently there's current games in the library right now that support it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But just hasn't been unlocked yet or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: GS191 has a good comment in chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh great, fucking Flash ads on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, I'm going to tell you this much though.
[SPEAKER_00]: What I've been waiting for is Flash for the website because you can do a live 365 player in Flash and that's good because you can listen to our show on the go.
[SPEAKER_00]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever happened to the days when video game systems played video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: well the PSP does play games and they've certainly got a lot of good games coming out this first quarter this year but
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we're seeing this trend with all the next-gen systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't want to be just the game system.
[SPEAKER_02]: They want to be that centerpiece in your living room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's what we've heard in a lot of press conferences, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: They want to be the place where you can download movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at Xbox 360, just released this week on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can download a music video now for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's kind of like, you know, they're really...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's all necessarily about the games anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is why I love my DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing that PSP has ever been useful to me for is actually just watching movies on the airplane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've watched Hellboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Luminous is cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Luminous is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't really played much else on the PSP that I really like other than that and Popolo Cross.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I want to play a game, I'm going to play a system dedicated to the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: by a company dedicated to gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care what it looks like, as long as it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know... It's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very... It's sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you think people's focus aren't on the games themselves anymore?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember the Odyssey 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That crap came out when I was two years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember watching the little blips on the screen and thinking that it was so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: Just seeing the way that games are going now, the systems especially, just sort of is heartbreaking.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very sad that people can't be satisfied with good gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you want to share on the Sony there, Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: I was just trying to think.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of the interesting thoughts about it, they did mention, I think it was the PSP webcam or their iToy, I guess they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's going to be
[SPEAKER_00]: They were calling it like PSP 290 or something.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I figured, okay, well, firmware 2.9 then is going to support this or something like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was just kind of the, I guess their item code or whatever for it kind of tied in with the firmware that will support it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm glad to see some cool peripherals and stuff come out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was hoping that that webcam or eye toy can be used as a digital camera.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope it's good enough for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only thing I don't understand is how the fuck are you going to use it as an eye toy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously, are you going to be flailing around?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not going to work like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's more like what you're saying there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be more for chatting and for picture taking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: If the PSP is going to be a little entertainment in a box, why not be a digital camera as well?
[SPEAKER_02]: People like digital cameras.
[SPEAKER_00]: People like cell phones that play music and have iTunes on them.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fucking dumbasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's go on to some other news this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get into some news about a very popular PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one being on the PS2, right Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_00]: God damn, we've been waiting for that for a long time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, if you're in Japan, you're already playing it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, if you're looking for it in the US, you're going to have to wait until Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because that's when it's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard fantastic reviews on this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, we mentioned Famitsu Magazine last week, but I'm very excited about Final Fantasy XII and I wish it wouldn't take him so damn long to release it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still laughing about the potion commercial.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen that yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know somebody posted... Well, I have a friend who lives in Japan right now who said, I guess she thinks it's tasty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the battle system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know a lot of people have acted really weird about it, but being the addict I am with Final Fantasy XI, I think it's a great combination of XI and the old school Final Fantasies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to trying it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it plays anything like XI, I'll guarantee I won't play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't play like XI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you don't have to spend an hour looking for a party.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's already there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's part of the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest... No, I don't like the gameplay in XI, which is part of why I quit.
[SPEAKER_00]: To be honest, it reminds me of a cross between Final Fantasy X2 or X and... X. Final Fantasy X and X2 and...
[SPEAKER_00]: I just like doing that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Parasite Eve.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, Parasite Eve, it reminds me of the battle system, the way they did that, where you've got this sphere where you can attack.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, it's just, you can run around and do shit, but it's still like kind of an active time battle system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XII Business Week
[SPEAKER_02]: The quote was, There are rumors that the revolution could be released as early as June.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that happens, and Nintendo sells around 1 million units, Sony could have a harder time catching up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that quote comes from Akitiro Itoa from Japan's game tracking service, Media Create.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, when you look at the reality of it, the chances of the console actually coming out in June...
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the reason why is because the development hardware is not out there right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if that's not out, it's going to be very hard for the games to be out by June.
[SPEAKER_02]: So probably November is a more realistic time frame.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Nintendo has also been kind of quoted recently saying Thanksgiving week of 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't think there really is going to be any June surprise in store.
[SPEAKER_02]: So nothing like that whole Sega thing we were talking about earlier where they surprise us at E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not likely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on, somebody that works for Nintendo, Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, Miyamoto reacted to the PlayStation 3 announcement this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not too surprising the way he reacted.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was basically, you know, kind of put a quote out there that's saying, you know, people are kind of getting tired of the same old video games nowadays, and what
[SPEAKER_00]: these you know like Microsoft and Sony are doing for video games as far as they're improving the graphics but they're not really changing the gameplay any and so he's not too worried just because they've never really seen the other companies as competition because they're kind of in their own boat basically as being innovative whereas you know these guys are just pushing graphics and stuff you're not really pushing better gameplay I'm not surprised to hear that coming from Miyamoto not at all it's just you know
[SPEAKER_00]: I have to agree.
[SPEAKER_00]: Games aren't really that much better.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's kind of what Jamie was saying just a little bit ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: They look prettier, but they're not different.
[SPEAKER_00]: In a personal stance, just looking at sales of different games out there, when I'm selling to customers and stuff,
[SPEAKER_00]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to ask Jamie, having said that a little bit ago about the, you know, it's sad that the systems are kind of leaning towards being all-in-one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does this strike you as Nintendo being committed to the games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's always what they've been about, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would they ever change their stance for the sake of
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but a good idea didn't really work out, though, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_00]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: At least they tried.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I would rather see them try and fail at it than not see them try at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: They tried to be innovative.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, look at the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dumb idea, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a step in the right direction.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Great Migraine Machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Granted, they should have probably not gone monochrome red, and they probably should have made it less cumbersome, but you know...
[SPEAKER_00]: It did have the best commercials.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: And they're going to be trying to make this money back.
[SPEAKER_00]: And to be honest, it's another fucking goddamn Grand Theft Auto clone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Except, oh, now it has Marlon Brando in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay, that doesn't make it any better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now, to be fair, that article was more saying they didn't spend $810 million on the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marketing, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not just that, but the fact that they didn't release it at Christmas time cost them about $800 million of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm sitting here going, wow, that still costs like multi-millions of dollars to make.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, I'm not surprised because you have all the voice acting in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're basically making a movie on a console.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm like, I totally see what you're saying there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Usually, these movie-to-games that they spend a lot of that money on are crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't think of a whole lot of good ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure there's some.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not coming to mind right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you take a game like Tetris.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: You were right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't even Nintendo say earlier that is not the reason why they delayed Twilight Princess?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's Miyamoto saying, and one of the most important features is that because Revolution can run GameCube software, when you play Twilight Princess on Revolution, you can take advantage of the Revolution controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which makes Nintendo our Liar of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're our Liar of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you're going to hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Script Magazine Script Magazine
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically just sort of a day in the life of the production process for Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, talking with the producer in France, going over some of the lame ideas he started to bring up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, well, no, we want to protect the integrity of the franchise.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a really neat article.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I take it no dog ending.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think after the credits.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like you stay after the credits and then there's a dog ending.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a UFO.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope they did that for the fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be so happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they were fully bringing up how awesome it was to work with Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's a very good article.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'll tell you what, as soon as I can find the power supply for my scanner, I'll make it available for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I would suggest going out and buying the magazine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, because illegal reproductions are wrong, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can transcribe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that Script Magazine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Script Magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: The I is in parentheses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you're probably not going to be able to walk into a grocery store and find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, you can walk into Barnes & Noble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Barnes & Noble.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to go to a more comprehensive magazine store.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was at Borders when I saw it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Tower would be very likely to carry it since they carry all sorts of interesting... I don't think they have that everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, regarding the PlayStation 3, there was some back and forth this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right after the conference, people were saying, oh, that hard drive's not going to really come with the system or that's going to make it the $900 system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, tell us once and for all, what's the deal with the hard drive?
[SPEAKER_00]: It is standard.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, of course you're going to... You need the hard drive to play the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've come out and said that it's not going to be like the Xbox 360 where...
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, if you don't have a hard drive, memory card, that would just be fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, you need the hard drive to play the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, of course, it's going to be standard with the system, and it was confirmed by Yahoo Games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wow, Yahoo Games is actually legitimate.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's surprising.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a bigger shocker than the... Don't knock on them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yahoo featured our podcast once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't hurt our relations there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: In that case, Yahoo's so smart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, speaking of hard drives, you may remember last week I called a certain gaming company a bunch of bastards for this news article.
[SPEAKER_00]: I do want to say one thing real quick.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's a great idea that they are including the hard drive because now developers can develop with the hard drive in mind, unlike the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: And speaking of the 360, I kind of called Microsoft a bunch of bastards last week over this news article, and it turned out to be false.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 100 gigabyte hard drive rumor that was going around a couple weeks ago, or actually last week, starting from the Best Buy employee or something, they actually got word officially from Microsoft, from the global marketing team, saying, we haven't announced any additional hard drives for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beyond the 20 gigabyte version available today.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'd like to offer an apology to Microsoft for calling you guys bastards.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Halo Rocks, please forgive me.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're still bastards.
[SPEAKER_02]: But not for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: For other things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Many, many other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: We could find a reason why all these gaming companies are bastards though this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Nintendo lied.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo lied to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel steep pain in my soul.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, chat room's saying that we're being too hard on Nintendo because maybe that wasn't... Where did that come from?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo Maniac 64, of course, defending Nintendo saying, that doesn't mean that's why it was delayed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that Zelda thing isn't necessarily the only reason why it was delayed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, good incentive, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think back to the Zelda games that were on Game Boy Color and the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why didn't they come out to the end of Game Boy Color for that exact same reason to transition people onto Game Boy Advance with one of their biggest franchises?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not surprised at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a question for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why didn't they give us the Satellaview?
[SPEAKER_04]: I had the best version of Zelda ever
[SPEAKER_02]: or we would never do that to you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bad thing is that all these magazines put their April issues out in mid-March so now there's all these lies coming to you from these gaming magazines saying, oh, it's an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_00]: God, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're on the second.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're broadcasting on the second.
[SPEAKER_00]: If only one more day we could have fun at that show.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, today we're doing it without a script!
[SPEAKER_02]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so now we would like to tell you about some of the real lies being spread this week by gaming magazines under the guise of April Fool's jokes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what's the first one?
[SPEAKER_00]: The first one is, I'm not necessarily going to call this an April Fool's joke because I'm not really certain if it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, it's some Duke Nukem Forever gameplay footage that was featured and leaked to the internet, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it looks like an in...
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, what's another big lie under the guise of April Fool's?
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3, The Ape...
[SPEAKER_04]: who said he transcribed an article about the game from an upcoming issue of Game Informer Magazine, which is GameStop's big magazine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It basically said that the game was going to have huge persistent worlds built around a modified Halo 2 engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was going to feature Master Chief and would have a co-op mode for up to four players.
[SPEAKER_04]: But according to Bungie, it's a big pile of poo.
[SPEAKER_04]: To quote, he said, We can't smack him for an April Fool's gag, not like we never did any.
Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo Combat Evolved Xbox Live Marketplace
[SPEAKER_02]: But not actually going to happen here.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least they're saying here that this is not likely to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably their April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you logically think, could Microsoft eventually jump on this bandwagon because you got Sony saying they're going to do the same thing with the PlayStation games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe this isn't such an unrealistic possibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're going to need a bigger hard drive if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we shall see.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, so moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go from lies to apologies.
[SPEAKER_02]: This has been a show full of apologies and lies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, who's saying sorry now?
[SPEAKER_00]: Starforce, and I wouldn't really say that this is... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's sort of an apology here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Starforce, if you guys remember back to last week, they were the ones that were reporting.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're the company that does security, cop protection software, and this...
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, they were leaking a torrent of Galactic Civilization 2 on their website just because Stardock didn't want to use Starforce's copper protection schemes.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, they said, yeah, we're sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's just like, you know, basically, I don't know, it's just,
[SPEAKER_02]: I was listening to some other podcasts this week that were talking about this company.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're really evil.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I never really, because I don't play a lot of PC games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, granted, between Final Fantasy XI and World of Warcraft, that's enough PC games for me because that's most of my PC game time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I never really realized they practically install spyware on your computer, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of fascinating.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm surprised they get away with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so basically they apologized for the incident and said they took down the link.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's just like, it's still pretty rotten to be doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little too late.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, here's the thing guys, and I see a lot of people in our chat room right now are going, yeah, F them, they suck, da da da.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here it is guys, vote with your dollars.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't like this company, don't buy anything that their product is involved with.
[SPEAKER_02]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then soon you will no longer see them because they'll go out of business because nobody's buying their stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vote with your dollars if you don't like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love Sonic Team!
[SPEAKER_02]: My God, do we know anything about why he's doing this or anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a speculation that he's going to be creating his own company that may be aligned with Sega, but that's, again, speculation.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is the man that brought us Sonic the Hedgehog, Phantasy Star Online, Knights.
[SPEAKER_02]: So pretty much like all the great Sega games you start to think about, this guy made them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yuji Naka is the man.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be like Miyamoto leaving Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Miyamoto left Nintendo, Nintendo would crumble.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega's already... I'm sorry, Sammy Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to say Sammy Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then again, Sammy did bring us Guilty Gear or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, Sega... Having something like this even be rumored, it just sort of makes me think how the mighty have fallen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I'll be...
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to have a Sega in 20 years if they keep this up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: It hasn't happened yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just mean for the greatness that Sega was.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, here's something else to mourn about.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, put this on your list of things to talk about when you're mourning.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do we have to mourn over as well?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you know, it was a good run or roll, I should say.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Katamari team has broken up, and so we're not going to be seeing any more Katamari games.
[SPEAKER_00]: How do you know this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because the website says so.
[SPEAKER_00]: KatamariDamasi.jp There was a three-day countdown.
[SPEAKER_00]: And people were anticipating, oh, hey, there's a countdown.
[SPEAKER_00]: Last time it was the announcement of me and my Katamari.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now it's, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's a really bad April Fool's joke?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the creator of Katamari Damasi himself has said he doesn't like video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Playground Equipment
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the problem with that being is that even if they decide to try to keep going with it, it's not going to have the same feeling that the games now do.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you have a recipe and you have it at the same restaurant and then another restaurant tries to copy it, it just doesn't taste the same way.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and at the same time, you can kind of maybe respect this decision, honestly, because part of the problem with games today as it is, that Katamari Damacy kind of really went against the grain with this when it first came out, is that too damn many sequels, too many copies of other games, too many, you know, of the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Katamari Damacy was well respected for breaking that mold, so I think maybe this is why they've decided to quit now, before they become the thing that they were representative against.
[SPEAKER_02]: So at that time, you kind of have to respect them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just hope that at least these guys will put out more games of some type.
[SPEAKER_02]: And even if it's not another Katamari Damacy game, you've got to admit, that sense of humor that's in Katamari Damacy, that level that the music is at and all that stuff, that could lend itself great to another very original concept.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I hope...
[SPEAKER_02]: We see many of the brains behind Team Katamari.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if they broke up, many of the same big minds behind it create something new that can be the Katamari Damacy of next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or just, I don't know, just get part of the development team and start a new team.
[SPEAKER_00]: It doesn't take the same minds to create the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: They didn't really change much from both games anyways.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Comments from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Arsef says, yeah, too many sequels would defeat the inventiveness of the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Xander C says, I hope he makes more games, but hopefully it'll be original stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: No more Katamari, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe fans are just kind of accepting this, that yep, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is what you gotta do to stay original.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, you know, at the same time, we can be original.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can also celebrate the classics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, you guys know the Walk of Game down at the Metreon in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, now, the Metreon was just sold recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't know how this is going to affect the Walk of Game, but they just recently had their 2006 ceremony where they inducted John Carmack, who was technical director at ID Software, you know, Doom, Quake, that stuff, Sid Meier, Civilization, among many other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that...
[SPEAKER_02]: That guy is honestly a god to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Sid Meier has made some of the greatest PC games of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they were lifetime achievement, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, some games that were celebrated for their characters as well as being a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: EverQuest, Final Fantasy, Lara Croft, and StarCraft all being inducted into the Walk of Game, which I have yet to really see.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I might have to take a trip to the Metreon before it gets...
[SPEAKER_02]: Turn into the Mega Mall that Westfield might turn it into.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of am hoping that maybe Westfield won't screw it up, and they'll try to still keep it like a gaming center, like make it appeal to gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would make me a happy kid.
[SPEAKER_00]: They'll put an EB in there as well, or GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they have the official Sony store, so that would be kind of competing, so I don't know if they could do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega Land Theme Park
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not Sega come open a store?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the third-party developers kind of sell off some of their big things.
[SPEAKER_02]: Namco could have a store, you know, all this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami store.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet in five years it's going to turn into a Pokemon Center.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not open up a Pokemon Center in it somewhere, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because Pokemon Centers are evil!
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people like it, so why not have it for them as well?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, something for everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that would be cool to keep it like a gaming-themed place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people worship the devil, too, but that doesn't make it right.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are entitled to their own religion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of people worshipping the devil, a certain game franchise has turned 25 this week, and we're not sure how this franchise keeps going.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe it is Divine Darkness Intervention or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frogger has turned 25.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get me wrong, Frogger is a wonderful game 25 years ago, but these recent releases... Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not so great.
[SPEAKER_00]: The original Frogger was a really good game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Every other Frogger game or game that has Frogger in the title...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I had a game on Commodore 64 called Frogger 2 3-Deep that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then after that, I'll back up what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_00]: Frogger... Yeah, pretty much Frogger nowadays is just... You see Frogger on a game or Frogger like Helmet Chaos, you're like, wow, crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's what that is.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_00]: Not much you can really do with Frogger.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's such a simple game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they still have another game coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played the Frogger that they came out with on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that was about the last time I played a Frogger game because I just wasn't into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't that great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, now they're trying to get a storyline.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just a goddamn game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think Frogger would be a good game on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: But,
[SPEAKER_00]: Do it super ultra realistic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have it look like a real frog.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have the traffic look real.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Multiplayer might be kind of fun, like a race to the end.
[SPEAKER_00]: I want to be the driver.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should be able to push.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about the innovation there with Pac-Man and on that Pac-Man versus, some people could be the ghosts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not have some people be the drivers on Frogger?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or have your frog with the ability to push other frogs in front of the car.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: See?
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone needs to play the crocodile.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami, you guys need to hire us to breathe some new life into your Frogger franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe there's another way to breathe life into the Frogger franchise and some people are trying to imitate this in real life.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's this about?
[SPEAKER_00]: What do you get when you combine lots of alcohol, a Roomba, and something that looks like a frog?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you get real life Frogger.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, they have taken this Bluetooth-enabled Roomba, a green t-shirt, and lots of alcohol, and they made it cross traffic.
[SPEAKER_00]: They made it cross a four-lane highway about ten times before it got run over by a Toyota 4Runner.
[SPEAKER_00]: And to be honest, this is way more entertaining than any of those Frogger games that have come out recently.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would do this.
[SPEAKER_00]: This would be something I would totally do.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this is excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pac-Man Ghosts
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, in a future episode, we need to do another listless and games I would like to see imitated in real life.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to think about that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe next week if we have time.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have to.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a brilliant idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: My hat's off to those kids who put that together.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're ready for booze.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Techmo has a new automatic update for the Xbox 360 for Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's meant to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Adjust some of the interface and balance the characters, tweaking the launcher moves, stun moves, sweeps.
[SPEAKER_04]: A few of the character speeds are changed, some sped up, some slowed down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the power moves do less damage, encouraging players to be more skillful.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you download the update, you will also have the option to reset your battle tactics.
[SPEAKER_04]: But your Zac money, avatars, all that will still be the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: The DOA4 update is available on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if it will make the last boss less of a cheap bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because she is!
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly haven't really super duper played a whole lot of Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've been too afraid to play online because I'll sit and watch some of those battles and I'll go like, you know what, I'm going to get my ass kicked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to play with people on my own level.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where are the handicapped players on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why aren't you ever on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Those people who need a handicap on their game because they're not very good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I need.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can admit it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not great at every game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was talking to somebody recently online who assumed that because I did this show every week that I'm good at every video game, and that's so not the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some games I'm good at, I'll admit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm pretty good at a lot of puzzle games, but not every game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you're going to add me to Xbox Live, if you dig through the Orange Lingerie forums and decide to add me to Xbox Live, be prepared that I'm not going to be much of a challenge in some of the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other games, it's on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will kick your butt on some of those arcade games, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob needs food badly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gauntlet was more fun for me when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: I find it to be too repetitive now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think our webmaster, VXChaseNXV, I think he challenged me to Root Beer Tapper when that one comes out on live.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you're on, bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're on.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to let us know how that one goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: 2K Games has announced that Civ City Rome, it's a building strategy based on civilization, is currently in development for PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's being produced by Firefly Studios.
[SPEAKER_04]: They brought a stronghold.
[SPEAKER_04]: And with Firaxis Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: According to 2K Games, it's going to have the most detailed look at Roman life ever depicted on a computer screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a quote.
[SPEAKER_00]: That is, until the sieves come out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, you know, then you'll have your nice Roman family that you've got to, you know... Yeah, I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, visit to the, you know, annual orgy and... Are we going Greek or Roman here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Roman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was also Greek.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, moving on from orgies, you'll start off with a small settlement build until you have an imperial city.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have amphitheaters, legionnaire forts, weapon workshops, circuses, gladiator school, a whole bunch of stuff, and then you can set it on fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: So like most, really you get to burn your city in a day?
[SPEAKER_04]: You could.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is like most civilization games, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Start small, get big, take over world, repeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are screenshots available, which I will be posting in our chat room, but these can be seen from, if you go to Eurogamer.net, the links are there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, I've looked this through.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very, very pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of...
[SPEAKER_04]: You can have ports.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the captures is of a port city.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got orchards.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have a huge, massive city with a coliseum.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that does look pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to link this in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still kind of neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what my hope is for games like this is that we see an actual degree of historical accuracy in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, because I think that
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that a lot of the people who know me off the show know I have a very big interest in anthropology and ancient history.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think something like this not only would be good for the whole strategy building side of things, but also a chance to offer a little bit of a history lesson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, civilization was pretty good with that because the world leaders that you would come across would be kind of like how they were.
[SPEAKER_02]: Siv-4 is getting an expansion!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I still haven't played Civ 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel really bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's one of those things where it's like I just don't have the time to play everything I want to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really want to try this out sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the expansion is called Civilization for Warlords with new units that are called Warlords.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll have some of the greatest military leaders and new scenarios.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can change history.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can take control of the ancient Chinese kingdom, fight in the Peloponnesian Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can join Alexander the Great, become ruler of the Vikings, pillage Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can be Genghis Khan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, and honestly, maybe I should just wait until all the expansions for Civ 4 are out because then there'll be that gold box set because there's always a gold box set at the end of every Civilization's lifespan that's like 20 bucks that has everything in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe I'm okay waiting.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alexander the Great in this game looks kind of historically accurate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of us who have studied a little bit of history.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anything else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm also posting that clip in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, by the way, our chat room is at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click on chat, of course, unless you're listening to this on the podcast or via our AllGames.com syndication.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do know that when this show's playing on AllGames.com, sometimes their chat room is chatting about the show a little bit, so check out their chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, you can always send us emails, and it's always just incentive, too, if you want to be a part of the live chat, Sunday nights, 6 o'clock Pacific time, OrangeLoungeRadio.com, we do this show live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Act of War, High Treason for the PC, Final Fight Streetwise
[SPEAKER_04]: The Blockbuster Exclusive
[SPEAKER_04]: Street Racing Syndicate, Elder Scrolls IV, Oblivion, The Godfather, Worms Open Warfare
[SPEAKER_02]: and, of course, we'd like to take it back to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: with what's on the U.S.'
[SPEAKER_02]: 's plate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, what are we getting this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: We're looking at Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion, of course, finally coming out for the 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: I completely forgot that was this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mimai Katamari, of course, that's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Milgar Acid 2, really good.
[SPEAKER_00]: What else was really good?
[SPEAKER_00]: Tal's Curse of the Demon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remember that one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only if you're a hardcore role-playing game person.
[SPEAKER_02]: Otherwise, skippable.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Godfather.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's really sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Worms Open Warfare on NDS and PSP, which is going to be really sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then, of course, Blazing Angels on Xbox and Xbox 360, which is also really cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Capcom Classics Collection Remixed on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: which includes Captain Commando and Street Fighter and Strider.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a Tetris TS commercial on TV this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the gaming sites picked it up, but I actually saw it for the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was watching some show and they aired it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: How did I forget?
[SPEAKER_00]: Karaoke Revolution Country is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: No way.
[SPEAKER_02]: and of course next week, Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'll probably just pick up the first three and wait a little bit to hear the reviews of Elder Scrolls a little more.
[SPEAKER_00]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_00]: How about you just see my copy of Oblivion when I buy it this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then maybe you could borrow my copy of Me and My Katamari or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which reminds me, I want the PSP back.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will get your PSP back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a funny story about your adapter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I loaned a Guanagirl my camera, and I gave her your adapter with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it looked like the one for my camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll get it back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guana Girl, if you're listening, I want that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I'm sending out the hitman.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got my camera back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't have your adapter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also, real quick, since we were just on the UK news, we actually have one of our UK listeners tuned in tonight, Simmel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, that's hardcore, to be listening live when you're living in a different time zone, because I know we've had in the past... It's 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we've had folks from Australia listen live, too, and I know that's more like afternoon time, but that's awesome that you guys are tuning in, listening live in those different time zones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray for our fellow night owls.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Man, I just wouldn't want to have to calculate the time zones, that's all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Too much brain work-y stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I moderate on the UK site.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think our streaming site, Live365, will auto-calculate on the scheduler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if you go to look at our scheduler of live programs, it'll auto-calculate the times for you, I think?
[SPEAKER_02]: So check that out on our station page.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: For UK, add five hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: For France, add one or two more hours.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, as I was going to mention, I was going to mention real quickly next week, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Beatmania, Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is up with the end of March?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is the end of March usually this big of a gaming time?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't remember this last year.
[SPEAKER_00]: It drops off next month, so let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, of course, more stuff for May.
[SPEAKER_00]: Far Cry, Instincts, Predator, and Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop gift certificates, baby.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to buy you the Game Boy Advance version of Cats, which is coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and I'm going to buy that a SpongeBob SquarePants Yellow Adventure game for you, because you should love that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could use it for Shermie's litter box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those who don't know, Shermie is my cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Named after a video game character.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fatal Fury Fatal Fury
[SPEAKER_02]: Fatal Fury 2 Samurai Shodown
[SPEAKER_04]: Ken and Ryu were ripped off for Art of Fighting with Ryo and Robert.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Capcom, to make fun of them, came up with Dan Hibiki in Street Fighter who wears a gi like Ryo and has Robert Garcia's hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never made that connection.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I used to play as Rob in Art of Fighting because he's got a good name.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyway, it is time to go ahead and break for this half of our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will be back with a little more Orange Lounge Radio after the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.