[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_03]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're here on this March the 12th of 2006 with episode number 176.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a pretty exciting first half there, talking about all sorts of stuff, the new PSP, talking about patching on the Xbox 360, and we're going to kick off this segment with some more news going over to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're saying there's a story going out on most of the gaming sites out there about foil and how it ruined the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently on the graphics processor...
[SPEAKER_05]: HeatSync, there is a foil layer left on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And one of the German sites out there on the Xbox scene forums, he actually opened up his 360 to show that the foil was still on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And saying that the foil left on there on the heat transfer pad is basically acting like a skillet, I guess, instead of a heat sink.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, that's kind of backing up the whole heat sink over the GPU overheating and that's what caused the Xbox 360s to stop working.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think Microsoft is going to replace that one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's basically... No, the guy that cracked it open.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, there's a follow-up by Microsoft and they've
[SPEAKER_05]: The video posted by the German blog GamesStore24.de shows the thermal interface pads that are installed per specification.
[SPEAKER_05]: This foil eliminates the need of a protective liner, which simplifies the final assembly process and minimizes shipping concerns and contamination issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I thought it enhanced it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought opening it up in it was full of cookies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that let the gnomes come out to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop looking at my shirt!
[SPEAKER_02]: I love your underpants gnome shirt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the whole thing is, is it, you know, is the foil actually causing this thing to overheat?
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just another article out there because... It gives better heat spread so you can cook better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I personally think that it doesn't because...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess if you had something on, you know, most of the time like for CPUs and stuff when you're talking like an actual PC, you have thermal paste in between.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some manufacturers will use foil instead because it also allows heat transfer from the CPU to the heatsink.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if this foil got in the way of that, it possibly could, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's kind of take this with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the Chinese website MyDrivers has reported that a Taiwan manufacturer, Compec, has received the orders from Sony to start producing the PCB.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, the HDI PCB.
[SPEAKER_04]: This would be the printed circuit board.
[SPEAKER_04]: for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no official announcement from Compaq, but the rumor says that this is going into production June or July of this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you are taking this with a grain of salt, just know that MyDrivers is a pretty reputable Chinese website, but don't take anybody's word for it until you hear it from Sony directly, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the PlayStation 3 sounds like it may be on its way after all, at least the first few steps to getting that done.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's go over to a Nintendo story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's new on the Nintendo DS?
[SPEAKER_02]: A bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in this particular, there's a new RPG on the way for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called Contact, and it's a game about hunting, cooking, fishing, training, collecting, and romance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoa, hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hunting, training, fishing, all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Organtrail.
[SPEAKER_02]: Organtrail with love.
[SPEAKER_02]: You play as someone named Terry.
[SPEAKER_02]: You meet a professor whose spaceship has crashed on a weirdo planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to collect cells, which are the power source for the ship.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're all over the place, so you have to go find them.
[SPEAKER_02]: As you're going, you train animals, collect items, play a bunch of mini-games.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's real-time combat.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's...
[SPEAKER_02]: An online version, but they haven't said anything about how that's going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's being produced by Goichi Suda, who is the director of Killer7.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the characters were designed by Atsuko Fukushima of Popolo Cross.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is actually an official site up for it too, and it's going to be published by Atlas in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: No UK release date stated as of yet, although they know that it's in development by Marvelous Interactive, and Rising Star tends to bring over their games in Europe, so there's hope for our European audience.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: The artwork, I have to say, though, after looking through the Japanese site, it is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, we touched on some new stuff on Xbox Live during the first half of the show, but set the record straight for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple new things are coming out, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ridge Racer 6 demo is now on Xbox Live so you can also check that out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a big fan of those type of games like The Outfit, but I'll probably check it out because, hey, it's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I heard our buddies over at All Games are really into it, and I was listening to their show, and they seem really into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole thing reminds me of kind of like G.I.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joe, sort of the whole... Well, when you put it that way, it sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way The Outfit is, I mean, because it's kind of like this, you know, over-exaggerated, like, World War II action game where you can call in, like,
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard that you kind of control a team of four.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like games where I get to be the boss.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, maybe I will have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though war games are usually not my type of thing, or battle, whatever the hell, I'll give it a fair shot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, I tried Battlefield 2, which is so not my kind of game, and I was very lost when I played it, but, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Gotta try it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't knock it till you tried it, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You left yourself way open for a joke and I chose not to speak it right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What right do you have being on this show tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you even a gamer?
[SPEAKER_04]: I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the last game you played?
[SPEAKER_04]: Diablo 2, like I said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burnout?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, Burnout Legends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just giving you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bug's my buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've known him forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: 17 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to put up with your shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to put up with mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Loki, going back over to you, what do you got on Silent Hill?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're working on the Silent Hill 3 team.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're working on a new project for PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_04]: So like Silent Hill 5, most likely, or maybe something different?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just know they're working.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're hard at work again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that... And tomorrow the sun will come out!
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, how stupid of a story... It's the third release of Silent Hill 2 for the... They're making another in a really successful franchise that has a movie coming out that's probably going to be one of the first video game movies that's actually good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be Final Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're making a sequel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, that's such a shocker!
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: is going to be on The Revolution when that comes out too!
[SPEAKER_05]: In Halo 3, it's coming out on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoa, shocker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, look, it was making the rounds on game sites, so we have to report it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, do you have something else then, Loki, that might be more worthy of our time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sega is developing a PlayStation 3 launch title, and what would you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: The sun's going to set tomorrow, duh.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but how many golf games does Sega make?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't make mo-cap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And plus, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care how long it's been.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is still weird to hear of Sega making games for other consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, they're currently developing a golf game, and actually it's two golf games, I should say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Doesn't sound that exciting to me, but I don't know, maybe it's Sonic Golf or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, just like everything attached to Sega is just always Sonic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Ooh La La's Sexy Golf would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Crazy Taxi Golf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's make some crazy par!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, DarkSakura is going to try and bring us back to Sanity World.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, who am I kidding?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's her website of the week, and you know it's going to be just as crazy as the rest of what we've been talking about this evening?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's a serious and important, relevant site that affects everybody's life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, cue the theme music?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Today's website of the week is www.cheese.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the number one resource about cheese.
[SPEAKER_02]: To quote from the website, cheese is nutritious food made mostly from the milk of cows, but also other mammals, including sheep, goats, buffalo, reindeer, camels, and yaks.
[SPEAKER_02]: About 4,000 years ago, people started to breed animals and process their milk.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's when cheese was born.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can search the database of 654 cheeses by name, country of origin, type of milk used to produce it, or by texture.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about head cheese?
[SPEAKER_02]: Headcheese is actually the brains of a cow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but does it have information about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's talking about dairy cheese.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, Flamanda Cheese then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Flamanda Cheese.
[SPEAKER_01]: I watch Red Dwarf.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: If anybody found Orange Lounge Radio's on-topicness for this episode, could you please email us?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we seem to have lost it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the cheeses listed on this site, we have... I believe it's behind the caffeine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Air Del Cheese, we have American Cheese, which is really crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Atun Cheese, we have Babybel, which actually is one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basket Cheese!
[SPEAKER_02]: Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I think I found the on-topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: This new game, Galactic Civilizations 2, it's actually a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little different in the digital rights management of the way the game is set up because the license of the game allows you to install the game onto as many machines as you want to, that you own, as long as only one copy is being used at once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their thought behind this, how many sales are lost because people want to have a game on their laptop and desktop, but they don't want to have to buy multiple CDs for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: and, you know, being a laptop and desktop owner, you know, I kind of like games like Warcraft that I can put on both of them, so that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the other side of that is this company called Starforce, which is an anti-piracy developer.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they kind of struck a low blow.
[SPEAKER_04]: A story here on 1up.com that was run earlier this week saying that Starforce, what they did, they actually posted on their company message boards, again, Starforce makes the anti-piracy software, by an admin, and they put a link in the post to a torrent file for Galactic Civilizations 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would an anti-piracy company be linking torrents?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, saying in the post, right now, several thousands of people are downloading the pirated version only from that website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it good for the sales?
[SPEAKER_04]: Unlikely.
[SPEAKER_04]: So in other words, it was kind of like a bully tactic, in a way, because they're an anti-piracy company, and they're saying that, oh, this company didn't use our software, and here's their game being rampantly pirated, and how dare they sue them?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what could happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, the post is gone now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Galactic Civilizations 2 did publish a response saying, Our primary weapon to fight piracy is through rewarding customers through convenient, frequent, free updates.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you make it easy for users to buy and make full use of your product or service legitimately, then we believe you'll gain more users from that convenience than you'll lose from piracy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting and rebellious stance from this company that I think is very customer-driven.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta say, kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Starforce needed any more negative publicity, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else have they done?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not very familiar with that company.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as the techs that they use, I think they're one of the companies that had spyware thrown on your PC that basically monitors what you're running, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty sure that was the same company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: They're on the naughty list this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got Galactic Civilizations 2 on the nice list for their outside-the-box thinking on their policy there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what else is being developed?
[SPEAKER_05]: This company called Bigfoot Networks has actually just gotten some money to develop what they're saying is going to be the end of all lag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lag is gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're developing, I guess, hardware that's going to be
[SPEAKER_05]: Use it in conjunction with online games or God knows what, and it will end lag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, I don't know, it sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of those I'll believe it when I see it type things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray for the idea that somebody's going to try and fix the lag problems, but can you really know?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll believe it when I see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: What?!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Miss Thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have some updates, well, not updates, but an interesting story on some games that were never released, but maybe should have been?
[SPEAKER_02]: To quote this title, which I think is perfect, cut down in their prime.
[SPEAKER_02]: What website's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Best Games That Never Were, from GameCloud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's just a list of various games that have been cancelled.
[SPEAKER_02]: One was Babylon 5 Into the Fire, cancelled September 1998, which was basically a big space simulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would have used some filmed content from the TV actors, but it was just dragging along for the development, so they axed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: XCOM Genesis XCOM Alliance
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, another victim of Hasbro.
[SPEAKER_02]: Daikatana 2, 1999.
[SPEAKER_06]: Games that should have been cut.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amen, The Awakening, January 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a first-person shooter at Cave Dog.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was an E3 demo at 1999, had a lot of interactive features, but they, well, had money issues and boop, down it went.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they focused on Total Annihilation and then closed down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultima Worlds Online canceled March 2001.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was by Origin and EA to create a sequel to the first Ultima to do sort of like a sci-fi fantasy thing, but they didn't want to pull people off of the original Ultima Online, so they
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting, because then years later, of course, you have EverQuest 2 doing battle with EverQuest 1 in a way, because people who built up their characters on EverQuest 1 didn't want to leave.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of like they saw this with Ultima years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another game canceled was Simsville, September 2001.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maxis announced it in 2000 as a mix of The Sims and SimCity.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually have an old copy of SimCity 3000 that has a promo material for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like, wow, this looks like it'd be interesting, but I don't know how the hell they're going to pull it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Bug, do you remember when we used to play SimAnt?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: The bright yellow ant.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But pretty much instead of doing that, they did The Sims Online and then went on to Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which probably was better, worked out better for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then we had TORN.
[SPEAKER_02]: July 2001, it was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was from Interplay's Black Isle Studios that would have used the Liftec engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hyped up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cancelled down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because especially Interplay hasn't done a game in two years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Duke Nukem Endangered Species.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cancelled 2001.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically because they're working on Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they were... Which we're still waiting on!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was a message by the 3D Realms CEO on the Planet Crap message board.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the best name ever, Planet Crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a game we had to give our publisher in order to get a very sweet deal in another area.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've since talked them out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the quote.
[SPEAKER_04]: To answer some questions from chat room, www.orangelondrader.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phoenix wants to know, why are we talking about games that were canceled in 2000-2001?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the list is the best of all time, or best games that were never, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's more.
[SPEAKER_04]: All time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us real quickly what's left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sam & Max Freelance Police canceled March 2004.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trinity in 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was sort of a response to Return to Castle Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_02]: SWAT Urban Justice canceled 2003.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mythica, February 2004.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ultimate X Odyssey 2004, Black 9 sometime in 2003.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting feedback from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they were starting to shout out some other games that came to mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ryoma says the Zelda demo with Ganon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess a while back there was that demo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it on GameCube, that first demo that they had?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to remember which one he's referencing because there's a couple that come to mind there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spirit Snare says they canceled Nintendo Puzzle Collection, Panel de Pon forever, but they released Pokemon Channel instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and Ryoma and GK128 are joining in, and EarthBound64, but GK128 pointing out EarthBound64 was canned, but it came back on the GBA in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, one that I can interject as well, remember the Final Fantasy VI in 3D demo?
[SPEAKER_04]: A very brief demo that was on Nintendo 64 or something, and drove the fanboys crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually still been trying to hunt that down.
[SPEAKER_02]: I saw it ages ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're an emulation site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the guy who did, and this was another game I was actually interested in was Robotech Crystal Dreams.
[SPEAKER_02]: The developer of that game actually has the ROM for it up on his website and his 3D models available.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see if I can hunt that down for folks in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, one thing that people have been waiting a little while to see a game made out of this is Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, High Voltage Software is going to be developing a Family Guy game for Take-Two Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be doing some video games there based on Family Guy, and I'm assuming that it's actually going to be multi-platform?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I read somewhere near it's multi-platform so you're probably going to see I would say it's probably going to be a very similar deal to what you see with like the Simpsons games but hopefully better games than what we got with the Simpsons games because there were only a couple like Hit and Run was okay but you know most of the Simpsons games were kind of poopy the good old arcade game oh well yeah the arcade game it owns everything but you know
[SPEAKER_04]: I personally want to see another arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this Family Guy jumping the shark, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's, I wouldn't really want my, you know, I wouldn't really want to see a Family Guy game just because I'm afraid of what they'd do with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if it's done right, then hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ryoma in our chat room at OrangeHuntTrader.com says, it's going to be Peter farting, Stewie cursing, Brian drinking, Chris whining, Meg also whining, Lois cleaning up after everyone's crap, and Quagmire being generally horny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll just be the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: There should be a Quagmire game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Quagmire!
[SPEAKER_04]: Xander C says, you know what they need to make a video game out of?
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't we have somebody a while back that was going to make a text adventure game based on Orange Lounge Radio or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: We need our own RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, we need to fire up RPG Creator and make something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's harder than it sounds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you know what, guys?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to do something like that and get our eternal worship, go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll put it on our MySpace or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on to another story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go on over to Loki, who has another possible movie jump in the... Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, Quentin Tarantino in video games, that's something you don't really hear that often.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please say Kill Bill the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kill Bill the Game?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: The theme of this year's game is coming out are old, classic, violent movies made into games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you have The Godfather, Scarface, and now Reservoir Dogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reservoir Dogs the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Reservoir Dogs the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So lots of cursing, shooting, and black and white.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be based on the movie and being developed by Blitz Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be primarily a third-person shooter, but we'll incorporate some driving elements as well as the torture scene where Michael Madsen reprises his role of Mr. Blonde and cuts
[SPEAKER_04]: 3rd person shooter involving some driving Why does NARC come to mind for some crazy reason?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what comes to mind for me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Enter the Matrix Oh, that's kind of weird Because it involves driving and shooting I don't like Enter the Matrix Again, is this jumping the shark?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably It's just a trend, I mean, it's just like Scarface Into the shark
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like Jaws, speaking of jumping the shark, the Jaws game is coming out later this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody was just telling me about that game the other night, that they're eagerly awaiting that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jaws jumped the shark when Jaws 2 came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Jaws 3D?
[SPEAKER_05]: With Jaws, they actually have a dismemberment engine, and you can dismember people in 25 different places.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you play as the shark?
[SPEAKER_05]: You play as the shark.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where have you been?
[SPEAKER_04]: I told you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, they showed it at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could have sworn we went and looked at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I didn't go look at that because I was busy whoring myself out to Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Echo the Dolphin on rabies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was in the line for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's where I was.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you guys hear this?
[SPEAKER_04]: In China, they are rising up and starting a revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Game Unions have threatened to quit playing World of Warcraft because it has to do with unstable servers, and it's just going crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, it's important to note that Blizzard really doesn't oversee the servers.
[SPEAKER_04]: In China, it's actually maintained by a company called The9, and they charge gamers by the hour to play World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost said World of Warcraft, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like the game, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Nine is having a lot of problems solving technical issues related to the game, and they're not seeking Blizzard's help all the time there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers are getting pissed off at severe time delays, long queue times, and frozen server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, WoW has about 530,000 players on it, and they're about ready to just rise up and quit playing the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to vote with their wallets.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's going on in the UK?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a few things.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is a zombie MMO on its way by Thinking Man Studios.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a survival horror MMORPG that lets you play either as a human or a flesh-eating zombie.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's titled Exanimus, which is Latin for without life for people who don't know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there a button for yelling brains?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think a zombie would really have the mental capacity to be able to say brains.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just go like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should be able to expect to see half-rotten corpses walking around tearing apart the bodies of the living for food.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a website that's stating it will be competitively priced to other MMOs currently on the market.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is only in development for the PC, but for a Max, Xbox 360, or PS3 version, they say you never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: With technology always changing, we are always interested in finding new outlets for people to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: No yet word of a release date, no screenshots out, but there is a site, and I'll be linking it to our chat room shortly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I personally want to play as a zombie so I can go around eating people.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, tearing off limbs, beating them with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shaun of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need Shaun of the Dead the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually a brilliant idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next up, Sony is removing PSP posters.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a particular poster that advises consumers to take a running jump from tram and train stations across the country after transport staff expressed safety concerns.
[SPEAKER_02]: The poster was part of a recent advertising campaign to promote the PSP in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: It featured a plain white background with red text that said, Take a running jump from here.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's been actually a bunch of other ones that are kind of teasing at the changes that are being made with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the ones we mentioned a couple weeks ago about pictures and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, a little bit more on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: A rail worker saw the poster to Tram Platform at Metrolink's Manchester Piccadilly Station and decided there was a safety issue and tried to have it covered.
[SPEAKER_02]: They saw it, said it looked inappropriate.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to quote on here, the message goes completely against all of our safety messages, particularly because PlayStation is aimed at youngsters and we are constantly telling them not to trespass.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Sony has taken steps down to remove the posters from the tram stations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lastly, guess what we've got?
[SPEAKER_02]: We have release dates, which would be nice if this Battle for Middle-Earth ad wouldn't cover half of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have actually had releases.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since we have passed the 10th, I'm going to go ahead and move on to the 14th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metal Gear Solid 3 Subsistence on PS2 on the 14th.
[SPEAKER_02]: 17th, 24, The Game, Ankh, Atelier Iris, Eternal Mana, Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Buzz, The Big Quiz, Driver Parallel Lines, Finding Nemo, JamesBun007 from Russia with Love, LA Rush, Midway Arcade Treasures Deluxe, Onimusha, Dawn of Dreams, Sonic Riders.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just not getting Sonic Riders?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Outfit, Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter, Worms.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, anything we should be looking forward to in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: to follow that up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, there's actually some pretty cool stuff coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Driver Parallel Lines coming out on PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's supposed to not suck, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Metal Gear Solid 3 Subsistence, of course, really awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you're into kids' games, I guess Ice Age 2 The Meltdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, to match the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, the movie's coming out later this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too much else coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: What have you heard about 24, The Game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though I've fallen behind on watching the actual show, just because I really haven't watched a lot of TV recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: The shows I used to watch all the time, I'll admit, I watch Survivor every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't been watching it, like, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: But how's 24 the game supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you heard anything about this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know the reviews weren't that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to seem really random, but of course we are an interactive show, and sometimes the chatroom is going to dictate the way we go on the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phoenix in our chatroom at OrangeMonterey.com says, This kid at my school got caught wanking in the bathroom to porn on his PSP, in response to the PSP bit that DarkSakura had to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that made me think of this clip that's going around the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you guys seen this?
[SPEAKER_04]: The guy that's playing World of Warcraft, and the friends sneak up on him, and he's wanking to the sexy night elf dancing, the female night elf.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you guys seen this on YouTube?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where have you been posting?
[SPEAKER_04]: worldofwank.com, Loki, you also have another worldly story for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, Nintendo is going to suit the Dutch.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do they do this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone's always picking on the Dutch, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I'm half Dutch.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband's Dutch, and you know what his grandfather says?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you ain't Dutch, you ain't much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I know I use a stage name on this show, but if you know my real last name, it's very Dutch.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, you can kind of tell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, long story short, they did a political ad for one of the politicians running, and of course, parodying Mario Brothers, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, so why are they suing the political party over this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's a Dutch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, run this by me again.
[SPEAKER_04]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Political party did an advertisement, I guess bashing one of their competitors or whatever, running, using like a Mario Brothers type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we have a clip or anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Dutch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I guess it's nice to know that there's many sue-happy companies in the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: What about parody and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't you... Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's an American thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about Dutch law, but shouldn't there be room for fair parody and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not when you're talking about Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sheesh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Parody and satire.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found it.
[SPEAKER_04]: God of War 2 It's Coming Out
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that's pretty much all we have to say about that at this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is coming out and actually Game Informer magazine actually has some screens from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, something to note, it is coming out for PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not going to be for PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty awesome, except I haven't got my freaking Game Informer magazine issues in the last three months.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why, what happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stupid people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, they just don't freaking...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, are you ready to get your hate on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, although this Dutch thing is really funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd have to say that my FU of the week goes towards, I would have to say the whole American work ethic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in, well, not necessarily the work ethic, but the attitude that corporations, different companies place on overworking employees, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's in the Netherlands that the government has mandatory four weeks paid vacations.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're here, what are we given, what, 10 days?
[SPEAKER_02]: 15 days?
[SPEAKER_02]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's including sick time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yet, they're just as productive as we are.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's, uh, you know, they wonder why we have the highest, uh, you know, amount of, uh, stress leave granted to employees.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because they're burning us out!
[SPEAKER_02]: So take a vacation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's been my FU of the entire week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, fuck you to the full auto multiplayer servers and for the people that constantly disconnect mid-race because they're losing and they suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes it really hard for me to get these last two achievements if people keep quitting the races and they're not counting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me a 360, I'll help you with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to give an FU to movie prices, because that's really why I haven't been to the movies in forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, I can pay $9.25 to go see a movie in the theater, or I can pay less than twice that to get a Netflix account and watch movies on my pretty HDTV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bug, do you have any FUs?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just a few to not having a job still since May, but I do have an interview this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to make your plea?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a lot of people listening to the show, maybe some in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are your qualifications?
[SPEAKER_04]: Unix admin.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to offer Bugged a job, send us an email.
[SPEAKER_04]: With real money, not... He's actually a really smart computer guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how everybody has that friend that they call when they need their computer fixed?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Bugged.
[SPEAKER_04]: I call Bugged when Loki's not available.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I just... It really depends on what the issue is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bugged, I call for most of my issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I had one more I forgot.
[SPEAKER_05]: FU to my work for blocking all internet access except for a few select sites.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is not really... I understand why they're doing it because there's a lot of people slacking off at work and going on MySpace and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the problem is it's also the sites I use for my information on games and stuff and to update our inter-office forms and stuff is being blocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have to constantly email them, like for example IGN.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't really understand how many subdomains there are to IGN until you actually have it blocked and try to have them unblock it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's like 60 different domains on there and they have to unblock all of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're arguably saying, oh, some of these are for ads, and we don't want to unlock two ads.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then I don't get pictures on that site.
[SPEAKER_05]: And GameSpot, same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have pictures on the site anymore, and all the site formatting is all messed up now because they blocked all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't get the CSS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, the other thing, too, they blocked all search engines, so if you're looking for information that might not be on those sites, oh, you're screwed.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about instead of blocking the entire internet, they just block MySpace?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe they should just block the sites that they don't want people to go to, which I've insisted they do in the first place, but the conspiracy theory around the office is they're doing it to make work uncomfortable so people will leave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, can you still play Solitaire on the computers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what did they fix there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just make sure you don't play when the governor comes through.
[SPEAKER_02]: What they did in my work is there's actually a corporate software that they can have go in with Internet Explorer that blocks certain sites registered as a certain type.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly, and that's what they did in this site.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they blocked even stuff that was registered as movies slash TV, which is our business.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's just gotten to a ridiculous level, and they've taken this whole back-asswards approach to try to solve the problem and...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how I know that we made it, though, in the business.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLonsRadio.com finally got blocked by WebSense at one point for being like an internet fan club or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can still access it at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I couldn't access it at one of our vendor companies because I guess they have a high level of restriction on WebSense.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we get picked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's excellent, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't wait to explain to my boss why certain things take longer than usual now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you have to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just have to give justification.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once management starts fussing, things will change.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it starts affecting how management looks, oh yeah, they'll make it change.
[SPEAKER_06]: When they can't hit their girly porn, they'll fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on and get back into some news here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, Konami, what are they up to?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're up to making some stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they're jumping on the Nintendogs bandwagon, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's making another dog simulator game, including a touch mode and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only difference is, it's for PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the pictures of this game all look like the dog is taking a crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's true!
[SPEAKER_05]: What is the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pooping Dog?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Dog Station is what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: This looks like a great game for me to poop on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why can't they make a cat game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, it's like dog picture dog pooping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dog picture dog pooping.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's the way he's sitting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dog poop is funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I remember correctly, though, I believe Dog Station was an arcade game, I want to say, because I know that Dog Station is a franchise that they have out there right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not exactly sure what you do, but DarkTetsuya in chat agrees with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be like Nintendogs at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next you're going to be getting Bunga Bunga, the home version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't know what that is, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're lucky.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have an interesting story about a game I've been looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know much about it, but it still sounds fascinating to me, just the little I have heard about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you need it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we could all use a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Brain training.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh-hoh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, their, uh, brain training is, um, actually there was an announcement in the Mainichi Daily News, which I think is funny because Mainichi also means every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, um, it's, uh, basically, uh, to help your brain fire on all of the nerve structures and now doctors are recommending it to the elderly to help stimulate their brain.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a memory loss clinic at Kyoto's Uchida Hospital for patients suffering dementia.
[SPEAKER_02]: They got a hold of the DSs and brain training and are using it to try to help
[SPEAKER_02]: People get brain function back.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a quote from a 67-year-old patient named Isamu Shishido who said that he hoped the game would help him stop forgetting things like names and phone numbers so his daughter will stop making fun of him.
[SPEAKER_02]: To quote, I don't want to end up some crazy old man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to play a little every day before going to bed.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, is he a...
[SPEAKER_02]: Reasonable Stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo basically though is using this as an excuse to point out again that people of all ages like it's brain training software and that they're trying to use this strategy to try and appeal to existing games, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers who are out of it, non-gamers, trying to basically appeal to the whole broad market of gamers as this is something you can use to... I can't help but think myself, is this going to be the next game that really crosses that gap and gets everybody in on it, like Tetris?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the theory is it's actually a publicity stunt because Nintendo is housed in Kyoto.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's going to pretty much help with, you know, because we're first marketing it to younger people and people of slow learning capacity, but if this is something that's going to also help keep the minds of older people sharp to hold off some of the effects of old age, then who are we to...
[SPEAKER_02]: But who are we to tell them not to do it?
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's actually helping people, if it does good, they should go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks in our chatroom might disagree with the brain training setting the stage to be a huge game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funnydale in our chatroom says, brain training, with that name alone, it's a sure bet that it'll fail in the USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think brain Olympics would have been it, but then you fight with the Olympic committee over something like that, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember a Fox special that was on, something like How Smart is America?
[SPEAKER_04]: or the Great American Quiz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't this a couple years ago they had this show on?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like a big 20-question quiz show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just attach the name American Idol to brain training.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Pop Idol.
[SPEAKER_05]: and as opposites of that probably sounds, you know, American Idol does well in the ratings.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I vote for, like, Brain Food.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're kind of winding down here with Orange Lounge Radio this week, but first off, a chance for anybody to get out any stories they haven't done yet before we get into tonight's last story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to become, well, actually, it should piss off a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: According to a post on Xbox.com, there is an internal Best Buy document, and we know how wonderful those are, stating that the new premium systems will now include a 100GB hard drive instead of the 20GB hard drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, my thoughts exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: You bastards.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is supposed to coincide with the DirecTV downloadable...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, last story of the night, Loki, what's the exciting news this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're a fan of really cheesy crap that's on TV, you might remember a show called Captain N. I remember how awful that show was.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, the NES era cartoon featuring Kevin Keen, normal teenager battling the evil mother brain in Videoland.
[SPEAKER_05]: Freakazoid was far better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, from the, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I thought the character models were pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's the deal?
[SPEAKER_02]: It jumped the shark with the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the deal with Captain N?
[SPEAKER_04]: DVD?
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming to DVD?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Jesus, when?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have a when yet, but it is coming to DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: So to put next to your Zelda cartoons from the Super Mario Super Show.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is also put out by the same people that did, I believe, what was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember the show now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was...
[SPEAKER_05]: Cops, the animated series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I liked Cops.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I might add got horrible reviews in the transfer, which sounds like real Ghostbusters versus Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the whole thing about Captain is that for anybody who ever paid attention to the actual storylines to the games, it was like a big old insult.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to clarify some things in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_04]: The statement there, coming from a couple people, I'll read Sephiroth 1215's line here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The HDDs aren't even 20 gigs, it was like 16.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is because of the emulator that's pre-installed on the drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, they forgot to mention that when they're selling you the 20 gig hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, there's already a big fat emulator on here that you can't really get rid of.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, it's pre-loaded with a bunch of songs, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I had to go through and delete all the songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I actually loaded a custom soundtrack on my machine for when I'm playing, like, the little Bejeweleds and Zumas and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put a custom soundtrack on there, so I had to delete all the crap that was already on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frustrating.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I do not like... I thought the way the Xbox handled the memory management was way better than 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because in 360, you have to dive into all the submenus to erase something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just very frustrating.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no global disk erase menu.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would you want to erase anything ever?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, kids, it's about time to wrap up this edition of Orange Lounge Radio, but not before we go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number one, reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Number two, the redeeming quality of Captain N was the mother brain and the eggplant wizard.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true, the eggplant wizard did rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bugged, thank you for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta play some more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually gotta try Burnout online.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hear that's good, but I need to get my full auto stuff done first.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my final thought is I'm about to be sucked back into Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kill me dead!
[SPEAKER_04]: Tick, tick, tick, tick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and listening to us and supporting us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, don't forget, help promote us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We would really appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're on MySpace now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can always leave us a review on iTunes or Podcast Alley or vote for us on Live365.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really appreciate all that, and it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Always send candy grams.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we will take financial donations, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Candy gram.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And candy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mmm, candy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or brownies with espresso in them, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, those had espresso in them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Till next week!
[SPEAKER_06]: See ya!
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!
Thanks for watching!