[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to the podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_03]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now the conclusion of episode number 175 for March the 5th, 2006.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 175.
[SPEAKER_08]: For this, March the 5th of 2006, it's time for Part B. If you've missed the first half of the show, shame on you, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go back and check it out on our podcast stream, OrangeLoungeRadio.com, for more information.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or, as we just announced during the first half of the show, we had Bobby over from AllGames.com to announce that Orange Lounge Radio and All Games are joining up to bring you Orange Lounge Radio Syndicated.
[SPEAKER_08]: Monday nights on All Games Radio 7 o'clock part A and B so it's a chance for you to check out the second half of our show before we put it on our own podcasting stream because they're just that good that they get it done faster than we do so check that out that's going to be awesome
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's get back into some gaming news here.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony is selling the Metreon complex and who do they sell it to?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mall developer, the Westfield Group and the Forest City Enterprises real estate company for an undisclosed amount of money.
[SPEAKER_08]: So Sony will continue to operate the official PlayStation store in the mall, but as for the rest of the stuff there...
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows what we could see going up in there pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Abercrombie and Fitch, for all we know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would just be peachy, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo-hiss.
[SPEAKER_08]: No idea what's going to happen to the walk of game just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But many of us DDR fans, like NorCal especially, with fond memories of Medtron, except for Loki who somehow missed it all, it's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes me a little verklempt.
[SPEAKER_08]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk amongst yourselves.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, but life goes on.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, moving on...
[SPEAKER_08]: to another story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you got some interesting, you had some real great exclusives in the first part there about PlayStation 3 and Revolution.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you got now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is kind of, you can file it under rumor, how Sony plans on combating the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the way they're going to do that, well, of course, it's going to be with the PlayStation 2 and the iToy.
[SPEAKER_07]: What they're planning on doing is because the PlayStation 2 is already an established console system out there, they're still producing them, and they're anticipating that the price point is going to drop down to $99 in 2007.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, with the iToy, they're anticipating that you'll be able to use this to create some really revolutionary games.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only problem with that is the iToy doesn't work that good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know this from first-hand experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: And let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wiping windows down and looking like a jackass while dancing on screen, not revolutionary.
[SPEAKER_08]: iToy Kinetic was fun for a day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Waste of $50 because my apartment does not light good enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it just does not work for iToy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And while I could go to Ikea and buy a lamp...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not changing the house around to make the iToy work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, when they're showing off the iToy games and they're against a nice white backdrop, that's the perfect environment for the iToy.
[SPEAKER_07]: But most of us people, we live in rooms with more than white in the room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like posters and paintings.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not good.
[SPEAKER_07]: But some of the other stuff that they're talking about, and this is actually kind of another thing that Xbox is doing too with their camera, is they're going to be using multiple cameras to track movement.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's more something on the Xbox 360 front.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be using that.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, they also showed how they can render your face in there by doing a screen cap of your face, you know, facing forward and sideways, and then render it 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're also going to be using that kind of as an eye toy or revolution thing as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: and B, The Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_08]: It wouldn't be that revolutionary if it were just that simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is all rumor.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is not good enough to combat the revolution thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's other things that are going to set the PS3 apart from the revolution, just as there's going to be things that set Xbox 360 apart from it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no need for these guys to all try and copy each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only good thing about the PlayStation 2 is it's not going to be as expensive as the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comments from our chatroom, www.orangeloungeradio.com We love the interactivity that taping live on Sunday nights brings us here.
[SPEAKER_08]: GS191 says, iToy, good concept, terrible games.
[SPEAKER_08]: What makes you think that the PS3 X360 camera is going to be better?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going back to the Metreon story there earlier, somebody had said... I'm trying to find the thing here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody had said that...
[SPEAKER_08]: Old tech TV shows had been taped at the Metreon, so it kind of further... Oh, Tomokun said, dude, it had tech TV shows taped there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just to further add insult to injury to the whole, you know, tech TV is long gone type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had X-Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: X-Play used to be recorded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or before X-Play, what the hell was it called?
[SPEAKER_07]: Extended Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Extended Play was recorded there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now it's going to be just a giant Abercrombie & Fitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Banana Republic going in there as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, moving in.
[SPEAKER_08]: I made all that up, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, EA, we talked about in the first half a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_08]: The VP over at EA, Dr. I'm going to say this, so horrible, Jens Uwe Intat, foresees that there will be a shift coming within the next 10 years.
[SPEAKER_08]: CDs, DVDs, and box games will be as antiquated as cassette tapes and vinyl records.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are they going in favor of there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Downloadable media.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're saying that the downloadable media is going to be the shift there in 10 years there.
[SPEAKER_08]: and of course you look at the success of iTunes and you think it's just a matter of time before movies start being distributed the same way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Heck, it's already happening on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some shows that maybe aren't even doing that successful on TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm thinking The Office does really, really well on iTunes and it does okay on TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it does really well on iTunes so it might be the future outlet for TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course independent vidcasting getting bigger and bigger.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well now, why not the same model apply to games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're also probably going to start streaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have the DirecTV tab that's going to be coming to the Xbox Live, your desktop there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're also going to be having location-free players for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, you've got the news that PlayStation 3 in Korea is going to start doing direct downloads of games straight to your hard drive because they want to combat piracy there, and they're going to offer them at less than retail.
[SPEAKER_07]: And hell, we're doing it right now with the Xbox Live Arcade, just in a smaller format.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I went to a panel at KatsuCon, and I asked a question about this, and I practically got laughed at.
[SPEAKER_08]: And people were saying, Xbox Live Arcade does not pose a threat to the regular system of downloading games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm thinking, okay, well now I've got this EA vice president backing me up, which I need to point out, he's actually Electronic Arts Europe vice president, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not clarifying that earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: That this downloadable games thing is going to be more and more of a force, I think.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, one thing he does say that, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: is a bit of an interesting point here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apple has kept their song prices at 99 cents per song, and this is a low figure that kind of makes people in the music business a little bit angry here.
[SPEAKER_08]: iTunes essentially has a monopoly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dr. Entente seems to think that with so many consoles available, there's not going to be a monopoly possible if this model works with games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can tell you this much.
[SPEAKER_07]: And here's why it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you have all the major retailers that make a lot of money off of these games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, you've got rental chains.
[SPEAKER_07]: If we all start streaming media, what's going to happen to the whole rental market?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got GameStop and freaking EB.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're the same company now, but their whole business is game purchasing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: If that happens, they're going to lose money from all these different outlets and then... Well, what about moving with the seas of change, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Tower Records doesn't still primarily make their business off records in the sense that we know them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blockbuster realizes that people like the Netflix model, so they copy it and do their own thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's to say that GameStop isn't one of the online services that decides to get in on that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is obviously all huge amounts of speculation, but you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a good question to ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where will gaming be in 10 years?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an excellent idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, those 28 hard drives that they were packaging with the Xbox 360s, not going to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but in 10 years, we're not going to be talking Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to be talking Xbox 1080 or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got another story here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Several stories, actually, from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since we had a little comment there from the Electronic Arts Vice President over in Europe, why not give our pals over in Europe a little more information on what's going on in their neck of the woods?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Jamie, you keep tabs on that?
[SPEAKER_08]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: We thought they were gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: We thought we heard the last of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Acclaim is back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, with a free MMO, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called BOTS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like it's all capitalized.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm already bored.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, they're describing it as a title that will appeal to everyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you start off with adaptable, upgradable little robots that are supposedly really cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can do cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Story about some evil virus, PvP, capture the flag, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you were supposed to have these near infinite combinations of upgrades.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, there was a game like this back in the days of the Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: It also reminds me of the Enix SNES game RoboTrek.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, they're working on this.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually a new Acclaim Games website where they have their beta tests up there to register for.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also a future title coming out called, it's a martial arts MMO called Nine Dragons.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you just go to Acclaim.com, it's the first link on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first little image there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I'll sign up for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks really cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually looks pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got a comment in our chat room here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma says, I saw the site for Acclaim's bots.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks just like the Ragnarok Online page.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's laid out just like a website for a Korean MMO.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Ragnarok Online, so I think I'll give the bots a try.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ragnarok Online certainly was cute, and it was the only game I've ever played that would allow my male character to wear a bow in his head.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have that photo.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was on my cell phone for forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I miss Ragnarok.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, anyway, uh, next up, uh, a comment by, uh, uh, Roger Bennett, who is the general director of, uh, UK Video Games Publisher Trade Body, ELSPA, said there's complete and utter nonsense about a speech made in Parliament by the Labour MP, Keith Vaz, uh, stating, uh, about new laws, or, relating to video game ratings.
[SPEAKER_02]: I brought this up earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, gamesindustry.biz was told, and I quote,
[SPEAKER_02]: Vaz was proposing an amendment to the Video Recordings Act in 1984 that would make it mandatory for video games to receive content ratings the same way that films do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a voluntary... The PEGI rating system is all voluntary to coincide with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he was arguing in Parliament that the current system...
[SPEAKER_02]: where basically it sees the PEGI ratings being complemented by the British Board of Film Classification to go along the same lines, but they're saying that's very confusing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me get the next quote on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a very long article that I've been digesting over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically, it was going back, Bennett stated, the fact of the matter is that we're one of only two countries in the whole 27 states in the European Union who have mandatory ratings.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everywhere else in Europe, these ratings are on the boxes, the PEGI ratings, and they make informed decisions for their kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: The more you take the responsibility away from the parents, the less responsibility they'll take.
[SPEAKER_02]: As soon as you take responsibility away from the people, then they rely on others to do it for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole process is mindless in my view.
[SPEAKER_02]: At the end of the day, as long as the information is there, we should leave it to the parents and guardians, to those responsible for young people, to make informed decisions about what they should or shouldn't watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: The blame culture in which we seem to live these days is a result of the promotion of the nanny state, no question about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's always somebody else's fault and they have to have somebody else to blame.
[SPEAKER_02]: That right there is my argument.
[SPEAKER_02]: This guy is my hero now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's bring down the old OLR hero wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to print out his photo at Kinko's and put it on the wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't think it's ever been stated better than I've seen it in print there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I really do think that's what it comes down to, is that we have these figures in government trying to basically...
[SPEAKER_02]: And this, you know, it's not just here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is proof.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to dictate what the people see, what the people watch, take responsibility away from the people, take away accountability from the people, and put it in the hands of government to babysit them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been happening more, especially, and I hate to say it, especially since 9-11, it's been happening more and more, where we've had our governments taking control over what they view as protection action, whether it's in censorship of video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not just that, I think more so, I mean, certainly I noticed it then too, but Janet Jackson, Boobie, Super Bowl, hello, yeah, that was a huge...
[SPEAKER_02]: What we're seeing is, you know, especially in, and I think that's actually even more of a slap in the face to those of us in the United States where we're founded on these principles of free speech and human rights where
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, though, that...
[SPEAKER_02]: the whole especially with, you know, Jackie Poo his whole agenda with, you know, seeing this come up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it really is more of a more of a view overall that they're not wanting us to be accountable for ourselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: They take the power away from the people and we're left just blindly following what they tell us to.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my theory behind all of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think
[SPEAKER_02]: That it all goes hand in hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send those cards and letters to Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com That's just my opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just my observation.
[SPEAKER_02]: But again, I find it very sad that governments are having to step in and tell parents how to do their jobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trying to dictate what you can and can't do.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more bit of European news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is the PSP Gigapack price has been slashed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, basically, uh, for any Northern Irish gamers hoping to pick up the PSP Gigapack, um, GameStop has slashed, uh, basically, uh, 25 pounds off the price.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can pick up the pack, which includes a PSP, a stand USB cable, and a 1 gigabyte memory stick for, uh,
[SPEAKER_02]: 189.99 in Northern Ireland branches of GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Game has also been lowered to 289.99 euros in GameStop stores throughout all of Ireland.
[SPEAKER_02]: Outside, however, the price is still 214.99 or in euros 309.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: So go to Ireland if you want to get your gigapack cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yes, what's coming up?
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't go without that, can we?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a little while, so now we're into a new month.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what's coming out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, tomorrow we have Snowboard Kids DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 9th we have Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: These are UK dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 10th, 24 The Game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't that make you happy?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been bad at watching 24.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't watch any TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except for The Apprentice.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched The Apprentice once and it wasn't even that good.
[SPEAKER_02]: For the rest of the games coming out, also in the 10th, Combat 121, Fight Night Round 3, Guilty Gear X2 Reload on PC, Lemmings for the PSP, Namco Museum 50th Anniversary Arcade Collection on the Game Boy Advance, NBA 2K6, NHL 2K6,
[SPEAKER_02]: Pipa Funnel 2 which I don't know what that is on PC Rhythmic Star on PS2 Beautiful Joe Red Hot Rumble that's really awesome also to mention on the 14th Metal Gear Solid 3 Subsistence
[SPEAKER_08]: WonderDog Harold would just like you all to know that watching 24 caused him to have a dream of naked Jean Smart from Designing Women who plays... Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_08]: She's on this new season, so... Oh my god, she still has a career?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, she actually has a great... She was the blonde one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I only saw... Wasn't she?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I only saw the first four episodes, or the first two long episodes, the first four hours, and she had a pretty badass role, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, her career is jump-starting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, but she's not in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, anyway...
[SPEAKER_08]: We'd love to follow up UK release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was it, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'd love to follow up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been cutting everybody off tonight with total randomness, and I apologize, but I've just been pent up for two weeks in Virginia.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what's going on with US release dates?
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, of course, March is a huge month for games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And as I mentioned before, Burnout, Revenge, and Ghost Recon Events, Warfighter were coming out this week for the 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other releases coming out this week, Championship Bowling for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dragon Ball Z Shin Budokai, the Dragon Ball Z fighting game, finally hits the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, we have Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter also coming out on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: Naruto Class of the Ninja coming out on GameCube.
[SPEAKER_07]: Naruto Ninja Council coming out on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Onimusha Dawn of Dreams is finally hitting the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: and if you're egging for some new Pokemon puzzle games, Pokemon Troze is coming out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hang my head in deep shame because I want to play this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: More PSP games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pursuit Force and Samurai Warriors are heading towards the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: A brand new RPG coming out, Shadow Hearts from the New World, which actually looks pretty decent, on PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Spongebob Yellow Avenger on the PSP, followed by Tales of Phantasia 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other notable stuff coming out later on the month here, we of course have Driver Parallel Lines coming out the week of the 13th, as well as Metal Gear Solid 3 Subsistence, which should be really sweet, The Outfit for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then finally, the week of the 20th, we've got a couple games coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most notably, The Godfather is hitting Xbox and PlayStation 2, as well as Blazing Angels is coming out on Xbox and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, the ever-anticipated Elder Scrolls 4 finally hitting the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finally, and me and Mike Hadamari.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got to put that in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Metroid Prime Hunters, because those are really good games as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tetris DS?
[SPEAKER_07]: TesterDS also that week and also Metal Gear Racer 2 and Mega Man Power Rift.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my bank account is going to cry the end of this month.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be a sad week at my bank.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Worms Open Warfare.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I'm actually looking forward to that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, just so you know, WonderDog Harold would also like to remind you in regards to our previous conversation, Gene Smart was also the voice of Mrs. Possible in Kim Possible, just for those of you following her career.
[SPEAKER_07]: And beat me in Indiana the 29th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which does not feature Gene Smart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Beatmania 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's also launched the same day as Karaoke Revolution Country.
[SPEAKER_08]: These games that we love, Beatmania and all that stuff, and we love US games too, don't get us wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love games from all around, but Japan certainly brings us lots and lots and lots of memorable, great games.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a magazine over there that has a lot of clout over in the Japan gaming market.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Famitsu.
[SPEAKER_08]: They recently polled their readers to vote on their all-time favorite 100 games
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Quest VII, Final Fantasy III, Tactics Ogre, Final Fantasy IV, Machi,
[SPEAKER_08]: 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Quest VIII 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Quest III 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy VII 1.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy X
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes sense because Final Fantasy X has this humongous fandom built around it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, and that's not surprising in any way, but let me get that straight.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's four Final Fantasies and three Dragon Quests comprising the top ten.
[SPEAKER_08]: Might I also point out Dragon Quest V, number 11, Dragon Quest IV, number 14, Dragon Quest II, number 17, Final Fantasy VIII, number 22, Final Fantasy IX, 24, Final Fantasy VI, 25.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shall I continue?
[SPEAKER_08]: So they like their RPGs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not surprising at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm actually really not at all surprised to see Tactics Ogre in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where was Final Fantasy Tactics?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see it in the top 50.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe in the bottom 50.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me keep looking here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy Tactics I know had a big following for a while too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Tactics Ogre completely does not surprise me.
[SPEAKER_08]: 84 Final Fantasy Tactics.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's on the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they have any of the PC Engine titles in there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like Dracula X?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if I saw anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Emerald Dragon?
[SPEAKER_02]: What about that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Animal Crossing's 43.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Metal Gear Solid, 50.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to know where Dracula X is on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's there.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Gradius, 98.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking, I'm looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: They published this over on next-gen.biz, by the way, is where I'm pulling this from.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see a single Castlevania game on here, but I'm eyeing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might be missing it, so I apologize if I'm wrong there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That wounds me in my soul.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: They are smoking crack, but Famitsu is notorious for being bastards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon Quest VIII Dragon Quest VIII
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, moving on, let's go over to Loki for some reports on the homebrew scene.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, as always.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, starting off of some wonderful games coming to the PSP homebrew scene.
[SPEAKER_07]: First one is a Halo clone.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, they're working on a Halo kind of port to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's based on the
[SPEAKER_07]: Game or Multiplayer App Iris.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's actually a mod, but it's going to be containing four-player deathmatch type of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of being worked on right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: As far as stuff that's out there right now, I've already mentioned this in the last podcast, but got to cover it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: The new Super Nintendo emulator SNES 9X version 0.4 has been updated with wireless multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can actually go ahead and play...
[SPEAKER_07]: People near you at some Street Fighter, and they've actually clocked it at 60 frames per second while playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other homebrew stuff that's going to be coming out, though, for the PSP, they've created an ISO loader using the exploit in Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another thing that they've also been able to do is launch Grand Theft Auto on version 1.5 firmware.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for those who have played Grand Theft Auto's Liberty City stories,
[SPEAKER_07]: you'll know that it forces you to upgrade to 2.0 so they've actually bypassed all that and got it to run on that same firmware.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other thing that they've also launched is an upgrade to that because they're worried that people are going to be pirating games and stuff so they've actually got a UMD loader for firmware 1.5 that will run any game that will force you to update to 2.0 or higher in 1.5 if you have the UMD because a lot of people do have games out there they want to play but they want to play their homebrew stuff
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they can.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other things, there was also kind of teased a little bit for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, you can have remote access to your PC using the DS, and that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: They showed a little picture of that, but no release on that yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep us posted on what's going on and whatever they install Linux on next and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I was waiting for the 360 for Linux.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, DarkSakura, you're going to get all the fun stories tonight on violence and political stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you got next?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm all about the violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the politics.
[SPEAKER_08]: The politics, the violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm all about the violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: With the increase of video game violence, we have crime going way down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that awesome?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, crime went down when video game violence went up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, with the increase of the first-person shooter genre, crime... I'm sorry, I was backwards on that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, we already went over that before.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the crime-based action games are declining.
[SPEAKER_08]: But still, that means there's more of a demand over here than there is over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: That says something.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically, I'm tongue-tied, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they were basically saying that even though the success of Grand Theft Auto and all that, you know, has been so big that there's still not so many of them coming out, that the first-person shooter is really taking prevalence in the whole video game industry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did have an earlier story that did state, I remember doing something on the show a while ago, that despite the violent video games coming out, people get their aggressions out on them or something, because overall, crime rate... The thing is, though, is that the study is still there, though, at the Department of Justice.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are charts proving that since, what was it, 93, when the PlayStation came out, that there has been a decrease in youth-based violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, two...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, you ready to get angsty?
[SPEAKER_08]: When am I not?
[SPEAKER_02]: My first, well my big only FU is I'm tired of being the emotional receptacle of the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I can take, and take, and take, and take.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't know if I'm just easily ventable to, but I have my limits too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not really an FU, it's more of an FU toward myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I can't... I have to get my aggression out too, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't see why everybody else... Let it all out, girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let it all out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why everybody in the universe feels that they can just tell me their whole life story like it's some horrible thing and it's going to really, you know... Like some complete stranger starts telling me about how bad their life sucks and I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are you telling me this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you tell them to stop?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just sort of said, I have to go now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's like, it's been happening more often than not lately that I've been getting rants, you know, in defense of people, you know, I never really mind hearing it, you know, if you need to vent to me, say, hey, I think you're a good person to talk to, let's talk about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But when it comes out, you know, completely unprovoked, I'm like, okay, what did that have to do with anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is so out of left field.
[SPEAKER_02]: and especially without, you know, even saying, hey, is this a good time for you emotionally for me to vent to?
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to make sure that when you're going to talk to somebody that they're going to be in a position to listen to you objectively and not just... Because, you know, say that the person you're talking to is really depressed, really stressed out, really just having an awful day and then you start talking about how much your life sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's that going to make them feel?
[SPEAKER_02]: The moral of the story is get a live journal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Vlog it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The moral of this though is if you have a problem...
[SPEAKER_02]: and you need to vent to somebody, make sure that your intended venting audience is in a position that they're going to be able to withstand your venting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's www.myspace.com That's where the internet goes to die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tom will be your friend when no one else will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm serious, so it's... I never mind listening to my friends when they need me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am always there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And listeners, I am there for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: But make sure that if you are going to vent to me that I am not having the utter shit of the day before you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really the only thing I'm kind of frustrated at is Xbox Live's arcade, or not really their arcade, their online play for full auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: The people playing full auto keep jumping out of the games like they're playing Mario Kart DS or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: and granted you know I'm not too worried about I mean because I understand people will do that and you know I don't think that it's a huge deal but the fact is you know I'm playing the game I'm not even doing that well I'm getting like sixth place and I'm still you know taking the spot and I'm willing to you know take the sixth place and not get that many points but it doesn't even count because everyone drops out of the game and so you know I waste time you know playing through these races for nothing and also god damn it I'm doing so good in those races and I hit a damn like
[SPEAKER_07]: Something will fly on the street like a little apple or something and my car will flip into the air like 50 feet because the physics are all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really frustrating, but goddamn at least I beat those stupid gang war missions because I don't want to break something.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was actually in a really crappy mood all day because PMS for men or something is what I've been going through today, but actually the show has put me in a much better mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I thank you guys for having a happy, super-duper show tonight, because I'm actually in a better mood.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I feel like throughout my randomness and my rants, I've been able to get it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess my only FU that is left is FU to the Oscars for daring to compete with our program tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going down, Stuart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mr. Jon Stewart, you're going down, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spike, you have any angst you need to get out?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, with a name like Spike, you gotta be an angry person, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, actually, I have two things, and they're both
[SPEAKER_09]: directed towards Capcom.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first one is that as cool as I think it is that you can play as the robot masters in Mega Man Powered Up, these new character designs have to go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because Mega Man is not meant to be one of those Duplo Block characters, and the fact that he is, baby Jesus cries for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Second,
[SPEAKER_09]: Capcom is putting out a collection of their classic arcade games.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a follow-up to their arcade classics line, recently launched.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Remixed Pack.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for some reason, in their infinite wisdom, they see fit to take up valuable space on that UMD with Quiz and Dragons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Quiz and Dragons is badass.
[SPEAKER_08]: You shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know how many quarters I wasted at the local pizzeria playing Quiz and Dragons?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I screamed like a little girl when I found that game in MAME like years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: So sit down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_08]: I am fucking serious.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell is Quiz and Dragons?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Quiz!
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a Quiz show!
[SPEAKER_07]: Choose Quiz or Dragons!
[SPEAKER_07]: I choose Quiz!
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, good, Dad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a Quiz thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a Quiz thing with dragons.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have the vegetarian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: People, alright, well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just for the record, I want to say, even though Spike got a little angsty there, you know, Spike is actually just one of the most cuddly guys I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's a nice boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: so uh moving on he just has dragons he just has some strong opinions about very good games that Capcom put out that were horribly underrated like Black Tiger absolutely I love Black Tiger but Quiz and Dragons Loki speaking of uh dragon type things okay actually this game has nothing to do with dragons I don't know what the hell that was just just just take over wow that was an
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to stand back for a second.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the most awesome transition ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I told you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm having an off night tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two and a half weeks of... Forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of quizzes and dragons, Soul Calibur the movie is actually being worked on right now because you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently some movie studio out there is like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have money to burn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's burn some money and... Yeah, anyways, they launched their website for this and it teases that the movie doesn't show anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, it was like a Nostradamus quote or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_08]: www.soulcaliberofthemovie.com or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: www.soulcaliberofthemovie.com and it loads up this wonderful strive to understand what I have found through my... Just stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're not Mr. Movie Phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, so it puts up stupid little text on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And not a single picture of Ivy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this sword shall smite the earth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was bullshit when I first looked at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I said, ah, fan thing, bullshit.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was like, okay, maybe there's something going on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I put on my Google hat, and I went over to Google, and I started searching all around, and sure enough, I found this page on backstage.com, and it shows films that are currently in development, in the early development process, and sure enough, there it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Soul Calibur the movie, action.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at this, Romania, China, and Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's where they're going to be filming this.
[SPEAKER_08]: VJP Agarwal Canada Almost Resembles Romania
[SPEAKER_08]: and China.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's just like the Oscars are on tonight, the big movie tonight, Brokeback Mountain.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it weren't for all the French people and snow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they're saying Brokeback Mountain is driving all this tourism to Wyoming.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was filmed in Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is, you know, amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still trying to find this guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's figure out what else he was affiliated with.
[SPEAKER_08]: The executive producer there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Such wonderful films as...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if this is the same one here.
[SPEAKER_08]: That can't be the same one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: More to come.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do research and get back to you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: He hasn't made Jack.
[SPEAKER_08]: For now, let's go back to a story about Electronic Arts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, they make a lot of their money off those NFL games, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: The NFL and the Players Association are currently involved in a debate over salaries and players' cuts, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless they get to an agreement, they're going to maybe go on strike and maybe there'll be a lockout in 2008.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: If there is some antitrust that goes in here, if the antitrust rules go into play with this whole strike or whatever, it would void Electronic Arts' contract with the NFL.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that would really suck for EA if that happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ubern.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poor babies.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they better hope there's no strike.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't deserve that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know a lot of you guys that listen to this program probably don't play those games.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for those that do, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what else you got?
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband does.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, a couple weeks ago, there was this wonderful little arcade show in Japan where they showed off some really cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: AOU 2006, they had a couple wonderful highlights here we're going to cover.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first one being Time Crisis 4, because, you know, Time Crisis rocks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Soul Calibur 3 is finally making its way to the arcade, as well as some other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Taiko no Tatsujin coming out now with Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: songs, so that should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other things, of course, Half-Life 2 Survivor, which is going to be the arcade version of Half-Life 2, kind of with a lot of Deathmatch stuff there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, some stuff from Sega, Virtual Fighter 5, which looks pretty cool, and House of the Dead 4, which is really neat, better graphics of course, and they even have a version that's kind of one of those, you know, arcade ride simulator type of things, with a 100 inch screen, and it actually, you know, they strap you in and it rotates around and kind of coincides with the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, other things, of course, would be Virtual Strikers 4, you know, for your soccer fans, and some new brain training game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something of note for those of you local here to the Sacramento area, the movie theater over in Roseville currently has a test machine of House of the Dead 4.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was there last night, it was rather impressive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it still have the awful voice acting?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes!
Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: And that Lindbergh board is putting out some textures that amazed the hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome 3D and bad voice acting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to go spill coke on that machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wake me when Typing of the Dead 2 comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, I love Typing of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I'm not... I want to do a cosplay where I strap a Dreamcast to my back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Been done.
[SPEAKER_07]: People have done that.
[SPEAKER_02]: People have done it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob...
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft could be working on that next if this whole, you know, DDR email thing falls through.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what that whole typing of the dead setup reminds me of?
[SPEAKER_08]: The origami.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a bajillion emails in the last couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've tried to reply to as many as I can.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I have been sort of pooped on by school, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in, I'm sort of skipping class tomorrow to finish my homework.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, back to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm such a responsible student, aren't I?
[SPEAKER_02]: We got an email from... Robert sent us an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who had a question about Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there any talk about Guitar Hero being made for Japan?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, Red Octane is, as far as I know, an American publisher, unlike Konami, who did the Karaoke Revolution series overseas as well as domestically.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the current song selections are very US and European.
[SPEAKER_02]: But do you see the game competing well with Guitar Freaks?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think most Bomani fans in general, and I'm making a broad generalization, of course there are exceptions to this, I think most of the community prefers Guitar Hero over Guitar Freaks because Guitar Hero kind of improved on the Guitar Freaks model.
[SPEAKER_08]: So could the game do well in Japan?
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they'd obviously have to change the song list, but go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Guitar Hero would have the potential to do well in Japan, but the thing is you have to really focus on how the Japanese gaming market does.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to stick more with the Bimani series, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Namco has a guitar series out.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few other companies have various other ones, and still the most popular of them are still the Bimani ones, even if the other ones are better.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the most likely thing to happen, if it were to happen in Japan, and please understand this is pure speculation, I think Harmonix would probably license that out to someone else to develop a Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_08]: or maybe, you know, like, I don't think it would be that same Red Octane Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they would sell out the license, the idea, to somebody who's interested in localizing it for Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe the game engine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that seems most likely to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I don't see anything happening this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to see, like, Guitar Hero Visual K Edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what's interesting is that, you know, Guitar Freaks V is still supposedly on its way.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't heard anything in a while, but supposedly it's still coming in Japan, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be interesting if Guitar Hero were to come out to counter this, but would Konami get lawsuit-y over it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a whole other can of worms there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all speculation.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also have an email from our friend Rob with two Bs.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a lot of Robs tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a good mailbag night.
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked about this last week, I might add.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm reading the email, which has nothing to do with last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically the Sierra game titles are being re-released from Target.com So just go ahead and check out Target.com, their whole series of them Police Quest, Space Quest, King's Quest Which will explain why they didn't get added to GameTap Oh no, Space Quest is on GameTap So I kind of was hoping King's Quest would make its way Anyway
[SPEAKER_02]: Also an email from Justin, who I helped with the song title, said he saw the Lemmings game for PSP out and released in the UK and wondering if it was way too important and if it would even play on the US PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: The answer to that is no, I don't think, because aren't they...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if they're region encoded.
[SPEAKER_01]: PSPs aren't.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_02]: So actually, yeah, you would be able to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would just say, you know, check Amazon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I order from Amazon UK all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: The reason why it's easier to do this with handhelds where you can cross import and all that stuff and like, you know, Game Boy Advance games work, Japan, US, doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: is because the handhelds have their own screens.
[SPEAKER_08]: The biggest problem you run into with the UK versus the US... Anything on TV is going to be PAL versus NTSC.
[SPEAKER_08]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And until everybody's on high def, we're always going to have this problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, if you've got a high definition screen and the imported system, you will not run into a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: One thing of note on importing UMDs is that UMD movies are always region coded.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, just as a general rule.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what had me thinking because I knew the movies were, I didn't know what the games were, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, you should have, I suggest, honestly suggest Amazon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I order CDs through Amazon UK and Japanese Amazon all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I'm going to be paying $30 for a Gorillaz single in a couple of weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Freak.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't say it on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did not bring you here to be a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fanboy away.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jaime emailed us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the Jaime, not me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I do remember this.
[SPEAKER_08]: She told us about the Darwinia?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Though it needed good games, the golden rule of video game systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys were pretty accurate on that show, if I remember correctly, on your predictions for that system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking about a best of show because I still have every show since you guys have been on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I still love to listen to some of them for a good laugh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some good ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR Week of...
[SPEAKER_02]: 8105 to 8705 with Matt, listen, I guess this is a Matt quote, Loki quote, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Listen, I'm not knocking the Mac or anything because granted the processing power may be what I'm looking for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their cases look cool though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, their cases are nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, Rob, did we just go to Bizarro Orange Challenge Radio because I just heard Loki say something nice about the Macintosh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, and then you said, the cases look nice, but that's all they are, just big graphing calculators inside of a nice case.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember him saying that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then bringing out the Mega Man 2 sound.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some funny bits in the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can dig 20 episodes back at olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, these are great!
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll take you back to about...
[SPEAKER_08]: November shows, but the other old stuff, you're going to have to wait until we put out a CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't we have that wiki quote page or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a wiki quote page somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to put these up on wiki quote, because these are hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's one about the final thought that you did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, we were talking about Pizza Man, and then you said, no, I said, Al, your table got GTA on my elbow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you said that she got beat up by Pizza Man.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I probably played that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I remember that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you played the Mega Man theme.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Retro.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he's winning more of our older, older, older shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, oh my god, the older shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if you listen to episode one of our original live show, where Loki was talking in a tin can.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my horrible quote show, was the very first show when I talked about the King of Iron Fingering.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that was the first, but it was in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the first.
[SPEAKER_02]: I left the show with such a migraine because I was using that headset.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Those quotes that you put up, dude, you would be our hero if you put them up on a wiki quote.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or just put them on the forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a quote thread on our forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should totally put them up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't necessarily have to be the IRC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, start a new thread on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Show quotes thread.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any other mails?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we have a couple more, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Two more.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's...
[SPEAKER_02]: This is from Sakarina.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi Sakarina, one of our big ol' regulars.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi buddy, one of our Canadian listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to posters on DSMeet, actually it's dsmeet.com slash t slash 3463, UK game retailer chain GAME is selling a third-party headset for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently the headset works with mic-enabled games such as Nintendogs, and mic quality is much better than the one built in the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think UK gamers might want to pick one of these up once Metroid Prime Hunters hits the streets in May for Europeans and March for North American gamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the thing I always hated about Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: People would be talking during full auto and stuff and I can't understand anything because I can't hear the sound effects and music.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if only they had better mics or weren't stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not being stupid does help.
[SPEAKER_02]: We also, the last email comes from Ace Man in Calgary.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like our Canadian listeners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually, I am probably taking a trip to Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm planning on celebrating, I'm taking a vacation.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a me trip, not a work trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last couple weeks was a work trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be taking a me trip.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to celebrate 4th of July in Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to Canada voluntarily?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Vancouver.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to go to Vancouver.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's probably where I'm going.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've never ever left the United States.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it looks like my trip to London next year is getting pushed back again due to money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I really want to go to Canada.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're definitely thinking about doing a 4th of July in Canada just to be ironic.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, there's a link sent to us by Aceman about Yui Bull deciding to not do any more video game movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: and there was much rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually it's a relink to a Eurogamer article about Yui Bull basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a whole interview up there and I'll see if I can't find the link to post in our chat room and maybe repost on our website.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically there's a regarding the feedback that he's received from gamers to quote
[SPEAKER_02]: The dangerous thing right now is that a lot of people bash me without thinking about the movies.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fashionable to hit on you, Abel, and this is what I don't get.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't get why this comes so harshly from the game press.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's another quote on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I won't say I won't acquire another video game license in the future, but I'm not so eager to do it anymore, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: After Far Cry, maybe I'll go away from video game based movies and everybody can be really happy about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we will!
[SPEAKER_09]: Are we supposed to be sympathetic because I'm not?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, he just, you know, I actually clicked on the Eurogamer article.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have some of the best stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But another quote on here says, If people don't see that, then it's not my problem, but I think that those people who hate me or want to bash me, normal people, people who buy movies or watch TV, they see that absolutely.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't you just actually pay attention to what the gamers are telling you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Take it as feedback like any real professional would.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually follow that feedback and put out a quality product instead of taking your own stupid little take on it because you're just screwing it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's why people are bashing you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe if people are bashing you, it's because there's a reason they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not necessarily because, you know, I'm sure one or two people out there are just doing it to be buttheads.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, if you're getting it from the community as a whole... The world, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm focusing on the gaming community.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you're getting this feedback from the gaming community as a whole, why not listen?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you're taking a series that we all, at least chunks of us, love and making a travesty of it
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not do what they're doing with Silent Hill?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're freaking working with Konami on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's what he has to understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: He doesn't get it because he's getting all this people saying that the movie sucks, but he's selling millions and millions of copies on DVD or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's my analogy to the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm under the assumption dog crap probably tastes like dog crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's probably not very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, we know it's bad, but I'm not going to know how bad until I actually chew on a piece of dog crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Same goes with Uebowl's movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they're bad, but I'm not going to subject myself to them to know how bad they really are.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just know that they're so awful that I'm not going to watch them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Worst analogy ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I think the dog crap one is fairly relevant.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com Send us some love.
[SPEAKER_08]: We love to get emails.
[SPEAKER_08]: More interaction to come a little later here in the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, a couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are going to open Skype line very, very, very soon, but not until we get to a story from Loki about Windows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go Windows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Windows will be enhanced with Origami.
[SPEAKER_07]: Windows Vista is going to have a gamer enhanced version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to actually have
[SPEAKER_07]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: GameSummerCamp.com
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura Do I?
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, actually, I know what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft is going to start releasing a $10 best of type deal.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isn't that cool?
[SPEAKER_08]: Best of Platinum Hits is what they're called.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the best of the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: What games?
[SPEAKER_08]: $10 isn't bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there good stuff in there, or am I going to be subjected to Barbie, Paradise, whatever?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some good stuff in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of Tom Clancy stuff, like almost all the old ones, like Ghost Recon, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first Ghost Recon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tony Hawk's Underground, Pro Skater 4, True Crime Streets of LA, Counter Strike, Elder Scrolls 3, Enter the Matrix, that's a pretty decent one, Fusion Frenzy, Mech Assault, Project Gotham 2, Shrek 2, and the one that makes me happy is Soul Calibur 2, which I already own on several systems, but still, Soul Calibur 2, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like one of those things like, just buy it already if you don't have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if they were going to show a lot of love for the listeners, they would actually put out, you know, recreate the Dreamcast fishing controller so that we could do Rod Caliber.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of our listeners may not have heard this.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Dreamcast for Soul Caliber, you can take the fishing rod and play Soul Caliber with the fishing rod controller, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rod Caliber.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are...
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go to the Skype line and we're going to pick up some calls here over on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.orangelongerator.com Click on chat with us or interact with us and you can call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can also pick up the phone and call us 916-226-9067 but please make sure you ask whoever owns the phone line first if you can call because this is a toll call unless you happen to live
[SPEAKER_08]: in Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to the line and pick up a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Holy crap, I made it on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who else would it be?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was my buddy at KatsuCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma's the reason I went to KatsuCon and put up with six people at my panel.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it was great, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a good experience, and I did a lot of networking, which was really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_01]: You gotta come back for 13.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I already told you my D.Va line.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll only do it if my panel's at a certain time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I'll help you out with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, I just want you to know the gifts that you sent along, I just handed out before the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have our matching Mario hats as like a present, a late Christmas present, I guess, to Orange Lounge, or just a present for no real reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got little Mario hats, and I have an S for Sky, a red hat, and then DarkSakura has a pink hat for Princess, DS DarkSakura, and then Loki has an L for, not Luigi, but Loki, and a green hat, and it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we love the hats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm so glad you liked them.
[SPEAKER_08]: What else is on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just came back from playing a couple of rounds of Drunken DDR this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: How'd that go?
[SPEAKER_01]: The drinks weren't as strong as I thought they were, so I really couldn't get drunk per se.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, the only time I ever really played drunk DDR was in Vegas, and I still got, like, this is when DDR was still new, and you would always get a crowd every time you played.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you should have seen the crowd I got playing DDR while drunk.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I just remember, like, when you would do jumps, very heavy the jumps felt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very heavy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: You ever notice when you're playing DDR, you turn around after two songs, you have this entire crowd behind you, and then on your next song, you just fuck up, and then you turn around, people are gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like American Idol or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: You screw up one week, bam, you're voted off.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're just playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_01]: This weekend, I was the only one that could really play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody was just giving me requests.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: and I finally checked out Strike.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I haven't checked it out yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: DDR Strike, which just came out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's your favorite new song in Strike?
[SPEAKER_01]: Everybody's... What's that one song?
[SPEAKER_01]: I must have drank it more than I supposed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't remember the one song I loved the most on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard a lot of good things about the new Akira song.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think I played that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a good song.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doll?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard a lot of good things about Doll.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's Dance, David Bowie.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know that's got to rock.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm so excited about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: That loves me some David Bowie.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to get to other callers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_01]: When is Loki doing more fusions?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, when are you doing more fusion mixes, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't you have a thing on MySpace?
[SPEAKER_08]: You haven't plugged that in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but it doesn't have anything new on it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, still.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of our podcast listeners probably don't even know you do these.
[SPEAKER_07]: MySpace.com slash LokiFusion.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all one word, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, all one word.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been dabbling, but I haven't... The last thing I did was the not-finished version of Legend of Trance 2006 or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was about the last thing I did, and I haven't really done anything since then.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been trying to... I've been fighting writer's block, trying to do something original for that Konami contest thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: See you later!
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, I forgot to mention, tonight on a very special edition of the Skype line, we're going to play Mention the Oscars, Get Hung Up On.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the chat room is lit up with talk about the Oscars right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do know that all those votes are bought, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Oscars don't mean shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want you to know, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're getting Xbox 360s and you're not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they get Xbox 360s?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's completely pure speculation pulled out of my head.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shame on you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so mention the Oscars, get hung up on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tonight on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you there?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're having a hard time hearing you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So sorry, gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be sure to give Echo123 a call and you can always hear what you sound like there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or of course, you can always try the phone number 916-226-9067, which generally has very few problems.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's try another call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, how's it going?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, DMN.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, first, I want to know if you guys have any thoughts on Tetris DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: I cannot wait for Tetris DS because I have very fond memories of Tetris on the Game Boy, and I love that they're just redoing it, and it's going to be the whole, like, ten players locally and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be a good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Great party game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everybody...
[SPEAKER_08]: Any... Tetris is like the... Anybody can play Tetris.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the nice thing about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's such an easily accessible game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's going to make it a lot of fun and get new people on the DS and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I tested it and I had a huge blast with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You tested it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I kind of work over at Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad you're under NDAs or I'd be grilling you for the scoop right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's worth the $30 when it comes out, I guarantee it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome, that's a great tip.
[SPEAKER_08]: What about, I have to ask, Metroid Prime Hunters?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kind of getting mixed feelings on this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you get a chance to check this out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I played the demo, I have the demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: My impressions are that first-person shooters do not work on portables.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Doom on the GBA and it was terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: The demo was just atrocious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's going to do well at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I've got to ask, since you work in the inside, and maybe this is NDA, so feel free to deflect if you must, but do you know something about the revolution that the rest of the world doesn't?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know the same thing you do right now, which is nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't seen it in the department.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going on over there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I might as well plug my anime convention up here.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm the gaming manager of SakuraCon.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's in downtown Seattle.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be March 24th through the 26th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Son of a gun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody's trying to get me to come up to SakuraCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's one of those things where if I can get the time off work, I would go, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's over a weekend, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Different weekend as what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, it's Friday through Sunday, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd be totally stupid to have a con during the week, so I hope so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, tell that to the people who do Anime Expo, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I'd be down for at least a day of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, how can I pass up SakuraCon?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll think of a way to get there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to take some clever plotting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seattle's not that far of a flight from here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to open up the cosplay box and break out the bike and costume.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're also venturing a new part of DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're combining DDR and a game show, so we're going to see how that works out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, if we come up, can we get a panel or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: or is it too late?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a little late, but I could probably see if I could swing you guys in as industry guests or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would rock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk offline.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send us an email, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, no problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and Kennewick because, well, his family lives in Prosser.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so we've been up to Washington State before and we've been sort of thinking about looking for housing in Washington.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right around the corner, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we want to go, we've got to book a flight like this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know my husband wants me and him to move to Washington, which I've said no.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to talk to my friend in Seattle, see what we can cook up.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: No promises.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do one more call.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to go over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Intended Maniac 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm real angry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio doesn't work in Winamp.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio doesn't work in Winamp?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It keeps asking me to log in with my Live365 account.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live365 gives us issues sometimes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you letting the computer retain cookies?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do us a favor.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send Live365 an email.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish there was more we could do on that end, but there's really unfortunately not a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Believe me, though, we are aware, and every time things like this happen, it makes us not want to be there anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, we're kind of stuck for right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm living with Frio Player right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Many people don't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works.
[SPEAKER_08]: I use iTunes sometimes, but the thing is that Winamp is the only way you can get MP3 Pro.
[SPEAKER_08]: Little known fact, the podcast is actually encoded in MP3 Pro.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you listen to the podcast in Winamp with the codec, it actually sounds a lot cleaner.
[SPEAKER_08]: So just a little thought there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, Nintendo Maniac, thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unlike the last guy, I'm actually excited about Metroid Prime Hunters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any particular reason why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well... Online?
[SPEAKER_05]: Multiplayer, maybe?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I need another online player.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just curious if that's going to be as cool as it sounds.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking forward to it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_08]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, thank you guys so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_08]: We appreciate it there.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get back into the news for one last story here tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, first, before I get to the last story, I'll go around and see if there's any last-minute entries here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, because I think I saw you bring up something on the origami.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that like a last-minute addition here?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a picture of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little bit smaller than the concept video that they showed because that video was pretty old.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, I think I could take somebody out with this thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been giving this thing a hard time tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, if I had the money to throw away on something, if I was a business person that made a lot of money,
[SPEAKER_07]: maybe I would check this out but until we hear about some gaming stuff it's still going to be the butt of our jokes sorry yeah anyways um well first thing I gotta mention because this is like a major story we're just kind of glancing over oh sorry DS Lite actually launched in Japan oh yeah I thought you covered it's so pretty I thought you covered this on one of the mini shows yeah well I may have mentioned it but yeah DS Lite launched it's pretty it's bright it's
[SPEAKER_07]: It's everything we had hoped for.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then what else was I going to mention here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, if you like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a nice little knockoff here you can download at www.incitti.com slash blitz and they've got a nice little game you can play here that's a clone of Geometry Wars 3 and also another game called Marble Insanity which is just like Marble Madness and unfortunately that's not available for download yet but it looks really sweet with what they're doing and finally of course Rockstar announced a new game that they're making this week
[SPEAKER_07]: Table Tennis Table Tennis Table Tennis Table Tennis Table Tennis
[SPEAKER_07]: And as I mentioned before, Trauma Center is coming out for the revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's according to the IGN podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you didn't get that joke, by the way, ask your mommy and daddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But don't tell them you heard it here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ubisoft announced that they're going to be releasing a new Rainbow Six game for next-gen consoles, Rainbow Six Vegas.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this has actually come from the brand-new issue of EGM.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it looks pretty sweet so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, Bungie says that I Love Bees 2 is fake.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate viral marketing because viral marketing is not viral anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just no one cares.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's trendy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like before, you know, people didn't know what they were advertising.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just something that's like, whoa, what is this, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: And you try to figure out more information.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like the whole thing with...
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if that could be an announcement for the Splinter Cell for the 360 or whatever, it's just retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just my rant there.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, you have any last stories for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything you've been holding out on?
[SPEAKER_08]: Just wanted to check.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will continue to keep my secrets.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, here, I have something that might interest you.
[SPEAKER_08]: This seems like something you'd get a kick out of because it's Sega-related, and we know you're a Sega fangirl.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is a story that ran on Joystick earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you know that there was a Penn & Teller Sega CD game?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was...
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Penn & Teller Smoke & Mirrors is what it was called.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was never released actually, which is why you've probably never heard of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But get this, there actually is a torrent out there now floating on the internet so you can download it, burn it, and just load it up in the Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's actually a part in this game that the article talks about called the Desert Bus Minigame.
[SPEAKER_08]: You drive a bus in the desert.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your goal is to go from Tucson, Arizona to Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your bus never goes more than 45 miles an hour, so the trip takes approximately 8 hours in real time to make.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no scenery or even other cars on the road, just plain desert for 8 hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and your bus veers to the right just slightly, so it's impossible to just tape down a button and go do something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rumor has it that if you make it to Vegas, you score one point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't wait to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never released.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one more story, but it's quite funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted the last story.
[SPEAKER_07]: French developer Cyanide has launched their online home of their forthcoming action RPG, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not a whole lot of content on the site at the moment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a forum and some screenshots.
[SPEAKER_07]: But my guess is going to be it's based around my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: As exciting as it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Trolls and all.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I just had to point that out because, you know, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: On that egotistical note, it's time to end the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our special guest, Spike, our buddy Spike, thank you so much for being here tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for having me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And laughing at our jokes, which makes us feel good, and praising the almighty Dark Sakura, I noticed, at certain points there during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make my ego grow.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just add Wata.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I'm really excited now to go download this Penn & Teller game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me know how the bus driving goes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Any final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_08]: Quiz and Dragons?
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a challenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're issuing a challenge here.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I can't wait to play some new games this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Burnout and...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess Burnout's not exactly a new game, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I look forward to playing Burnout again.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is the Oscars are a sham.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't you just go watch a movie that looks interesting and not that somebody told you to watch or told you that was good?
[SPEAKER_08]: Make up your own mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: They pay millions of dollars for those ads and variety.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a sham.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go outside.
[SPEAKER_08]: Support independent films too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can watch a big blockbuster once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't forget to go to your local art house cinema because you might be missing something good.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: From us here at Orange Lounge Radio to all of you, thanks so much for joining us back here after our little break.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thanks for not forgetting about us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Support independent podcasts.
[SPEAKER_08]: HelloAllGames.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're very happy to be here.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: you've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production for more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com see you next week