[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight, March 12th, 2006, the PSP gets a facelift, Guitar Hero 2 is announced, and we talk about some of the best games never released.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio Hello everybody and welcome to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio, this being episode number 176 of
[SPEAKER_05]: for this March the 12th of 2006
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, my name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's frustrating?
[SPEAKER_05]: You were in such a good mood just like two minutes ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wasn't in a good mood because your mocha attacked me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do appreciate the... I'm chocolatey good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, now you smell like chocolate, so... I smelled like cherries before.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd rather.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, chocolate-covered cherries is a delicacy in some places.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello also to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing great.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once in a while, we like to invite somebody special to come on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to our local buddy, Bugged.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just special now?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you're very special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bugged has known me for how long?
[SPEAKER_05]: How long have you known me, Bugged?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't admit this.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then I'll say it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably been at least... 17 years?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I guess it has been 10 years since high school.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's why I didn't want to... Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of our listeners are 17, even younger than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well... I'll go get the canes.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: I quit school to play video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Way to set an example for those 17-year-olds listening.
[SPEAKER_00]: I dropped a class due to time constraints.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've played Animal Crossing and Puzzle Fighter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puzzle Fighter?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that's an oldie but goodie.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we've had some burnout going on in the house, and I've been avoiding it like the plague.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why?
[SPEAKER_00]: Because that game gives me a headache.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, because of all the motion and stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, because of the really loudness that Dan has our TV turned up to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puzzle Fighter Puzzle Fighter Puzzle Fighter
[SPEAKER_00]: That made me twitch because it just made me realize that, yes, I am older than you are.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not by much.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because what I was playing in college was the Saturn had just come out and my friend imported one and we were playing Gundam.
[SPEAKER_00]: If it makes you feel better, that was like... KOF 95 and I had a PlayStation in my room and we were playing Toshinden all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it makes you feel better, this was like...
[SPEAKER_05]: My junior year.
[SPEAKER_05]: My freshman year was all about Super Mario Kart because I was the only kid in the dorm with a Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: I had a Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_00]: And by the way, you're making me cry because of next month.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're also one of the few that were sober.
[SPEAKER_00]: My birthday is next month.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, but you're having a big birthday extravaganza, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where I get so drunk I forget that it's my birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this year you might need that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But don't we still love you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Age is just a number.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, how's your gaming week been?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Been playing both the new Burnout, well, not quite new Burnout, new to the Xbox 360 Burnout, and Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Burnout hasn't really changed.
[SPEAKER_03]: They made it a lot blurrier and, I guess, higher resolution textures, but everything's so blurry and dark, it's, I don't know, it's tough sometimes finding out where you're going.
[SPEAKER_00]: Headache-inducing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not headache-inducing, but just, you know, trying to see down like a tunnel where you're driving 200 miles an hour and everything's like I got cataracts or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just not good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like what they're doing with these games where they're putting this like halo effect on everything so to, you know, to hide the fact that the textures aren't quite as good as they should be and the edges aren't quite as smooth as they should be.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listen, we know that
[SPEAKER_03]: you know the case is that these textures aren't as good or the graphics aren't as good you don't need to try to hide it by making everything blurry don't pull a Nintendo 64 now I'm curious how does
[SPEAKER_05]: Burnout is more racing, whereas Full Auto is more blowing stuff up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, they do have crash mode in Burnout.
[SPEAKER_05]: Burnout lacks weapons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, you don't have weapons.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, for some reason, the burnout on the 360 is a lot harder than I remember being on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you smash in the cars and they just do not want to crash.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really, you know, the AI is a lot harder this time, which I guess is good.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, the crash junctions are still fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the graphics are a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_03]: The car models are more detailed, so you see more damage being done to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's not like, ooh, this is a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm waiting for the next burnout to come out, and that'll be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm willing to take donations of Xbox 360s, Burnout, and FlatOut to make all these... Full auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever the hell the thing's called.
[SPEAKER_07]: FlatOut sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just FlatOut sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: FlatOut 2's coming out soon as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can I say about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is probably one of the killer apps for the 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only problem is the learning curve is incredibly high.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, I have never played a Ghost Recon game in my life and I tried this today.
[SPEAKER_03]: now granted it's very pretty and stuff and I kind of got the you know handle of how to work things but actually throwing me down into missions is about as effective as throwing me down into a mission in Call of Duty 2 on veteran mode and basically it's like you know walking into the Iraq war without any training and hoping to survive it's just not I don't know it could be fun I really need to like get better at it but the game itself looks amazing just
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole story part where you're flying over Mexico City, it's just wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then on top of that, of course, I've been playing Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm very excited that they're going to be releasing a new Grand Theft Auto on the PSP soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Liberty City Stories is supposed to be coming out on the PlayStation 2 at the end of April.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully we'll have online multiplayer with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and it says the number of races hasn't gone up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So nothing's counting.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm wasting my damn time on this stupid thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that because people are dropping before the race is actually finished?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what the case is, but there is a big problem with people dropping out of the races in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Half the players drop out at the very end.
[SPEAKER_03]: You ever leave them negative feedback?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: People randomly boot me from games in Marble Blast.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's not like I'm any good, so I don't know why they're booting me from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even have a headset, so it's not like I can trash talk them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they boot me from the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I leave them negative feedback when they do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, a lot of times it's hard for me to remember who's dropped out of the game because they're not going to appear at the very end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to get the last few achievements in full auto.
[SPEAKER_03]: And those are the online ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm up to rank 8 right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I only have two more to go, but it's really hard when it's not counting half the races that you're playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could be playing it for three hours and only count two races.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they really need to fix this kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get into this later about how these games are coming out really glitchy and buggy, and they're just letting it go to market real quick because they can fix it later by patching it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just a poor excuse of programming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bugged, anything in your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, actually I started up Diablo 2 again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I started up Diablo 2 again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And been bringing up old characters that I've found laying around on other old CDs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there still a big online community for Diablo 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't play online?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes I'll play with other local people, set up Hamachi to do local network sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: With Hamachi, it looks like everybody's on the same network.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't touched Diablo 2 in probably years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever played World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: To me, there's a lot of similarities.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't do subscription games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That whole lack of funding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever thought about Guild Wars?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because Guild Wars isn't subscription-based.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's not World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll stick to Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely no fucking Final Fantasy shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what's funny about Final Fantasy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know you two are going back into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shane's trying to get me back into Final Fantasy XI and I think I'm going to do it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're gonna start over on a new server.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, though, you going back to that actually reminds me, I did do something else gaming-related.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm downloading Ragnarok Online again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to be playing Ragnarok Online on a private server.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that sad that we've all gone back to the crack games that we used to play?
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't go back to World of Warcraft until after I get finances sold, so, like, well, crap.
[SPEAKER_00]: I need gaming crack.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I'm actually still paying for PSO Blueburst, and I forgot...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna be playing, I'll play PSO So you have to pay for live plus PSO?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you're Julie She hasn't had to, they haven't billed her
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks to the new setup on Xbox 360, I think games like Final Fantasy XI, that won't apply.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's the whole Xbox Live Silver and Xbox Live Gold.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you don't pay for Silver.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silver comes with your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Silver is enough to get your account and your basics and see who's online and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can't actually play games against people.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Silver is all you need to connect to play online.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then you pay Sony to do their thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like Windows XP.
[SPEAKER_07]: In a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you can get online, but you can't do shit until you actually buy the real stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're going to see a lot of connectivity between Windows Vista, especially, and the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's just very natural that Microsoft's going to try and interlink all that best we can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're already trying to link the Media Center Edition 2005 version.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the ads for the Gateway machines coming out with that are listing.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you look at the bottom, it says compatible with Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know I saw some link on the internet somewhere where you can link your Mac to the Xbox 360 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was going to check that out for my new little lappy laptop, Mr. iBook.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I'm probably going to get back into Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least I'm going to try it and see if I can rediscover my love for the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know I left the game because the Gil selling thing got out of control and they banned all those people, so
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to give it another shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to try... I am really curious about this expansion that's coming out for Final Fantasy XI, The Treasures of Odd Organ, especially because now they have the Puppet Masterclass, which looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just added this week, announced, and you know, Blue Mage, and Shane's really excited about being a pirate, so he's trying to convince me to get back into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Corsair, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's trying to convince me to get back into it, and I'm like, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Buck Pirate, Rectal Buccaneer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's see, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing a little bit of Xbox 360, Loki loaned me some games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing Perfect Dark Zero, which I just, I'm sorry, I couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see why people really enjoy this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, as far as first-person shooters go, it is pretty intricate and a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: RIDGERACER 6
[SPEAKER_05]: Ridge Racer Cameo
[SPEAKER_05]: The first time I played it, it was all like really overwhelming to me, like that first level that you have to go through.
[SPEAKER_05]: But once you beat that level, like there's a story event that happens that kind of makes you start again from scratch.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I felt that was kind of a better way to kind of start the game for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of learning everything from scratch.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was easier for me to get into when I wasn't like overwhelmed with everything at once.
[SPEAKER_05]: But to the game's credit, it's got a pretty good help system in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you can always ask your little, like,
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like in Zelda, you know how that fairy follows you, and you can always ask the fairy for help?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, in this one, it's a little dude that's in the book, and you can always ask the book for help.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, it helps idiots like me find their way through the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of like Partners in Time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sure a lot of games adapt this same idea now, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm enjoying that game and just other stuff on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have probably downloaded damn near every game they offer on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get Backgammon or Hearts or any of that crap, but I did get... I got Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did I buy Bejeweled?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, because I'm a sucker, and I wanted to play it in pretty, pretty HD.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to see if I could get some more achievement points, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bejeweled has harder achievement points than any game I've seen on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, you have to be a Bejeweled master to get achievement points in that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: The best bet for achievement points, and I was reading, they actually have this article that's on GameSpot right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's how to score 6,000 easy achievement points.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's sports games are where you get the freaking easy-ass points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to our chat room, www.orangeslaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Click on chat, reading some feedback here in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: GK128 says, Cameo is terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I'd call it terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it as good as Zelda?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it even as good as Fable?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But is it entertaining for me for a little while?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it worth $60?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and you have to use these gems.
[SPEAKER_00]: That just illustrates something to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_00]: That when people say, oh this sucks, say specifically why so that people have some idea what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, some of the dialogue in the game is a little lame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like they have these real lame jokes, like you said, like the old guy in the book and the little witch with one eye or whatever have this little back and forth thing going on, but it's really like canned humor.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like canned sitcom laughter type jokes.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: So honestly, you put a game like Cameo next to a Zelda or next to a better type of adventure game, and it is kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you have to remember, it's a launch title, and launch titles usually, unless you're Nintendo, aren't your best games.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of my favorite games ever that was a launch title was Jumping Flash.
[SPEAKER_00]: on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I don't even remember that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a little mechanical rabbit.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I played the hell out of the demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing about Cameo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cameo's more like Spyro than it is like Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were trying to position it to be like a Zelda killer, and no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, isn't it more like the Banjo-Kazooie or Banjo-Tooie or whatever?
[SPEAKER_07]: Which was just made to exist, not necessarily be good.
[SPEAKER_00]: The one thing that they need to keep in mind is that when you're trying to come up with a game that's going to go against the big names, not only do they have quality to worry about, they also have reputation to worry about.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I'm sorry, nothing's going to really dethrone the Zelda franchise, the Final Fantasy franchise, the Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_05]: Besides itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was reading in the chat room before the show started a lot of hate going around for Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy Mystic Quest Final Fantasy Mystic Quest Final Fantasy USA
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that just, I could have sworn I read that somewhere and I'm like, that just makes us look bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: I tried playing, well, then again, our Super Mario 2 was out over there, Super Mario USA.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it had already existed over there in, what, Doki Doki Panic, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: But differently, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it wasn't Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's amazing what a little Italian plumber can do for your game, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: But also keep in mind, though, that a lot of times when we get the RPGs over here, they repackage it for Japan as the international version because it's got more stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Square does that an awful lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think about 10 and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what we're here to do, let you guys know what's going on in the gaming world and bitch about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, we're going to start off with you tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's something some PSP owners might bitch about.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: They redesigned the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not surprising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it's something we've been talking about for weeks now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's just kind of, you know, I don't know, not very surprising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, this comes from Any Cool News.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's this guy, Joseph Merrick, who's saying that he's got the insider information about their new PSP system, including that it's going to be a more sleeker, slimmed-down version of the PSP, including a 4GB flash drive and a digital camera.
[SPEAKER_03]: No word on what the price is going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: How Nintendo of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's supposed to be released around Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this Sony doing a knee-jerk reaction to the insanity of the DS Lite in Japan?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so, but here's the thing about the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless you're pirating games to the memory stick, I don't know why you would need more than a gig.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: 4 gigs 4 gigs 4 gigs
[SPEAKER_03]: It's facing the user, so it would be used as a webcam.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're watching you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is kind of stupid, but obviously I'm sure that's going to be fixed later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see the real need for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, a 4 gig hard drive in there as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it going to be a hard drive or flash?
[SPEAKER_03]: Flash.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be probably a micro drive or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Micro drive is hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: NAND flash drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: That makes more sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because adding another rotating media just sucks more battery life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to come out sometime around Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully the PS3 will be coming out at the same time because I heard they're having a lot of trouble with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they going to do different colors and all that stuff too?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure they'll do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have white and black right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll probably come out with some
[SPEAKER_03]: Other colors that can get blue, pink.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I've been a little tough on the PSP lately, but it does sound like there are some good new stuff coming out for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially game-wise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully with this new PSP, they'll come out with a second goddamn analog stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like they friggin' need on this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't want them to change it that radically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because now me having a first-gen PSP who's not really interested in upgrading, I'd be totally screwed if games started supporting it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like the whole Xbox 360 hard drive thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've got a core with no hard drive, you're going to get screwed in some of these later releases when people require it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, look at the games that came out for the late PlayStation stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: They supported only the DualShock 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you didn't buy a DualShock controller, you're fucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, that's going to be the case with this.
[SPEAKER_03]: They needed to have a goddamn second analog stick on this because you try, you know, controlling, I don't know, say for example in Katamari, you try controlling your Katamari, the four buttons, doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not as good as an analog stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need another analog stick on there because it'll just be so much better for a lot, especially if they're first person shooter games that they have coming out for this, it'd be a whole lot better.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII Final Fantasy XII
[SPEAKER_05]: The Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time, Soul Calibur, Vagrant Story, Zelda The Wind Waker, and Nintendogs
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Have they played Vagrant Story?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's not that great of a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, but maybe we have that whole audience in Japan versus audience in the US.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I played Vagrant Story.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't that good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Famitsu begs to differ with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, of course, this score is now just building more and more excitement amongst the fanboys that, you know, OMG, this game's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, do you know when Final Fantasy XII slated for the US?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: It keeps getting juggled around.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't have a date.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, like, when Advent Children comes out?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, around that same time?
[SPEAKER_00]: Around the same time.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, that's the same time we get the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Advent Children is in April.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before the apocalypse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, obviously before Christmas, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got to come out before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: We know at least that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Christmas, what year?
[SPEAKER_05]: What decade?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, another very popular franchise would be, well, anything made by Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what's Miyamoto getting?
[SPEAKER_03]: He's getting knighted by the French.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not sure if that's more of a compliment or a...
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, now watch it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We might have listeners in France.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be careful.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like wearing some one-up shirt and he has the Zelda sword and shield.
[SPEAKER_03]: He just looks like a dumbass, but it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's just so happy and childish.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Kojima, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or not Kojima, Miyamoto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I was thinking of another upcoming story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Miyamoto, though, because he's always so animated, like whenever you see him.
[SPEAKER_00]: I bumped into him at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you survived?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, and I survived.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't fall down?
[SPEAKER_07]: I bumped into Kojima too, the year before I've been touched by fame I'm a Silent Hill
[SPEAKER_00]: We were doing an interview that never recorded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't remind me about the lost interview at Konami booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's move on to another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go over to DarkSakura, who has a story about the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a little program out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a freeware called Pointy Remote, where you can use your DS to control your computer.
[SPEAKER_00]: I personally haven't tried it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm not about to go opening up my DS or anything.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it lets you use the touchpad to select icons to zoom in.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's actually on oneemulation.com there's a thread actually going on about it for anyone who wants to check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's
[SPEAKER_00]: It looks like it's still very experimental.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're still working on it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looks cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: I honestly don't think that I would ever bother doing anything like that with my DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think you have to open it up, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: All you'd have to do is just reflash it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't feel like doing anything to my DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm still busy playing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, my DS is a holy object that cannot be violated by the hands of man.
[SPEAKER_00]: It actually will be using the Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you could actually, in theory, take it out and use it elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I don't think I would do anything with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: They should, though, have a similar device, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they could make a lot of money with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on, let's go over to Loki for some updates regarding Midway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some news on the newest Mortal Kombat, hopefully?
[SPEAKER_03]: Midway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got some news actually for Midway, Namco, and Ubisoft, so it should be good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first, of course, is coming from Midway's Gamer Day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was unaware that everyone had their own Gamer Day, but I guess they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, some of the titles that they've announced, they're coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first one being...
[SPEAKER_03]: MLB Slugfest 2006
[SPEAKER_03]: which is going to be actually a budget game coming out in about 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty cool for PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, they have some info on the new Mortal Kombat Armageddon which is basically going to contain every single Mortal Kombat character in the Mortal Kombat universe plus a creative fighter and creative fatality mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: and then for your PSP fans they of course have Mortal Kombat Unchained or Mortal Kombat Deception Unchained which is kind of an update to the original Deception game of course with bonus characters including Katana, Jax, Frost, Blaze, Goro and Shao Kahn as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then of course if you're an NBA fan NBA Ballers Phenom which also goes with NBA Ballers Rebound for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those kind of
[SPEAKER_03]: A different take on the basketball games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you have to kind of become a star in a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you get noticed by both sports agents and talent agents.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what's kind of funny is they had one mini game in this that's kind of like DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're dancing with mascots.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rampage Total Destructions
[SPEAKER_03]: on top of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus, it includes the original Rampage game and Rampage World Tour that came out on PlayStation 2 a while back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a big fan of any Rampage games since the original MSA.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also under $20.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're not a huge fan of it, at least it's not that expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe a rental.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, their big title for this year is going to be The Spy Hunter, No Where to Run, of course, featuring The Rock and with the movie coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that risky?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I don't see that movie doing very well, but of course, now that I said that, it'll probably be huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a good action movie, put it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Doom did pretty well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It did?
[SPEAKER_03]: It did okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to do better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it certainly did better than House of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's leave it that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Strangehold, a third-person kung fu cinematic game
[SPEAKER_03]: which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, all done with Midway here, let's move on to Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ubisoft is going to have a ton of stuff coming out in the Tom Clancy series.
[SPEAKER_03]: First being Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Vegas which is coming out on both PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 and The Revolution as well as PC and PSP and probably current gen stuff as well, I'm assuming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon 4
[SPEAKER_03]: Firehawk
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never really heard of Firehawks, so that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Assassin, coming out also on all the next-gen systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: One that I was really excited about, Luminous 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray, me too, very excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: PSP and PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big kisses.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then a couple other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's Rayman 4 coming out on the next-gen systems and PlayStation 2 and handhelds.
[SPEAKER_03]: and the new Might and Magic game, Dark Messiah of Might and Magic on the next-gen systems and PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dear Luminous Creators, online versus K-Thanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Finally, Namco's lineup, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got actually next month Ace Combat Zero coming out if you're an Ace Combat fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Me and my Katamari coming out later this year, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snoopy and the Red Baron coming out fall of this year, which is going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only next-gen game they had coming out this year is Frame City Killer, and that's been delayed numerous times.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's now slated for around July, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course, Pac-Man fans...
[SPEAKER_03]: Pac-Man World Rally Warhammer Mark of Chaos
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots and lots of goodies coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're now in that period of the year, especially building up to E3, where we're going to hear a lot of flood of just game announcements.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got another one for you guys, and this is kind of a duh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we all knew this was coming, but Guitar Hero 2 has been for all purposes confirmed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kelly Sumner, who's the CEO of Red Octane, has said, We are working on Guitar Hero 2, which will have 40 plus new tracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: I think a lot of us were waiting for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the part that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: He also says that there's going to be genre spin-offs like country rock, metal edition, and possibly even doing a plug-and-play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know how they have those joysticks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what if you just bought a guitar?
[SPEAKER_05]: No PlayStation needed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plug a guitar right into the TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: That worries me a little bit because now I'm going, uh-oh, is this too much of a good thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can oversaturation destroy...
[SPEAKER_03]: Guitar Hero, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Depends on how they do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they do it like, if it's exactly like Guitar Hero, you know, just as good, then maybe it might work, but no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of worried about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of too bad for Red Octane that Guitar Hero wasn't an Xbox title because then they could be doing these expansions through live.
[SPEAKER_05]: But,
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess PlayStation 2 doesn't really allow that same type of thing, so I guess this is what they have to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, have we ever really had games here that use the append idea like they did in Japan with some of the Beat Manias, where you have appendists?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's something that they can do, and this is kind of a brand new thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did it with SOCOM, with downloadable maps.
[SPEAKER_03]: You pay a fee online, I believe it's $5, and you download the maps to a USB card.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if you have a USB memory card or something like that, then you plug that into your PlayStation 2 and it unlocks the maps and it downloads to the hard drive type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, that's a lot of factors that don't really bode well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, the PS2 Slim doesn't have a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not everyone has a USB memory stick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not everyone's willing to pay for this and download it off the internet type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comments from the chatroom, www.orangeloungeradio.com We have Wolfwind Shadow says, do an 80s version on Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be like hair rock power ballads.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy just won the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to see early 90s music as well, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want my Nelson, my Poison, my damn Yankees.
[SPEAKER_00]: Motley Crue, Tesla.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's just do Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just need Guitar Hero Ted Nugent for Guitar Hero Queen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heck yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All Queen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, they have one Queen song in the... No, we need a Guitar Hero J-Rock version to go out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_00]: Think we'll ever see Guitar Freaks?
[SPEAKER_00]: DDR Supernova
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, now they're doing location testing in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot more songs have been added to the location test, including some of our old favorites here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our new Captain Jack, Centerfold, the 130 BPM Move It remix, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They also feature some Doesn't Really Matter by Janet Jackson.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kaimano, Love at First Sight, Twin Master Plan Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some pretty big names there, Janet and Kylie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Wookiee Wookiee by Macho Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, and for every big name there's got to be a what the F is this, alright?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought that was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it De Capo by Ace of Base?
[SPEAKER_05]: De Capo, I think it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: De Capo, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Golden Sky by SmileDK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Return of Small Decay My Only Shining Star by Naoki featuring Becky Lucinda
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Shouting the lyrics to the song, and it's exactly like your D2R, really for you type things.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I listened to the song once, and I'm like, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Naoki fans will be fine with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's exactly 1998 or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you like that superhero beat stuff, great.
[SPEAKER_03]: D to the A to the N to the C
[SPEAKER_03]: Extra Stages are kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: On top of Fascination Max, they also have Healing D-Vision by D-Stard, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which I'm sure is just another Naoki pseudonym, honestly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the one more Extra Stage is Chaos by Desire Returns.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that'll make people happy, because Desire did Trip Machine, and I think it was a big Healing Vision and all that stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: So that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm happy to hear a new Healing Vision song and Chaos sounds good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fascination Max sucks so bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at least they're giving you options now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have to play that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it sucks so bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, I thought that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we know that we have a lot of fans out there who grew up with us on the music games, but of course we talk about all the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: We want to open up the floor right now for your feedback, and you can give us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're on the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Username is Orange Lounge Radio, or you can actually pick up the phone and call us, 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo Maniac 64 Hello Nintendo Maniac 64, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I want to give a shout out to uh Shout out!
[SPEAKER_04]: To who?
[SPEAKER_04]: Carissa Gregory Okay, why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, because I hope she's listening in because like I referred her to the show here and I just hope she's listening in Is this a special friend?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just a friend in general Okay, just, you know, I had to check
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you guys are talking about, like, cars with guns and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you want a game with cars with guns, like, play Battle Mode and Rush 2049.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't played it, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: What makes this game so great compared to Burnout and Full Auto and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, think Mario Kart Battle Mode, except you actually have guns mounted on top of your cars, and you literally are shooting each other and blowing each other up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that sounds like Full Auto to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Full Auto's pretty much the same thing, except you get mines and all that fun stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, he's saying Rush 2049?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought they didn't have guns in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, he said Battle Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Battle Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Battle Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same game, just different mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, obviously, this is a very popular genre of games, as cars with guns and destruction is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm all for it, because honestly, if I can take out my aggressions on the Xbox and I don't do it for real when I see those old ladies driving the SUVs that can't stay in one lane and all that fun stuff...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: You're so awful!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, just messing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo Maniac, any other feedback, hellos you want to say before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not really sure if my MP...
[SPEAKER_05]: MP3 Pro will only work in Winamp, it doesn't work in iTunes, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I'm using Winamp.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not going to hear too much of a difference this time at the 64K, it's really good either way.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you have it installed and you have it selected and ready to go, you should be set.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I have one last question?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, does it affect regular MP3s too?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not unless you purposely save your MP3s as MP3 Pro.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some programs like Adobe Audition will allow you to encode an MP3 Pro right away, but you're probably not going to notice much of a difference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go to another call here on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Wolf Windshadow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Wolf Windshadow!
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're the one that wanted the 80s Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, I grew up in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_05]: We did, too, and we were just talking about how old we feel tonight, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We need an old-school Aerosmith loving an elevator.
[SPEAKER_05]: How fun would that be on Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, not too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just run into your show for the first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome, how'd you find us?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just randomly searching for places that use Skype.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty unique.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'm going to say, we were, and I'm going to make a claim here, and somebody will probably dispute that, but we were honestly one of the first online radio stations to back Skype instead of a Skype line, because we've been doing Skype for a long, long time, and now it's really catching on, but, you know, we're happy to have pioneered the Skype line thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I'm a computer consultant.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have it up on my website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you sound great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should have guessed you were a former Skype user because sometimes we have first-timers on Skype that don't sound so great.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're really glad that we got random people connecting to our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: What kind of games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, not too many this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting ready to go back to school and finish up my degree.
[SPEAKER_05]: Real life's got to come first sometimes, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sadly, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sometimes you have to cut classes how to accommodate life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, if you didn't have to be going back to school, what game would you be checking out right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I'd be checking out some of the games with cars and guns.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a big thing right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you a burnout man or a full auto man?
[SPEAKER_02]: Full auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any particular reason why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really, just interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you actually get guns on your car in full auto, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Wolf, Wind, Shadow, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, not tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually enjoying the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_05]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love getting new listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, tell a friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help support independent online radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give us money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not asking for money yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks so much, Wolf, Wind, Shadow, for tuning in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Write Red Octane and tell them your idea for the 80s Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it should happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go to another call here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go, we'll pick up this line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, turn down your speakers because we're hearing ourselves pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it good now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we're okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, I kind of joined in a bit late, but I heard Loki talking about a song that he just hated.
[SPEAKER_01]: What song was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I know it's on the new mix.
[SPEAKER_01]: What song was he talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fascination Max, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you just trying to get me to hate you?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I'm a Mac user.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Fascination Max.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you just trying to get me to hate you?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a Mac user and he loves Fascination Max.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's just the anti-Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got bad taste in music and computing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I can tell you right now that Loki does not blow up in the presence of Max because there's one pointing directly at him.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's one redeeming quality, the PSP homebrew.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, diversity makes the world go round, my friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes we're just going to have to agree to disagree.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think when Loki goes to hell, it's going to be like an Apple store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Flat panel iMacs everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just thought of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think they're going to have a dedication to Captain Jack on Supernova?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ray Charles?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ray Charles is in DDR and there was no real... Wait, Ray Charles?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he still alive?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: He died last year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you see how much I follow the entertainment news?
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ, really, only time will tell.
[SPEAKER_05]: 17 years of this crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: What would you do if you were Konami?
[SPEAKER_05]: How would you pay your respects to Captain Jack, who passed away last year?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, probably have a little picture before the pre-game animation saying, this is dedicated to Captain Jack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they have that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You haven't seen it?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know who the hell it is, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Some guy, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some doctor.
[SPEAKER_00]: They can show his picture and do R.I.P., you know, birth date, death date.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think if they did something really lovely with the background, I think that would be appropriate, so when people played the song, they could, you know, why are you laughing?
[SPEAKER_07]: They do it like Pixar, where Pixar, at the end of the credits, has babies that were born during the production of the film.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could have people that have died in the production of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really morbid, but... They could put, you know, Captain Jack, my soul.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, SSJ100, Matt, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Our profit margins?
[SPEAKER_05]: Roxer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing really.
[SPEAKER_06]: I managed to actually get a sneak peek of a video game movie that's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called Staying Alive.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what's it about?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not that movie with John Travolta, was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not Staying Alive, it's called... Stay Alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Stay Alive.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the one where the kids play the game and when they die in the game, they die in real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw a trailer.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not necessarily a video game movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more of a really crappy movie that they based around... It's capitalizing on the violent game culture.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: You saw it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, no, I didn't really...
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't really see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was at an old school.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went to visit it and I visited the video game section.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were giving them sneak peeks of the gameplay in the movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: The movie itself looks like Nightmare on Elm Street meets Ring.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you die in the game, you die in real life.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's nonsense like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it something that you will probably want to see?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that kid from Malcolm in the Middle in it?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, actually, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the guy from... I think he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: The guy who was in Hebrew Hammer, I'm not sure if anyone knows that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Adam Goldberg.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Goldberg.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn, you beat me to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just that good, Bugged.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should know after 17 years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but I saw in the trailer, this shouldn't be much of a spoiler because you see it in the trailer, he dies, which means his role isn't that big.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, obviously not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well we'll see when the movie comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Much like Scream.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll have an OLR at the movie day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, SSJ1Hermat, thank you so much for calling.
[SPEAKER_05]: Appreciate it as always, bud.
[SPEAKER_05]: You too.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: Nope, there's going to be no online mode for Virtua Fighter, which actually I don't really care about Virtua Fighter, but I just thought it was pretty funny that they were even trying.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hiroshi Kataoka, who was the...
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess big guy behind Virtua Fighter told EGM basically that they tried to do it online by simulating lag and timing and that it wasn't really going to do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: It changed the gameplay way too much.
[SPEAKER_00]: To quote, if we ever wanted to do an online fighting game, it would have to be something besides Virtua Fighter.
[SPEAKER_00]: So maybe that's a hint at something else, but for right now, no online mode.
[SPEAKER_00]: Awww.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know many people that are Virtua Fighter fans above all else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know people that like Virtua Fighter, but they also like Dead or Alive or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know plenty of people who are diehard Virtua Fighter fans who have been since day one.
[SPEAKER_00]: My bias against Virtua Fighter starts from day one because the game gave me massive headaches.
[SPEAKER_00]: and so I just never got into playing it too much and then I found my love for Tekken.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, can you actually be a fan of both Virtua Fighter and Tekken?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I'm sure you could.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I'm not, but anyone can, it just depends on what you like.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't see why you have to hate one thing to like the other.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, wasn't Virtua Fighter kind of the response to Tekken?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, Virtua Fighter was out, if I do recall, before Tekken.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Virtua Fighter 32X
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_00]: Virtua Racing had the humongous Genesis cartridge.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Virtua Fighter was on Genesis, if I do recall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me do a quick bit of research.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it was either on Genesis or 32X.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they put out a crap version on Genesis is what it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it was really awful.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Tekken didn't make it to the home until PlayStation was out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it still has a promo pack for my Saturn that has Virtua Fighter 2?
[SPEAKER_00]: Virtua Fighter 2 was one of the pack-in games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, with Daytona and something else I forgot that I don't play.
[SPEAKER_00]: Christmas Nights?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Christmas Nights was a mail-in thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Knight in our chatroom says, Saturn first, then 32X, then Genesis, but they're kind of going back and forth a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, because the 32X version was out before the Saturn was out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to figure it out right now in chat, so, I mean, honestly, it's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, because I had a 32X.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, well, I would trade back and forth my Nintendo and 32X with somebody, and he had Virtual Fighter on 32X.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I have the game now on 32X, but... Zaku in our chatroom, Legend of Zaku, says 32X is the worst add-on ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you agree?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, because of Knuckles Chaotix and Calibri.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you can play Knuckles Chaotix on a GameTap, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like Knuckles Chaotix, because who remembers... If anyone is into emulation, there was a game called Sonic Crackers, which, from what I understand, was the template for what Knuckles Chaotix became.
[SPEAKER_00]: Colibri was a really cool game we played as a little hummingbird.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, I played that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the best home version of Space Harrier, apart from the re-releases, was on 32X and Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Colibri on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It made no sense to me at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a freaky little weird game, but it's cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: But no, the best versions of Space Harrier and Afterburner were on 32X.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on to another topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to talk about the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on to a new platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have a 360 but somehow haven't bought Xbox Live Gold, you're going to get your chance to sample what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming up at the end of the month, March 31st through April 2nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only in the US though, sorry listeners in UK, Japan, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Verizon is going to be sponsoring this.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be giving Xbox Live Gold to everybody for the weekend and also giving away 1 million points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not all at once, but you can collect your 500 free Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not sure how.
[SPEAKER_05]: I imagine it's going to involve selling your soul to Verizon in one way or another, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at the dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: March 31st to April 2nd.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's right in the middle.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're advertising it on Xbox Live right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't think it's an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_07]: The points are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're also going to have some tournaments.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know one of them was for Geometry Wars, which I think is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, sure, it's corporate, but it's nice to see something different happening and some little promotions going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, if you happen to purchase a copy of Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter, you get 48 hours of free Xbox Live Gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a card in there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But most likely, if you bought that game, you probably already have Xbox Live Gold anyways, because it's
[SPEAKER_03]: Virtua Fighter Saturn, June 95, Virtua Fighter 32X, November 95
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll settle this right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Street Fighter is greater than everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: What's Nintendo cooking up, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're cooking up a new game here for the revolution, and this is actually a
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the good kind of scare for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: So kind of like, you know, think Silent Hill to an extent, you know, because I know Silent Hill is pretty bloody.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, definitely things like, for example, they'll use the Revolution Controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can use it as a torch to scare away rats or to slit the throat of...
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not gory at all
[SPEAKER_03]: That actually was done.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eternal Darkness
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Parties
[SPEAKER_03]: There's really not anything killer coming out for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only other thing lined up for it is the next Zelda Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love me some Nintendo, but I think the GameCube is slowly fading to black, which is sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's go on to another story.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you play one too many of these survival horror games, you might just start going crazy and have to go into a recovery program.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, the gaming industry, there's been a suggestion on the internet lately for a recovery program of its own.
[SPEAKER_05]: Correct, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_00]: There was actually, I brought up a 12-step self-esteem recovery program at the game marketing conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now this isn't for gamers though, it's for the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_00]: The gaming industry, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the gaming industry has been kind of one-two punched by the government a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_00]: So number one, promote the rating system.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, there's a good rating system by the ESRB, so make sure people know how it works.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well deserving of being the number one spot.
[SPEAKER_00]: Two, evangelize the benefits of video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, it actually references a book, Everything Bad is Good for You.
[SPEAKER_05]: But mom, it helps my hand-eye coordination!
[SPEAKER_05]: Vaguely.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, just to go ahead and read this out, video games involve data pattern recognition and tracking multiple characters and multiple storylines, sustained concentration, complex problem solving, they're interactive, they're not passive like music or reading, there's more open-ended gameplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, especially with puzzle games, that article that I had brought up last year was saying how those who played more video games had overall better problem solving skills than non-gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: out of their control group.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number three, do more quantitative research with leading universities to prove the positive impact of video gaming and qualify any negatives.
[SPEAKER_00]: They need to share the good and the bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: 4.
[SPEAKER_00]: Publicize that history shows we never embrace new media.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is true for silent movies, radio, pulp magazines, comic books, and every new music wave, including Mozart.
[SPEAKER_00]: Video games are not the devil incarnate and not capable of half the devil tree our critics claim for them.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's a quote from there, by the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Number five, preach moderation and promote good parenting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Remind parents moderation in all things, including video games, is important.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're responsible as parents to oversee this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Amen!
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_00]: What site is this coming from?
[SPEAKER_00]: This is actually from Next Generation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, this is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is pretty smart.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_00]: Six, benchmark against sex and violence in Prime Network TV and movies.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think video games have cornered the market on sex and violence.
[SPEAKER_00]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's funny that they showed a slide of David Hasselhoff in a Speedo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they suggesting that the gaming industry run essentially like a political ad smear campaign would be?
[SPEAKER_05]: Try to run a campaign that says games are not as evil as movies?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of how I read that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, keep in mind that
[SPEAKER_00]: Watching the news, how many violent acts do you see or hear about just watching the news?
[SPEAKER_05]: True, but the politicians are trying to say that's all because of games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Again, the facts are there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Crime among youth has been in decline.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't believe me?
[SPEAKER_00]: Ask the Department of Justice.
[SPEAKER_00]: The numbers are there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seven, embrace the Constitution.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have a right in this industry to make and market our product in an unregulated manner.
[SPEAKER_00]: We should be talking about what our rights are.
[SPEAKER_00]: Video games are part art and part commerce.
[SPEAKER_00]: Both parts are protected.
[SPEAKER_00]: Eight, lobby.
[SPEAKER_00]: Make political donations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: 9.
[SPEAKER_00]: Harness our best spokespeople.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have them talk about why they like video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: have basically using high profile celebrities benefits just to bring different people in by saying their favorite stars say, oh, I like this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sadly enough, I don't want to mention this because I really hate the idea anyways, but you have the Hip Hop Gaming League.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, most people, I wouldn't see them as really...
[SPEAKER_03]: Number 10 was demonstrate the most creative games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Halo and Grand Theft Auto represent us in the marketplace, but we need to show people it's not all about guns and boobs.
[SPEAKER_00]: Katamari Namashi, DDR, Parappa, Donkey Konga, and Guitar Heroes are all games the whole family can enjoy and play.
[SPEAKER_05]: But a little guitar, or I'm sorry, a little guitar, a little violence and boobs never hurt anyone.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: I still think we need air guitar freaks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Over 18.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray for boobies.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was a good album.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was Bloodhound Gang.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not that retarded when it comes to pop culture anyway.
11.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the problem in statistical perspective, less than 20% of all games released are M-rated, a minority of the product.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_00]: Amen.
12.
[SPEAKER_00]: Be proud.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't be ashamed to say you like video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just be sure to tell people why you like them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I run into this all the time at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll tell people that, yeah, I do this thing on the internet about video games, and they're kind of like, oh, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh, you're like that, huh?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's weird?
[SPEAKER_05]: I get more of a reaction from telling someone I'm a gamer than telling them I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tell somebody at work I'm gay and they go, oh, okay, yeah, we all knew that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I tell somebody that I'm a gamer, they're like, oh, wow, you play games?
[SPEAKER_00]: Crazy, crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weird, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the culture.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am a proud gamer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_00]: There should be a number 13 on there.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you're female, tell the boys to piss off if they say you can't play a video game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or just beat them to shit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: You take those platform boots and knock them upside the head.
[SPEAKER_00]: You heard that from me.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a very good top 12.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next Generations I came from?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tipped my hat to that website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's next-gen.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got a story here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're trying to wrap up this first half of the show here, but plenty more stories to come here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to talk about GameTap real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: GameTap is now going to be offering previews and trailers on their service.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like a try before you buy type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they recently signed an agreement with Strategy First, who made Galactic Civilizations, and
[SPEAKER_05]: This will allow customers to preview full versions of their pre-release titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds to me a little bit like the Xbox Live model, a little bit like the demos, but a very interesting way for the PC publishers and GameTap to find that harmony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I'm all for easy access to game demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's a great idea, so I tip my hat to GameTap as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of smart people in gaming this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is good news.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's go to the next story, which is from Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, let's talk a little bit about Xbox and the patch systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta love the way they patch games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's a dumb idea to release games that aren't ready for the market because they have bugs, and they do it knowingly that they have these errors in the games.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, Dead or Alive 4, there's a mandatory patch that's fixing bugs and adding no new content coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also going to help balance some of the characters, but
[SPEAKER_03]: basically the fix the save bug yay that's something great oh guess what you know those demo kiosks out there that you could download the xbox car for burnout guess what it doesn't work it doesn't work at all because it's broken yes that's right um EA has actually said there's at right now there's no official date of the patch but there will be one to fix the 360 kiosk car because it doesn't work very fun um another thing
[SPEAKER_03]: Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter is going to be getting updates soon to add the Southpaw controller configuration and to fix the bugs in their save system that cause your save game to get deleted, just like it did in Full Auto and in Call of Duty 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: My question is, why are they releasing all these games out there if it's constantly...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_05]: I definitely don't think that people should be releasing games that are only half-finished, and I don't think patching is the way to fix your game on the back end.
[SPEAKER_05]: But at the same time, I do realize that the occasional error is going to come up that people don't find.
[SPEAKER_05]: People that find loopholes and stuff, and let's say they didn't know about this whole full-auto patching.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: That screams, oh, we didn't test this on a normal TV.
[SPEAKER_03]: We just used our LCD monitors that we have here at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looked fine on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, that's just lazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Extremely lazy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then they have to go back and fix that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: What can we do about it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Vote with your wallet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Still though, I mean, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of times we don't know that these bugs are there until after you buy the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you know, you play all the way through Call of Duty and all of a sudden, oh, my save game's gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a nice bonus feature that wasn't mentioned on the box art.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the idea of patching it to fix stuff and maybe add content later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't like it as an excuse to release a game like Call of Duty 2 whose online multiplayer sucks ass because there's so much lag on it and they obviously didn't test it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you have a response to Loki's little rant, you could always send us an email, and that was sent to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love to hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week, DarkSakura likes to go into our mailbag and stick her hand in the mailbag and dig out her favorite letters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that is mailbag with a B, not hag with an H. Mail hag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is DarkSakura our mail hag?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just teasing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I say that I tease because I love.
[SPEAKER_00]: That disturbs me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't give me evil glares.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't give you an evil glare.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was a disturbed look.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DarkSakura likes to dig into the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going to do that right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: With a shovel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you all sanitized and ready to go?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've got the hazmat suit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, who emailed us this week?
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Attention rocks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, our good buddy Roblay pointed out a few things.
[SPEAKER_00]: That basically, not only is Xbox getting in all over the 360 thing, we now have 360.yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have the Colgate 360.
[SPEAKER_00]: And we have Anderson Cooper 360 on CNN.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is a brilliant observation.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to launch Orange Launch Radio 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that can be the name of our fan club.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, speaking of fan clubs, can I plug the new Myspace?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, as someone didn't do in our LiveJournal community either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, my bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a new MySpace.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's brand new.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's different from the group.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a fan that made a group, but now we have an actual user account.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're a band because we want to be rock stars.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can actually listen to clips from old shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you remember Jaime's email from last week where she was pointing out all the good clips from older shows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually put the Mega Man clip on our MySpace.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's www.myspace.com slash OrangeloungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we know MySpace is where the internet goes to die, but if we can promote ourselves on it, hey, we'll sell our souls to MySpace.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was actually listening to that the other day, and just cracking up, and my husband thought that I had gone nuts.
[SPEAKER_07]: The freaky part about MySpace is Fox is now using it to promote their TV shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am not surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they own it, so why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: MySpace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and add us because we want like a zillion friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_00]: We got an email from DJ Ratchet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, just to go into it, if we wanted to thank us for reading the email in the last podcast.
[SPEAKER_00]: but also asked a question about Kingdom Hearts 2 which I actually did reply to about the different summons wanting to know if Chicken Little was in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Chicken Little has been confirmed as a summon in Kingdom Hearts 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just thought I'd let you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what, I actually should be playing more Kingdom Hearts 2 but I have this issue with playing games in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can do it, but then reading... I have to sit there with my dictionary and try to translate the kanji and it gives me a headache.
[SPEAKER_00]: She said dick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, I had to do that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I say dick all the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we should just cut that little clip and put that on our MySpace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dick, dick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dick, dick, dick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why am I now thinking of that scene in Spaceballs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I have to separate you two?
[SPEAKER_05]: Next up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have an email from, and I have to scroll down to see who this is from, Sycoon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is about, you know, old school games.
[SPEAKER_00]: He's a big fan of the old school games, like in the gameplay, but lots of people out there are saying graphics over the games.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I know, it's like they're saying, oh, this game sucks because it doesn't look pretty.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Case in point, Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pretty, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Geometry Wars is a pretty game, but it's not exactly pushing the 360s hardware to its limits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Radiant Silvergun is awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then again, so is Ikaruga, and that was really graphically pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once in a while, you can still pull up...
[SPEAKER_05]: You could still pull up an old Atari 2600 Classic on GameTap or emulators or whatever you want to use.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're still fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: Unless it's E.T.
[SPEAKER_00]: because that game sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, but they don't have E.T.
[SPEAKER_05]: on GameTap and I don't think they exist.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Atari's pretty much written E.T.
[SPEAKER_05]: off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't buy them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dios!
[SPEAKER_00]: But just to go ahead and read a paragraph out of this letter, it said, I just want to know why many people now think that graphics are more important to a game than gameplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually played Sonic Adventure with a friend of mine, and he complained about how blocky it looked to him as compared to Half-Life 2 and Halo 2, and he didn't like it just for that reason, although Sonic Adventure still is a great game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he was comparing first version to 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Sonic Adventure 2 wasn't as...
[SPEAKER_00]: Sonic Adventure was really smooth, very nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't think of any games on Dreamcast that were blocky at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, not since the early PlayStation games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And even then, it's like, who cares?
[SPEAKER_00]: One of my favorite games ever on PlayStation is called Evil Zone.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's really horrible looking, but it's so cheeseball.
[SPEAKER_00]: We want to make fun of every anime in existence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's just spoiled by next-gen pretty stuff, you know?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's just because we grew up with the we have nothing but gameplay that we have a better appreciation for a game that plays well versus a game that looks pretty and plays like crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Half-Life 2 plays well.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't play first person.
[SPEAKER_05]: Halo is a pretty game and it's a good game, don't get me wrong, but don't knock Sonic Adventure just because it's not pristine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic Team Camera
[SPEAKER_00]: In another Dreamcast game, Blue Stinger, I had the Japanese version, where it had the big cinematic camera angles.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's really hard to do that scene where you're climbing up the tower when the camera is like 50 miles above the tower.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, oh, yay, I'm going to pretend I know where I'm going.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, next letter, shall I?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another one from Rob.
[SPEAKER_00]: About Lieberman being the porker of the month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, fatty?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: CDC Investigate Video Games Disease Control?
[SPEAKER_05]: This Katamari game made me lose my mind and I've just gone crazy and I worship the king of all cosmos.
[SPEAKER_00]: They want to look at the impact of electronic media use organized by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
[SPEAKER_00]: To go ahead and read a little bit of this article, even though the legislation called the Children and Media Research Advancement Act does not include restrictions, it appears to be intended as a way to justify them.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's because a string of court decisions have been striking down anti-gaming laws because of a lack of hard evidence that minors are harmed by violence in video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, take that out on anyone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your tax dollars at work, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like, they can't admit that they're wrong.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've, you know, how many times have we seen all of, you know, the courts basically upholding what we've been saying for ages, that there's not really any type of major harm to come to it unless you're counting home environment.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they're saying, no, no, it's a video game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Parents are not allowed to raise their children.
[SPEAKER_00]: Stupid people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why is it that
[SPEAKER_00]: Tag and Release Program Best Name Ever for Vaporware Like Melbourne, Australia?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to go ahead and quote from here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would like to add a bit to what he said.
[SPEAKER_00]: The company spent around $62 million on stuff for the last year, with around $3.5 million spent on the actual console development.
[SPEAKER_00]: This may be because the console is a scam.
[SPEAKER_00]: You see what the console makers, or non-makers in this case, could be doing is just getting lots of money from investors to say they're going to make a console when they actually spend very little on the console and keep some of the money for themselves.
[SPEAKER_00]: For example, they hire their family as consultants, pay them $200,000 a year while also paying themselves money.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you ask me, quite a good idea, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Launch Radio will be coming out with its own console very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're looking for investors, so if you have $11 billion, please send us an email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'd love to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember when they were showing the Phantom at E3, was it in 2004?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a cute little booth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they had a booth, and I tried to go in the wrong entrance or something, and they got all pissed off at me or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: So then I walked around the normal way, and then I saw their
[SPEAKER_03]: T-shirt sucks, um
[SPEAKER_03]: No, the only thing I liked about the console was the case, and I wanted to make a computer out of the case.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was about it, because it had this, like, glowing blue light on the front, and that looked cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But other than that, it was, like, huge.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was the size of a large VCR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, this thing was ginormous.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looked like a stupid brick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any more emails?
[SPEAKER_00]: One more, one more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_00]: From Jaded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Jaded.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: There's an interesting article that he wants us to look at about, it's actually something on Slashdot.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's actually a really, really quick little article, so I'm just going to read what it says.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kotaku has a great feature up today written by James Wagner, a formerly embedded reporter in the world of Second Life.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: For the thing of it is, game magazine previews are almost uniformly positive even for the most undistinguished titles.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it unrolls thus.
[SPEAKER_00]: Publisher makes mediocre game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Press reviews, I'm sorry, press previews depict mediocre game as being good or at least worth a look.
[SPEAKER_00]: Excited gamers read previews, foolishly believe them, start making pre-sale orders of mediocre games driven by preview press and pre-sale numbers based on that press.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, Yola.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe if we add on to that successfully, we get E, gamers discover independent podcasts.
[SPEAKER_05]: F, gamers get the real story from people who actually play the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: G, quality games inherit the earth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hooray for us.
[SPEAKER_00]: We are your video game saviors.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that it for the mail?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, send your mail to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com Loki, take us out of this hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have some follow-ups, some quickie little follow-ups to things we were bitching about last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the first thing is, if you're hoping for another NFL game by someone other than EA, sorry, NFL extended the CBA and EA still holds exclusive rights to the NFL.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh, I kind of saw that coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Origami, what is the Origami?
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a 7 inch tablet PC that runs Windows and it's going to be under $1000 Only?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, is it a gaming system?
[SPEAKER_03]: No
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not a gaming system.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's more of a micro-laptop type thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Minesweeper on the go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, there is a video file out on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love YouTube.
[SPEAKER_00]: Where someone apparently leaked one of their marketing demos that they were showing during their little meetings.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it did show somebody actually playing a game on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, that wasn't a market.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was on their viral site that they had online.
[SPEAKER_03]: OrigamiProject.com and it was just a concept, proof of concept.
[SPEAKER_03]: They weren't actually playing a video or a game because it was showing Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then they listed it there as a potential for the machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya in our chatroom says $999.99.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you say under $1,000, does that mean $999.99?
[SPEAKER_05]: More likely.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to sell it for $656.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have three different versions of the
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not even really the origami.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, I forget what it's called now.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the mini PC or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forget how they were calling them.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically just this really small PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any other follow-ups?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I think we're finally due for a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our first hour has turned into our first hour and a half segment, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcasted to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.