[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to the podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_04]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now the conclusion of episode 174 from February 12, 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is February 12, 2006, and this is Part B, the second half of Episode 174.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys so much for joining us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Incentive for you guys to listen live on Sunday nights if you can, those of you guys out there I mean we podcast for a reason, we know not everybody can listen live Sunday nights But Sunday nights when we do do this live, we play music during the breaks when we do this show And tonight we played some pieces in that break from some classic Super Nintendo and Genesis titles We played a song from Secret of Mana in there, one of the songs from the beginning of the game And then we played the Emerald Hill Zone song from Sonic the Hedgehog 2 And the reason why I'm bringing this up
[SPEAKER_07]: We can't play this stuff on the podcast because of copyright stuffs.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I brought it up because it inspired some comments here in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.orangelontario.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: VXJasonXV, who also happens to be our lovely webmaster, he listens too.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, a lot of games just don't have memorable music like this anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Catchy, but not memorable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Agree?
[SPEAKER_07]: Disagree?
[SPEAKER_07]: Katamari.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was also Space Channel 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then again, the game was pretty much all music, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean, I understand what he's saying, is that with a lot of current titles, you either have licensed music, too, you play a game like Burnout, everything you're hearing is licensed, same stuff you hear on the radio, or, you know, it's not like the same it used to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of see where he's coming from.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of agree on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The same care isn't being put into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that when you have limiting circumstances, when you do something...
[SPEAKER_02]: When you do something that excels, you know, under those limiting circumstances, people are going to recognize it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to see the effort that went into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nowadays, you can make something that sounds really good with minimal effort.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe it's harder to stand out above the pack in that case?
[SPEAKER_02]: I really think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, anyway, just a little side topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just thought that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love when our chat room inspires conversation here.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, we're an interactive show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Truly interactive.
[SPEAKER_07]: www.orangeonstradio.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a profanity study done this week for Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love the way that they intro this.
[SPEAKER_05]: What exactly is a profanity study?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's studying the frequency of profanity in Halo 2 during online games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, I love the way they intro this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's basically, when you log into Xbox Live, more often than not, you're greeted by a 14-year-old that learned a new word on the playground that day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyways...
[SPEAKER_05]: This study, here's what they've basically come up with over the course of 33.9 hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, the number one word, of course, that appeared would have been fuck, with 43% of the time, with an average of 8.11 uses per hour.
[SPEAKER_05]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: of course some of the other colorful language that was in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: 9% of them were racial slurs, 7% of them were sexual slurs including, you know, I want to fuck your mom, that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait a minute, does I want to fuck your mom count as the usage of the word fuck or as sexual usage of the word fuck?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, basically, sexual phrases which were not homosexual.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck was not included in this unless it was directed at a person, i.e.
[SPEAKER_05]: your mom.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, how...
[SPEAKER_05]: How many times did Frack appear?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how they do it on TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: 7% of them were homosexual references.
[SPEAKER_05]: In other words, you're gay, you suck, you homo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn appeared 3% of the time, bitch 7% of the time, and ass 5% of the time, you know, being asshole, assbag, asshat, etc.
[SPEAKER_07]: and actually... I know why you wanted to do this story tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just wanted an excuse to say ass bag and sound professional.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Game experiences may differ during online play.
[SPEAKER_05]: That, I guess, does make sense now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I prefer Oh Poopy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, thank you very much, Loki, for earning this episode an explicit tag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job!
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna pwn you, you fucking noobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remind me, before you say all these words again, what was the point of this study?
[SPEAKER_07]: Scats whores or what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious how many times people really do say fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was basically that they're trying to kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess bring this to light, you know, all these stupid people that are on Xbox Live and stuff and kind of that, you know, maybe that they should.
[SPEAKER_05]: This isn't exactly a plea, you know, for the government to crack down or tighten the control in the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just basically information that parents can educate themselves with.
[SPEAKER_05]: That this is how much, you know, fucking language they're going to hear during the course of Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is why Halo 2 is the number one Xbox Live game.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much more do they hear in their house?
[SPEAKER_07]: I,
[SPEAKER_07]: I like this tweak in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says, Asshat is my Xbox's name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, good for you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan's Halo team was called Badass Ninjas, but it was AZZ.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great study.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray, hooray.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to a more serious Halo 2 related article, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, for the love of God, please save us.
[SPEAKER_07]: Try not to use ass bag in your story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, about Ass 2 on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Halo 2 on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to Xbox.com, the Xbox game Halo 2 is being put on PC, but there's a hitch on that one that it's not for Windows XP, but for Windows Vista.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you'll be able to do playing on that one next month, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, buy Windows Vista, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's an excuse to upgrade to Windows Vista.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can freaking play Halo 2, which really would be better if you had an Xbox anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Being half the computers right now anyways can't run Windows Vista's default theme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sad!
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft is not learning anything!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know where our chat room's going with this now?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm back on the swearing thing, but this is a good indication by our chat room here.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're bringing up... Have you guys ever seen that video on the internet of the kid?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know if it was staged or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: People say it's legit, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some kid is playing on Xbox Live and he left his voice chat on or whatever, and you can hear him yelling at his mom.
[SPEAKER_07]: and people are quoting it in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like SSJ100 to Matt and Fireboma are going back a little bit back and forth in the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mom, I want my fucking chocolate milk.
[SPEAKER_07]: You promised me, you bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm in a clam match.
[SPEAKER_07]: You said I could get whatever I wanted and I said chocolate milk but now I want Mountain Dew.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you ever heard that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how else to describe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard children talking to their parents this way though.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I just had to bring that because it made me think of that and those guys are on it too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's talk about something pure and wholesome and good in the world like Oprah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, maybe that's a controversial subject and you're probably wondering what in the hell does Oprah have to do with gaming?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is she going to have video games on her show?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not yet, but who knows because Nintendo has their sights on Oprah.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was Reggie Fils-Aim speaking at DICE.
[SPEAKER_07]: He said that Nintendo is considering using new marketing outlets such as Oprah and Ellen.
[SPEAKER_07]: He said a, quote, blue ocean of opportunity through new types of gameplay, end quote.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, obviously, Nintendo's trying to attract a whole new set of gamers here, and I think we've kind of seen this in the early releases for the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: I seem to remember them saying, well, this controller looks like a TV remote.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody's used a TV remote, so we're trying to expand to a whole new base of gamers, and you can see that Nintendo is being very aggressive with this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, he went on to point out that Nintendogs was a great success.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brain Training in Japan sold 2.5 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Brain Age, Train Your Brain in Minutes a Day is coming out here on April 17th.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm very interested to check this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very interesting there on how Nintendo's being aggressive there with their marketing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They feel, I guess, not enough moms are playing the Nintendo systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: I suppose not.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mom, why are you ponying noobs on, you know, Smash Brothers Revolution?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, what do you have for us next?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you know that games are like porn?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what games you play, but... I know you said you and Dan kind of have some fond memories over games, but I hope this isn't the kind of thing where... More like me screaming at him for being a... Okay, every time that we play, like, Street Fighter and he wins, he has to talk shit, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, oh, I won!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you suck!
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm like, I'm not gonna play with you again then.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd be... You know, if it were me, I'd be all, I am putting out tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be like, bitch, you watch out, I'll use Cammy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: He hates when I use Cammy, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: because I own him every time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, no, I did not know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, let me take your bait.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Jamie, I didn't know that games are like porn.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's been a bit of a talk going around about how games are being marketed.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's been this obsession going around with basically making them all cinematic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game pitches are being done like
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like this movie, or it's like this movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, you know, they've got to go out and use different media to market the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you sit and watch, you'd be watching a movie trailer at the theater, and you get a game thing up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I'm not watching a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm watching a video game ad.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually a quote out here by, is his last name pronounced?
[SPEAKER_02]: J for Joff, David Joff, who was the creator of God of War.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he's basically putting down the video game industry to imitate Hollywood movies and not offer the decent wages that you find amongst the Hollywood industry because the games are being marketed just the same way.
[SPEAKER_07]: So are they saying, they're not saying games are like porn, take that literally, but they're saying games is like how porn is viewed in the entertainment industry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that what I'm reading?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of wondering if this was going back to the Rez and Transvibrator thing again.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but I have a story on that coming up later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love this quote here.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's referring to the tie-in with Peter Jackson's King Kong.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of reviews praise King Kong's lack of HUD, but what's wrong with an HUD?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's wrong with a health bar that raises good to the player when he replenishes it?
[SPEAKER_02]: And why are we applauding in the press for abandoning the native language of video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's also another quote in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm
[SPEAKER_02]: about the obsession with cinema, and he admitted, I am guilty of that as well because God of War was inspired by Raiders of the Lost Ark.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, he explained he wanted the game to give players the experience of watching Indiana Jones as a 10-year-old rather than being Indiana Jones themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this is where the porn industry ties in another quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like the porn industry, sort of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I read about this guy who had this topless review that he was trying to add art to, and it's bombing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe games fall into that slot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some days I think games can be something else, the next great entertainment media.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then days I feel like it's just like porn or motion rides where there's no capability to reach high emotional levels.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a very interesting quote.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have an immediate reaction to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to sit on that one and think about it for a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's how games are like porn is that when you try to be artsy with porn, people don't buy into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to wonder what would happen if we had more people with creative sensibilities.
[SPEAKER_02]: If more games had a soul, had something to say, something that resonates.
[SPEAKER_02]: He also was resentful over the fact that people that create games receive pretty meager wages compared to how Hollywood directors and screenplays receive.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, I'm really frustrated with the way the industry is structured.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a sense of kind of being exploited.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an industry problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he has, of course, no intention to leave the industry.
[SPEAKER_02]: He said, if Sony came to me and told me, we're making God of War 2, I might have to decline, he said before admitting, I can stand up here and say I won't do it until they kick me out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: but you know but I you know my whole thing with that is you know like I said earlier not only is it that we're seeing the same type of standard in video games that's expected you know if movies we're seeing them marketed the same way too you know right up along there with your feature flick you've got the game to go with it you have other games being marketed in the same genre why aren't they getting the same type of of you know pay that anyone in the cinematic industry would receive hmm
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have an easy answer for that right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gives us something to think about, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm curious what the chatroom thinks about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: OrangeLogicRadio.com, click on chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we'll get some Skype calls about that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for that story.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's move on and talk about Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Part A tonight, we talked a lot about the DS and Xbox and stuff, but we didn't talk a whole lot about Sony, so Loki, save the day here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give us some Sony news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, one of the first things we have is, could the PlayStation 3 kill Sony?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if you think about it, this thing is taking forever to come out, so you kind of have to look at it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things that's being brought up is...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: They're saying, oh, it might be $400, could be $500.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, people don't have that kind of money to drop on these console systems like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, with Blu-ray coming out and stuff, not many people feel the need that they need Blu-ray because you're not going to see a big difference unless you own a high-def TV, and only 24% of the market out there owns a high-def TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that number is going to increase, though, certainly throughout the next few years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, it will, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony needs to drop the price hint already so people stop theorizing about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Developers Conference would be a good time to do that hint hint, but we all know we're going to be waiting until E3 to see the real meat of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other thing is, and I think this is probably going to change right now, that we haven't really seen much in games right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing's really been finished.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now, I think the whole point is everyone's starting to kind of...
[SPEAKER_05]: All Doom and Gloom
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that a crazy price point?
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a crazy price point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think so too, but I'm just saying people will pay it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, people will pay it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's over retail.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are they going to be charging for these if there's a shortage?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, $2,000.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that they need to come out with some information, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: The sooner the better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, is it possible there might be any shows coming up where we could see some of this information?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: At the TGS show, not the Tokyo Game Show, but the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Taipei Game Show 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony will be showcasing their next-gen console featuring numerous booths, 80 booths actually, covering all the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And 20 of them exclusively for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's just going to be recycled stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would they announce something new at this show?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the new thing added is going to be the Boomerang competition using the controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boomerang controller has been redesigned, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was an article put out by, I believe there was some gaming group that got to test out the PS3 and three of the games that have been made so far on the dev console, obviously, and the controller being used does not look like a boomerang.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're basing it more around the DualShock type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because DualShock, if it ain't broke, why fix it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it could be an ergonomic DualShock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, the Boomerang of Death is probably not going to be the controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even if it was the Boomerang of Death that was the controller, third-party people are going to make a DualShock-looking one anyway, so you can always buy that.
[SPEAKER_07]: About prices, Sephiroth1215 in our chat, remember back when PS1 was like $500?
[SPEAKER_07]: People paid that when that first came out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be insanely stupid for the PS3 to be $700.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's murder for their system right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we'll go ahead and move on here, get into another story, and actually it kind of relates to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just a real brief thing I have here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Activision has revealed that they will be releasing three titles at launch for the Sony console, and of course one game for the Revolution as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: As far as what games those are, well, that we don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: For whatever reason, those are being kept well under wraps.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say everybody's holding on to it so they can blow their load at E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think E3 is going to be an avalanche of information.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know if it's not that it's going to be murder for the publicity of these systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, there's so much hype around this year's E3 with these two systems, Revolution and PS3, that both companies better be prepared to lay it all out on the table, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's interesting because the article on this site that this ran on here, gamersreports.com, where we found this, says you can guarantee that one of these...
[SPEAKER_07]: One of these games will be Tony Hawk something.
[SPEAKER_07]: And certainly that would make sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: A new Tony Hawk game on PS3 at launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Successful series, why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good theory.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else might the PS3 bring us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully lots of violent games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know Grand Theft Auto 4 is going to be for the PS3, but one of the things that we've been actually seeing, there was a...
[SPEAKER_05]: British, or yesterday, actually at the British Embassy in Tokyo, there was a seminar on British gaming and demonstrated how the powerful graphics of the PS3 can display lots of violence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: From headshots to body shots, they had basically, this developer, it's
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a duh for me because as graphics get better, so will the detail of violence.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know what else is going to get better?
[SPEAKER_07]: The tits and ass will be more realistic as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to come out with a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tits and ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Headshot.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the selling point.
[SPEAKER_07]: The tits and ass headshot game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming to PS3 exclusively.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that'll be DOA Beach Volleyball 2 at 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that if the PS3 does usher in a lot of violent games, you know who's gonna love this?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know who's gonna love that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, not just you, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Jacky Poo Jacky Poo
[SPEAKER_07]: Robano?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the difference between two games?
[SPEAKER_07]: You do know we're a video game show, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he's one of Elevation's key investors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elevation partners.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're trying to obtain Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay, so Jack Thompson hates Take-Two, Bono wants to buy something he's got to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what do you say in the letter, do we know?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear Bono, the letter begins, I write you as a fellow brother in Jesus Christ, appreciative of your bold witness to the transforming truth of the gospel in both your words and your deeds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I write to encourage you respectfully and in the spirit of brotherly love not to purchase Take-Two Interactive Software Incorporated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, my brain is burning.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because you're going to hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay, we all got our spot reserved.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you should have wrote Bono and went, you know, in the name of love.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, the whole terminology there, I admit...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that it's just a very poorly masked attempt to, besides the get publicity thing, to try to use religion as a front for his own personal agenda, which I find horribly insulting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you're a religious person, you should probably find this insulting too, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, he's also said in the letter that Take-Two has lied to the investment community in its latest SEC filing and warns that ongoing criminal investigations have put the publisher's very survival at risk, despite the fraudulent assertions in the recent SEC filing that they are all without merit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know...
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, Jackie Poo?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_02]: Sit down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: He needs to just cry me a river, build a bridge, and get over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, did he ever get our flowers?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they weren't our flowers, but we helped, and our name was on the little signature of the letter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: The host of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did he ever get those flowers?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, he did, and he forwarded them on to the offices of Rockstar, and I believe the attorneys representing Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll bet he never even looked at them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he even took a minute to smell the flowers.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said they were pretty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did he?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said they were pretty.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he basically called it harassment.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it says this harassment of me follows take two and blank Rome's lead in characterizing me in the media and in Alabama's courthouse as variously a bisexual pedophile, mentally ill, paranoid, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because I believe that's what the letter said at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, what a dumbass.
[SPEAKER_07]: How is sending flowers harassment?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ordering pizza to somebody else, that's harassment.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not what happened here.
[SPEAKER_07]: The whole point of this thing was to do something that was non-harassing because there are a lot of people that have chosen to respond immaturely to Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this was supposed to be the anti-harassment.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said that the flowers were sent to harass him and he sent them, you know, to them to basically, they're forwarded in a memory of the innocence that each of you three men helped kill, as Jack Thompson put.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's forwarded in the memory of these victims whose killers have yet... I want to know how many people he thinks have actually been killed by Grand Theft Auto and how many of these people actually, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: If there's like three people they're talking about here, and how many millions of people have played this game, I would say that's a pretty small number.
[SPEAKER_05]: If everybody was learning to kill from these games, wouldn't there be millions and millions of killers out there?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't send him a puppy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ross makes a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I can't send him a puppy because the moment the puppy tried to bite him, he'd have the puppy locked up and then put to death.
[SPEAKER_07]: Poor puppy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't send him any puppies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't want to talk about Jackie Poo.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually seriously thinking about and compiling the statistical data myself and writing him a letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know when I write a letter to anybody...
[SPEAKER_02]: I put statistical data to back up every damn thing I say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm curious now with this whole activism thing, what's next for the Flowers for Jack folks?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, they created a huge thing here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they've been arguing back and forth with Jack Thompson over email.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like it says, get over your Jack Thompson obsession.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is not about me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about Rockstar's sale of murder simulators to children.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe you should encourage the parents to do their job.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope to God that the next Grand Theft Auto game that comes out is Grand Theft Auto Murder Simulator for Children.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what's the website?
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't the Flourish for Jack folks get so big they had to make their own new website?
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe it's PixellantiNation.com And of course Pixellanti was a term that Jackie Poo coined.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so keep tabs on that and we'll be keeping an eye on it too to see what they do next.
[SPEAKER_05]: As much as we'd like not to talk about them each week, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you of the week time, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: My FU of the week goes to San Francisco traffic for sucking out the soul that was sitting within me happily after leaving the Kintetsu Mall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yesterday I went with my friend Becky to the Rosicrucian Museum in San Jose to go look at the Egyptian exhibit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we went on to San Francisco to go shopping and look for Japanese stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And after we were done with the shopping, we decided we were going to go...
[SPEAKER_02]: to find somewhere to eat and I got lost.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I didn't really get lost.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was more just the streets there make no sense because you'd be going down the road and all of a sudden, oh, we're going to split off here and not make any type of real sense in how we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So finally got to turn around and got back up and made my way back to Mission, which I knew would lead me to Van Ness.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we were going up Van Ness going, you know what, let's eat at the Hard Rock Cafe because as far as she remembered it was on Van Ness.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're like, oh crap, we don't see it anywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we headed back to go to the fisherman's wharf.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were going to try to eat at Bubba Gump.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there's a two and a half hour wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we found the Hard Rock Cafe had been moved there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're like, great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So after us saying out of spite we were not going to eat at the Hard Rock Cafe, we ate there anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not really pissed off at anything, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: What if I threw a book at your head?
[SPEAKER_05]: What if I give you something to be pissed off about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody step on Loki's foot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: You stay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: TheFerretHasNephew
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU of the week goes to the fact that I'm not going to be here for two weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: That kind of stinks.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I mean, it's for my day job, and I like my day job and all, and getting out of town once in a while on the company dollars is cool and all, and, you know, I get to go teach, which is what I love to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it still sucks because, you know, I have to put other stuff I like to do, such as this, on hold.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that bites.
[SPEAKER_07]: So an FU to that frustration feeling that comes with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grr.
[SPEAKER_07]: and an F you to the fact that I probably won't really get to play games while I'm out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to fall behind on this gaming stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be able to read websites and stuff, but my laptop that I'm taking is not that hot unless I convince Extrovert to let me borrow his.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, I won't get to play World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: I won't get to play Xbox or PlayStation or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I could always rent the... Jamie's cradling her laptop.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I know you won't give up the precious, but I could always rent
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo 64 games in the hotel room.
[SPEAKER_07]: The last hotel I stayed at.
[SPEAKER_07]: The last Hilton I stayed at had that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should take your PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll probably take the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: I probably will.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I originally... You can chat with us on Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to think if there's any really good games coming out for the DS or Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, I'll probably take that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jackie can stalk around.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see ya.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do have free Wi-Fi, so maybe I'll actually get back into Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get back to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel better now that I've vented.
[SPEAKER_02]: I paid off my last loan, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not my very last loan, but I've got my second room now.
[SPEAKER_02]: My second downstairs room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, me too.
[SPEAKER_07]: 845,000 bells!
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a lot of fish.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh no, I've been using fruit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And selling furniture.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tekken is coming to the PSP, so that'd be great, except we don't know if it's going to be a new Tekken fighting game, which it probably will be, or something crappy like Death by Degrees, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyways, I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another thing, if you missed out on Nintendogs, you might get your chance with The Dog Happy Life.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually a Nintendog-like game, and you can...
[SPEAKER_05]: Customize your dog's room, and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Teach it stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, it'd be interesting, I'm not sure if they have this, but since they do have the mic, which you can use for the PSP, maybe you can actually train your dog via voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: So have voice recognition or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: No word on that, but one can speculate.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's scheduled to be released in Japan on the 27th of April.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, if you are in the free stuff, there's a nice little transport tycoon clone out there called OpenTTD.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's actually available for download on PSP Updates.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also available on PSP Updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, by the way, those of you guys with PSPs, you should be visiting olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_07]: That site's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you gonna do something nice for the folks at olrpsp.com?
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to give them some updates.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some new wallpaper or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need to do something for the folks there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been working on stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, you know... We just did a photo shoot.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need folks to be able to put our ugly faces on their PSPs.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do not need validation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm married.
[SPEAKER_02]: My husband says I'm hot all the time I've been reading one of Margaret Cho's books and reading about what it's like to be a celebrity when you don't expect yourself to be one
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like, oh my god, that sort of happens to me sometimes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please understand, we're grounded here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We realize we're not super celebrities, but there is a teensy bit of recognition that comes with us.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the whole thing where I don't expect to say, oh, I've listened to you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember who it was I was talking to.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just on a message board somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: And someone says, oh, is that you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, two of my friends from college found me through our website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, see that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it's great though, we love it, we love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But do remember guys, A, this isn't our day job, B, you know, we do this because we love games and talking about them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I joke all the time about being an internet celebrity, but it's sort of true.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you're grounded with that, you don't really think.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have delusions of grandeur or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I go to work, I go to school, and I go to the gym, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I play my video games and I come talk about it and it just happens to be that people all over the world listen to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: No big thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: No big whoop.
[SPEAKER_02]: 555-4444
[SPEAKER_07]: The Secret History of Video Game Sex
[SPEAKER_07]: And they hit on some of the high points of sex and gaming in history.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so they have this cute little timeline.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's available on 1up.com that starts off with Custer's Revenge in 1982, of course, being one of the most memorable porno games on Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_07]: And not only porno, but, you know, racist and violent, like, all wrapped into one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, this is your X-rated game if there ever was one.
[SPEAKER_07]: There will never be anything like it again, that's for damn sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was Custer's Revenge even really sold anywhere?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe 10 copies were made and one of them got on the internet and now it's this big cult phenomenon?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: River City Ransom they put in their list because it had the first pixelated butt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because remember when they went to the sauna?
[SPEAKER_07]: You could see the little butt.
[SPEAKER_02]: To its defense, River City Ransom was actually a Japanese game called Hot-Blooded Downtown Story where you went, instead of going to the little shops, they actually said, you know, did all the really cute stuff, and you did go to a bathhouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's more, you know, it's a cultural thing in that case where it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: But for us, here in America, that was a bit of a, oh my gosh, booty!
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomb Raider in 96, Lara Croft, enough said.
[SPEAKER_07]: Metal Gear Solid in 98 is cited for Meryl.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because she walks around in her underwear if you go interrupt her changing clothes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And moving on the list, of course... She should also say she's more comfortable with her Desert Eagle than with her bra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dead or Alive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nuff Said There is cited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bouncy Boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fear Effect 2, Retro Helix, because it's got sexy protagonists who are lovers.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little bit of lesbianism.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rez in 2001 is cited for a certain peripheral that came with this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very hard to find now, but it's called the Trans Vibrator.
[SPEAKER_07]: And trust me, when they developed it, they weren't thinking of the uses that some people have come up for with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The article was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enough said.
[SPEAKER_07]: BMX XXX in 2002.
[SPEAKER_07]: I own that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played this game because you had it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually a very fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Matt Hoffman's Pro BMX.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a really cool game though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does have strippers and naked people in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And pimps.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got that as well, but it takes forever to get the boobs on the bike.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't take very long to get the stripper cutscenes, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's just these random stripper cutscenes inserted in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That you can get pretty soon, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also on the list here of 1up.com's Secret History of Video Game Sex, Leisure Suit Larry from 2004.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enough said, although I'm kind of curious why they didn't cite the earlier games, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blood Rain, simply for the fact that she ended up being in that Playboy spread, that virtual girl topless thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, hot coffee, duh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Playboy The Mansion, that game, was cited here on the list here.
[SPEAKER_07]: And God of War...
[SPEAKER_07]: In 2005, because of course, you know, he had some, you know, boob stuff too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And lastly, UMD Pornography, making their list here of the steamy side of Gaming's Past.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking here in the chat room to see some of the points that folks are saying here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like a lot of people are talking about Bubble Bath Babes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's Bubble Bath Babes from the list?
[SPEAKER_07]: That game sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that game sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, and then people are talking about hacking your NES ROMs to give nudity in the games.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of those are stupid, though, like Super Nude Brothers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, lame.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll never forget the one that was a game that was never released here, but in Japan they had an old, old, old NES title called Nuts and Milk, and it was the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, somebody hacked this ROM, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just fill in the blank.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what they did to this game, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: The end.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's excellent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, please say you have some type of serious story for us here.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Jamie, first, you have a story for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: New cost porn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quantic Dream has canned InfraWorld.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been pretty much tossed in the garbage, kicked out to the road.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: In an interview with the German website, working title, William de Vandermeer, I suppose I pronounced that right, said InfraWorld at date is cancelled.
[SPEAKER_02]: The concept did not appeal to publishers.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did say that Omicron 2, which was announced at the same time as InfraWorld, is actually still on track and is now titled Karma.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it won't be out on shelves until 2009.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quantic Dream is actually working on another unnamed title at present.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another quote on here, We have production set, but I cannot divulge the name or details of the project.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is an original franchise of ours, a game for PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, PSP, and PC systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speculation is that it's a sequel to Fahrenheit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no Inferworld.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our Skype line is open over at www.orangelandradio.com Click on interact with us and I'd be picking up a call right now but nobody's calling in.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm thinking, I'm looking at our chat room and people are doing this.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're collectively doing this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sick.
[SPEAKER_07]: So fine, we'll go on to the next story.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you guys don't want to call, fine by me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: The holiday is coming up pretty soon here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, we have to talk about sexy cheats.
[SPEAKER_05]: for Sexy Games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other things that they have here.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually talk about Meryl's underwear in Metal Gear Solid, which I thought was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can actually...
[SPEAKER_05]: Blood Rain into Juggie mode by entering Juggie Dance Squad as the code to basically unlock this new mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what exactly that does, but it'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: BMX XXX, they have Topless Girl mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: You basically have to win first place in both competition levels to unlock the Topless Girl option.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball, See-Through Swimsuit,
[SPEAKER_05]: and you can actually play with Helena, Leifang, and Christie to basically get a transparent swimsuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, it is censored.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, the guide game, if you happen to unlock some of the video that's in there, you can hit Triangle Deposit and
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, who has some news about Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, Sonic's old.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I grew up with Sonic the Hedgehog even though I was a Super Nintendo person in my younger years.
[SPEAKER_02]: There actually is a next generation Sonic game that made an appearance in GamePro.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a big world exclusive thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is a few interesting points that were made in the article.
[SPEAKER_02]: The typical Sonic character model was about 1500 polygons.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time around it has 1 million, according to the developers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game will also be faster than any previous Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually a quote from Nakamura, who is the game creator.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has motion blur, you can see it in some of the images that have been out on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there were some that were published in the magazine too.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game will feature huge environments that have night and day cycles as you progress through the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have morning, noon, night, changing the lighting, sort of how Ocarina of Time was with the day and night.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will also use the Havix Physics game engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: GamePro mentioned also that there was a sequence where Sonic faced an army of killer robots and they went flying everywhere with, quote, startling realism.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see what it is when it's finished.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds like it could be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we're about ready to wrap things up here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, Loki has a couple quick stories he wants to go through real quick here, some things that fell through the cracks that he wants to make sure we talk about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things that they've actually got on this website, knollriver.com, for all you Mac owners out there, if you do have a 360, you're able to share your music back and forth with the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: using this program they made called Connect360 and allow you to sync up your iTunes as well as photos, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check that out if you own a Mac and a 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, that was a nice olive branch from Loki, I think, in a way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are actually more video game movies in production right now, and there's been some updates on those, mainly Max Payne and Alice.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've actually signed on Sarah Michelle Gellar to play the role of Alice, which will be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Max Payne, I believe, is still in production right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell her to gain some weight first.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The new wave of Xbox 360 games to come out may require you to have a hard drive to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the case with the Japanese game Football Manager 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Liar!
[SPEAKER_05]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was also, during the DICE Summit that's been going on right now, they've had actually a list of, they were doing their own awards for it, the Game Awards.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically, the winner for Game of the Year this year is going to be God of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I remember we went over the nominees a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: So God of War won for, and actually God of War won a lot of categories, Console Game of the Year, Game of the Year,
[SPEAKER_05]: Outstanding Achievements in Animation and Original Music Composition as well as Sound Design.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other nominees that won here actually Outstanding Achievements in Gameplay and Engineering.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a tie between Nintendogs and Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I heard Guitar Hero won a bunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Design, Guitar Hero won as well as...
[SPEAKER_05]: Best Soundtrack, Guitar Hero won that one as well, so that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very interesting because Amplitude and Frequency were such wonderful games that, if you think about it, aren't that much different from Guitar Hero, except for the fact that you have a guitar.
[SPEAKER_07]: People really loved it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another hot coffee thing that hit the internet was advertising a brand new movie, Running Scared, with Paul Walker.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in this minigame that they have on their website, you would pleasure his wife orally.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, yeah, it was kind of like hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, it got pulled off the site due to its graphic content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: So much for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lego Star Wars 2 is actually going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lego Star Wars 2 Return of the Original Trilogy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: It should be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got a bunch of screenshots from it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like it's going to be covering the original Trilogy Plus.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have co-op and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quick poll, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have never played a LEGO game in my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have any of you guys?
[SPEAKER_05]: LEGO Star Wars was pretty sweet, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was actually really well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I missed the boat on that one somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And finally, dust off your Dreamcast...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some more games for you for free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Marathon has been ported over to the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to thank Bugged for this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually have the Marathon Trilogy you can download on Dreamcast Evolution or it's dcevolution.net They have links to that where you can make an image to play on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only catch is you're going to need a Dreamcast keyboard and a controller to play the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're a fan of Halo...
[SPEAKER_07]: Dreamcast, one of the most horribly underappreciated consoles ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That right there would sell the game for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would buy it just to play as the Burger King.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're about ready to wrap things up here on Orange Lounge Radio, but not until we get one last story from Loki, and this is quite interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'm glad they gave this to me because, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: Ice Cream Man in the UK was busted for running a counterfeit piracy operation and he'll serve 200 hours of community service for selling fake video games, CDs, and DVDs out of his ice cream van.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I believe 4,000 pirated DVDs, CDs, and games were seized during the raid on him.
[SPEAKER_05]: So unfortunately... See, I thought, you know, when I hear ice cream and I think of Sweet Tooth, you know, it'd be a new Twisted Metal game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's this world come to nowadays when an honest ice cream man has to turn the piracy to make a buck?
[SPEAKER_07]: At least it wasn't drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least it wasn't drugs.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're done with this week's episode and we're going to say goodnight now.
[SPEAKER_07]: First though, a couple quick notes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am going on vacation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going on a work leave for my day job.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I will not be back until March 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I will be gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll see you guys then.
[SPEAKER_07]: As far as the show itself, stay tuned to the podcast stream.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have something new for you guys up the next couple Sundays, at least in some capacity.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what, though, guys?
[SPEAKER_07]: We've been doing this show every week for the podcast at least.
[SPEAKER_07]: No matter what, there's been a new podcast every week for over a year now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if we take a little break this once, please forgive us.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we earned it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a slow news month anyway until we get to E3 and the GDC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes you've got to take a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going for ice cream.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mmm, ice cream.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's get ice cream.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's all just take the next five weeks off and just eat ice cream on Sundays instead.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, I can't wait to play Full Auto this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll have a review.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be up on the SUF blog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good luck getting it to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want ice cream.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: And reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is, I want ice cream too, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what I really want?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is a brownie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, a brownie with ice cream.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love the fact that you have taken the opportunity to support an independent podcast and we will continue to provide radio for you until we sell out or die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until next time, this is Rob Roberts for the rest of the folks here at Orange Lounge Radio saying, have a great week.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Due to other business commitments in our personal lives, Orange Lounge Radio is going on vacation until March 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't abandon us though, as the hosts of Orange Lounge Radio will bring to the podcast stream exclusively three special solo shows featuring news and other commentary leading up to our return with episode number 175 on March 5th.
[SPEAKER_07]: From the staff here at OLR, thank you so much for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you soon!