[SPEAKER_00]: Welcome to another edition of Orange Lounge Radio, that's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rob and Jamie are both still out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Jamie's actually feeling a bit under the weather right now, and her microphone is broken.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Rob was trying to record a podcast on an iBook, and well, that didn't work out too much, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: So much for those Mac products.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, I'm here to deliver another podcast for you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's so much news, I couldn't possibly pass it up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, I'm going to start things off like I start off every week with how my gaming week was.
[SPEAKER_00]: Once again, I've been playing full auto all week long, and I've gotten to the point now where I'm almost done with the game, about 90% done, and it's gotten goddamn frustrating.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have slammed controllers, cursed at my 360, and literally almost broke the game in half.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just really annoying, especially when you get to the part where the gang war's
[SPEAKER_00]: and you have to work with some AI that's completely retarded and they want to end up blowing you up and you get penalized if you blow them up.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's just really frustrating to get a gold in that and I'm really trying to do it but I just have to really take breaks from it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing a little bit of Hex HD a little bit and it's an okay game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tried a little bit of the Xbox Live Arcade Gauntlet and man do I suck at the original gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, been playing a little bit of Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories and Deathmatches.
[SPEAKER_00]: Finally finished up February's runnings, and unfortunately I came in second this time around.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, well, better luck next month, I guess.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, let's start things off with Microsoft's Origami Project.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is a brand new device put out by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've been teasing it a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_00]: The full details are supposed to hit the internet on March 2nd.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right now they did have a teaser, kind of a concept video if you will, showing off what this thing can do.
[SPEAKER_00]: It can basically play music, show some pictures, link up with the internet, has GPS, also a media PC extender, Wi-Fi, touchscreen, and of course they showed a little bit of gaming going along with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm thinking they're trying to use this as a PSP killer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Possibly an iPod killer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just trying to combat all the portable gaming and media systems out there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Should be interesting to see how this pans out.
[SPEAKER_00]: It did look a little bit big, so I'm not really sure if they're going to be trying to pass it off to the same market as maybe people that have iPods, but definitely a good alternative to a laptop or a media PC or, I don't know, just something that you can take with you on the go, browse your email and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, got a little bit of a scoop for you guys.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have Activision's 2006 and 2007 lineup for their upcoming games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's actually going to be something that they're going to be debuting at the Destination PlayStation show.
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of the notable features on here.
[SPEAKER_00]: We've got some of the movie expansions coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: also Quake Enemy Territory coming out on the PC of course that one looked really sweet
[SPEAKER_00]: Tony Hawk, Downhill Jam Marvel Legends
[SPEAKER_00]: Some of the other games coming out, of course, Call of Duty 3 on the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360, X3, you know, tying in with the new X-Men movie, as well as some really interesting titles, including Pimp My Ride, the game, and Kabbalah's African Safari, as well as the History Channel Civil War first-person shooter game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know how that's going to work, but it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you do happen to have, though, a PSP or a Nintendo DS,
[SPEAKER_00]: They haven't forgotten about you either.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gun is coming to the PSP, as well as Call of Duty 3 should be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Or Call of Duty is going to be heading to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not sure if it's going to be Call of Duty 3, but probably a port of something or other.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, they have Over the Hedge, which is going to be tying in with the DreamWorks movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: And Pimp My Ride as well for that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Looks like the DS is also getting Spider-Man Kids.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have no idea what that is, but sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Speaking of the revolution, though, there's been some more titles announced for it as well, one of them being Pennant Chase.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pennant Chase is actually a baseball game that was slated for August of last year, and it's been pushed back and pushed back.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, now they're talking that it's going to come out on the revolution.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whether it be a launch title or not should be interesting to find out, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, speaking of the revolution, the cost of the revolution has definitely been one of the points that everyone's been looking at.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're debating whether it's going to be about $200 to $150 retail when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And a little bit of news that's actually going to back that up.
[SPEAKER_00]: The software development kits have been priced, and they're only going to be costing developers $2,000.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, in comparison here,
[SPEAKER_00]: The PlayStation 2 software development kit when it first came out was $20,000 per kit at launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: In fact, the original PlayStation was only $4,000 to $5,000 at launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they're even cutting that in half.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's only backing up the fact that they're trying to lower development costs and basically just lower the price of games as we know them.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's something to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course, more stuff about the revolution is coming our way in E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: And one of the rumors that we're going to see at E3, and I've been saying this before, is going to be some sort of virtual reality.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, well, we've got some more hints at that.
[SPEAKER_00]: A member of IGN's forums, going by the name of Discrete here, actually posted some information about what's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the information that he posted, well, it was about...
[SPEAKER_00]: This brand new 3D technology brought out by a company called 3DH.
[SPEAKER_00]: And 3DH is basically a company that's developing hollow projection as well as the glasses to use this.
[SPEAKER_00]: And some of the pictures that they show on the website look pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: So imagine using a 3D controller with this hollow projection system, possibly the glasses.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can see that the revolution is going to stand in a class all by itself.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's going to be really sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another title that's also rumored to be coming to the revolution, of course Nintendo's denying it, would be Zelda.
[SPEAKER_00]: Zelda is actually the brand new Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been delayed until November.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now we all thought it was because of the launch.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, as I've been saying week after week, it's because they're adding something special to it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So this has been confirmed that they're adding some added functionality to
[SPEAKER_00]: GameCube title.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, no word if it's actually going to be on the Revolution, but still a game that's going to be launching with the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, on to another Nintendo platform here.
[SPEAKER_00]: We have Metroid Dread DS, a 2D Metroid sequel, rumored to be in the works for the new DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: Fansite DSX is basically saying that the rumored non-3D sequel
[SPEAKER_00]: of the Metroid series is still in the works, but still, you know, rumor right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Still looking forward to the brand new Metroid Prime Hunter, which is going to be coming out on the DS here in March, as well as, if you haven't played it yet, Metroid Prime Pinball, which I hear is okay, but I don't know how well pinball games do on the DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: In other news, The Legend of Zelda has reached its 20th anniversary.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, 20 years of Link.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: And that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's going to be coming out here only a couple days prior to E3.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it'll be worth checking that one out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, another little thing here about the DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's been a lot of rumors going around about a brand new revision to the DS.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, we're all familiar with the DS Lite, the brand new slimmed down DS with a brighter screen.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's still possible a third revision to the DS, and actually there was a patent discovered this week that kind of backs that up.
[SPEAKER_00]: The patent is for a brand new portable gaming system from Nintendo, and it actually shows dual touch screens.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, not necessarily saying
[SPEAKER_00]: Two screens that are touchscreens, but actually being able to point two positions simultaneously on the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, why is this important?
[SPEAKER_00]: If you think about it, for example, one of the demonstration photos that they had on there was like of a flight sim, and you'd put your fingers on the tips of the wing and basically be able to maneuver your plane through whatever obstacles that you might encounter.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very similar to a Nintendo Revolution controller.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_00]: DS Lite Game Boy Advance
[SPEAKER_00]: PSP2, 8GB NAND Flash Hard Drive
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyways, that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another rumor going around about the PSP2 is that it will be containing a video camera, a new webcam, and now this will be used actually as a mobile camera, or possibly to put yourself in the game, kind of like an
[SPEAKER_00]: Sony Ericsson Mobile Phone Camera
[SPEAKER_00]: will be placed on the PSP's screen right about now where the PSP logo is currently found.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, I don't know if that's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_00]: Personally, I would like to see it at the top of the system where you could rotate it around to possibly use this as, say, a digital camera.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because personally, I could use a good digital camera.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, to kind of back up the PSP camera rumor, there's actually been some ads spotted on London trains recently that kind of point towards possibly a camera coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now the advertisement shows basically a blank screen with the words, View, no way, delete, view, oh my god, delete, view.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't remember taking that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Delete, view, at last, a decent one store here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now that sort of sounds like they're viewing digital photos, so kind of pointing towards maybe that the camera is coming out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Should be interesting, good addition to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: X-Box Live Camera and Microphone
[SPEAKER_00]: The camera is going to be able to shoot 640x480 video at 30 frames per second and take 1.3 megapixel still photos.
[SPEAKER_00]: The camera will support built-in video chat and video messaging on Xbox Live, plus being able to use it as sort of an iToy type of peripheral, being able to put yourself in the games and that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Still got one more peripheral for the Xbox 360 owners.
[SPEAKER_00]: This one's going to be an Xbox 360 transfer kit from Daytail.
[SPEAKER_00]: The transfer kit's basically going to be just like the Exchange 360 site, where you can transfer your game saves from your Xbox 360 to your PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's pretty interesting that they're going to come out with something like this.
[SPEAKER_00]: The only problem, though, is you can only dump the whole card at one time.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's expected to retail about $14.99.
[SPEAKER_00]: On to a completely different topic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Phoenix Wright, Ace Attorney, is coming to American cell phones.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, the popular DS title, which was a remake of the Japanese Game Boy Advance title, Gaikuten Saiben, and the only one of the three-part series to get the official U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: English translation.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gaikuten Saiben 2 and 3 are now being localized for the U.S.
[SPEAKER_00]: as downloadable content.
[SPEAKER_00]: In other news, some of your favorite old-time games from Sierra are coming back.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, Sierra's classic adventure games are being re-released to run on the Windows XP.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everything from Space Quest to Police Quest to, of course, Leisure Suit Larry.
[SPEAKER_00]: Should be very interesting to see those come out.
[SPEAKER_00]: They're going to be retailing at about $20 each, so look for those coming soon.
[SPEAKER_00]: Speaking of titles being re-released,
[SPEAKER_00]: The Sonic 360 director has been hinting that Dreamcast titles could possibly make their way onto Xbox Live's arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: Masato Nakamura was asked if Sega had any plans to release Sonic on the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_00]: He did reply, Yes, we hope we can do something like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Was this a hint towards Dreamcast games being released on Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_00]: Or possibly some re-release of an old Sonic the Hedgehog game?
[SPEAKER_00]: on the 15th anniversary of the series.
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, for all you folks who are fans of the show, you'll know that my favorite topic of discussion is the PSP homebrew scene, and we've got some good stories for you this week.
[SPEAKER_00]: The first is going to be the brand new Super Nintendo emulator.
[SPEAKER_00]: SNES 9 version 0.4 has been updated, and this time the brand new feature is going to be wireless gameplay.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, you can do multiplayer via Wi-Fi ad hoc.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: One of the games that they've been able to run so far on it has been Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's been able to run at 60 frames per second while playing versus over Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's amazing.
[SPEAKER_00]: Can't wait to try that one out, actually.
[SPEAKER_00]: Another homebrew game that we've got coming out here is going to be Commander Keen.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, everyone's favorite shareware game is back.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've actually added emulation for all games.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: The emulator for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can actually run some of the Zork games, including Zork 1, 2, and 3.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can find out more information on that on PSP Updates, of course, and check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: I believe you need Zork 1 for DOS, and then they basically walk you through on how to be able to run that as a Game Boy ROM, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, let's switch focus here and talk about...
[SPEAKER_00]: Game System, Infinium Labs, Phantom
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_00]: News station WGN has apparently stumbled onto video game addiction.
[SPEAKER_00]: They've actually run a piece, Philadelphia's Channel 6, showing how video games could be like the next version of crack, the way they basically have portrayed video games, showing how kids ignore their families and ignore their dog.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, who cares?
[SPEAKER_00]: Dogs don't need attention anyways, especially when it comes down to video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the whole story is just a blatant ratings ploy, basically.
[SPEAKER_00]: And huge backlash over that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, so you've spent a lot of money, you've got your brand new TV to go with that new snazzy next-gen system.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, if you're thinking about buying a Blu-ray or HD DVD video player, think again.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_00]: 3 million HDTV owners out there are going to be screwed.
[SPEAKER_00]: Why are you guys going to be screwed?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, that's because the brand new next-gen systems, or at least the video systems, are only going to have HDMI or DVI connections.
[SPEAKER_00]: So your standard HDTV is not going to have that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, guess you should have bought a more expensive TV.
[SPEAKER_00]: So screw you, Sony, and screw you, Toshiba.
[SPEAKER_00]: And since we're on the topic of screwing people, let's talk about screwing Electronic Arts.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right, if you haven't pre-ordered Black, then you probably didn't know that there was actually a hidden code to get a brand new gun in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: The big fucking gun, as you would put it.
[SPEAKER_00]: 5SQQ-STHA-ZFFV-7XEV
[SPEAKER_00]: Have fun, enjoy the big fucking gun, and blow up a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, well that about does it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I will see you guys later.
[SPEAKER_00]: Enjoy this podcast, and we'll be back live again on March 5th.
[SPEAKER_00]: Talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you soon!