[SPEAKER_01]: Hello everyone, this is Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is Sunday, February 19th.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is episode 175, part 1 of 3 episodes that will be coming out this week and next.
[SPEAKER_01]: Both DarkSakura and Sky are out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sky is on the east coast cosplaying it up.
[SPEAKER_01]: And DarkSakura is off visiting relatives.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: One of those games that you're going to need to have a lot of patience for.
[SPEAKER_01]: It does get extremely hard towards the end of the game, and really I've been yelling and throwing controllers, so definitely something to think about, but one of the best ones for the 360 so far.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways, let's start things off here.
[SPEAKER_01]: First up, we've got some news here coming out from Capcom's Gamer Day, and they're
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, this is kind of a press-only event that they have here.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've announced a lot of different games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's start off here.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got Capcom's Classic Collection Remix, which is kind of a reiteration of the collection that they had on the PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, for the PSP, one of the other games that we had coming out, which is pretty sweet, is Capcom Puzzle World.
[SPEAKER_01]: It actually has a bunch of really cool games in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first one being Puzzle Fighter, one of my all-time favorite games for the
[SPEAKER_01]: PlayStation 2 and Arcade.
[SPEAKER_01]: The other thing that they've got is Block Block and Buster Brothers.
[SPEAKER_01]: So if you're a really big puzzle fan, that's going to be one that you're looking for.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's going to be coming out, looks like, on the PSP, which is going to be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of my other favorites that came out of that is going to be the Power Stone collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, for those of you who haven't played Power Stone, it's actually a pretty sweet arcade game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It came out in the Dreamcast for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: and it's a three-on-three just slugfest basically you collect these
[SPEAKER_01]: different gems that make you super powerful and you can pull off different moves well they actually are bringing out the collection now on the PSP which is going to have ad hoc multiplayer as well as a bunch of mini games so that's definitely going to be one to look forward to what was missing though was some of the bigger names in games of course that would be Resident Evil 5 and Devil May Cry 4 unfortunately those weren't looks like ready at the time they did
[SPEAKER_01]: have a big push behind their next-gen games, Lost Planet and the upcoming Mech Assault for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or actually, it's Mech Assault-style shooter for the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of reminding me a bit of Resident Evil with mechs in there, so it should be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, of course, Dead Rising, the complete ripoff of Dawn of the Dead, but still going to be a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And finally, one of the last games, also an old-time favorite, is Ultimate Ghosts and Goblins, which is definitely a throwback to the original side-scrolling game.
[SPEAKER_01]: They've added a few different things this time.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can actually use a shield, and they have a magic system in there as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely a lot of support for the PSP this time around, and a couple 360 games, so worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also...
[SPEAKER_01]: Street Fighter 2 on Xbox Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_01]: to kind of coincide here with the Xbox Live stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got a few more updates coming to some of the games that are already out.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of them being co-op over Xbox Live for Cameo, which should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not sure how that's going to make the game any better, but it should be pretty fun anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also some more multiplayer maps for Perfect Dark Zero, which should be pretty cool as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game I actually haven't even touched since I bought it, but here it's a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some other stuff coming to the 360 later on.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first thing is going to be Bomberman Act Zero, which is your favorite Bomberman type of game, except this time he's basically on steroids and taking it from a little cartoon character to some hardcore first-person Bomberman game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely a different take on the whole series, but it should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, the kind of...
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar Hero is coming to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Red Octane's Dean Ku told MCV,
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds like a lot of rumor to me, but should be still pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: One game we do know that is coming out on the 360 is going to be Phantasy Star Universe.
[SPEAKER_01]: It should be really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're actually going to be having... where you can interact with the other consoles and be able to transfer your character online.
[SPEAKER_01]: Different stats are going to be saved on these Sega servers.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it should actually appear on the 360, which is going to be...
[SPEAKER_01]: Final Fantasy XI
[SPEAKER_01]: So speaking of the 360, we do have some news regarding the Xbox shortages.
[SPEAKER_01]: This time they're blaming the memory chip makers, and one in particular, Infineon, having trouble making the right speed chips.
[SPEAKER_01]: Peter Moore refused to blame any one particular supplier, but he did blame the shortages on the component shortages.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, take it as you want, but I think it's a big excuse.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of the 360 a little bit more, one of the interesting developments that's actually come out of one of the recent edition of the Xbox magazine is DirecTV coming to the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: What they're talking about is actually being able to download episodes onto your 360 or possibly being able to use it as a DVR, which they've actually were talking about during this year's CES, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: GameCube, Twilight Princess
[SPEAKER_01]: This time is going to be coinciding with the launch of The Revolution, and that's going to be all the way into November again.
[SPEAKER_01]: One whole year wait for this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, that's really interesting that they're going to be launching a next-gen system with a current-gen title, but it is official.
[SPEAKER_01]: Straight from the mouth of the head of marketing, Reggie Fils-Aimé, told basically...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely a really good system, and the fact that the price point is going to be cheap as well, but hopefully we're not going to see current-gen stuff on the system, and hopefully they are going to be pushing the envelope a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, speaking about the revolution, Techno's first revolution game has been revealed, and the game actually is going to be sort of a mini-golf affair.
[SPEAKER_01]: Definitely interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's coming out here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like the game's going to be entitled Pena, and it's
[SPEAKER_01]: The web browser is based on Opera and will support most web features except for Macromedia Flash.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xbox Live
[SPEAKER_01]: and it's supposed to be comparable, if not exceeding that, of what is on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we'll have to see about that since Sony's plan for action for their online service has been very lacking, especially with the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Other things, talking about Sony here, the PS3 is definitely not going to have a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, a hard drive will be available, but not sold with the system.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're mainly doing this to keep the cost down on the system, which right now, analysts are saying is going to be upwards of $800 per unit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, whether this is actually going to be passed on to the consumer, that is, you know, us to see, I guess, when it eventually comes out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, the main cost of the unit right now is the Blu-ray drive, which is costing about $350 per
[SPEAKER_01]: No word on what the official price is going to be when this thing launches but hopefully it's not going to be too expensive.
[SPEAKER_01]: One game though that is going to be coming out for the PlayStation 3 and a favorite is Hot Shots Golf 5.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is confirmed for the PlayStation 3 and looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't know how well next-gen graphics are going to do for this game but still a really fun game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now one thing we are going to be looking at though is seeing how well the system launches.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Sony is expecting shipments for the PlayStation 3 to be in 2006 and they're definitely saying that there's not going to be any shortages.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, promises, promises.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll have to see though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, as far as other games coming out for the PlayStation 3, you have your normal big hits for the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_01]: SOCOM, the series is going to see its fourth edition for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is actually going to be at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_01]: It should be
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty interesting, of course.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a surprise to most people.
[SPEAKER_01]: God of War 2 is also slated for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whether it's going to be a launch title or not, that is to be seen.
[SPEAKER_01]: It should be pretty interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, as far as other next-gen systems, one system that's going to be coming out eventually is going to be the PlayStation Portable 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Samsung says it's actually in the works right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're making more flash memory chips for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_01]: Should be interesting that they're saying that... In addition, Samsung is making flash memory hard drives instead of a UMD player for the new PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, it'll be interesting to see if this is just rumor or if it's actually going to happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know that, especially with the larger memory chips, they've actually had problems with piracy and stuff, so hopefully they'll have that taken care of.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, I don't know about most of you people, but I know that my games...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that might not be a worry coming soon.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's actually a company called Scratchless that is bringing a brand new version of the CD-Rs and DVD media to the market.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right now they're working on technology that is basically you can do anything with this and you cannot scratch it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have a 4 micron layer of polymer that's being developed by GE right now and there is nothing you can do to scratch this.
[SPEAKER_01]: And right now
[SPEAKER_01]: with nearly a million dollars in funding.
[SPEAKER_01]: This should be coming to market pretty soon in their own line of blank media.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of DVDs, there was a story this week about Ui Bull and how he's fed up with the gamers and hating on his gaming movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, mainly most of the internet he's fed up with.
[SPEAKER_01]: The dangerous thing right now
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not really a bad thing that games are being made into movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, the Silent Hill movie is coming out right now, and it's going to be a really awesome movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, with games being made right now that are more cinematic and more realistic as far as how violent and stuff they are, it should be no surprise that they're passing a law in Utah that are grouping games in with porn, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Utah Representative David Hoegs attempts to lump violent games in with obscene pornography under law that has passed through Utah House Committee by a 7-2 vote.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, the law defines the offending games as those featuring inappropriate violence and lacking serious literary and artistic, political, and scientific value for minors.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's pretty vague.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think it's going to be constitutional and probably won't get put in place, but it'll be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now speaking of porn, the strangest group of individuals to bash on Grand Theft Auto has hit the news this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Prostitutes are actually calling for a ban of Grand Theft Auto based on the way players can pick up prostitutes and then kill them and steal their money.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently they didn't think too highly of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_01]: is in shock!
[SPEAKER_01]: as Black has been leaked to the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: The first person shooter that's going to be probably one of the best games for February has leaked to the internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a huge surprise, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: But what is a surprise is who they think the culprit is.
[SPEAKER_01]: They think it's actually one of their employees that they just recently let off.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of the 350 hardworking employees that stuck the proverbial knife in the back of EA.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not too surprised, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: The game is...
[SPEAKER_01]: Slated to hit store shelves though at the end of February, so check it out if you can legally.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now on a more positive note, it was announced that Play is going to be seeing one of our favorite artists out there, and that would be Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's going to be wearing Silent Hill Live.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: The competition will begin in Louisville, Kentucky at the Kentucky Exposition Center from June 15th through the 18th, followed by four additional events throughout the year, ending with the championships in December 2006.
[SPEAKER_01]: Each event will span three to five days and will be open to the public, and they'll be sponsored by Xbox 360 and presented by Intel, so it should be very interesting to see how big this ends up being.
[SPEAKER_01]: and finally I'm going to wrap up the podcast with my topic of stuff that I like talking about and that would be the hacking and cracking world there
[SPEAKER_01]: XBOX Live Arcade Games
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, they don't condone the piracy, but they do condone the sharing of the save games, so if you don't feel like beating your Call of Duty 2 or Need for Speed Most Wanted, definitely check out the website.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be xbox360gamesaves.com or actually 360gamesaves.com is what you want to check out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, my favorite topic here, the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of the games we do have coming out for the PSP is a longtime favorite on the PC, and that's going to be The Mist
[SPEAKER_01]: The first game is going to be put out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going to have bonus content in the form of new adventure scenarios as well as updating the game's visuals for the PSP widescreen format.
[SPEAKER_01]: No release date yet for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of the PSP, one of the brand new homebrew emulators that's been brought to the scene is going to be an Atari Jaguar emulator for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, all of those Jaguar owners out there are probably...
[SPEAKER_01]: So happy, all five of you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should be interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right now, the emulator is still very early in development and doesn't exactly run many cards.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, at this time, of course, we want to plug the Orange Lounge Radio PSP website.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be at olrpsp.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you can check out our podcasts on there as well as check out the shout line we have on there, our nice little chat feature there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, of course, if you're more into the instant messaging chat, you'll be happy to know that AOL Instant Messenger has been brought to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to www.aimonpsp.com and you'll actually be able to chat to all your AIM friends straight on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: So definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And finally, everyone's favorite website this week,
[SPEAKER_01]: has definitely been the Katamari Flash game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you haven't checked it out yet, what the hell are you waiting for?
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to go check it out right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be at katamaridamasi.jp slash qa underscore data slash katamari.html So definitely check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: See how big you can get the Katamari there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least waste a few minutes of your time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And finally this week, though, if you're looking for some new games, it's a good week for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Got one of the biggest ones of the month coming out, Fight Night Round 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be coming out on the 21st here.
[SPEAKER_01]: So definitely check that out, especially on the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Sonic Riders as well is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very good Sonic the Hedgehog racing game.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're more into a simulator racing game, Toko Race Driver 3 is going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You race from everything from big rigs.
[SPEAKER_01]: to Monster Trucks, to Sprint Cars, to even Riding Lawnmowers.
[SPEAKER_01]: So definitely check that out if you're into racing games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I hope you enjoyed this solo affair for the Orange Lawns Radio episode 175.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production For more information on our live and podcast programs visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you soon!