[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to the podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_08]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to listings with past episodes.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now the conclusion of episode number 173 for February 5th, 2006.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're back here for the second half of Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 173.
[SPEAKER_09]: For this, February the 5th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hope you guys are doing well.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had a pretty fun first half, very long first half.
[SPEAKER_09]: As you may or may not have heard, hopefully you guys have all went back and downloaded part A of the show, for those of you guys listening on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I was having a little bit of printing drama.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wasn't able to print my boarding pass for my flight tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki finally got the damn thing to work, and we printed my boarding pass during the break.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm very happy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if I do have a crappy B-Pass, damn you, Southwest and your stupid system.
[SPEAKER_09]: Even if I have a crappy B-Pass, at least it works.
[SPEAKER_09]: So thank you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: No mic?
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Christopher, like, you tangled me up in the chair.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, of course, if you didn't hear Part A, also, I'm in a very angsty Xbox 360 mood tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm not going there again.
[SPEAKER_09]: You'll just have to download Part A to figure out why.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if I sound bitter, I have a good reason.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's get back into it though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk about something else that makes a lot of people bitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's lack of Advent Children.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you know we were supposed to have this movie out like months ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, what did you do with it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I had it months ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but what did you do with the rest of our copies?
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's our English version of it?
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you do with it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I ate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Barf it up so we can have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, really.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where is Advent Children for the USA?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, I...
[SPEAKER_01]: We're supposed to be getting it sometime this year according to the digital bits, which is basically what's been said about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a quote.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's taking a little extra time to work with the director to get all of the supplemental elements finished, which is why it's delayed.
[SPEAKER_01]: For as long as it's taking us to get it, I feel really awful for our friends in the UK who are probably not even getting it until after we do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, it's February.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's my Advent Children?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this thing going to still sell when it comes out?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to have to have a lot of extras.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, people are going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know they will.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, I'm very much in a wait and see mode over this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can watch it whenever I want.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm trying not to be too pushy on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I want to see the stuff on the desks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to watch it on my computer the first time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to watch it on a TV, a big TV, as big as possible, for the first time.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want it pixelated or none of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want it beautiful.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mine's actually a full DVD rip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn you people.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks pretty on my screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to be legit with this here, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: I legitimately downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to support Square and Sony here, but I'm finding it harder and harder to as this thing keeps getting delayed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever the problem is, fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_01]: If it's to my credit, I have removed it from my hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You had a release date on this at one point, and now it's shot again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they keep pulling it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was even a rumor going around saying that they're redoing all the animations to match the English dubbing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, I guess that would be a good reason why it's taken so long.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, that might be a decent reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nah, I don't think that's what the reason is.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the UK was actually, there was an article I think out this week about the UK and they're getting theirs in 2006 as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I'd imagine they don't have to do any sort of localization for a UK release.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's move on and talk about something that's going on in Japanese arcades right now, but not US ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's going on is Soul Calibur 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: The PlayStation 2 exclusive game is finally hitting the arcades where it needs to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to actually have all the same characters from the home version along with some redesigned versions of three bonus characters from that version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amy, Li-Long, and Wong-Syung-Kyung.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe that's how you pronounce that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Will I be able to take my custom dancer character and use it in the arcades?
[SPEAKER_07]: That I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says when the player finishes the game of Soul Calibur 3 Arcade Edition, the screen will display a barcode symbol and password.
[SPEAKER_07]: This will be used to join an online mobile phone-based Soul Calibur 3 game called Mobile Conquest Mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, by taking a snapshot of the barcode symbol with the person's mobile phone and using the password, players can register their characters and challenge other players throughout the country via Soul Calibur 3's mobile phone website.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of unique.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is unique.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I realize mobile phone is way bigger in other countries than it is here, but that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish it would take off here, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game is slated for release in the fall in Japan and should be coming out here I'm sure at some point.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like to see Soul Calibur 3 in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know everybody said, oh, PlayStation 2 exclusive, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Exclusive Windows up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Soul Calibur 2 is a great, great arcade game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd love to see 3 hit the arcades, although I kind of think it should have been the arcades first.
[SPEAKER_09]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: If they can come up with these kind of cool features like it sounds like they're doing, if they can carry some of that coolness over to the US, I won't have such an issue with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, you know, we were talking also in the first half because we had an email about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we started as a DDR-centric station.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, of course, music and rhythm games, we love them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, Loki, you have an article to hit the Internet this week about rhythm games, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameSpot ran the 10 spot, the top 10 rhythm games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, another list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody loves lists.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lists are what they do when news gets slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's human interest.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: First,
[SPEAKER_07]: Samba de Amigo
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Number 9, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this in order or is this just 10?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this is just 10 in no particular order.
[SPEAKER_07]: This one actually was on the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Osu!
[SPEAKER_07]: Tatake Uiden, which was for Nintendo DS, was kind of a game we never saw.
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard of this game, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people are importing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar-O-Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_01]: Guitar-O-Man!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vib-Ribbon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love that they're not excluding import titles and things that weren't released here because there were a lot of good stuff that weren't released here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, the original guitar favorite, Guitar Freaks, Busta Groove, or Busta Move, however you want to call it, Frequency, then Guitar Hero, and you know, let's see here, of course, Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they named third mix specifically, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say Third Mix was definitely a peak.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had so many great licenses.
[SPEAKER_01]: I remember way back in your old apartment of doom.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first time I ever got a little bod thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Watching you play DDR, not DDR, playing the Jungle Book game on the Jungle Book pad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Baby's first dancing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had my little mini for midgets.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was a DDR pad for midgets for the Jungle Book dancing game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jamie Fix.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: So is that it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Was that ten?
[SPEAKER_09]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get Guitar Freaks off that list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Put Beatmania in there instead.
[SPEAKER_09]: No crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we can all say the Guitar Hero kind of improved on Guitar Freaks, so there's no need for both of them on the list there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get rid of Guitar Freaks and put Beatmania in there instead.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else missing?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think otherwise it's a pretty solid list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Space Channel 5?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, good call.
[SPEAKER_09]: That should have been somewhere on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, good call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Space Channel 5 is a great game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would have said Amplitude over Frequency.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm at least glad there's a little bit of Harmonix love in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Karaoke Revolution's not on the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: In which two, it's Loki says, good!
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like their game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: comments from the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, we've got folks saying no Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_09]: PKakira88 says no Pump It Up, no In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rini says, where's poppin' music?
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots of interesting choices.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's the thing about lists, you guys, is so that they can leave something off just to ruffle your feathers about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did it work?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I love reading Kojima's blog.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that he's a pretty interesting person.
[SPEAKER_01]: And kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just like the pictures up there with his little foxhound thing on the side.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of interesting insight into what he's got going on, as well as opinions of certain other people, which I'll leave for somebody else to bring up.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he also apparently just...
[SPEAKER_01]: has all kinds of things sneaking out in his blog, along with changes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Didn't you notice a couple?
[SPEAKER_09]: I honestly haven't really read it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I will visit it now that it's hit your list.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, also, though, you can find the link to Kojima's podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that's right, and I have a quick little follow-up on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, I do know something about that because I saw something on another site about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, that podcast is going to be delivered in English soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Hideo Kojima is not going to suddenly start speaking English for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, what's going to happen is that it's going to be handled by the international manager, Ryan Payton.
[SPEAKER_09]: Payton's going to summarize Kojima's podcast and bring on guests and give behind-the-scenes information on the latest happenings of the company.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not really like a word-for-word blog, but it's, you know, it's like the English spinoff, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you want to give the address there for folks who want to look up that blog?
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely, and I'm going to give the link to the English blog.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's www.blog.konami.jp slash gs slash hideoblog underscore e. All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Visit it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love it, because DarkSakura said so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, one thing that will not come up on the Hideo Kojima blog ever again...
[SPEAKER_07]: What's this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be an Uwe Boll adaptation of Metal Gear Solid, and to which I will paraphrase, because he says, absolutely not, over my dead body, fuck you, Uwe Boll.
[SPEAKER_07]: He did not say fuck you, Uwe Boll, you're not paraphrased.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, basically, there's no way, they didn't contact him on it, they would never let him touch that property, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: because Alone in the Dark sucked ass, as did other movies like Blood Rain, which only pulled in $2.4 million over 30 days.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I made $2.4 million in 30 days, that would be a great thing, because then I could fund my evil empire.
[SPEAKER_09]: But for a movie in Hollywood to make $2.4 million over 30 days and not be like an arthouse movie type thing...
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not saying much considering that the production budget of the movie is $25 million and the marketing costs apparently reached about $22 million putting it a good They marketed that movie?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I maybe saw one billboard.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That puts it in the hole quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hey, if you still want to see more Weevil wonderful movies and stuff, there's In the Name of the King, two-part Weevil.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop plugging that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody wants to see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just don't plug it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Epic movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three hours of crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't plug it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming out in November.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: My FU of the week goes toward my own body for betraying me in a most heinous fashion.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went over to one of my co-workers house to help her and her son with their mp3 player and I forgot about her dogs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now normally if I'm around a dog I'll get sniffy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I might itch a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Normally I take like a Benadryl before I go over there and I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm there for all of ten minutes and I start to feel the sniffy.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I start to feel my eyes itch a little bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was like, yeah, it's allergies.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm leaving in a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, within not even five minutes of that, suddenly my eyes were swollen shut.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were bloodshot.
[SPEAKER_01]: I burst two blood vessels in my left eye.
[SPEAKER_01]: and my eyes had swollen so much they were pulling the skin tight around my eyes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_01]: It was really disgusting and then they were all gumming up and it was all bloody.
[SPEAKER_09]: And many podcast listeners just threw up in their mouths there with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was very disgusting.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going into detail so that people will understand my level of rather well-contained rage right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, and you know, I wasn't really, you know, my friend kept apologizing.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not her fault.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, she...
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had my glasses off at that point, and I turned and looked at her, and she was like, OH MY GOD!
[SPEAKER_01]: And started to get out of the car.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, Tia!
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_01]: I just have zombie eyes.
[SPEAKER_01]: My eyes, I actually took a picture of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: How it was after, get this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Will you post it on the website?
[SPEAKER_01]: I will.
[SPEAKER_01]: Three doses of Benadryl.
[SPEAKER_01]: And all kinds of eye drops, including, I got those neat Japanese minty eye drops, though, that make your eyes feel all cold.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I slept with a cold compress on my face for two days I went to the doctor yesterday because it actually the bone around my left eye started to hurt and so he gave me some lovely drugs and now most of the swelling is down but it's still there I looked yesterday like I got punched in the eye Dan proceeded to say well that's what you get for not ducking my husband
[SPEAKER_01]: So yeah, fuck you to my jeans.
[SPEAKER_01]: I blame mommy and daddy and all the drugs they did in the 70s.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Loki, your turn.
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU this week goes to the restaurant chain known as Hooters.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you for your really crappy service and your really crappy food.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went there actually on Saturday to get some food and, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: People wanted to go to Hooters to check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nellie had never been.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we got there, and I give them my name.
[SPEAKER_07]: They write my name down as Ben.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, no, it's Matt.
[SPEAKER_07]: They write down Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, that's close enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're waiting, we're waiting, we're waiting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Finally, we get seated and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It takes them a half an hour to take our order.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then afterwards, we're waiting, waiting, waiting.
[SPEAKER_07]: It takes an hour for us to get our food.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they hadn't even delivered the wings we had ordered, which were going to be an appetizer.
[SPEAKER_07]: On top of all that, just the people there were retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, just completely retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're trying to talk to these people, and their coke was really watered down, and their burgers weren't that great, and the wings, you know what, even if they are world famous, they sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, fuck Hooters, I will never be going back there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Arsef in the chatroom says, who goes to Hooters for the food?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's definitely not for the intelligence.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome to Hooters!
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to add on Loki's hatred for Hooters.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's not that great.
[SPEAKER_09]: Their food isn't that good.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the girls are like, thank you for coming to here.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're like, they have more brains in their boobs than they do in their head.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can address those cards and letters to extifer at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Email me your amazing, you know, stories on how I meant something in your life.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this debut here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, speaking of something meaningful, Kingdom Hearts 2 is a very meaningful game to some of us, and we've been waiting to hear some news on the US version, but do you got something for us?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, actually I've got a confirmed list of some of the voice actors in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we have Haley Jo Osment, of course, as Sora.
[SPEAKER_01]: For Aerith, it's Mena Suvari from American Beauty.
[SPEAKER_01]: One I don't want to say because it's very, very spoilery.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should I spoil?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, plug your ears real quick.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's in it for like a very short time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: So close your eyes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Close your ears.
[SPEAKER_01]: One, two, three.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tifa.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rachel Lee Cook from Antitrust.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, open your ears again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like they heard that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Riku, David Gallagher, Kyrie, Hayden Panettiere, Ruxus, Jesse McCartney, Namin, Brittany Snow, Hades, James Woods, Chicken Little, Zach Boff, Cloud, Steve Burton,
[SPEAKER_01]: and I do not see anything about bringing back my man as my man.
[SPEAKER_05]: David Boreanaz as Squall?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Leon, remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, sorry, Leon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: On IMDB they had him listed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, by IMDB.
[SPEAKER_01]: IMDB lies.
[SPEAKER_01]: IMDB, all they did was copy the same people who played whoever in whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, IMDB is a... I will not say lying piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will just say inaccurate source.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do agree.
[SPEAKER_09]: But for the stuff that's already out, they're pretty reliable.
[SPEAKER_07]: And no Pirates of the Caribbean voice actors, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, nothing listed there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And no Lance Bass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no reason scheduling conflicts to their new movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although, in an article that I read, they were taking great care to capture some very Keith Richards-like motion for how he would walk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, all this talk on Kingdom Hearts, I think we need to bring back a segment, because we've been doing this new format for a little while, and part of the reason we went to the new format is so we could bring segments from our live show we used to do, and one of those segments is...
[SPEAKER_03]: List lists!
[SPEAKER_03]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, now I know our podcast listeners are hearing list lists for the first time, so we're going to kind of set this up for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those of you guys listening live tonight on Sunday night, you guys get to directly participate in this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your votes will come up with the lists.
[SPEAKER_09]: As we've been talking about in the show, people love to make lists.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're no different here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once in a while, we like to take a topic, and we like to come up with the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: So I bet you're all dying to know tonight's topic and see how this works here.
[SPEAKER_09]: The topic for tonight is World I Most Want to See in Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now here's the catch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doesn't have to be related to Disney or Square.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're living in a fantasy world right now, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: We realize that it's got to be Disney or Square to realistically be in a Kingdom Hearts game, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: We live in a fantasy world here at Orange Lounge Radio, so we're opening it up to any fandom, any cartoon, whatever you want, any type of Kingdom Hearts world you think ought to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's your chance to name it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to come up with the Orange Launch Radio definitive list.
[SPEAKER_09]: One other small little teensy weensy change.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're doing a list list from the way we used to do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: When the chat room votes, you will be able to pick not just one, but now you can pick a number one and a number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can actually pick two things from the top list.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you do have to tell me what's your number one and what's your number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: And if you don't specify, I'll assume the first thing you listed was your number one.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Enough chatter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get to the list, shall we?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start making our list here.
[SPEAKER_09]: And DarkSakura, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_09]: What's your number three pick for a world you would most like to see in Kingdom Hearts 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doom.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doom?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now would this be with The Rock or not?
[SPEAKER_09]: This would be hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we have Doom on the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any other reasons why you want to see Doom?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to put the characters in hell?
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just like to see really fucked up things.
[SPEAKER_09]: No kidding, lady.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're number three.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was actually picking more Disney-themed stuff, so Darkwing Duck.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Darkwing Duck level.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, I like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Are you the terror that flaps in the night?
[SPEAKER_09]: My number three pick is, I didn't have a better name for this, so I'm calling it Secret of Mana World.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's another great square game that ought to be given some love.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Secret of Mana World.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dare I ask, Extrofer, what's your number three pick?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to be pretty predictable.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to choose Silent Hill World.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: My number two, Labyrinth.
[SPEAKER_01]: With David Bowie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And his member.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh yes, and his member.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there were two stars, there were three stars in that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jennifer Connelly, David Bowie, and David Bowie Schlong.
[SPEAKER_07]: And each of the characters will be dressed up in tight pants with giant packages.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: And your special helper will be the little dog on the other dog.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or Bluto.
[SPEAKER_09]: So bad!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's keep it moving.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your number two pick for worlds you most want to see in Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since all the answers have been quite ridiculous, how about we do Hello Kitty world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sanrio world, there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello Kitty, Chrono Trigger World, and then traveling in time.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be complex.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xtifer, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I think that I'm going to go with Serenity World.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because... And this is collective Joss Whedon fanboy coming out.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you have Mal as your... Cat in tight pants as your partner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's going to age you and maybe have a hot sex scene too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Against the men with blue hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Time for the number ones.
[SPEAKER_09]: You ready for it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Number one worlds.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're making the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once we've done this, this is done.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is all sealed and done.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're sending it to Square and saying this is what we want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't listen to what anybody else says.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the top three right here.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your number one fantasy world for Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time world.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not any of that crap water world crap from Dreamwaker.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Legend of Zelda World.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, something that would never happen, the Nintendo thing on the Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if anyone looks at my DeviantArt profile, I have done fan art for this.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's hardcore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hardcore nerd.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was tough.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to go more realistic and do like, you know, Treasure Planet or Rocketeer, speaking of fighting Nazis.
[SPEAKER_07]: But since we're going ridiculous, DOA Beach Volleyball World.
[SPEAKER_01]: I almost put that one on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: DOA Beach Volleyball World.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what exactly would you be fighting?
[SPEAKER_09]: You would be fighting clothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just see this doing nothing but playing volleyball there, because when you go to the undersea level in Kingdom Hearts 2, all you do is sing.
[SPEAKER_01]: You sing under the sea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: My number one pick is Microsoft World.
[SPEAKER_09]: And in Microsoft World, things glitch out.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have to fight the evil glitches and things that disappear.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the world just disappears suddenly on you and things go blank.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a real crazy level.
[SPEAKER_09]: What was that one game on GameCube that totally messed with you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Eternal Darkness, was that it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it Bitterness World?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, Microsoft World actually is what this is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's be glad the Tron world is not powered by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my number one pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Extifer, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet you I know what this is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just have a feeling.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just need to go that one step further in my Joss Whedon fandom and create once more with Feeling World.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you were just going to say Buffy World.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it was the musical episode of Buffy.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was great, especially with the whole hot lesbian scene with Tara and Willow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do so much with that world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's see, now here's the part where the chatroom yells at us for the things we didn't put on the list, and guess what guys, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't have this anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see, we have Minimi283 says Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy World, Legend of Zaku, YTMND World.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Roz says, Beer Pong World, Nintendo Maniac 64, Hentai World, Sephiroth 1215, Oregon Trail World.
[SPEAKER_01]: We all die of dysentery or a bear eats us.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a great one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fireboma, Pleasure Island, Monkey Island, coming from MiniMe283, PKAcura88, Dragon Ball Z. Lots and lots of great picks from you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rio World World.
[SPEAKER_09]: Too bad, because here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: So now's the fun part, because this is where we get mad at each other, because we're going to take off some from the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here it is as it stands right now, the top 12.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doom World, Darkwing Duck, Secret of Mana World, Silent Hill World, Labyrinth World, Hello Kitty or Sanrio World, Chrono Trigger World, Serenity World, Zelda Ocarina of Time, DOA Beach Volleyball, Microsoft World, and Buffy the Musical World.
[SPEAKER_09]: Once more with Feeling World, if you so choose.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so DarkSakura, one of these has got to come off the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's going off the list?
[SPEAKER_01]: Move your hand out of my way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft World, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: You evil little bitchling.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why did you take that one off?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I don't want to play a reality game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to play something for fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm okay with that answer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, Loki, what's coming off this list?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I'm just going to have to take off
[SPEAKER_07]: D.O.A.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beach Volleyball World
[SPEAKER_01]: I like that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sora was going to become a man.
[SPEAKER_09]: You took that away from him.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's done is done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now he'll never get any because he's never going to find Kairi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Extra Pearl, what's the last one coming off this list?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'm going to go with Hello Kitty World.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Hello Kitty World.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's your turn to vote.
[SPEAKER_09]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your top two.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your number one and your number two.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Doom, Darkwing Duck, Secret of Mana World, Silent Hill World, Labyrinth World, Chrono Trigger World, Serenity World, and Zelda Ocarina of Time World.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us what worlds would you most want to see in Kingdom Hearts 3, assuming that, you know, Disney and Square only is out of the picture, your fantasy world.
[SPEAKER_09]: Send those over private message and we'll reveal the answers a little later in the show, the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the meantime, more news.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we're going to go on over to Loki, who's going to tell us what's going on
[SPEAKER_09]: with the Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we talked about some of this in the first half, but you had a little more like PSP also.
[SPEAKER_09]: So what's going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, basically they're just boasting that their online service is going to be better than Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, so they said that this time it's very real.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony is dead serious about their online service and it's being designed to match the service of Xbox Live and exceed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're going to be basically, as mentioned before, linking a lot of the PSP and PS3 stuff together.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, promises, promises.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that a little bit too much too late?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Xbox Live has already established themselves as the definitive... Well, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: If Sony puts out something better, there's no reason they can't take the crown.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not necessarily going to be their big thing, though, because you can have beta, which is better than VHS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, their plan of, you know, fuck it, we don't need a plan, didn't really work out too well with the PS2, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to have to try it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, oddly enough, wasn't Beta by Sony?
[SPEAKER_05]: Something to think about there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go over to DarkSakura, who likes to keep tabs on what's going on overseas because we love our listeners throughout the world, not just those here in America.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, we love the America ones, we love the Canada ones, and all the other countries, but the UK doesn't get enough love from a lot of gaming things out there because they get games late and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, DarkSakura, what's going on in the UK?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, actually, the first thing we have up is that Daedalus is doing a new Xbox 360 hard drive.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's supposed to be 2 inches square, weighing 4 ounces.
[SPEAKER_01]: The drive will be able to store thousands of songs and over 5,000 images.
[SPEAKER_01]: The idea is you can transfer MP3s from your PC to your Xbox 360 or whack all of your JPEGs and use your TV to watch them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically a 4 gigabyte USB drive that's shaped like the power button on the 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Close.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're actually giving a speculated price of 99.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkPlanets is already taking pre-orders for 74.99.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's in pounds.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, though, they still have not yet confirmed the price point.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're still working with the distributors, but an official price will be out along with their release date next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So about $150 USD
[SPEAKER_05]: About 150 US.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, there is a very interesting bit of news about Dead or Alive 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: It has basically removed Need for Speed Most Wanted from the top position and has taken number one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, it's a pretty game, but I don't know how it got to be number one.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: From what I saw about it, because I saw very little of it, because, you know, Rob's Xbox broke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, I say that Rob's Xbox broke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for the reminder.
[SPEAKER_09]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, his Xbox broke.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so, basically, when I saw it, though, it did look really pretty, but I don't think I would ever play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was pretty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they're saying that all across the board, the top three titles in the charts are all on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, four Xbox 360 exclusives have come into the top 20 for the first time since the December 2005 launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got Call of Duty 2, we have Project Gotham Racing 3 at number 7.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also Perfect Dark Zero that hopped up from 27 to be at number 14.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Sega's Condemned is also back in the top 40.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's coming in actually at number 18, they said.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I thought Condemned was a really good game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That should be higher up there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But honestly, people are liking what they're playing for those with working systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: One other bit of news, too, is that there are
[SPEAKER_01]: I heard about there were doing some layoffs here in the US, so it probably has a lot of people over there on edge, but not going to happen, hmm?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what it's looking like.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their UK studio is in Chertsey.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks like it's coming out without the job cuts that we're all seeing over here in the US.
[SPEAKER_01]: The studio is supposed to be cutting off, I think, 5% of their global workforce.
[SPEAKER_01]: There haven't really been any indications.
[SPEAKER_01]: One of their spokespersons said that they cannot confirm that there's not any that might come up.
[SPEAKER_01]: To go ahead and give the quote, every division is going through evaluation.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're looking around the company to see how to best align teams everywhere against what needs to happen for future growth, which means we're giving you a noncommittal answer because we can.
[SPEAKER_01]: So far, about 350 people were cut in the U.S., laid off from the Vancouver, Redwood Shores, and Tiburon jobs.
[SPEAKER_01]: The joys of corporations.
[SPEAKER_09]: It happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Too bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I wish the U.K.
[SPEAKER_01]: employees a good bit of luck.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, another bit, actually...
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks like February 17th, Shadow of the Colossus will be out in the UK.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a pretty neat game from what I understand.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't played it myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't get too into it, but it's kind of one of those games, try it out, because it's kind of a polarizing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: People either really like it or they don't get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, certainly for those of you guys who have been really wanting to check this game out, you're going to get a chance.
[SPEAKER_09]: So good for opportunity.
[SPEAKER_09]: I believe in choices.
[SPEAKER_09]: So go for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Breath of Fire 3 for the PSP
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Breath of Fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: Command & Conquer, the first decade, also, that's on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dora the Explorer on GBA.
[SPEAKER_01]: EA Sports Rugby 2006, full auto, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is Dora the Explorer popular over there, too?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an early childhood game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry if she's popular over there, although it's a great Halloween costume.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw some Dora Halloweens, funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they would only get Nickelodeon by Sky Satellite.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mario and Luigi Partners in Time, Mario Party 7, Space Invaders Evolution on the PSP, Star Wars Empire at War on PC, Tales of Eternia on PSP, The Rub Rabbits on DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never heard it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It must be something over there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dear UK listeners, please tell me what The Rub Rabbits are.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Rub Rabbits would be the sequel to Philly the Magic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I thought that had... Change names.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, I thought it was something really perverted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where do babies come from?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, where do babies come from?
[SPEAKER_01]: You have bunnies!
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_01]: And last up, Totally Spies for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_01]: I, however, am feeling very happy for our friends over there because on the 17th they get Guilty Gear Yusuka.
[SPEAKER_01]: That game is cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Very, very cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: And Super Monkey Ball Touch and Go comes out on the 17th as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I will be going more into detail when the time comes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, do you have some release dates for the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming this week, we'll be getting Arena Football in the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's Ride Silver Buckle
[SPEAKER_07]: Stables, crappy game for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Resident Evil Deadly Silence coming to the Nintendo DS, which should be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rub Rabbits also coming to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Street Fighter Alpha 3 Max coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gotta love those Street Fighter titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tales of Legendia coming to the PS2, which kind of combines a fighting game and RPG in the one, which is really neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, our favorite company, Konami, World Soccer Winning 11.9 coming to PS2, Xbox, and
[SPEAKER_07]: PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later on the month, of course, we've got Drakengard 2, Grandia 3, Mark Echo's Getting Up, State of Emergency 2, which will be fun, also dropped down to $29.99, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fight Night Round 3, really big boxing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Touka Race Driver 3, which will be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exit, Sonic Riders coming to the PlayStation 2, Xbox, and GameCube.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then a bunch of other stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, we'll cover those once we get closer to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lots and lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're starting to get back into it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, summertime will be really big too.
[SPEAKER_09]: March is going to be a big month as far as stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, you also have a little bit of a follow-up to something DarkSakura talked about.
[SPEAKER_09]: She was talking about DOA4's success over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's going on with DOA4?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're doing an update.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be a patch which is coming out in mid-February.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's going to be happening is they're going to be balancing some of the characters as well as
[SPEAKER_07]: fixing the bug with lots of save games and one of the rumors is going to be that they're changing the interface and adding a new character one of the new characters that they're talking about here well at least rumored is going to be a Taekwondo character basically one of the things that they found out between you know kind of browsing some of the data files on there seeing a big section of characters missing and just some other stuff so that would be something to look forward to
[SPEAKER_07]: Coming mid-February.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something else that's going to be coming out soon, and this is according to Pacific Business News, is that an online version of the classic puzzle game Tetris is going to be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now I'm kind of thinking, wait, don't we already have Tetranet?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, why would you want to pay?
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing is that Tetris Online is going to allow people to do this game and other casual games for just $3 a month.
[SPEAKER_09]: So they're trying to put this at like a super low price point for folks to do this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still say, though, you got Tetranet for free that's still out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's going to have to have some features to make this worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't know if this is trying to ride on the coattails of projected success for Tetris DS or what.
[SPEAKER_09]: But nevertheless, this is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Something that should be noted is that this is being funded by Hank Rogers, who sold his interest in the blue lava wireless mobile phone company Jamdat in 2005.
[SPEAKER_09]: That stock sale will net him another $108 million via Jamdat's upcoming sale to Electronic Arts.
[SPEAKER_09]: His partner for Tetris Online will be former Nintendo of America president Minoru Arakawa.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good minds coming together because the mobile phone Tetris is actually pretty good for a mobile phone game.
[SPEAKER_09]: So promising things coming out of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: This may not be just crappy Tetris knockoff.
[SPEAKER_09]: This could be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I did need to make a statement on something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did want to go and also correct myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually told you wrong regarding the subsistence.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now I'm doing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Subsistence.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll just call it Metal Gear 3 S. Subsistence.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mistakes happen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you sometimes look at what's going on in the hacking and cracking world.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's been hacked now?
[SPEAKER_07]: First thing is the original Xbox DVD firmware has been hacked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is that important?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, with the hacked firmware...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Xbox doesn't realize a game is burned or is an original copy.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can pop anything in there without a mod chip and it will run.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's something that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what's important about that also is the firmware on the original Xbox is very similar to the firmware that's in the new Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're thinking that maybe they can break it the same way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rise of the Triad
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want to check that out, PSP Updates has a download for you for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, for the Nintendo DS Linux, they actually have added Wi-Fi support, which is pretty cool there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you've got a modded DS, definitely check that one out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, the PSP has some more functionality added to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they have a homebrew program to use your PSP as a universal remote.
[SPEAKER_07]: And finally, one last thing here, P6, the
[SPEAKER_07]: Shell coming to the PlayStation firmware 1.5 has been released and that's actually kind of a new GUI that they've added and a lot more functionality is going to be going into that as well so look for more updates from us and also you'll probably hear some more things on PSP updates as well and let's see finally they've had some rumors about new firmware updates coming which are going to allow email and GPS to be added to
[SPEAKER_07]: The PSP's list of enhancements.
[SPEAKER_07]: So email and GPS possibly coming later on.
[SPEAKER_09]: 916-226-9067
[SPEAKER_09]: So please ask Mommy and Daddy if you don't own the phone line.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you own the phone line, hey, do what you want.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, but we're going to be taking Skype line calls very soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: But since there's a bit of a delay, before we go to that, we want to go ahead and announce tonight's listless winners.
[SPEAKER_09]: Votes are in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember, this is the Kingdom Hearts 3 world we would most like to see.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, of course, we're living in a fantasy world.
[SPEAKER_09]: It doesn't have to be square or square.
[SPEAKER_09]: Disney-related.
[SPEAKER_09]: It could be anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: The votes are tallied, and this is the definitive list through this highly scientific process.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number three world we most want to see, the Zelda Ocarina of Time world is the number three world they most want to see.
[SPEAKER_09]: The number two world the kids most want to see is the Doom world.
[SPEAKER_09]: They want to see them go to hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, and the number one world, as voted by our chatroom, this is something that could actually happen, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chrono Trigger World is the number one voted answer there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool, very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: No love for Serenity, extrovert, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it got some pity votes.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you say, the Silent Hill World?
[SPEAKER_09]: Silent Hill World, I think, was a close fourth, I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, actually Silent Hill World was kind of trailing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Darkwing Duck almost made it though.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was number four.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we'll do a list list again soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know we have to do match games sometime too.
[SPEAKER_09]: We haven't done that in forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see if we have interviews or not next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all time pending stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's go to the Skype line and hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: So again, it's 916-226-9067 or you can call us on Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's username OrangeLoungeRadio is who you want to call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Xander from Florida.
[SPEAKER_09]: Xander, you call us too damn much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, what's on your mind this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing better to do on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd like to point out real quick, you're saying that Chrono Trigger could actually appear on Kingdom Hearts 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hypothetically, they could do one of those loophole things, or are you talking about it's a rights issue?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the characters... They could, but Nomura won't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy is strictly background cameo stuff in Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will never be a world in Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have any idea where I could get Vibra Bun?
[SPEAKER_09]: Any idea?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do they still push new copies of that around on some of the import sites?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I ordered one so, so long ago that I don't know if they still sell this anymore because it's a PS1 title.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I would say probably your best bet is going to be something like eBay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't be afraid to try Yahoo Auctions, but the Japanese one.
[SPEAKER_09]: might be a good place to try.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yeah, you're going to pay more money to get shipped over here, but if you really want the game bad enough... I didn't expect that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other suggestions you guys have?
[SPEAKER_07]: Liksang?
[SPEAKER_09]: Liksang, maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's going to be hard to find because it's PS1, but if you want a PS2 title that's similar, you can always try Mojib Ribbon.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard it's very language intensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a different game as well, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's close.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the closest thing you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, good luck to you, Xander, finding that.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you find a copy, let us know so we can tell our listeners where you found it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, Xander.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to another call here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's General Psy, I got the name there, but you're breaking up just a little bit, but go ahead and get your questions out.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: First and foremost, I'm kind of angry at my computer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me get... Yeah, we're kind of angry at your computer right now, too, because it keeps cutting you out.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can't hear you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to have to let you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're just kind of not there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think somebody should call in and do the... Have you checked the children?
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to do one more call here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all the net traffic's tied up because of the stupid bull.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's try going to another call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously, you already know who this is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could this be the legend of Zaku?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you're on the mark.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's set aside ten minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, since I started that, you know, since I started a, you know, a weekend habit of just playing 2DX really drunk, I kind of need, I kind of need suggestions of, of liquors that would go great with that sort of activity.
[SPEAKER_02]: How old are you, young man?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm 21.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been 21 for about, for over a month.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, just wanted to make sure you're of age, because we can't encourage this if you're under 21.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, liquors that go good with playing 2DX.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guinness.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do enjoy Guinness.
[SPEAKER_09]: Vodka?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hard liquors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything 40% alcohol.
[SPEAKER_09]: Take a shot of 151 and drop it in a glass of Guinness.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's called an Irish Car Bomb.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyways, besides that, I'm surprised that they charge money for cell phone games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though as a person who happens to make them for a senior project in order to get it out of college, I find it appalling.
[SPEAKER_02]: And people charge, you know, that company's charged monthly for a damn game Yeah, the monthly fees is a little bit, now I'm like, okay, well obviously you can charge money for a game Because, you know, that's how, that's what funds these people's paychecks Yeah, but I mean, I thought most games were just like, you know, two, three dollars and that was it But then they have the gall to charge you monthly
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, the repeat thing's a little lame for the cell phones, especially when they're bad games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know companies like Sprint that they charge a certain amount of money for a certain amount of time, and then you have to keep paying it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't buy them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't support that crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I see a game that they want to charge a monthly fee, I say, screw it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, as I said, certain phone providers and game contractors
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: See...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's up to the programmer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anything else on your mind, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully, a lot hasn't been touched up on Supernova yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since location testing already happened and the next one is going to be
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, good, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, fixed bugs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fine by me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, that's the idea of dual locations.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's only what I've been hearing from other places.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, you know, it's a little bit of rumor at this point.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure the game will be fine when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, hopefully, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, Zaku, time's up.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm letting you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, that was the Skype line, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how you do the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how we do it here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we're getting towards the end of the program here, but not until we bring you one last story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Couple more stories.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yes, Loki, why don't you start us off then, since you must have found some late additions here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody loves making fun of Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_07]: But remember his Modest Game Proposal?
[SPEAKER_09]: Justin, I thought we could go one week without that name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, I'm not talking about Jack Thompson.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm talking about his Modest Game Proposal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And someone else finished one of their games for the Modest Game Proposal.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called I'm Okay, a Murder Simulator.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can check it out, actually, at... Unfortunately, the website that was hosting it went down, so they have it mirrored here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's...
[SPEAKER_07]: 67.15.42.30 slash I'm okay and you can check it out there it's a 12 meg download has nice Super Nintendo looking graphics and you basically murder and murder and murder and murder and lots of murdering and it's great so definitely check that out
[SPEAKER_07]: And finally, for those people who are fans of Burnout, they're doing a promo now with the retail kiosk that you can find out there for the Xbox 360, where you can bring your memory card to the location and download an exclusive Burnout Revenge card that's actually going to be Xbox 360 themed, as well as a dashboard theme and gamer pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just wanted to say, I got a quick tip here from a chatter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, Mike.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says that JapanVideoGames.com has VibRibbon.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Xander, go take a look there, and hopefully you can get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just to say, I've ordered through them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, they're good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bought Beatmania through them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I bought my Drummania through them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Their prices usually tend to be very comparable.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no free advertising.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying, as I don't want to misguide any of our listeners, and we have gone through a number of importers among us, avoid buy-write at all costs.
[SPEAKER_09]: They suck!
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: They owe me $70.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you can take me with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you could fly to the country and buy it there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And take me with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if that's an option.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's get on to our last story tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Last story.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, no more stories, Loki.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have no more.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_09]: So DarkSakura, this is a good note to finish up on tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's coming our way pretty soon?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, this has to do with our good friend Itadaki of Team Ninja, who...
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, there was an interview with Famitsu Xbox 360 regarding the Dead or Alive franchise where they spoke with Itagaki about the delays.
[SPEAKER_01]: He did actually make an apology for the last minute postponements that were going on over it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, there was a mention about...
[SPEAKER_01]: DOA Extreme Beach Volleyball 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Before I get into that, I am going to make a mention that there were plans to release new outfits for the DOA 4 characters via the Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, due to budget and staff issues, they had to put that on hold.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where the bikinis went.
[SPEAKER_01]: But there is still interest in doing it, but they may have to do that for a charge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, as I was bringing up DOA Extreme Beach Volleyball 2, Team Ninja is working on the opening and ending scenes for the game, currently implementing some changes to the original design
[SPEAKER_01]: and there is not a release date being mentioned.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said it will be an action game but that it won't necessarily they're also working on an action game that's not really going to be in the Ninja Gaiden franchise but
[SPEAKER_01]: Project Progressive, Dead or Alive, Code, Cronus, or another title.
[SPEAKER_01]: He said the key word is interactivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything that Team Ninja does, Team Ninja, in my esteem, is up there with treasure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some pretty, pretty games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially that DOA 4 on my Xbox 360, you know, when it worked.
[SPEAKER_09]: When it worked.
[SPEAKER_09]: And on that note, I think it's time to wrap up tonight's program.
[SPEAKER_09]: But we have to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Extifer, thank you so much for being on the show tonight and giving us your 50 cents or so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for having me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is that stupid shipping box is going to get here tomorrow when I'm out of town.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'll be here to collect.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_01]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think for yourself!
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Britney Spears does.
[SPEAKER_09]: From us here at Orange Lounge Radio to you guys, have a great week and we'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!