[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight, July 3rd, 2011, online videos may soon make you a criminal, Nintendo spends big bucks on a new facility, and an early build of an anticipated 360 game leaks to the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are live at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com as we are every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific and 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_10]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we're going to get into, of course, all the good stuff we like to do at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your gaming week and so forth?
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm going to start off tonight's show with a bang.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's going to be in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat.OrangeLounge.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I even knew our website.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com I'm going to give away one of my birthday presents right here, live on air, starting off the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I love the listeners that much, I'm going to share my birthday with you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an Xbox 360 game, so I'm going to give it to one of you guys in chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: So all I need you to do is whoever wants it in the chat room say, I want Rob's 360 game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just type that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want Rob's 360 game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You only say it once.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you say it more than once, you've disqualified yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: at the end we'll pick a number one through whatever of how many of you said I want Rob's 360 game and we are going to give it away right here at the top of the show this week I'll tell you more about what it is after our gaming week see that's what we do is a little thing called a radio tease it's Yaris I can say with a clean conscience this is not Yaris it is something I received for my birthday on the 360 and I'm giving it away
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to sweeten the pot a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not only are we going to give it away, I'm going to sign it, so is DarkSakura and Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's going to be like an autographed OLR game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll sign it with my butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: And DarkSakura will sign it with her butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to give it away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give it away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give it away now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's start off.
[SPEAKER_10]: How was your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: I played WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got 50 mounts today.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now I have an albino drake.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it has a skin condition.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lol.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're addicted to WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your fault.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, then Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you been playing anything that's not WoW?
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course I haven't been playing WoW, because I don't get WoW, nor would I want to play WoW.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I played more Grand Theft Auto this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Same old stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: and then of course Earth Defense Force Insect Armageddon because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got that early this week and was able to play through quite a bit of it and I'm happy to say it exceeds my expectations in every possible way.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um, it's just, it's very fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the multiplayer over the internet is actually pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: We've been playing a few games, uh, because I picked up a few copies of it, um, between my coworkers, and it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tried to play some games over the weekend, though, and was unable to connect to my other coworker that has it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, uh...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm definitely digging this game and highly recommend you pick it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it's... Depending on where you go, it may be out yesterday or out on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's an interesting story behind that, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, so it's really fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, graphics and sound are pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, especially when you're comparing them to Earth Defense Force, you know, the first one, it's just night and day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, there's a little bit of slowdown.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of your AI are kind of dumb, but they're actually pretty smart this time around.
[SPEAKER_11]: They actually do a lot of work and they don't die quite often because you have a three-man team the entire time, whether it be with players or AI.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the different suits you can try out, those are kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But overall, it's just a great, great game and I really...
[SPEAKER_11]: I love playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, I'll be playing some of it during the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because that's what I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be careful, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't want to stream it anywhere to the internet because you might get arrested for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we'll get into that later in the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So how does this game outshine the original?
[SPEAKER_11]: How's it outshine the original?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, the original was really, really, really buggy and just really cheap, but it was fun because you're fighting a bunch of different things all at once.
[SPEAKER_11]: This one kind of ramps up everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: The graphics are better.
[SPEAKER_11]: The detail in the game, like destroying buildings and stuff, it's not just...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Sound is actually really good in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought it was just really action-packed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just all the missions seem to like, oh, here, you're going to be attacked by these things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and now here's this thing coming in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and some dropships just came in, and they're going to be making your life hell.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just really overwhelming, and yet without being too difficult.
[SPEAKER_11]: And although I am playing on the...
[SPEAKER_11]: Normal mode right now because I'm starting everything off normal then going through the hard and then the Inferno which is just insane.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is ramping up difficulty pretty fast, and that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: In each mission, whereas the first game, the missions are pretty short, and they have like 73 of them, this one, the missions have different waypoints and different things going on, and they have the game broken up into chapters with different bits of the story going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like right now, this part I'm
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to our chatroom at chat.orangelongeradio.com, the ever-present fourth guest here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: SSJ100Matt says, I played Earth Defense Force 2 at PAX East, and it really just reminded me of a next-gen version of the N64 game of Body Harvest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I sadly didn't like it as much as Loki likes it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breakman says, wait, what's going on here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki actually likes a game?
[SPEAKER_11]: I like games all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I look for this, I'm like... You're the only one that cares.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you think you... And that happens in gaming sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sometimes we like a game that nobody else seems to like for unexplainable reasons.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why are you so drawn to this freaking game?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of taking games back to where...
[SPEAKER_11]: What the focus should be in any game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not about the great, great graphics or, you know, making sure everything's cinematic and has a great story.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all about being fun, and that's what this is.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is basically like a popcorn action flick or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: The story, yeah, there's somewhat of a story there, but who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, our intelligences have a better name for it, but that's what we're calling it.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was a part where I got picked up by this one dropship, and the pilot, he's just doing all the really typical...
[SPEAKER_11]: and yes, off to the left you'll see here there's a giant swarm of enemy ants attacking and you'll notice that we'll be cruising at an altitude of... It's kind of like Starship Troopers.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is very much like Starship Troopers, just without all the propaganda in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: and, you know, the spaceships, when they crash, they just kind of slowly sink through the ground and you could be in the path of one of them and it just clips right through you and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, this one, I mean, the actual ships, when they crash, I mean, they will take out buildings and they explode and they will possibly kill you if you're too close to it or, like, the enemy kind of spaceships are flying around.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you're shooting them and they get damaged enough, they will actually try to kamikaze into you and try to destroy you that way, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just, it's ridiculous fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And really, I mean, when you look at it in the month of July, there's not a lot coming out anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you're not a fan of football, then you're left with Harry Potter and Call of Juarez, you know, the cartel, which I hear is kind of terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, at least it's not Grand Theft Auto 4, which is all he ever plays.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: True that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm excited to hear Loki give an in-depth review to something else on the show for once.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Dan just walked in without a mic, interrupting the show, saying that Shadows of the Damned is fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've heard this is kind of a... I haven't played it at all, but I've heard it's kind of fun too.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a road trip movie game in hell, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like very Grindhouse-ish, but it's just, I don't know, insane.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I bought a new headset.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I saw on the shelf, for $40, I saw a copy of Dance Dance Revolution on the Xbox 360, which is the brand new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the reboot, quote unquote, of DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had the brand new game and dance pad for $40.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was like, well, you know...
[SPEAKER_10]: How bad could this possibly be?
[SPEAKER_10]: I like DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, OLR was built on DDR and all that, so why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I took it home and played it for a little while, and I was sad because it is horrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is a step backward for the genre.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is just a terrible, terrible version of DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: And big parts of that I can really blame on the song list.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: and then the song that just made me want to crinkle up my dance pad and throw it out the window Need You Now by Lady Antebellum that's right that slow jam song country western music somehow is appropriate for DDR and I was just like I died inside so the song list is terrible the interface is set up like a what no wonder it was 30 bucks it was 40 you overpaid what's that you overpaid
[SPEAKER_10]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Islander in our chat says, Was Rob trying to sign his computer headphones with his butt?
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's not just the song list that's offensive, but the interface is just crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, there's really nothing to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The videos are just very generic videos.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't even... Like, it's just... Like, they didn't even try.
[SPEAKER_10]: And when you put this game next to the Universe games on DDR, which, granted, at the time they came out were just kind of okay, now...
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't realize how good those fucking games were compared to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I've got the most value out of this game using the dance pad because my old one was long destroyed.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been using the dance pad to go back and play DDR Universe 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is what I've been using it for.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, go into our chatroom at chat.orangeonestrater.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have an issue with websites tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw says, so what Sky is trying to say, DDR360 is an abomination.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, and don't forget, this is the same game that's on the PS3, only it has move support, so whoopee, you get to wave your arms too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait, but this has vision camera support.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it does, I don't know where it is, because I didn't see an option for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does the Kinect not read the same way as a vision cam?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it should.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it's in there, I didn't find it, and I really didn't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's also on the Wii, and here's the hilarious part.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you look up videos of the Wii version, the Wii version actually kind of looks like the arcade versions.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm saying the Wii version's interface looks better than the 360, and presumably PS3 versions.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you explain that one to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: All these weird combo things that are supposed to add points, I didn't even understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the mode where you unlock stuff is the club mode, which is just non-stop mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that the songs come non-stop.
[SPEAKER_10]: And occasionally the difficulty will just randomly change in the song, or the arrows will move faster or slower.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then unexplainably, the way you unlock songs is you gain points.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't even fucking explain it.
[SPEAKER_10]: This game is just poopy poopy caw caw terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it makes me sad as somebody who liked DDR so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is time for the Dance Dance Revolution franchise to be revoked from Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: They no longer deserve to have that franchise based on this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I truly believe that somehow some divine being needs to come into Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how this happens, but somehow there needs to be a legal decision.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Supreme Court should be involved in a 7-2 decision to revoke DDR from Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I realize they're a Japanese company.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somehow that needs to happen where they are no longer allowed to make Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_11]: Give it to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can take care of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll clothe it, take it in, give it some shelter.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, anyhow, by the way, by the way, while I was playing that random non-stop mode, guess what awesome DDR jam started playing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, yeah, because, you know, sometimes there's, you know, there's these, there's the American songs you would expect to cross over, like some of the 80s classics, like, you know, Walk Like an Egyptian and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, oh man, I just couldn't believe my ears.
[SPEAKER_10]: I always thought this was such a great dance song, and I've always wanted to play this in DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the fall of
[SPEAKER_02]: What the crap is this?
Who is this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't listen to her.
[SPEAKER_10]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, hold me tight and we'll dance to Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_10]: We could do the four-player mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold each other's hands.
[SPEAKER_10]: Step, step, step.
[SPEAKER_10]: Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did that have, like, was it the quad?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, why does love feel like a battlefield?
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, did that have the new pads with the eight arrows or some garbage?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's the exact same fucking pad that came with Universe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, clearly the surplus that got sent back to Konami headquarters was just packaged in this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breakman in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: What the fuck is going on tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki likes games, Sky is angry, and DarkSakura is quiet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like games all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you heard me talk negative about Saints Row the Third, Grand Theft Auto, Motorstorm Apocalypse, I'm sure there's other games in there that I liked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_11]: So in our chatroom, we have... And, and, and, this goes back a few mixes ago, but what is the fucking abomination that is the new Dynamite Rave?
[SPEAKER_10]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not even gonna, I'm not even gonna try.
[SPEAKER_10]: We also have Frisbee, I'm sorry, was it Frisbee?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Frisbee in our chatroom says, this is like Kelly Clarkson in Supernova PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm so glad you brought that up, because guess what another one of those awesome songs in the tracklist is?
[SPEAKER_10]: At least that's danceable.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least, like, that one didn't, I mean, lover or hater, at least you can kind of dance to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Step, step, step, step, step, step, step.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, it has a beat.
[SPEAKER_10]: That one, not so terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all right to have, like, one of those songs in there, but not...
[SPEAKER_10]: I get that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Songs like that to cross over to mainstream audience, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have a problem with that song being in DDR.
[SPEAKER_10]: But like the Jordan Sparks and Leona Lewis, and I like Leona Lewis when I'm feeling sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, let me talk about a game that was a much better investment.
[SPEAKER_10]: As you know, going on right now, Steam is having a sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's tons and tons of stuff that's discounted on Steam right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the games I grabbed on sale was Bit.Trip Runner was $2.50 on Steam.
[SPEAKER_10]: Somehow I stepped into the Twilight Zone where that's the game I should have paid $40 for and DDR was worth about $2.50.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Bit.Trip Runner is cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I wasn't expecting a whole lot out of this game because Bit.Trip beat...
[SPEAKER_10]: was neat, but it kind of, like, the shtick got old pretty fast, so the whole Pong thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I liked Bit.Trip Runner a lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, it really reminds me of an old-school 2600 game like what it would look like today, with the chiptune music, very simple controls, but a lot of that whole kind of repetition about how to learn to beat a level, and, you know, I...
[SPEAKER_10]: Even throwbacks to the classic Atari console with the whole bonus levels looking like pitfall complete with a noisy television.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like if you've ever tried to hook up on an old TV with the RF switch, you get that noise in there mixed with your game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just loved the way it looked.
[SPEAKER_10]: A Bit.Trip Runner was a great deal for $250.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played more of that game than I did the $40 DDR game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Bit.Trip Runner, I endorse that game especially.
[SPEAKER_10]: you could call it a music game because yeah it involves chiptunes but to me that's kind of the niche that makes it that much more awesome to me it's just like a classic Atari game what it would look like today just the chiptune element makes it attractive to those that maybe don't always care for the simplistic games if that makes sense so
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, anything else I played this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I checked out some demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't always like to review games based on the demos, but I'll quickly say I checked out the 32nd Hero Super Mega Neo Climax game on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: I own the PSP version of that, so I wanted to see what it looked like on 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like how the 360 has the completely different art modes that look completely different.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have the cel-shaded hand-drawn mode, which is pretty cool, but they also have the retro mode, which looks more like the PSP version or an 8-bit Nintendo classic.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: um let's see uh and um what was the other demo I played oh Galaga Legions DX I think I'm gonna buy that one that one was really cool that was kind of like Geometry Wars with the whole Pac-Man Championship Edition elements in it with the music and everything because by the same team if I'm not mistaking but it played a little more like Geometry Wars but it doesn't play like the old Galaga games at all so I thought that was kind of neat
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ezam in our chatroom says, Bit.Trip is more rhythm puzzle than anything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rhythm puzzle, I think, is a good way to describe it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, going into our chatroom, Blackwolf says, hey, that's not the Glee version, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Breakman says, I hear Glee versions of songs every time I go to Target.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's the other awesome music franchise that Konami's doing right now, Glee Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: It sells for them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I don't know either.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bet you all are dying to know more about the game that I'm giving away here on the program.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the top of the show I said, who wants to win my birthday present?
[SPEAKER_10]: And we are going to give that away.
[SPEAKER_10]: But to tell us more about the birthday present...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to call the person who bought it for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is my significant other, Salacious Pop, that we're going to bring on the line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm giving away the present that my significant other bought for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're going to talk about why.
[SPEAKER_10]: He actually ordered a copy of Child of Eden for me online.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I want to talk about why we are giving away, once it arrived, why we're giving it away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Salacious Pop, are you there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I...
[SPEAKER_05]: decided that that was definitely what you needed to get for your birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I went on a hunt online to try and find it at a good price because I wasn't really prepared to, you know, drop the 60 bones or whatever it costs at Target.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I checked out Amazon and a bunch of other sites and I just wasn't happy with, you know, how, what they were offering it for.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I ended up through Google Shopping, I ended up on eBay and
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure already some people in the studio might know where this story is going.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found a lot of retailers with tens of thousands of feedback positive score that I could have got it from, but I found this one sort of dog and pony show seller with a feedback score of five or six.
[SPEAKER_05]: and selling Child of Eden and a bunch of other games like Halo Reach and Madden 11 and a bunch of other stuff new shrink-wrapped in America for what I thought was a good price.
[SPEAKER_10]: And at least it was a feedback of one or higher.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't some new eBay account, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was five, which is still pretty low for the fact they had like 80 auctions running at once.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was like, all right, I am going to give this a shot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I sell a ton of stuff on eBay and I take it very seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think I kind of projected the fact that I'm a legit EJ seller onto this stranger person.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And three days later, when I get my tracking number, I see that for one, I notice that they closed their account.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they've unregistered from eBay and their feedback score is now zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I look at the tracking number and it is from China.
[SPEAKER_05]: and anyone who ever orders anything on eBay knows that if your item comes from China, it is a counterfeit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a bootleg because the piracy market over in China and Taiwan is millions and millions of dollars of counterfeit titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was like, well, shit, it's going to take this game three weeks to get to me and it's obviously fake.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it arrived on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: I open it and here's the punchline.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is a counterfeit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, it's
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised at how good the quality is, but it's not good enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you can tell, like, wow, they printed this on a very high-quality, expensive color laser printer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it definitely looks like a color copy.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's very high-quality, but if you look closely, you can just kind of see that ink, inkjet little dotting.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you ever look at an original and an inkjet side-by-side, you can tell the difference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so obviously it's a counterfeit, and if you look at the underside of the disc, you can see that it's like a DVD-R that they just bought a huge spindle of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the game wasn't even a counterfeit Child of Eden, it was a counterfeit PAL edition, so they bootlegged the European version, of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's a bootlegged game from China...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the PAL version, Whammy number two.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the wrong counterfeit game from what I ordered, Whammy number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that is some Yakety Sax, Benny Hill-themed shit right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we want to give, and before we had the call tonight, I asked you to pick a number from one, two, of all the people in chat who said that they wanted my 360 game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we want to congratulate...
[SPEAKER_10]: Kaijudo won a copy, bootleg copy of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood PAL edition on the Xbox 360 signed by DarkSakura's butt.
[SPEAKER_10]: My birthday present.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I care about the listeners, I am giving away my birthday present.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, I opened a case for it on eBay and I'm confident that I'm gonna get my money back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: The price that I got it for was sort of in that nebulous, too good to be true, but I could see someone selling the game for cheap at this amount.
[SPEAKER_11]: so even if I get screwed over which I doubt I will it's not a horrible heartbreaking amount of money but come on eBay it's not completely unreasonable for someone to sell stuff for cheap for example I take games sometimes that I get for free and I just don't want them and I don't really care what I get for them so I start the auction at one penny and whatever they end at that's what they sell for so a lot of times you know I think Brink was one that went recently it went for $24 so it's not unreasonable for that to happen
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: I sold them on the adult section of eBay for a penny and some of them only went for $10 and they were perfectly brand new retail good items.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I absolutely understand how that could happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you thought maybe you'd find somebody like you who was just giving away their excess promo copies of Child of Eden but unfortunately you got a PAL copy that's not even real of Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of a game that I didn't order, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: So TigerClaw in our chatroom says, what's the moral of the story?
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't order from Amazon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I think you got the moral mixed up.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's don't order from eBay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Order from a, quote, legit store like Amazon or Best Buy or Fry's or whatever the hell you want.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thankfully, even though PayPal is evil, usually...
[SPEAKER_11]: WTF, if I would ever try to give away a gift from my girl, she would fucking kill me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So are you going to fucking kill me, SalaciousPop?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we've found an even better solution to get you your Child of Eden fix, and I get to play it too.
[SPEAKER_05]: So no, I'm not too heartbroken over this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we can go ahead and share what we ended up doing instead.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually kind of, in an ironic way, it's actually kind of funny this worked out this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, a listener of OLR, I'm trying to think of his name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nicholas Austin.
[SPEAKER_05]: his screen name Miklatov called us today Miklatov told us that on BestBuy.com or the brick and mortar store if you have one nearby for today and tomorrow Kinect games are two for one so we picked up Child of Eden and
[SPEAKER_05]: and a fitness game that looked like a fitness game that wasn't actually horrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got both of those, so that's your birthday present are those two games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I ended up getting a two-for-one deal out of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which fitness game?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the Year Fitness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, because, no, trust me, we looked.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're like, okay, Zumba Fitness is the one that's selling really well in Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Went to Metacritic.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like 40-something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unless you like Latin dancing, and I'm talking about Latin female dancing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do like Latin female dancing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Your Shape Fitness Evolved, which I think is like a 74 on Metacritic for a fitness game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have the sequel coming out this year, but I mean... We just kind of went to Metacritic and picked the one with the best score, and that's the one we went with.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we were like, well, let's get a fitness game, because I've actually kind of been into fitness and all that stuff lately, like trying to walk more, eat better.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've lost seven pounds in the past two months, so I kind of want to keep that trend going without having to join a gym.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, Breakman in chat says, so basically someone wins Sky's coffee table drink coaster.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I never said it was a good game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do you think I was giving it away?
[SPEAKER_10]: But Kaijudo says, I will put that game up on a plaque.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm glad someone won it who will appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So congratulations once again.
[SPEAKER_10]: You win my birthday bootleg PAL copy of the wrong fucking game, Assassin's Creed Brotherhood, signed by myself, Loki, and DarkSakura's butt.
[SPEAKER_11]: and uh I think doesn't Loki probably has a system somewhere that would play it that was actually my first reaction I'm like one of Loki's like 10 360s could probably play this game I don't have 10 360s no my my JTAG which which by the way I broke this week but I will be fixing it um yes I would probably be able to play that but Loki I've decided I'm gonna give it to a listener instead in fact uh Dan's JTAG out there probably could play it all right well oh well
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, Salacious Pop, while we have you on, anything else you want to share with the listeners?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just that really insane Steam sale that's running, I think, all week.
[SPEAKER_05]: People need to get on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some great stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And win tickets.
[SPEAKER_10]: And join the OLR group while you're on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_10]: More information at OrangeLawnsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, take care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, Salacious Pop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it really is one of those situations where it's the thought that counts like I just laughed it off like I kind of knew he was getting me Child of Eden because when I tried to buy it in the store he's like don't you want to wait till after your birthday to buy any big purchases like that you know that whole little thing so I kind of knew that was coming but you know the story behind it is even better than just the game showing up on the doorstep you know and you even said ahead of time that you felt or that Alan felt something like that might happen
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Team Fortress 2
[SPEAKER_10]: Or Portal 2, your copies on PS3 that work on Steam, what have you We actually do have our own little Steam community And you can see that on our website, orangelauntrader.com On the left hand side is a little button for Steam In the extended play section Steamcommunity.com slash groups slash OLR So there you go Alright, let's get into tonight's news There actually is a lot of gaming news too this week So let's get right into it Loki, start us off, what's going on in the news?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we talked a little bit about this on our tease with Bobby.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Resident Evil Mercenary 3D just came out last week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there was a big controversy over the fact that Capcom decided, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know that save game data that you have on there?
[SPEAKER_11]: It cannot be reset.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, for example, say you get really far in the game and you decide to sell it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then the next person that buys it, they're stuck with your save game and having everything being unlocked.
[SPEAKER_11]: it was funny because actually at one point GameStop and a lot of the major retailers out there were not going to be taking the game in as a trade I guess they've reversed their policy on that but they're saying upon further review of the process with our publisher partner Capcom GameStop will resume taking trades on the game effective Wednesday June 29th makes me wonder a couple things here one
[SPEAKER_11]: So, GameStop probably bitched to Capcom.
[SPEAKER_11]: GameStop Employee GameStop Employee GameStop Employee
[SPEAKER_11]: Overseas, though, it says retailer HMV has ceased taking trades in for the title.
[SPEAKER_11]: EB Games Australia has also stopped stocking the game altogether.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, they're just saying if, you know, EB Games, I guess, if you would like to purchase it with us, then of course we will sell it to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will be a case of an order with our store.
[SPEAKER_11]: We made the tough decision to remove it from sale because we had everybody's best interest in mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't feel that it's fair that you guys would be paying $60 Australian for what is essentially a one-use game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, let's get back to the root problem here, because amongst the whole 9th anniversary show and the fact that this news kind of came out on a Sunday last week, we kind of overlooked this story.
[SPEAKER_10]: In what fucking universe was this a good game design idea to not reset the save file?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I get the defense as the whole, well, it's like an arcade game, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just saying that is the defense I'm not saying I understand it but that is the whole like well it's it's like an arcade game and it's not detrimental so what like I hate it when game companies try to tell me what I want as a gamer because that's what the gamers want no I'm telling you that's not what I want I do sometimes like to reset my games well here's the thing about I did it on Final Fantasy 13 a few weeks ago
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like an arcade game, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's your defense then?
[SPEAKER_11]: Arcade cabinets I can reset the goddamn high score.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, Capcom arcade games I can reset the high score on.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, where's your logic there?
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, clearly, somebody made this decision, and I think this decision absolutely was made to impact the used market, because somebody made a conscious decision not to let the game save to the 3DS card, internal memory, like all the other freaking 3DS games do, where if you wanted to reset your data, oh, it's as easy as deleting the file.
[SPEAKER_10]: How easy is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Somebody made the conscious decision, no, we don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're specifically moving it to the cart and not making it deletable.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yet now they've come up with all this crap to kind of backtalk their way into how that was a great decision and it's where the game industry is going.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really what you wanted.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's what we wanted.
[SPEAKER_11]: You wanted an arcade experience, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I didn't really want to play the Mercenary missions from 4 and 5 ported to the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would like, I don't know, maybe a new Resident Evil game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, but guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: You can play the demo for the new Resident Evil game on this game itself.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess there's something to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But once again, you know, I mean, to be fair, it didn't get very good reviews because apparently the game wasn't that great.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so, you know, I don't really consider a big loss.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting, though, because this news story yet has people talking about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And despite the fact it was a mediocre game that probably, you know, the Resident Evil fans would have been, yay, but most other people would have been like, bring on the other 3DS games.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's another entry in the long line of bad DRM decisions from Capcom.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's not, oh, this game needs to be online at all times in order for it to work even in single player.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or in games that don't even have a multiplayer component, oh, and then the PlayStation Network goes down and their game stops working for a month or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so I'm being corrected by the chat room as tends to happen sometimes on this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf in our chat says, actually Rob, none of the 3DS games I have saved to the SD card.
[SPEAKER_10]: They all save to the 3DS card, but you can do data management.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only things that save to the SD card are the street pass and maybe data that won't fit on the card.
[SPEAKER_10]: So fine, I just haven't noticed because there hasn't really been that big RPG 3DS game that I've wanted to reset the data on so far.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, when all is said and done, would I probably really want to reset the data on a game like this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me, personally.
[SPEAKER_10]: I probably wouldn't have noticed this if it hadn't been called out.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what ticks me off about it is this whole, we all see what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quit trying to make excuses to say otherwise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, it's very obvious why they're doing this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop lying.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's because they don't want to piss off the fans.
[SPEAKER_11]: They don't want to piss off the fans because they're trying to do this to save some money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then they are assuming that their fans are stupid and you should be offended.
[SPEAKER_11]: And really, how much money are they saving?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because this game itself is probably going to sell, what, maybe 400,000 units?
[SPEAKER_11]: And that right there is a really...
[SPEAKER_11]: Generous estimate.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, 400,000 units in the lifetime of this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, we're talking like, you know, maybe a few 10,000 copies or whatever that they're going to lose out sales on because someone's going to buy it used.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, okay, say like 25% of those copies are going to sell for used or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: How many people are you really turning away from putting this feature on there?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, what, maybe let's just say 10,000 of those people.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, that's such a minor, minor, minor number compared to, you know, people are just not going to give a shit or they just won't buy your game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf in our chatroom says Hey, this is an investment opportunity Buy 5 copies this week, save them for 3 years and sell them as unopened on eBay for $100 each.
[SPEAKER_10]: Profit I don't know if that will work if the game is only kind of mediocre
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, however, I say at the end of the day, vote with your wallet.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's really what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, to be honest, I probably wouldn't have bought this game anyway, but I especially wouldn't have bought it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, if I was on the fence, I would have said, no, I don't really want to support this methodology.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, see, that's what was going through my head the whole time, is why the crap would I buy that game?
[SPEAKER_07]: There hasn't been a good Resident Evil game since 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, come on, 4?
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, oh my god, that's one of the best GameCube games ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Period.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I realize everybody has their own opinion.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I cannot agree with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: My favorite to this day is still 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: 4 was, like, one of the best games they had.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I really liked Code Veronica.
[SPEAKER_10]: Period.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I would be with you that 5 was not what it could have been.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, 5 was not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, vote with your wallet, kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's really what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, now, speaking of fun money-related decisions and what you support and what you don't, where the industry is going, last week on the show we talked about the impending Supreme Court decision, and I gotta admit, we were a little bit in the negative defeatist realm last week where we were pretty sure that it was gonna come out and
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: So in Brown vs. Entertainment Merchants Association, which used to be Schwarzenegger vs. Entertainment Merchants Association, but we've had a new governor since the law first went into effect, it was reversed in a 7-2 decision.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: We understand why there might be a law, just this wasn't really the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The way you're defining offensive here is a little vague.
[SPEAKER_10]: Things like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So is this all going to be said and done and over with?
[SPEAKER_10]: I guarantee you it's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, there was some reaction this week from Leland Yee, who was the state senator who originally drafted this whole bill in the first place.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's a Democrat representing San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_10]: and he put together a whole little statement that said that the ruling of the Supreme Court puts the interests of corporate America before the interests of children as a result of their decision Walmart and the video game industry will continue to make billions of dollars at the expense of our kids mental health and the safety of our community good god
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you read the terms... He clearly didn't read the syllabus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because... And I read the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It goes in there to say that the research that they used was inherently flawed.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that actually the same researchers who were trying to make the claim that violent video games were harmful to children said also television, movies, books, Saturday morning cartoons...
[SPEAKER_07]: were all equally harmful.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, on top of all that, he's saying it's in the interest of children.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, children aren't able to purchase, I mean, as it is with the company policies, they're unable to purchase these games in these stores.
[SPEAKER_11]: And last time I checked, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, these same parents, keep in mind, are encouraging their kids to go play high school football and participate in sports where far more injuries occur as opposed to those related to video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And deaths.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, don't forget deaths.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, by the way, Leland Yee, at the end of the day, basically said he's going to try again because there were a couple people on the fence.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, no, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: You haven't wasted enough taxpayer money yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would like this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so you guys lost the case, Leland Yee.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you're going to pony up that $2 million that we wasted on this?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what else is very interesting about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: You hear a lot about partisan politics in this nation and this whole Republican, Democrat stuff going on here.
[SPEAKER_10]: This really is one of those things that doesn't seem to fall on one party or the other.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, a Democrat wrote it, but then when you look at who
[SPEAKER_10]: and the Supreme Court decided to dissent against the majority and actually side with Leland Yee.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of those justices was Clarence Thomas, who was a Herbert Walker Bush nominee to the court.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other one being Breyer, a Clinton appointee to the court.
[SPEAKER_10]: This isn't partisan either, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there's so many issues in America where it's like, you know, it's a Republican issue or it's a Democrat issue, but this is one of those things that's really all over the map.
[SPEAKER_07]: Partisan politics is bullshit anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's trying to add regulation for something that there's already regulation for.
[SPEAKER_11]: I suggest that they go in there and we need to enact some sort of force that'll go out there and stop people from committing laws.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: and and that you know they understand parents have a right to want a little bit more assistance from the government and which I think is bullshit but um the whole point is that it's basically the government shall not step in on your personal liberties we've already had enough of that going on this is where we draw the line
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't understand the whole needing for education for the ESRB ratings.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does anybody need education for the movie MPA ratings?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never seen somebody go, oh, I don't know what an R-rated movie has in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, does that ever confuse anybody?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I see no point to this excuse anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, as a parent, I don't understand English on the back of my box that says violence, nudity.
[SPEAKER_11]: Does this game contain violence and nudity?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, it says right there that it does.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_07]: But the issue, and I'm not even going to say this flat out as a parental issue, I'm going to say this as an essentially American issue, people are fucking lazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody wants to think for themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want everything handed to them on a plate that says, here, here's everything spelled out for you, so now it's easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to take out the hard work part of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you see the part, did you see the whole thing being discussed on the Daily Show?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you see that whole clip of Jon Stewart talking about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I watched some of it in the moment that he said he supported it, I left the room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I...
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't think I didn't get that impression necessarily supported it it sure seemed like it watching it but then there was part of me that was like it was very tongue-in-cheek like is this kind of like tongue-in-cheek onion style humor that maybe we're just not getting because what amazed me about it is as he was talking about the bill and you know these horrible games that would be sold yet he was showing clips uncensored of the games on his program that I could just turn on my television and watch and
[SPEAKER_08]: But granted, primetime.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, surely this is just highbrow humor that I'm not getting.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think he was actually serious.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you knew nothing about the issue at all and you were just presented this, oh, hey, there was a law that was going to ban these violent games from ending up in children's laps, then you could see, oh, well, why did they vote against that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, that doesn't make any sense why they would vote against these violent games going in kids' laps.
[SPEAKER_11]: Until you explain that, hey, there's already regulation in place, you know, done by these retailers where they're not selling this stuff to people.
[SPEAKER_11]: And there's also not this sort of regulation, you know, done by the law for any other type of media, including TV.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, that's the point that he forgot to point out.
[SPEAKER_11]: But because, you know, it's more interesting to have, you know, this violent imagery on screen and him going, you know, just because that gets him.
[SPEAKER_07]: One point that Dan brought up was that now this might set a precedent for people to basically sue a company for not selling the game like when they've sent their kid in to go buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the company says no, but it is part of the business that you have.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Violent enough to fall under this, that's the problem with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Go into our chatroom at chat.org.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Salacious Pop is actually commenting in our chatroom right now and saying, Loki, there's actually two movies where that happened, and I think talking about some of the violence.
[SPEAKER_10]: Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom, which was PG, made parents flip their shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's why PG-13 was invented.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw faces melting when I was a kid, and I turned out okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember that scene?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was in Pee-wee's Big Adventure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my God!
[SPEAKER_10]: When he gets in the truck with Large Marge.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she does this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's telling the story.
[SPEAKER_10]: On a night just like this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: And then she goes, and it looked like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: The whole claymation thing, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Little kids bursting into tears across the country, scarred for life.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still can't watch that scene.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's why we are afraid of truckers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our generation is afraid of truckers.
[SPEAKER_07]: My daddy was a trucker.
[SPEAKER_10]: He actually still is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Do not find the damn picture, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not finding the picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just want to make sure the movie was rated PG.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check IMDb.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, look, I can't figure out what this freaking movie is rated.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, should it be this typical?
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, IMDb.
[SPEAKER_10]: IMDb.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, actually, there was one movie that I saw when I was a kid, and it was rated R movie, and I went to see it with my uncle.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen tons of rated R movies when I was a little kid.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's PG.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, IMDB.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is the only movie rated R that ever scared me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now, today, you will laugh at this.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Poltergeist 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That I was afraid of mirrors for like a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at any Disney movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, okay, Tarzan.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've all seen that Disney movie, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Spoiler alert, the main villain dies in the movie by being strangled to death.
[SPEAKER_07]: By falling down with vines wrapped around his neck, with his neck broken.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I remember seeing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they show the silhouette of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, this is very violent for kids.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or how about Snow White?
[SPEAKER_10]: Almost all Disney villains die by falling off a cliff and then you just see that little poof of smoke that rises from the bottom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or how about Snow White?
[SPEAKER_07]: Movie from, what was it, 1947, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: The queen is the old witch trying to push the boulder down the hill and instead lightning strikes her, she falls off the cliff and the boulder lands on her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, lots of people in chat talking about the Large Marge scene and how actually there were a lot of people that apparently were scared by that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dungeon Buster mentions the death of Optimus Prime.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope I'm saying this right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rade, or maybe that's Raid, Rade says, Oh Jesus, Large Marge, that scarred me for life.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breakman says, Yeah, that was scary because it was so unexpected.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Frisbee says, I still can't watch that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're not alone.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, SSJ100 Matt provides a YouTube link if you want to see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Zether, another one here.
[SPEAKER_10]: The boat scene in Willy Wonka scared me shitless.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, that movie was fucked up.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't like the new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: The old one is far more fucked up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I appreciate them both, but the old one, I was actually a child when I saw the old one, and it was kind of fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was a little afraid.
[SPEAKER_10]: When she's a bad egg and she falls through the chute and all these...
[SPEAKER_07]: I want the world, I want the whole world There is no way of knowing where exactly we are going I was afraid of Gene Wilder when I was little For a while For a while
[SPEAKER_10]: Our whole generation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, where do you think... Why are we not more screwed up?
[SPEAKER_10]: And yet we all turned out fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we turned out fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not saying that kids should be subjected to this violence.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I think that's a parent's decision to make.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw Star Trek V in the theater and I'm not fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that was awful.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think any parent that's saying, I didn't know what this game was rated or I didn't know that this game had violence in it or I didn't know this is just retarded.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if you're like, I didn't know how to read the rating system...
[SPEAKER_11]: You're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep in mind what our old Saturday morning cartoons were like.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I realize I don't have kids, so maybe some people are not going to value my opinion, but whatever, F you, it's my show.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I had kids, I would want them to see that violence the first time, because they're going to see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to see it at a friend's house.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to see it at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to see it on CNN.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to see it when they're flipping through the TV, and they'll see it on Comedy Central, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't understand the double standard between sexual stuff and violent stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll, regardless of the ESRB rating, I'm just going to pick games that I think are suitable for my child.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that may be different than, like, honestly, if you teach them well enough, they know what fiction is, I mean...
[SPEAKER_11]: The people that I'm killing in Grand Theft Auto aren't real people.
[SPEAKER_11]: And obviously you don't want to go emulate that on the street by going and killing real people.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they're just AI computer controlled people.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can brutally murder them and nothing happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: My point was going back to Saturday morning cartoons.
[SPEAKER_07]: How many of us grew up with Pixie and Dixie and Mr. Jinx?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tom and Jerry
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I grew up watching Tom and Jerry with, you know, Tom and Blackface.
[SPEAKER_10]: We watched Tom and Jerry cartoons in church.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went to a Baptist church when I was younger.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll save that discussion for another day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was raised in one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember there was a lock-in, quote-unquote, at the church once, and we watched Tom and Jerry cartoons all night.
[SPEAKER_07]: So... We watched Song of the South.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, look.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to move on to other topics, but I... But the point...
[SPEAKER_07]: The point is that parents need to do their job.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's better that you were there with them to explain it than leave them unexposed.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I did actually know somebody who was pretty much blocked from everything when she was growing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't know her while she was growing up.
[SPEAKER_07]: My friends knew her.
[SPEAKER_07]: But from what I understand, she was a lot more messed up than anyone I know who grew up exposed to everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me quickly get some comments from chatroom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat.orange.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breakman says, if I ever have kids, I refuse to use cutesy names for things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want my kids to know that they have a penis or vagina, not a wee-wee or a hoo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bonds006 says, I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: My mom had us watch a lot of adult shows and movies, and personally, I don't think it messed me up.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then DungeonBuster says, I love the Penn & Teller bullshit show where they looked at violent video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I'll have to find you the clip.
[SPEAKER_07]: They get a 13-year-old with his mother's permission, put a gun in his hand, and they have a trainer there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's supervised.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a police officer there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They give him an automatic weapon and say, okay, go ahead and shoot it once.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is how you do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shows him the proper everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: The kid shoots the gun, steps back, and says, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the guy goes, do you want to do it again?
[SPEAKER_07]: He says, no, I don't want to touch this thing again.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then they showed him later on that he was in tears, 13 years old.
[SPEAKER_07]: But he goes home and plays SOCOM and all these violent games, yet is this the reaction that those people who are putting out that propaganda want to think is going to happen?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I would go to that extreme to teach my child but then again I have an issue with guns but we'll save that for another episode of the show but you get the point you're saying no I do I do the point was do these games train kids to be killers and clearly not first of all he didn't even hit the target or like he hit like way off right and second of all he didn't even want to touch it again
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Ab1371 in 2003 Strengthens informed consent requirements for mentally handicapped patients that take part in medical research
[SPEAKER_10]: 2004, AB 2412, allows part-time community college faculty to access unemployment benefits.
[SPEAKER_10]: AB 3042, enhances sentences for child prostitution.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, 2006, AB 409, establishes tighter controls and higher health standards for nail salons.
[SPEAKER_10]: AB 1207, adds sexual orientation to the list of protections in the Code of Fair Political Practices.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know, he's not been all about, you know, take it or leave it, whether you, I don't know what there you agree with or what you don't agree with.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's been other stuff to him than just this violent video game law, which I think, unfortunately, he's making a whole career defining thing out of.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a heads up, he is running for mayor of San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_10]: You may or may not know.
[SPEAKER_10]: San Francisco, the former mayor, Gavin Newsom, is now the lieutenant governor of California after the November elections.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they have an interim mayor, and that means there's going to be a new mayor election this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there are a handful of candidates in the ring, and Lee Lanee is one of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Possibly maybe violent video games will be banned in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're banning Happy Meal Toys and Circumcision, too, on top of everything else.
[SPEAKER_10]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll just throw violent video games in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm still trying to find this one article that was talking about the greatest cartoons for traumatizing children.
[SPEAKER_07]: But how about we talk about Zynga?
[SPEAKER_07]: Zynga has something... That's pretty traumatic for children.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has something very new.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm actually going to quote this article because I like the way it's laid out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a new venture.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's something different from Farmville and Frontierville.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here's where the quote begins.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't actually have VIL in the title.
2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Players play with actual, totally real money.
3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Players' companies won't necessarily grow.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, it may shrink through no fault of their own.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: Players play with real money?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: The company is Zynga, and it's not a game, but a stock offering.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going public.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are filling an S1 form and going to be publicly traded.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can really fuck them now
[SPEAKER_10]: Now with all this talk about the decline of people using Facebook, Google Plus is coming out and has people talking.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, don't put it in the nail coffin of Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Assuming that they let people in.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm just saying, there is this talk about Facebook might be slipping a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: So is this the time for Zynga to say, trust in us?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I really think...
[SPEAKER_10]: Zynga's Profile
[SPEAKER_10]: FarmVillain Facebook Games
[SPEAKER_10]: That and a very neutered dog on their logo Doesn't that name have like a weird meaning to it too?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't remember like where the company name came from Something silly Islander says I didn't know Zynga was on Facebook I've just been playing on Myspace Ladies and gentlemen we have found the one person that is still on Myspace I thought it was Tom I thought it was Justin Timberlake but go to chat right now he's there
[SPEAKER_07]: Zynga is the CEO's dog.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, so that's why the logo's a dog.
[SPEAKER_10]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, we got a tweet about this tonight from Twitter user Nathan Jackson.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would like you all to talk about Zynga going public.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you all think it would be sustainable with games like Farmville going down?
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of that same point I was just making, like things are declining.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think the only way Zynga can be...
[SPEAKER_10]: I just hope to God it's not true that they tried to buy PopCap.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be, that would make me very sad if Zynga and PopCap merged.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get to some other news stories and release dates soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some more depressing news.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you thought, you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: The bill states that 10 or more public performances by electronic means during any 180-day period of one or more copyrighted works will result in not more than five years of imprisonment.
[SPEAKER_11]: So as long as the performance in question is valued at at least $2,500 U.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: or the value of the license to legally perform its content is valued at $5,000 or more.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Now they're saying right now it says if it manages to pass.
[SPEAKER_11]: The homemade gameplay clips, which I've never heard of them called like this, but apparently referred to as Let's Play videos, fan-made music videos, a webcam, cover songs, anything I guess that involves music or video.
[SPEAKER_11]: It could potentially cover cell phone videos of concerts and press events.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, basically, they're saying that this could apply to YouTube users and also sites that embed YouTube content as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And really, to get down to the bottom of it, I think they're going to have a hard time regulating this stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, if they're going to go after everything, then...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is only going to benefit what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I understand that, you know, for example, if you take a song off an album and you put it as a YouTube video and you leave it there so people can listen or, you know, pirate that song, I understand that's bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: If, for example, you know, you're... And I don't even know about so much the, you know, music videos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't have a real big problem with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially gameplay videos.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't understand gameplay at all because...
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not really the same as putting a movie up, like an actual cinematic movie and you're pirating or a TV show or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: This law is absolute, total, utter bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the problem with it is that it's just shittily written.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that a word I can use?
[SPEAKER_10]: Shittily?
[SPEAKER_10]: It can be.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: This law was shittily.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's shite.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is total, utter shite.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the reason why it's shite, it's just badly written because it includes all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get what they're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: What they're trying to do is they're trying to get at these websites where you can log in and you can stream movies that are in the theater.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can stream them.
[SPEAKER_10]: or current TV shows and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they're doing, but because they've left the door so wide fucking open, if somebody gets on there and tapes a karaoke performance and puts it up on YouTube, it could be subject to this law.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you might be saying, well, that's not what they're trying to go after, but unfortunately when you have a shittily written law...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: The problem is this is also, it's just taking a big fat dump all over fair use.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I should be, yes, I should be able to upload video for the purpose of critiquing and commenting on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you mean I'm going to have to contact the copyright owner to get express permission to do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_10]: All of your game review videos are going to be done by IGN, 1UP, GameSpot, and all the big companies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Activision, all those times, they don't have the time for little pissants like you and me that they're going to sign off on the rights for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So say goodbye to independent media if something like this passes.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Say goodbye to Orange Lounge Radio if this passes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I'm telling you, if this bill in its current form passes and goes effective, I'm walking away from this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I am not going to go to jail because I like to play music over the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: for the purposes of critiquing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is not a threat.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is a promise.
[SPEAKER_10]: If this law passes and is enforced, there will not be Orange Launch Radio anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Period.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe Loki and DarkSakura will decide they want to do it, but somehow I don't think they want to subject themselves to that either.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, that is the seriousness of this bullshit law.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get what they're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not doing it right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you need to contact your senator, contact folks, and tell them that this law is a bad thing for America.
[SPEAKER_07]: There actually is a site up there that will generate email to your local legislature.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you do have a way of getting out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I have relinked it on my Facebook.
[SPEAKER_11]: And who is voting these goddamn people in the office?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, seriously, all these Lenys and shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and he's going to become mayor now because he's such full of wonderful ideas?
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember what I said about lazy Americans?
[SPEAKER_07]: The fact that people won't get up and vote when these things come up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just sit back and bitch about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, you don't vote about it, you have no right to complain.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, yesterday I was on JustinTV and I did a search for Transformers and sure enough people were streaming a bootleg of Transformers 3 in a foreign language.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then that needs to be worked out between JustinTV and the copyright owners of the work.
[SPEAKER_10]: And JustinTV should take action thusly against those accounts of people doing it because I'm sure that is against their terms of service.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, that's the law you need.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not sending me to jail because I want to sing...
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to post a tape of Jessica and I singing Love Shack on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I would never post that tape on the internet, but she did.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't want her to go to jail for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And on top of that, that would make certain games illegal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I believe SingStar and stuff like that allows you to take songs and record videos to them and post them up on the internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also there's going to be a game like SingFor the Hits Edition that's
[SPEAKER_11]: are going to have connectivity with YouTube as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: So all those are basically felony makers.
[SPEAKER_10]: unless of course those people that own those songs or you know own those video game companies and stuff like that don't stop these things from going because if no one complains then you know it's going to be alright Blackwolf in our chatroom says well to be fair I don't know if the guy who wrote this bill campaigned on this so they could have voted him in without knowing he was going to pen this specific bill and that's a true point you never know what politicians are going to do but we need to hold them accountable
[SPEAKER_10]: And I plan to write my congresspeople and say, if you support this bill, I will not vote for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will not vote for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's it take to, say, for example, get these guys out of office?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there's these elections that they have every few years.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I understand that, but hey, we can Recall, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what happened with how Governor Schwarzenegger got into office in the first place.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember the Governator?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's where that all came from.
[SPEAKER_10]: He terminated the other governor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't do shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I think we ended up with the worst governor, but I don't want to make this show political.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm too late for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially after last week where things got a little heated, I really didn't want to have a political show tonight, but we can't fucking get away from it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all that's in the news this week is all this political stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's make our own country.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Oelaria.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, the senator that's behind this is Amy Klobuchar, Democrat from Minnesota.
[SPEAKER_10]: Minnesota.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a whole website, opencongress.org, that will show you who's in favor of it and who's against it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right now, 51 companies for it, 3 against.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm telling you, though, if it goes through, it's going to be yet another one of those laws that gets tied up because I would be fucking pissed because this just seems to violate fair use.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't film somebody at karaoke?
[SPEAKER_10]: That is wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: How more ridiculous is this going to go?
[SPEAKER_10]: On the bright side, American Idol will finally go off the air.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say, for example, the Happy Birthday song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is that public domain?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are people going to get sued because there's a song playing in the background of a YouTube video or something like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wedding videos?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Leland Yee, at least one quote.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's talking about different stuff, pandering towards corporations.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think this is one of those things that panders towards a corporation.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not necessarily the one that you were quoting when he made that comment, but there are definitely a lot of bills and stuff that go towards these corporations that have these senators in their pockets.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just so you guys know, here's some of the organizations that are supporting this bill.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Directors Guild of America, the Screen Actors Guild, the Motion Picture Association of America, Recording Industry Association of America, NBCUniversal, Viacom, Sony Pictures Entertainment, Ultimate Fighting Championship...
[SPEAKER_10]: Church Music Publishers Association.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we're fucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's all the RAA and MPAA and all the different movie studios because no one wants piracy.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have no problem with them fighting piracy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get the...
[SPEAKER_10]: The reason this bill is going into place, I get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: This bill doesn't cut it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You need to close these loopholes in the bill before it's... What is going to stop every website in Canada and other countries?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is another reason... I promised I wouldn't get political, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_10]: China.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd rather live in Taiwan
[SPEAKER_11]: We can still stream it, you know, stream to Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I can play all the Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't have to say where we're located.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're in Canada.
[SPEAKER_11]: And not in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm not Benji in our chatroom says, actually, happy birthday is copyrighted.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you put up a YouTube singing happy birthday to someone, you're going to be, your ass is going to jail.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would love to see that article.
[SPEAKER_11]: Grandma goes, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: What happens if you do three different songs?
[SPEAKER_11]: If you sing Happy Birthday and then a couple other karaoke songs, and that's three strikes.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that's not three strikes.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's major violent felonies, I think, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Morpheus in the chat room, our good buddy from Under Sedation Live, Saturday nights here at All Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But not to worry, this is going through Congress, so the public will have a voice and courts to fight it, unlike CARP, which was all secretly done behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, goddamn, sir, I hope you are right, because three words, this bill sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fucking sucks, four words.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is really more important than balancing a budget, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkTetsuya says, well, we're still waiting to see if Under Station Live will be banned in China.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be a great little thing for the network.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be like the show from China versus the show that can't be in China.
[SPEAKER_10]: All on one network.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said, AllGames.com will also have to move to China or Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where could AllGames.com go if this bill passes?
[SPEAKER_10]: AllGames.com, what country would we put them in?
[SPEAKER_10]: Where would Scott Rubin want to be?
[SPEAKER_10]: They can go to... Where would Scott... Amsterdam.
[SPEAKER_10]: Amsterdam.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's football, but not... Well, then I guess they could do Canadian football in Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: This bill is taking far too much time on our show, but at the same time it is very important.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so we just want to bring your attention to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not fucking around.
[SPEAKER_10]: If this bill passes, say goodbye to a lot of your favorite gaming press stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is bad for the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if they don't see it,
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, on Tuesday, I think was the day it was finally posted, they finally posted a response.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fans have been waiting for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quote, we never say never, but we can confirm that there are no plans to bring these three games to the Americas at this time.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Twitter response thanked Operation Rainfall folks for being such incredible fans but said there continues to be no plans for Nintendo of America to release these three games right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't seen people rally for a Wii games release in a very long time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not since President Cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: So our little campaign was not forgotten, which I think is great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they actually said, the game is called President Cat, people, which made me laugh because the game actually wasn't called President Cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: We kind of gave it that name because the translation was like Boss Cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just kind of came out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's call it President Cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the definition of a sukeban is like a delinquent gang leader girl.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, if you imagine a cat being like a delinquent gang leader who is also the president of the company Yes Then that's what it's like Gangbanger cat
[SPEAKER_10]: That could be the sequel.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jeez.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, by the way, Xenoblade is still getting a localization for an English-speaking country, and then some.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a European localization in the works, and this is for Xenoblade Chronicles, and it was in an Iwata Asks interview that's a little video clip there.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Xenoblade is coming out in Europe on September 2nd it's going to come out with a red classic controller pro in order to localize a game for Europe I think it's got to be in English, French, Spanish, German and I'm forgetting a language but like there's like five languages Swahili probably wait English, French, German, Spanish probably Italian that's like five different languages the game's got to be in to come out over there and they should just do it in Latin
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not worth the money to put out here
[SPEAKER_11]: To which I put, dot dot dot, instead we have some more Nintendo 64 games we'd like to port over and make zero changes and Zelda you get a premium.
[SPEAKER_11]: Love, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Zelda Ocarina of Time in 3D?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xenoblade?
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hey, you know what though?
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo's gonna be... You don't understand.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's how Nintendo's gonna fucking play this shit off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, we have no plans on doing that right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: But come E3...
[SPEAKER_11]: fans demanded it and Nintendo we hear you fans we're gonna bring it out for you because we're so gracious we're gonna bring them out to you it's basically you're gonna beg for it and then they're gonna say no and they're like ah well we're so gracious we're gonna bring it out to you so you know what when they do that don't fucking buy it tell them fuck you wait but why wouldn't you if they finally do decide to release the game isn't that what you wanted because it's the attitude that they're having with it
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if I meet you all the way there like I don't disagree that something like that is very likely to happen but I had said before the show I said watch because Nintendo likes to kind of take games and redo them for new consoles like these will all be games on the Wii U and they'll be able to say that oh we're listening and we're oh these are games that the hardcore gamers want Last Story Plus Edition on the Wii U it's Last Story U and Xenoblade U
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's not going to be that at all, because that would take additional effort.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not going to put in additional effort.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even understand what the point is, because they've had other games that they have translated into English and released only in Europe and Japan, and never brought the Europe version of the game over here, which...
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I would think if you're spending the money to translate into English, why not release it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell, you don't have to fucking advertise this thing very much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just put it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: You will sell some copies of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a bummer that it's the Wii because if this was the 360 and there was enough fan demand, we've seen now where that game, and I forget what it was, Death Smile or whatever it was, that Japanese shooter game that came out in Japan and they just said, you know what, we'll put it up as a download title.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're not going to bother to translate it though, so fucking here it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just take it if you want it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I think people are generally happy with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now there are special box sets and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, unfortunately, it would be great if the Wii could support that, but it can't.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on top of that... Maybe the punchline is the Wii U will, and these games will be downloadable on the Wii U. No, and here's the funny part about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: On top of the fact that they won't even bring it over here, they give Europe a nice collector's edition with a controller and everything for them.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, obviously, they know that the game's popular, but they just still don't give a fuck about you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rickster in our chatroom says why do that Nintendo has already put the Wii out to pasture and I think that's a good point is you know well they've already said the Wii U is coming so let the Wii die basically a slow death as we get our last little hurrah Zelda game people still own Wiis and people and this Wii U isn't coming out until the end of next year so what the fuck are they gonna put out is everybody planning on buying a Wii U day one no if I've learned one thing from Nintendo consoles no I'm not
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not planning on buying this thing day one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, unless there's that just kick-ass must-have game.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll wait and see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am a consumer whore, though, so I still may succumb to needing it early or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It really, so far, hasn't... I mean, it's basically a Wii with better graphics and a stupid controller that I don't really give two shits about.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm just gonna like, well, just because, okay, like when the PlayStation 3 came out, the PlayStation 2 didn't just roll over and die.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it still hasn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: God of War was still going, and the old systems don't just roll over and die.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think these games could keep it going.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially not the Wii, because you have to understand...
[SPEAKER_11]: Just because everyone bought a Wii does not mean they're going to buy a Wii U. In fact, I think because you got all these old people and stuff like that to buy Wiis.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that is not going to translate into more Wii U sales.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just because you can use these Wii games on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, Rob, I need to buy a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hey, it's okay because I can still play my DVDs on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, why am I going to buy a new unit if I already have something to play DVDs?
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: I gotta say this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not the only one that doesn't understand your perspective, Loki, of campaign to get the games out, and then when they come out, say fuck them because of their bad attitude.
[SPEAKER_10]: Derek H in our chatroom says, Wait, so you'd be upset if they do what you want them to do?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's like going to McDonald's, buying a Happy Meal, then throwing it on the ground yelling, Fuck you, Ronald McDonald!
[SPEAKER_10]: The sad thing is I can see Loki doing that.
[SPEAKER_10]: There isn't enough fucking bacon.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's my problem is how else then do you teach a company like this that you're not going to fucking take their... Oh, well, you're going to just have to take Reggie and bend him over your knee and say you're being very, very naughty.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like fucking Konami with, well, if you really want this game to come out, you better have those pre-orders in.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not buying your goddamn game then.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't give a shit if you put it out, because it will probably suck anyways, because all of your games, especially music games lately, have really blown.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like doing the pre-orders to determine things, because that's how we got the low cost on the Macross box sets.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like how the random ass DDR, we can never get away from that.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no, it's because they pulled that bullshit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Capcom, why don't you step up and do this bullshit?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know, this seems perfectly down your alley.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that what Nintendo should do?
[SPEAKER_10]: Should Nintendo put it up on their website and say, okay, if 10,000 people order Xenoblade, then we'll put it out?
[SPEAKER_11]: If that's what it's going to take for them to do it in time and matter, then fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you do it?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, because I don't want to buy this fucking game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't play the Wii anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who do I care?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck you, Ronald McDonald!
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would, seriously, I would boycott the game then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you don't want to bring it out?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just want to put out some more Mario and Kirby games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kirby, which, by the way, I don't know if anyone still cares about Kirby, but... This is like the opposite of Operation Rainfall.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Operation Thunder Snow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yo, fuck those games!
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you should start a campaign on Twitter Operation Thunder Snow Don't release those games In fact, don't buy Wii games P.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you, Ronald McDonald
[SPEAKER_11]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everyone's going to get fucking raging boner over goddamn Skyward Sword.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, it's a Zola game with stuff in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to say, though, the last story looked fucking great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was looking forward to seeing that announcement E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: And would I have bought that on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, yes, I think I would have.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have one of those boners for Mistwalker that I kind of do for Q Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, even their mediocre games, I will still support, like Blue Dragon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Mistwalker, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just because you had Nintendo publish your game in fucking Japan, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Other companies will fucking publish it over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't need to go through all this bullshit of having to beg a company to bring it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's companies like Ignition...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Guilty Gear that you would never ever fucking play if you relied on Nintendo to bring that shit over.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know how many decibels I've taken down your mic this episode and it's still not enough because you keep getting louder?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, I'm just saying that... You're just passionate.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am seriously passionate about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The fact is I don't think that it should result in people begging a company like Nintendo to try to get them to understand the niche market.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need companies that already understand the niche market and will bring this shit over regardless.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask this and then we can move on with more stories because we're an hour and a half into the show and haven't got to the end of part A yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is your passion?
[SPEAKER_11]: My passion?
[SPEAKER_11]: As far as these games go?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do these stories get you so angry?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it's this whole, oh, we're this big company and we're just, you know, you should be gracious for everything they were putting out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they just don't, they think they understand what their users want and they don't.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_11]: and we could bring this stuff over because we know we're doing the translation for Europe because hey they're a smaller market and I guess that makes it worth translating the game for it we could bring this over here with little effort whatsoever but no we're going to be assholes and say basically no we don't have any plans on doing this and yeah I know that you guys all rallied and really want this stuff over here and have committed to really going to buy this stuff
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Morpheus in our chatroom says Loki needs Prozac flavored bacon.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really want bacon flavored like medicine.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why would you want to flavor bacon?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you meant bacon flavored Prozac.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sky, is Loki turning green yet?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope, still as white as you can believe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on with another news story and then we'll get into the release dates.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: you've been a very quiet lady over there and usually you're the opinionated one so I've got to know what is your thought on all this mess like Nintendo not releasing these are they being hard-headed is does it make good business sense I say it's average for Nintendo this is just par for the course I'm used to this shit that this is why this is why you've just become desensitized to this
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically people... And not like I play my Wii anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo does something wrong, Loki yells and screams about it, lather, rinse, repeat for the past nine years.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's basically people are... They're barking up the wrong tree.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're asking Nintendo to bring over this really niche game when they should really be bugging these other publishers that put stuff out on the Wii as well as other systems to bring over the games because I think these people... Like, you know, like, Atlus.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's another perfect example of a company that would do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: They...
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all they deal with is niche shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, we get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need the return of working designs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, actually, one of our pinball tables belongs to the owner of working designs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Our Twilight Zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of right, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how we got our Goemon doll.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo plans on spending 16.5 billion yen on a new research and design facility in Kyoto.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nikkei, Japanese Stock Market
[SPEAKER_07]: They basically are trying to move everything into one house.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are bringing in their R&D offices, all of the main staff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything is going to be under one roof.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Loki, 16.5 billion yen on a new research and design facility, yet no last story.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they want to put everyone under one roof.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't see a problem with that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apple's doing the same thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're building some giant space saucer thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they're building a metal donut in the middle of San Jose.
[SPEAKER_10]: Homework approved.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no square wall in the building or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They actually wanted to make a building that looks like Steve Jobs' asshole.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they're building in the middle of San Jose.
[SPEAKER_10]: So everybody can literally walk up his ass day in and day out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's going to be all made of glass.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can actually point out something.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a psychological reason that you want to remove hard edges is that it reduces the urge for violence.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, because when I think of Apple products, I think of violence.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's to make happier workers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: I know people that would kill someone, literally kill someone in the dead of night to get a job at Apple.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I don't think of Apple as having angry workers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: The whole, like, fact that, you know, it's been shown that circle buildings or whatever cause people not to be violent.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sounds like the hippie mumbo jumbo that Steve Jobs would be spouting anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hectagons piss me off.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I think the whole thing is that he didn't like being called a square, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's why.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, ha!
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't call me a square now.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a fucking idiot.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a hippie.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to plant some trees.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go plant some trees, Steve.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually, we're going to plant a lot of trees.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't need the brew me right anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like how Loki had a wide open door to do more Nintendo bashing and he decided to take a pass.
[SPEAKER_11]: What am I going to say about Nintendo opening a facility?
[SPEAKER_11]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're opening a building.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not like this facility is going to research more Mario games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just they're consolidating their stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me get you a little platter.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'm gonna hand you the joke on the platter, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Here it is, here it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're building a, they're putting all these billions of dollars into a research facility for all those new franchises they put out.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not... Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't believe they research shit for any of their franchises, so that's obviously not what it's for.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's for their new consoles that are so innovative and different from their last console.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, this new console, what, it has a tablet for a controller.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's such a genius idea that they need a new research facility.
[SPEAKER_10]: Clearly an idea like that only could have come out of a building shaved like a donut.
[SPEAKER_07]: and basically quite a number of articles I just randomly found from anthropologists, different biologists, psychologists all pointing to the by the circle is a comforting and familiar shape to the mind on an unconscious level.
[SPEAKER_07]: As well as in art, we study the golden mean as a curve.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that it's like the shape of a shell, the circular shape of a shell.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why a more circular face in some cultures is considered to be more attractive, they look for symmetry.
[SPEAKER_10]: The hectagons are still very rude, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_07]: So for the record, they're actually a psychology behind it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't believe in psychology.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's clear.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's that witty retort I've been waiting for DarkSakura all night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's move on to release dates.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to travel the world and check out what's coming out to a store near you and eventually we'll get through this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll save yourself some time because there's only one thing that's coming out this week that you really need to pick up and that would be Earth Defense Force Insect Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_11]: and that's of course assuming that Earth Defense or assuming that they didn't release it on Saturday wherever you live because that was the case in fact since we're getting into it now I will explain why it's being released on Saturday because it's a funny story actually and it also goes to show you GameStop they're fucking assholes
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so get this.
[SPEAKER_11]: D3, they put out the game, they shipped it to stores or whatever like that early and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They misprinted the street date letter or the street date number or whatever on the master cases that went out.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it said streets July 2nd, despite the fact that all their paperwork, the street date letters, etc.
[SPEAKER_11]: say July 5th.
[SPEAKER_11]: GameStop's going, no take-back Cs, no take-back Cs.
[SPEAKER_11]: It fucking says the second.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're putting it on the second on all systems, even though it was only the 360 MasterCases that they messed up on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Instead of, you know, D3 saying, you know, hey, GameStop, you know, I understand that we did misprint that on there, but the street date is still the fifth.
[SPEAKER_11]: Could you put it on the fifth?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're like, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're putting it out whenever we goddamn feel like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so that's kind of what happened.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pinch, poke, yell me a coke, no take-back Cs.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's basically now everybody's kind of putting it out because, well, GameStop's doing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they advertised it on the website.
[SPEAKER_11]: They called all their pre-order customers.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're assholes.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: The benefit of it is that you get to play the game early.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a lot of people are going to be putting it out as well other than GameStop early.
[SPEAKER_11]: So bug killing on the 4th of July doesn't sound too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the moral of the story is D3, learn to type.
[SPEAKER_11]: yes and that's coming out on PS3 and 360 this week and I kid you not that's literally the only thing that's coming out this week
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: on the PlayStation 3 Angel Senki comes out as well as Earth Defense Force Insect Armageddon Infamous 2 gets its Japanese release this week Just Cause 2 gets a price reduction Knight's Contract L.A.
[SPEAKER_10]: Noire a game called R.U.S.E.
[SPEAKER_10]: moves into the Ubisoft Best Collection and Tom Clancy's Hawks 2 also a Best Collection price reduction this week on the PS3 it's a busy week on the PlayStation 3
[SPEAKER_10]: moving on to other consoles let's see if I can get to the Wii or the 3DS here my list oh my list is starting to show Vita releases but not till December over in Japan no hard dates yet I think those are all placeholders just so you know Sony PSP Suzumiya Haruhi-chan no Mahjong they're doing a Haruhi Mahjong game yeah look at that right there check that out and it's Mahjong
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how to play Mahjong.
[SPEAKER_10]: You should teach me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've never played Mahjong?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I played Shanghai on the old Macintosh.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think that counts.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's Mahjong Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm talking about, like, for real Mahjong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tekken 6 gets a price reduction this week on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Nintendo Wii, a red Wii Remote Plus control.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all that's coming out on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: But 3DS gets a couple games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dr. Lotrek Tobuyaku no Kishidan comes out from Konami Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is... It's Dr. Lorcan, I don't remember the fucking subtitle to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's from Konami, it's coming out in September.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's not Professor Layton.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very similar to Professor Layton, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next week, by the way, in Japan, you can look forward to this, not this week, next week, the 14th, the Flare Red 3DS and Star Fox 64 are the big releases in Japan next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: UK!
[SPEAKER_07]: One thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Virtua Tennis 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 8th.
[SPEAKER_07]: For PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, hooray.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love tennis.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who plays tennis on the PC?
[SPEAKER_10]: Couple more news stories for you guys, and then we're gonna get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll tell you what, this week's classic game of the week is old.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, really old, you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Game for Windows well at least the marketplace is going to be no longer is actually merging with Xbox.com on July 11th and that's all you need to know I guess they tried to overhaul it back in November and no one cared so now it's going to be part of the Xbox marketplace
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: This actually kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, Games for Windows was having a hard time kind of finding its market, especially versus Steam, to merge all the gaming into one place and to really kind of homogenize, if you will, the Xbox gamer tag and the experience and all that, bringing that, you know, connect to PCs even and all that, kind of bringing that all together.
[SPEAKER_10]: That all seems kind of smart for Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this seems logical.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I guess there's really not a lot else to say on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be interesting though what will happen with the Windows 8 integration.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I'm most curious about because you know it'll somehow integrate into Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm really curious how Microsoft is going to tie together the 360 and Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now there's only so much they can do because they don't want to get... Well the new interface looks like Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's an optional interface, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's one thing that they haven't been... That was one type of interface that you can have.
[SPEAKER_10]: Windows will still have the traditional way of doing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wait, that's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Optional on Windows.
[SPEAKER_11]: My mistake.
[SPEAKER_11]: Required on 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's just like, what is that thing called?
[SPEAKER_10]: The multimedia Windows thing that you can do on the 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Windows Media Center.
[SPEAKER_10]: Windows Live or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a lot of what was shown with Windows 7, but how many people really use that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't use that in my house.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's too damn slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't know how many people use that, but there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, anyhow, one other story for you guys and then we'll get into the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is about a different classic game, GoldenEye.
[SPEAKER_10]: A domain has been spotted for a game called GoldenEye Reloaded.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not just one domain, a bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it possible that last year's Wii game will be coming out on the 360 and PS3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Could it maybe be getting a sequel?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or could it just mean fucking nothing?
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be any of the above, but that domain has been spotted and it indicates that GoldenEye
[SPEAKER_10]: is not quite dead, even though the Wii version got kind of lukewarm reviews.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what would happen if that game came out in HD on the 360 or PS3?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say that's actually kind of rad if that happens.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, someone had already done the translation to HD already, but it got kind of tied up with the whole rights being owned by... Yeah, but doesn't Activision pretty much solely own the James Bond stuff now?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but I think that's why Goldeneye came out on the Wii and not on the other systems because the other James Bond games are terrible.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let's go to the gaming vault.
[SPEAKER_10]: and we're going to take a stroll down the gaming lane and find a classic video game in the vault that DarkSakura says, hey, you kids need to respect where your games come from.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, you wouldn't have Earth Defense Force Insect Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_10]: You wouldn't have The Last Story or any of these games if it weren't for games such as this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a game that I played when I was five years old.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, so this would have been like 50 years ago?
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called The Quest for the Rings, and it was on the Odyssey 2 and Video Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: Came out in 1981.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's listen to some of those bleeps and bloops.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, that's the game sound.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's when it's having you pick your class.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me get to somebody like... That's gonna hurt our listeners' ears, but there you go, it's in the background.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And keep in mind, I played this game actually for a few years, because when I moved next door to a couple other friends, they had an Odyssey 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I got to play it again, and I loved the game even over the years.
[SPEAKER_07]: But okay, Quest for the Rings basically was sort of...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's what Gauntlet should have been based off of.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was very Gauntlet-y, but this came out four years before Gauntlet existed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It had a board game released with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a combination of a video game and a board game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It came in this huge-ass box.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had one person who was the ringmaster.
[SPEAKER_07]: So sort of like a combination between playing the D&D board game and playing Gauntlet.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you could play the board game with the stuff that would go on in the quest mode, or you could actually just play the game in quest mode and play through the different levels.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was the game that I was trying to remember the name of a few episodes ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you had four classes that you could play as.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could be a warrior.
[SPEAKER_07]: He can kill stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could be a wizard who can stun other enemies.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could also be a changeling who could turn invisible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except when the changeling was invisible, you couldn't see him either.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then there was the phantom who could walk through all kinds of walls except for one kind and he did it at half speed which actually I would usually pick either the phantom or the changeling but the phantom was super convenient to have because there were levels later on where the walls would change location
[SPEAKER_07]: It was super aggravating.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, the gameplay video stopped because there was only about two minutes of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I found this related video that I'd seen before that's actually pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is how games were marketed back then.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to play the commercial for this game real quick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wizard of Odyssey?
[SPEAKER_00]: Is the keyboard really the key to greater challenge in video games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can play strategy games like Quest for the Rings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plan your strategy on the game board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Use the keyboard to change heroes, enemies, places.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be a wizard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Outwit fiery dragons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take that dragon.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wizards hate to lose.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Master Strategy Series, only from Odyssey 2, where the keyboard is the key to greater challenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Buy Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get $82 worth of free games, including Quest for the Rings and Pickaxe Pete.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had pick XP too.
[SPEAKER_10]: $82 worth of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was $41 a piece.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this game with its bleepy bloops, $41 in 19... What is this commercial?
[SPEAKER_10]: 1981, I think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was this commercial?
[SPEAKER_10]: and that's... I mean, games were expensive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's interesting, too, that they used the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really the niche for the Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess just be competitive with the 2600.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, real gaming uses a keyboard, which is funny because that argument is still used today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the other thing with the Odyssey, too, is that it was also advertised as an educational system, too, because there were a number of educational games on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, one that we used to play all the time was CryptoQuip, where you put in a word...
[SPEAKER_07]: We put in a word and then it scrambles it and we would always pick one person in our group that had to unscramble the word and so they'd have us face the wall except whenever it was me, I mean I was always really good at it anyway but the wall that they would have us face had a mirror on it and I've been able to read backwards since I've been able to read so it was never that difficult.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this also was a system that had Casey Munchkin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or was it Munchkin or Crazy Chase that was the Pac-Man clone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Casey Munchkin, I think it was called.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I've actually got a couple copies of.
[SPEAKER_07]: But there was a cease and desist put on them.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to find... I mean, it's not really super expensive, but to find a copy of Casey Munchkin is, you know, kind of a find.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what made this game awesome to a five-year-old?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it was just that you could, you know, you could fight a dragon.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the dragon, you know, you couldn't kill the dragon.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it was just an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, look how awesome the dragon looked.
[SPEAKER_07]: The big green blip.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was serious graphics.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Godzilla.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to show everybody what this picture looks like because, I mean, seriously, that was pretty hardcore awesome graphics for, you know, when I was five.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, there it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry, there's more?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you sounded like we were done.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, then what else?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was going to tell you about the other things that were in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay, well, please do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then let me restart the music.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had five kinds of monsters, and they had the most awesome names.
[SPEAKER_07]: There were orcs and fire wraiths.
[SPEAKER_07]: who were really... They actually looked just alike, except they were different colors.
[SPEAKER_07]: One was pink, one was blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then you had dragons, which they basically moved left and right across the screen, but if you got in their way, they'd be like, and run at you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you'd be like, oh shit, it's a dragon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there was...
[SPEAKER_07]: The Nightmares, by Droth Tarantulas, and Doomed Wing Bloodthirst, which makes me think that the designers of WoW played this game and took inspiration from the characters in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I mean, I always... This is one game that I seriously thought they should totally remake.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because... It was just... The theory behind it was so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really was.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was simple, simple gameplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it did it so effectively that I don't think any other game has been, you know... If I'm looking back to this as one of my favorite classic games ever...
[SPEAKER_07]: Then, you know, it's got to have something, say something for its staying power.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'll go ahead and actually link what the cover looked like in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it had a really epic 80s cover.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, man, that's when people actually juice shit by hand.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Classic game of the week, the quest for the rings for the Odyssey 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn, that's old.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, we're going to take a break here, but don't worry, there's plenty more of Orange Lawns ready to come.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank God there's no work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fear!
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yep, we can stay up late a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pinkberry run.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pinkberry closes at 10.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're not going to be done by 10.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate to break it to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll send the husband to go get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now that I can buy into.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we gotta take a break though.
[SPEAKER_10]: When we come back, there's plenty more Orange Lounge Radio to come.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're gonna talk about Portal 2, we're gonna talk Minecraft, we're gonna talk DDR again, so Mal's making his way into the show, PSP remasters, and plenty more when we come back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your Twitter topics as well, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get those in in the next few minutes so we can talk about that when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are live on this July the 3rd of 2011 with the 418th episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're listening to us live at All Games Radio, why don't you head on over to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com where you can chat with us live and give your instant feedback on the stories and just have a good time with the other OLR listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you're listening to us on the podcast though, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope you've enjoyed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever we're helping to fill your day with.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know we have a lot of folks that listen to us while they're at work and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: So thank you for downloading us and choosing to spend your day with us because it's a pretty long show, especially this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: So thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you do like Orange Launch Radio, of course, we do always encourage you, please help spread the word of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can also visit Ice Tunes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why did I say Ice Tunes?
[SPEAKER_07]: You were thinking of vanilla ice.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, maybe this lovely cup of ice water I have.
[SPEAKER_07]: In that case, you should stop.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can visit us on iTunes and leave us a nice five-star review.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or if you are not an iTunes user, there's plenty of podcast sites.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wherever you found this show, you should leave a nice review and help send other people over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: while you're out shopping for podcasts might I recommend one of our other Orange Lounge production shows I guess you could say The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth www.hordehouse.com it's a show about the world of Warcraft and it's myself and Extifer
[SPEAKER_10]: Doing lulzy Warcraft chat And this week was a real fun show We talked a lot There was a brand new patch in WoW this week 4.2 And also huge news about Warcraft It didn't make this show roll Probably because I already talked about it on Horde House But WoW has gone free to play in some ways Until level 20 Basically what existed as the free trial before Is now an unlimited trial It's not capped to 14 days So you can play all the way to level 20
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: which we actually got into a discussion about we really wish that there was some way that we could cross zones in play because you can't play on... Oh yeah, it's one of the biggest drawbacks of WoW is that there's no way for us to roll on Europe and they can't roll on us unless you actually buy that region's copy of the freaking game and do it that way and it's kind of a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's butt-hearted.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the host over there still, we're good net friends because she's been on Horde House a couple times now and always brings the lulz.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I signed up on their forums.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're fun people.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we had a really, really good time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really long discussion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope to go back again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Prospects seem hopeful.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they were just great people.
[SPEAKER_07]: All three of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really enjoyed the time I had.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't you just love EJ's accent?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love her accent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just want to put it in a little voice box and open it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The haters are going to hate.
[SPEAKER_07]: She says, fuck all, better than anyone I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, by the way, we got a tweet from the Girls Gone Wow show on Twitter at twitter.com slash OLR is our Twitter and GGW show is theirs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I loved having DarkSakura on our podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: She was an amazing guest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm in your show kidnapping your host.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kisses.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're here first.
[SPEAKER_08]: Clone, clone, clone, clone, clone.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I think that's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, since I said it on Bobby's show tonight, I guess we could say it here.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is a third podcast in the works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're looking at taping the pilot in the next week or so.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm hoping we'll have more information soon.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's all you get.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can say one thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It will involve a Dan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, we can say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, it will involve Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will involve Dan.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we are going to leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said A-Dan.
[SPEAKER_10]: A-Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did not say which Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will involve a Dan.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to the news that there's lots of news this week and some of it we just don't have time to talk 15 minutes about like we did some of those Nintendo stories tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kotaku, I don't know if they've been doing the actual translations themselves, but they've been running on their website every Thursday starting a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Localized versions of Retro Game Master.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, for those who haven't heard of Retro Game Master, it's a show in Japan that has this game master who plays through old classic games, and there's kind of commentary going along with it, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's like the same thing I see on billions of YouTube channels and JustinTVs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kind of like that, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: He has trouble with some of the games, and it's his commentary.
[SPEAKER_10]: Professionally written, I guess?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the first episode was Ninja Gaiden, and then, of course, this week's episode was Super Fantasy Zone.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you can check them out.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're streaming, like I said, every Thursday on their Thursday at 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: Eastern is when they have the thing going.
[SPEAKER_11]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the type of stuff that should have been on G4 back in the day when they talked about games.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the Portal 2 information.
[SPEAKER_10]: Portal 2... Sorry, I was talking to our chatters who now of course are asking a ton of questions on that little tease about the other podcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: They teamed up with Kotaku to put the episodes out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I'm not knocking Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a fine website, what have you.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not like a big Hulu or Netflix or even YouTube.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a very kind of niche gaming site.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's one of the bigger gaming blogs, certainly.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's just an interesting path.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I don't think of Kotaku television very often.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's interesting for them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Portal 2 Patent Pending
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm also another called Infinifling.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was, I guess, focusing on mid-air portaling techniques.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was second.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then Endifice, which is based on some destroyed aperture chambers, picked up an honorable mention.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, all these are available to download at, of course, the portal website, thinkwithportals.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: and many other user created levels so if you've played through Portal 2 already on PC and you want to go back and try some custom maps and stuff you can go and download these and it's really easy to access them in game so I haven't really played around with this yet but I always thought if this came out it would kind of all be integrated into Steam but it's not like I have to go to this website and do like I don't have to hack my game per se right but don't I have to have this dev mode or something
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just pull up the console in the game by hitting the title key and then there's a simple command you put in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well that's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'd be kind of cool if they integrated it with some sort of option in a menu or something like that where you can just select a map and play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or maybe make multiple maps or something like that so you can have your own single player campaigns.
[SPEAKER_11]: And of course, obviously, not something that you're going to be able to play on consoles.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then finally, Left 4 Dead 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently they had a little Easter egg in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: There was a community-made campaign called Suicide Blitz 2 in Left 4 Dead 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's one of the officially featured fan-created add-ons for the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it has a very neat Portal 2 Easter egg buried in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently if you...
[SPEAKER_11]: You find a portal, I guess, into the actual Aperture Science.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can, I guess, find the Aperture Science and also Companion Cube, Propression Gel, Special Infected Zombies, and all sorts of neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was watching the video.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a video attached to the story that had two giggling girls playing the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked really well done from what I was watching.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked like you were freaking playing Portal but inside Left 4 Dead.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like those wacky, zany crossovers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, and I like how you have to find a gnome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Street Fighter 4, the ports keep on coming
[SPEAKER_10]: Volt, it's now available.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not something you have to wait for.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was announced at a Capcom event in Tokyo, but it's available now.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are three new fighters available.
[SPEAKER_10]: Balrog, Vega, and Cody.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind that when Street Fighter 4 was ported to the iPhone, not all the fighters from the
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's Street Fighter IV Volt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, in retro gaming's getting upgrades, Boulder Dash.
[SPEAKER_10]: You remember this game, Boulder Dash?
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember this because this was huge on the Commodore 64, was the series Boulder Dash.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think a lot of the old PC, not PC, sorry, old computing platforms like the Apples and so forth, this game saw some type of port on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: These games were huge back in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's getting a remake, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's an HD update.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's coming to Xbox Live Arcade very soon, July 13th.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will be just shy of the Summer Arcade promotion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, it's going to be going up against Ms.
[SPEAKER_10]: Splosion Man, so it might fall through the cracks a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you're fond of the old game on the 64 or whatever computer back in the day, Boulder Dash XL is on its way.
[SPEAKER_10]: it will have 7 times the amount of caves as the original 1984 version it's coming out from Calypso Media there will be a new puzzle mode with items like speed enhancers and telescoping arms, online leaderboards it will set you back 800 Microsoft points there will also be a PC version late in the summer if you are a personal computing purist and you don't want to play the game on one of those evil consoles
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: This all coming out from an interview with Zelda longtime producer Eiji Onuma, who said, so when we show a graphic demo, people think, oh, this is what the next Zelda will look like, but that's not necessarily the case.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they also cite, again, the Wind Waker GameCube comparison there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So confirmed, we use Zelda to be cel-shaded, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, maybe not quite.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Broadband!
[SPEAKER_07]: New download content!
[SPEAKER_07]: It will be For What It's Worth by Buffalo Springfield, Man on the Moon by R.E.M., Aerials by System of the Down, Hypnotized by System of the Down, and Turning Japanese by The Vapors.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for Aerials and Turning Japanese and For What It's Worth, there will be pro guitar bass expansions available for another 80 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And next up, Final Fantasy Tactics for the iOS is delayed.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's according to Sequenix's Facebook page.
[SPEAKER_07]: It needs a little bit more time, so it's going to be in late July instead of June, as they said it would.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that might be a little old.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to have the bare minimum of an iPhone 3GS to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is the remake of the PlayStation 1 version, so it's the good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, last but not least, oh, you addict people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Minecraft!
[SPEAKER_07]: They passed 10 million registered users.
[SPEAKER_07]: and that's according to Marcus Persson's blog.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they are now officially at 10,005,304.
[SPEAKER_07]: The people who've actually bought it are in the 2 million range.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's still pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: 2 million copies of the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: One out of every five are buying it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they say that basically they're getting 42,000 new players registering in the last 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can I take my registration back?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not that big a jerk, I promise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yay for Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yay for our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every week you guys send us tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we read some of your tweets here live on air.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a lot of tweets tonight, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's like not a lot of Twitter news tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: MNZiba says this tweet saying, Xenoblade or Monado, beginning of the world, is actually number three on the best sellers in Nintendo Wii action games list at Amazon.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: and she gives us a link here to Amazon.com bestsellers.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually up to number two now, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Super Smash Brothers Brawl is the game that's beating it and it in turn is beating, Monado is beating Lego Pirates of the Caribbean, Super Mario Galaxy 2 and Lego Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, granted, keep in mind, we are looking at just the action game list.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see where it ranks overall.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking at the overall list, and it's number 16.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's still not bad overall, but just so you know, overall, Monado is being beat by a Wii Nunchuck controller in black and the HD component cable, which is number 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another tweet to us from TigerClaw sends us a tweet saying, Space station internet too slow for online video games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see, it links us to a Kotaku article here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Regarding life in space, everyone has three questions.
[SPEAKER_10]: How do you poop?
[SPEAKER_10]: Has anyone screwed?
[SPEAKER_10]: And can you play video games up there?
[SPEAKER_07]: They poop in a vacuum tube.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura would know the answer to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, a Canadian astronaut, I didn't know they had astronauts in Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: Canadians in Space.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'd be a great sitcom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, Canadian astronaut Chris Hadfield said that the internet connection aboard the International Space Station is simply too slow for games.
[SPEAKER_10]: He compared it to a 56K dial-up modem.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I guess the reason why it stinks is because of the space station's orbital velocity speed.
[SPEAKER_10]: That thing moves at five miles per second.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because keep in mind, it's orbiting the Earth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hadfield was the first Canadian to walk in space, and he's in line anyway to become the first Canadian commander of the space station.
[SPEAKER_10]: And clearly he must be a gamer.
[SPEAKER_10]: This all came out during a Canada Day event in Edmonton, so thank you for the link, Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blinder says this is a tweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blinder222, to be specific, on Twitter, says, Did any of you play the Uncharted 3 beta?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'm assuming because it appeared on my... Just fucking download it if you're going to get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The servers are fine now.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it appeared on my download list now, but it's just... I have my PlayStation up in the front room and I have to drag an Ethernet cable because remember, old-ass PlayStation, no Wi-Fi built in because it's a 20 gig.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I have to put an Ethernet cable, drag it into the front room and
[SPEAKER_11]: See you last night.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to play Earth Defense Force online as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And yeah, I can do that with my console, but for some reason I wanted to plug it in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, I'm going to check it out hopefully in the next week But I tell you guys, I have a backlog of games to play I still have Loki's L.A.
[SPEAKER_10]: Noire I haven't even touched yet And I have two racing games that I have for my rental service And I have touched none of it Because I've been playing this new Warcraft patch I've been playing the other games I've been talking about And Final Fantasy XIII I'm up to 30 hours in Final Fantasy XIII Rob, are your racing games PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any of them?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're Xbox 360, but they're from my rental service.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I was gonna save.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got, like, a huge driving setup for PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nah, it's 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Test Drive Unlimited 2, and one of the Need for Speed games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shift 2 Unleashed?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or is it Hot Pursuit?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's Hot Pursuit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to look.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't Hot Pursuit the one they just announced that isn't even out yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, Hot Pursuit is the one that came out last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: That one looks badass, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_10]: That new one looks fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hot Pursuit is the one that came out back in November.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shift to Unleashed was the one that's sort of like Project Gotham that came out back in March.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then, yeah, The Run is the one that's coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yes, at some point I will get to Uncharted 3 before they close the beta.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually have a pretty big gaming queue right now of stuff I want to play, and I'm still trying to beat Final Fantasy XIII, which is just, I'm so into it right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's spreading.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you see Bobby Blackwolf, our guy before us here?
[SPEAKER_11]: I should finish mine.
[SPEAKER_10]: He posted a tweet last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: After a year, it's time for me to beat Chapter 10.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is funny, because I didn't struggle on that same boss fight.
[SPEAKER_10]: There were boss fights I struggled on, but not that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: There were some Eidolon fights that made me want to just... I'll have Sazh's Eidolon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god, I went crazy on that fight, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to find my save.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's on one of the hard drives I have, because I've swapped hard drives around.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know it's not on that console, because that's the internal hard drive.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I have to track it down, and once I do, then I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another tweet, last tweet here from TigerClaw305 on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Professor Layton Movie is getting a US release.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, oh, I hate these websites that have ads you have to click through.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: See how they do that, Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_10]: They release something that's English language and release it in British markets, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: they can come over here without any effort whatsoever because it's already translated into English.
[SPEAKER_10]: As revealed at Anime Expo 2011 this weekend the feature length animated film is on its way to North America reports Anime Your Way.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was actually fairly well received and the developer Level 5 has already commissioned a sequel and would like a new movie out annually.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'd like to add also, seeing as we're talking about anime movies coming out soon, they announced a Trigun movie coming out, and that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: The trailer, did you watch it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: So nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will take place, obviously, during the series, for obvious reasons.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that is very exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, that's it for Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get back to some other gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's talk a little bit about Minecraft since we were just talking about Minecraft not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Minecraft 1.7 is out now and it adds pistons and deadly sheep.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Black Sheep, Pistons, Minecraft
[SPEAKER_11]: Update 1.8 has been delayed a little bit by a week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And 1.8 would add the Minecraft Adventure mode.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that'll be coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, 1.8 is released in the next few months.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they're saying that they're also starting the crunch for the full release, which is going to be on 11.11.11.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the adventure mode, I believe, was where you can actually create your own... I know that they've added maps recently, but maybe you can make your own Zelda-type game or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Should be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Definitely adding a lot more stuff to this.
[SPEAKER_11]: At some point, I'll have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just not yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, DDR News, DarkToagag wants to know, before I get to DDR News, does Loki have Minecraft?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have it on my iPod, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know, that one Minecraft app or whatever that came out and they got pulled immediately?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I found it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I have that, but I haven't really, I mean, trying to use it on an iPod is just...
[SPEAKER_11]: that's retarded no I haven't really played it yet I thought I had downloaded it at one point but I guess not
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Dance Revolution X3 vs. Dance Dance Revolution 2nd Mix
[SPEAKER_10]: There will be a second mix mode in the game where you can play the full version of Dance Dance Revolution second mix including all the licensed music that appeared in that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: E-Amusement Capability
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, X3 is really the highlight, and that's the game they want you to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: 480 tracks in total, standard DDR music, mix, songs, let's see, a variety of Bomani artists, transplant songs from other Bomani series, eAmusementGate, a community-oriented website for Konami games that allows players to form groups, share scores, and interact with other players.
[SPEAKER_10]: That actually sounds kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will it make an arcade here?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Could it get a home release that good?
[SPEAKER_10]: Doubt it.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, that's the... Why can't I get that as a home release?
[SPEAKER_11]: See, this is what pisses us off so much, is like, they put all this effort into DDR for the arcade, which, you know, we would love to believe that the arcade is still, you know, a viable place to have these type of games, but at the same time, they can't just strictly port this to the home console.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever happened with the problem being...
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, back in the PlayStation 1 days, just take the arcade release, you bring it home, and you add a couple things.
[SPEAKER_11]: Done.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: People loved it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do you gotta change it up now?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't understand the point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, it's because probably licensing 480 songs for home would be a little bit expensive, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, I'm curious about this whole second mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, second mix, just to put it in perspective for those that haven't followed DDR like we have, it's like 11 years old.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the first one I owned, was second mix on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, so it's weird that they're kind of going back to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, dude, I wonder if second mix will have, what was that fucking mode that's only in second mix, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was like your favorite fucking mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance battle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance battle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe that'll come back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would actually be kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance Battle was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Battle's the one where you would have a measure where you could just make up your own steps, and then the other player had to do them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you could just... But you could only have, like, two things at any beat at a time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I mean, you couldn't go too shit crazy, but they would have to do whatever you just did.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we used to just try to fuck each other's day.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, on top of that, there was no vivid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was all flat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm really curious to see how this translates in the arcades, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll fuck it up somehow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Prove me wrong, Konami, I dare you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should play Strictly Businesses or Transfer Music after birth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remind me after the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop playing on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're trying to do a show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, can I say something that's pissing me off about Facebook right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still not in the Civ World beta.
[SPEAKER_10]: That pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm mad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't be mad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Get even.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Kazuo Hirai is now the chairman of Sony SCEI.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he's now the head doo-doo in charge
[SPEAKER_07]: And guess who is replacing him as group CEO?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be Andrew House.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's taking over.
[SPEAKER_07]: But guess what's happening to Ken Kutaragi, the crayon eater and helmet wearer?
[SPEAKER_07]: He's retiring for reals.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except he's going to hang around as senior technology advisor.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's going to a very special home where they serve crayons for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's going to be eating the rest of his dinner through straws.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the rest of his life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they don't give you food that you can hurt yourself with in the home.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's gonna be eating some Gerber!
[SPEAKER_07]: No, um, but yeah, he actually, uh, did retire, but he's remaining behind as Senior Technology Advisor, and, yeah, it seems like a really crappy time to do, like, oh, you just, uh, have the most insecure system ever, blah blah blah, oh, here's a promotion, but really the fact is that, um, Akira Sato retired, so that's why they're shoving people up.
[SPEAKER_10]: We knew there was going to be a management shakeup coming though after everything that they went through the past few months.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I thought it would be deserved firings.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sackings.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the word sacking a little more.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like them to be rendered redundant.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: We were talking... You're watching the Giggling Girls video, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, it's so awesome!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, it's GLaDOS!
[SPEAKER_11]: And now for two giggling schoolgirls!
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, that is the third podcast that OLR is working on.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Giggling Girls Playing Video Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wouldn't that be the Giggling Lesbian Show?
[SPEAKER_10]: I wish, if they still lived here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, the PSP remaster titles that were announced during both E3 and their own events, they're basically able to do this because of the help of a PSP engine that's a software development kit that Sony put out regarding these PSP remaster titles that allows them to be able to port them into HD.
[SPEAKER_11]: and with high resolution rendering, stereoscopic 3D and wireless controller support for DualShock 3 and apparently they haven't announced any more remastered titles other than Monster Hunter Portable 3rd and then also of course there's I mean they call it the remastered title but the God of War Origins Collection which is coming out that's basically the two PSP God of War games um
[SPEAKER_11]: Funny!
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry I'm slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm chatting with listeners about Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're talking about what parties we use.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're telling me that... Somebody... Who's telling me that they use... Dungeon Buster is saying I think it's Lightning, Saws, and Vanilla.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, who do you have as a Sentinel?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you don't have a Sentinel in that party.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, you have to have Fang or Snow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't use Snow because he's a whiny vagina.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I like Fang because she's hardcore.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I use her as my Sentinel.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, PSP remasters.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Cool deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any of those worth getting, you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um... I didn't really play Monster Hunter and God of War... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: God of War would be fun to play, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't really played in... I only think I went through all the way in 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I didn't play all the way through in 1 because my... It glitched out in 1.
[SPEAKER_11]: At the very last boss.
[SPEAKER_10]: um going on to anticipated games Gears of War 3 has leaked to the internet already uh oh this is a uh not a finalized build by the way but it does have the full campaign and there are some multiplayer modes this could be the E3 build of the game but not sure uh they say it's a developer build or what they call oh and you've heard this term on the show before a JTAG version of the game
[SPEAKER_10]: You may need a special modified Xbox 360 or dev kit to run it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Loki would never indulge in that because that would be wrong to download that and play that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, that would be wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's a developer version of the game because JTAGS basically can operate like a developer's console.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a dev kit too, so that'd be...
[SPEAKER_11]: so if you're trying to keep yourself spoiler free on Gears of War 3 stories you might want to leave the internet you might want to take a break from the internet for about 6 months or whenever this game is supposed to come out yeah, careful because they do have a bunch of different I guess builds in here they have a testing, shipping, release and then multiplayer so they're testing a bunch of different things
[SPEAKER_10]: by the way I love having a podcast can I just say that I love this like you know I was just bitching a minute ago that I'm not playing Civ World and one of the listeners just said oh there's an invite in your inbox now aww love the internet love it I love it I wish Google Plus had been that easy if I didn't invite you like during that 90 minute window that one night you got screwed I didn't get my invite I know cause they shut it off like I cannot invite people now to Google Plus fucking retarded
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be opened up soon for others.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's not a lot on there right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, you know, yay, I'm on Google Plus and it's not Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like that's what every status update I see on there is right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's not Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, it's not Facebook, but is 10 times more awesome is our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com Every week DarkSakura opens up the mailbag and dives in and reads some emails.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's going to share them with you right now if she can stop playing on Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm putting something important to other artists on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I will tell you what it is because it's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: The iCloud logo is actually using the golden ratio as its design background.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Implications of Brown vs. EMA ruling.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll talk the subject to death this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I find whenever I try to explain this to a non-gamer, they not only don't care, but they think it doesn't affect them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every time they play Solitaire, Farmville, Bejeweled, take an online test, give games to their kids, or anything else software related, they're doing so without fear of breaking a bunch of state-by-state laws.
[SPEAKER_07]: Soon we won't do anything without some sort of interactive media, be it a question or a controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: It affects everyone in the USA.
[SPEAKER_07]: My two bits without repeating a story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've given him some more babas.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, okay, there is a couple, actually one from Game Politics, another story that he linked, about Star Wars Galaxy's players filing a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to know more about that, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because the game is shutting down soon, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: So they're filing class action lawsuits?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's got to be lifetime subscriptions, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically it says that more than 50 Star Wars Galaxies players are filing a class action lawsuit against Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there are a bunch of other players that says that they will do the same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Sony is shutting down... They basically are having their petitions go out.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the problem is that they agreed that Sony could cancel the game at any time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: and their SOL.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm pretty sure that's in the terms of service for any MMO, even Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can pull the plug at any time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember Warcraft shut down in China for four months?
[SPEAKER_10]: That could happen here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It won't, but it could.
[SPEAKER_07]: well also about the whole Resident Evil Mercenaries basically Amazon customers are actually putting like huge huge negative reviews on Amazon like there is one person saying I don't care how much fun this game is or how good it looks or how much it costs there's one save slot save data is permanent and cannot be deleted Capcom is attempting to set a new precedent in consumer manipulation and control with this product
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, Dear Sakura, Loki, and Roger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Roar!
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Roger Roberts.
[SPEAKER_07]: This week, a game company did slash said slash didn't do slash didn't say something.
[SPEAKER_07]: This thing is the worst thing in the history of the world and ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Roar!
112.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay Black, Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: This message has been brought to you by Korn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Korn, great addition to tacos, bad addition to Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: After all, adding Korn to tacos has never caused haze.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sent from my iPad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm allergic to corn of all kinds.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm assuming my name got auto-corrected to Roger.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, because Julian called you Roger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's... He said, happy birthday, Roger.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shit, I forgot to bring back the cake plate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, by the way, a certain someone is listening right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope the four-year-old's not listening with all our potty mouth language.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't you say you wanted to say something to... I said it on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I didn't know you wanted to say something publicly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, thank you for the cake.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I expressed that last week.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this is from Chiggers, which that's the worst nickname ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I love that nickname.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know what those are?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh, is it something really... They're bugs that burrow under your skin and lay their eggs and infect under your skin and then the eggs hatch and they come out of your skin leaving these weird zombie-like trails on your arms.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen it happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear OLR, long-time listener, six years, first-time emailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, hearts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've noticed PS3 is now starting to put out TurboGrafx-16 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think it's possible they may try and get some games that were released out on the SNES or Saturn from any third-party publishers?
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep up the good work and belated happy ninth anniversary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yours truly, in Horde House, Gildy, Chickers.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, as far as the whole PlayStation 3, TurboGrafx-16 games No, they will not get games on the NES, SNES, or any of that Even if they were third party Even if they were third party because you're emulating the hardware that doesn't belong And so I think the whole licensing and all that would be I mean, they would have to completely redo the game Completely redo it And I just don't see that happening They're not gonna Yeah
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, never say never just like Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be hilarious if they did Saturn games on a PlayStation at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would just be lol.
[SPEAKER_07]: The big competition was the Saturn and PlayStation back in the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or what about PlayStation games on a Dreamcast?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have three video games that I can play on my Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the joke.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Tekken and Crazy Taxi?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tekken 3 and Crazy Taxi and Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Metal Gear Solid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was all Bleemcast, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were Bleemcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember when I tried to run Bleem on my PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Granted, this was way back in the day and that did not work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember when I had an emulator that worked better than Bleem.
[SPEAKER_07]: and we were trying to play Street Fighter EX3 that was lousy because it still ran like crap but yeah Tekken actually did look a lot better on Dreamcast just saying that's it
[SPEAKER_10]: Email us, Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com Make DarkSakura work more next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Send us more emails, Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com Meanwhile, we do a segment here every week on the show that sometimes has to do with video games, sometimes not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because we can.
[SPEAKER_10]: F-U's of the week!
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to everybody who's eating at Wendy's today, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Haters gonna hate.
[SPEAKER_07]: For not bringing me a Frosty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I wanted a Frosty all day.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't get a Frosty, but the berry tea was very good, I'm not gonna lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I even told my husband to go get me a Frosty, and you know what he did?
[SPEAKER_07]: He went across the street and got a hamburger.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then he brought me one, and I just had a hot dog.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, from your neighbors that are cooking?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're doing our barbecue tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: You did tell the neighbors it's July 3rd, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: No one curve.
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to Wendy's for sucking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they have terrible food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody send me a coupon for free Frosty since you gave Rob a Civ Beta thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of them is game related, the other is not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't care, I want a Frosty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frosty's the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know what Miklatov tried to convince me was a good idea once?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dipping your french fries into your Frosty?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, dipping chicken McNuggets into Frosty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, the Wendy's don't have McNuggets?
[SPEAKER_10]: There's people that love that.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like chocolate shakes.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: It actually is good.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's gross.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say, Miklatov, hey, I don't know if he's still working.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, he doesn't still work at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, he definitely does not work at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need the DLC for Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to pick up that pre-order shit somewhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: ask the listeners someone send me the DLC for Earth Defense Force and you will give them nothing a high five a handshake can't even do that alright my FU of the week goes to this is a work related FU because I don't want people thinking it has to do with other things it's work related FU to surprises work related surprises
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, that's really it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Otherwise, things are actually pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, unexpected, I guess, because life goes on, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Tokyo Game Show is going to have a pretty good showing this year.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're up to 146 exhibitors over the 138 in 2010.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, people are like, earthquake and all the developers, they suffered from it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, it's going to be a while, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Life does go on.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's going to be up.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're expecting to see, I guess, or they're going to try to reduce the power usage during the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to drop it down 25% versus 2010 as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: But overall, it's going to have a really good showing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's great that it seems like it's going to be such a big, big show.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's great that they're kind of bouncing with all that recovery stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm very happy to hear it, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on to one last story here about music, music-related stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, if you didn't already know about this, I imagine most of you listeners already have downloaded this and put them on their iPods.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if you are the one that has not...
[SPEAKER_10]: More Portal 2 free music is now available.
[SPEAKER_10]: Volume 2 of the Songs to Test By.
[SPEAKER_10]: 18 new tracks, 14 ringtones for your iPhone and Android devices.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had no idea there were ringtones in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to look more carefully at this stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can check that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: New songs include Bring Your Daughter to Work Day, I Am Not a Moron, and Potatoes Lament.
[SPEAKER_10]: which is actually really cool you can also have the orange or blue portal sound as your messaging ringtone unless you have an iPhone because you can't change your iPhone sounds that's why I didn't notice it yes you can only for the ones that they put on your phone oh yeah that's true volume 3 is coming soon how soon?
[SPEAKER_10]: I said soon
[SPEAKER_10]: also in music related news another Rockman Arrange album of course you know that, here's Mega Man Rockman Unity announced a new Rockman Arrange soundtrack We Are Rockman is the podcast it includes Mashihiro Aoki on guitar Yasumasa Kitagawa on bass he did work on Tatsunoko vs. Capcom All Stars
[SPEAKER_10]: Mitsuhiko, bleep bleep bloop maestro Takano on drums and there will be some guest musicians as well otherwise we don't have a lot of details about the album but some of basically Capcom's greats are getting together to do some rock band arranged music that'll be cool that kind of sounds like what the Black Mages did for Final Fantasy that's kind of what that sounds like to me so there you go
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, that does it for Gaming News tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_10]: But not until we open up the Skype line and take some calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give us a call and you can talk with us.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can talk about any of the stories we've talked about tonight or maybe we missed something that you wanted to talk about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you want to talk about Nintendo and the localization or maybe you want to talk more about, I don't know, Minecraft or Gears of War 3 leaking.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever it is you want to talk about, give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: In the meantime, you know I'm going to ask Loki if there's any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_11]: So apparently, because to celebrate Independence Day, you can now dress up your avatar on Xbox 360 as a Confederate soldier.
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go south.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, that's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not at all a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you mean that they... Oh, but okay, it's just like you do the right combination of hats and gear.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they have Civil War uniform, 160 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you could do also the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have also some funny hats.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because everyone loves funny hats.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love funny hats.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'd just be weird though, like, since a lot of that DLC doesn't translate over though into games, it would still be funny like playing, you know, seeing it or something like that with a civil, you know, a confederate soldier or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else in last minute news tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: Earth Defense Force is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually watched you playing that a little bit over there.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, and I'm only playing it easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, if you play the harder difficulties, you can turn your AI bots off.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even want to know.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then once you beat the game, they also have a campaign remix where you can play with different enemies spawning.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's got a lot of gameplay built in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry if I'm just ranting about this game, but it's worth picking up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You are a little bit, but it's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: We all knew this would happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've been talking about this game for like a year.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just you wait until Saints Row 3 comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: You think this is bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually kind of want to be there when you're playing Saints Row 3 for the first time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know how I can do that, but we need to have a Saints Row 3 party.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be fucking nuts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so here's something we can talk about.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can stream it on the internet, except, oh shit, we would be breaking the law.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR His name on Skype is Orange Launch Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bunchy Aerospace was finally announced.
[SPEAKER_11]: What that is, it's a partnership program with social and mobile devs where they're basically going to help either publish, promote, or draw interest for different games that are coming out on these platforms where they may not get as much interest.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Unfortunately, they will not be building spaceships as not part of the aerospace program.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR after this is done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pleasure.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just trying to recover before tomorrow and everything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, tomorrow's when the real parties are supposed to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tomorrow is when the real parties are supposed to happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, just like a barbecue at my place at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: That and trying to go out with this girl tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I hope he gets some.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much, just like trying to lament over the fallout of what transpired last week with the whole Supreme Court decision, which I know you probably covered in great detail before this call.
[SPEAKER_10]: We did, but what are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, on one hand, it's like they're grasping at straws and trying to legislate something that's already been declared protected speech for all intents and purposes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's like the people who were the ones who pushed the particular person that pushed the law and actually introduced the law and got it passed,
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, but what about how there were a couple justices that basically said, you can regulate games just not like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's leaving the door wide open for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some have said it's a 5-4 split in reality because two of them concurred with the... Yeah, two of the other justices concurred with Scalia.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so it's basically... It's like they weren't for it, but at the same time, they were in between.
[SPEAKER_01]: So...
[SPEAKER_01]: It wasn't like a, you know, if you really get, if you really go deep into that decision, there's not that much, there's only like a, you know, a thin, you know, thin margin of just prevailing opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you think about this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Something that's just like, that it barely got through.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me quickly ask you, what do you think about this other bill we spent some time talking about tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: The whole, you know, no more streaming of movies and games and so forth.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that one is...
[SPEAKER_01]: That one right there, that's a landmine.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pretty sure if it ever comes to court, one way or another we'll know what impact it has.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right now it's very murky.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you're just waiting, and they're just waiting, you know, the feds are just waiting to at least use it on something.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't wait for the 12-year-old.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some guy just, like, leaking a trailer on YouTube or just posting up a gameplay footage.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for some reason, you know, some video game company, which doesn't, you know, which took offense to that whole act, will sick the feds on them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't wait for the
[SPEAKER_01]: I understand, but guess who owns and still has control of the music?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I get it, but I mean, if I... The label, remember, Lady Gaga's only one person that, until she's met the, until she's already honored the contract with her label, she doesn't own her music.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's a slave, just like Prince was.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unless you own your master tracks and you can take them anywhere else, then you have control of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise, you've already sold your soul to the label, and they'll be the ones taking the feds on that 10-year-old kid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, any other quick thoughts before we let you go and get another call?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, take advantage of these sales right now on these sites, Amazon, Steam in particular.
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of really good stuff to be had right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Great FYI in chat from William Murderface.
[SPEAKER_10]: Always love that name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, if anyone's looking for a Diablo 2 fix and does not have Torchlight, it's on sale for $2.99 on Steam today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's a $3 game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm thinking about it right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_10]: If you even remotely like Diablo or Diablo 2, you will get $3 worth out of Torchlight.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I've played that game, you know, years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: All I remember is just, like, mashing my mouse.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just click mashing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very much a dungeon... Well, here's the great thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have a 360?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, but I... Go download the demo.
[SPEAKER_01]: I want to just do it for my... I want to keep it old school.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can at least download the demo to see what the game's like.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, I gotta let you go to get more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Torchlight's a great deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, it's a dungeon crawler.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't know, if you aren't into the dungeon crawlers, you may not like it, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up, everyone?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, just hanging.
[SPEAKER_12]: Chillin'.
[SPEAKER_12]: Smoking a little, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Smoking a J. I'm allergic.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, pass it over this way, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the fourth.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I can think of no better way on Spending Independence Day than burning various things, including fireworks, our money, and a J.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not going to complain, so it works for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Only in America will we celebrate fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: I have just one question.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've been meaning to ask you guys this for as long as I keep forgetting.
[SPEAKER_10]: The answer is no.
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the question?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: turn their back on the fans.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're just looking for a quick pop.
[SPEAKER_12]: The other half are saying Konami is doing this to garner interest into the series to see if it's worth another game.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a little bit of both, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's, you know, why not make a little more cash on games that were previously out, although they are having to redo them and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, they're having to change it up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if the game sold phenomenally.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the games will sell alright and as far as Konami's motivation I mean, it's hard to say because the whole repackaging thing you can't say that Konami's the first to do it so I think they're just jumping on a bandwagon that people have shown they want to be on God of War has already done it the Ico games Shadow of the Colossus all that stuff's being redone so the gaming populace has already shown they'll buy it so you can't really blame Konami for putting it out there
[SPEAKER_11]: and even stuff that's come out recently like the Prince of Persia trilogy, the Splinter Cell trilogy is coming out a little bit later and Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_11]: They already did all those as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, do you think maybe time could be also a factor in this compared to like if the games came out within a certain range and maybe a couple years later they put out the collection compared to maybe waiting like five, six years later for a complete collection?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sure I follow you.
[SPEAKER_10]: These collections are coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd say they put out Zone of the Enders 1, 2, and 3, let's say in 2000, 2001, 2002.
[SPEAKER_12]: And in 2005, they put out the collectors of all three together.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now let's say instead of 2005, they wait until about now to put them all out.
[SPEAKER_12]: They wait almost 10 years.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but they're going to up-res them and make them more current.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're redoing them in HD, so I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's also be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is this any different from the movie industry?
[SPEAKER_10]: The movie industry does this shit all the time, and we eat it up.
[SPEAKER_10]: How many times have the Star Wars movies come out?
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're coming out again on Blu-ray, and I know tons of people that'll be there right when they come out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't mean to interrupt, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's because George Lucas turned his back on the fans, and he's a money-grubbing whore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know that, but the new Star Tours is really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But what about Harry Potter?
[SPEAKER_10]: When those movies come out, they come out on Blu-ray and then you can get a box set with 1 through 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then when 6 came out, you could buy 6.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and then now it's a box set with 1 through 6 and maybe some other bonus features.
[SPEAKER_10]: A preview of 7.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, now 7's out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now there's a box set of 1 through 7 and there'll be a preview for 8.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there'll be another box set when 8 comes out and it'll have the special features online, Uber, God, Poopy Pop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Book 7 was the last one.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there was 8 movies.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm talking about the movies.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, book seven was two movies, but I see your point.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was just trying to be an ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're trying to be an ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, wait, wait, now hold on a second.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is not, is not this new movie the eighth movie coming out?
[SPEAKER_11]: I understand it's two parts, but it is, in the line of movies, the eighth movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, yes, it is the eighth movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Watch Warner Brothers release both movies together as movie seven.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just to fuck with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like Twilight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Aren't they splitting the last one into two so there's five movies?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, as if it hasn't drug out long enough already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's put the last one in the two.
Ugh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Morpheus in our chatroom says, actually, Lord of the Rings is the biggest DVD whore.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now Blu-ray whore because the super extended editions, yes, as if that movie wasn't long enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: And theatrical re-release bullshit, which I don't give a shit about and I won't go see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wouldn't mind going to see it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if I should admit this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never saw the third movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw the first two opening day, nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_10]: I never saw the third movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, for me, and people are going to go, oh, you're a hater.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the whole point is that I read the books.
[SPEAKER_07]: The movies were good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm more interested in The Hobbit coming out because I like The Hobbit better than I liked the other books.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't believe you read those books.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've tried to read those books.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, speak a language I can read.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tolkien was so fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a good story, but my god, we don't need that much description of the grass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma, I gotta let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Rob, before I go, I just want to say, in response to Twilight, I love that picture you posted on your Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: The one of the stakes on the fence that says, in case of sparkly vampires, or break off in case of sparkly vampires, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think I posted it and I put, how about screaming fangirls, too?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, and before I go, I'm going to say I dedicate this picture to you that I put on my blog post.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just posted it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry for the awkward silence there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was typing an important message because there's a YouTube I want to find real quick there, so I'm trying to find it there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me look at what Ranma posted to his Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on one sec.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'm following the link and let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's haters gonna hate but it's Frank and Furter from the Rocky Horror Picture Show.
[SPEAKER_10]: You see this, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you need to put that on Tumblr so I can reblog it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on Ranma's Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, then I'll reblog it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you follow him.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's up with... Now it's Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was LiveJournal, which I'm a permanent member of, so I always have to love LiveJournal forever and ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's MySpace back in the day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Friendster, shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now there's fucking Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never used Friendster.
[SPEAKER_07]: I never used it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: How did you avoid that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was... I love my LiveJournal so much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's Blender.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I kind of wanted to go back to this whole class action lawsuit that you guys were talking about with these online games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think eventually somebody's going to find a loophole and actually get in on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a couple of you guys are into Disney and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you remember the Virtual Magic Kingdom game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you ever heard of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember the NES game Adventures in the Magic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wait, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, it was the online MMO.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I ever played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That Disney put out for the 50-year anniversary.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I'm familiar with some of the Disney MMOs.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Club Penguin, and I know that they're infamous for not letting you type.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can only select from select phrases.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what they did is for the 50-year anniversary, they created an MMO, which was a free walk through Disneyland Park, and you can create friends and meet people.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it really messed up some people when they closed that site down.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I got a link.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if it's going to post, but... Rob, Peter was telling us about that when we were at the park.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't... I just... Because I have a pin from it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: That I do remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I tried it with a cast member.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I have one of the links that I just picked.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was from Joystick.com is when they closed the actual site.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it was really devastating because I was actually on it for like two years.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: It killed a lot of kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was like 10, 11-year-old kids, or even younger, that couldn't play this game anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I really think that if somebody's going to find a loophole with closing down these large MMOs, that they're going to...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: Here, open up your own damn servers, and if you want to copy your characters over, here's how you do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, isn't that right?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, you followed this better than I did, but Blue Burst, when they went under, Sega was very much like... Sega was like, here's your character data, and you can transfer it to the server of your choice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you're in an interesting position with Star Wars Galaxies, because they probably just don't... They want those people playing the Bioware Star Wars game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: the closest thing you get are these expansions such as Cataclysm that changed Warcraft so drastically it's almost like a sequel so that's what you're the way you're talking about it is breaking it up instead of like for example Virtual Magic Kingdom where they closed it down totally they should have gone open source so somebody who loved it could have kept it going but how can you force a company to do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and it's so funny because I had a bunch of friends on there, and we were on there for, oh, we'd go on there every day, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the thing was, the kids that were on this actual site weren't allowed to actually give out emails and communicate with each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were only allowed to talk on this virtual Magic Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, you weren't allowed to give any personal information away.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, right, because you were very restrictive of what you could say.
[SPEAKER_06]: All of a sudden they said in a month from now we're closing the site and it's done.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people don't...
[SPEAKER_06]: God, it just kills a bunch of these little kids, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's sad, but at the same time, how can you force a company to keep something going that's not making them any money?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, if the miniature golf place closes down, what can you do about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone's actually made a, quote, replacement called Virtual Family Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, no, yeah, I've seen that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, everybody jumped over to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was sponsored by the Smithsonian Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_06]: or Smithsonian Institute.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was just horrible when they went over to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't know if you guys saw the post that I put.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should see some of the stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were actually people protesting in front of Disneyland the day that it closed down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, maybe they'll be protesting on Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm going to be able to get some money out of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still think the terms of service are going to ultimately let the companies come out ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got to let you go, buddy, before we wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for your call.
[SPEAKER_10]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a good topic.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blender, live on OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know you guys, I got sent this YouTube and this is a YouTube of DJ Ranma S actually watching the Breaking Dawn trailer and let's see how Ranma actually reacted to seeing this trailer the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking massive boobs.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, Ranma, you're getting really upset over this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get naked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't get naked, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_10]: You were the one talking about vagina in the chat room earlier.
No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Breaking Dawn Trailer Badly Written
[SPEAKER_07]: I tried to read a page of that and I was like, who let this woman write?
[SPEAKER_10]: There should be a class action lawsuit against Bic for selling that woman a pen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I blame her for being Mormon.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love DJ Morpheus in chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just cold, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's coming from Travis, of all people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, that's just cold.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, that's going to do it for another week of Orange on Trail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do we have any other last minute news?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just real quick stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm alive.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's supposed to be coming out still.
[SPEAKER_11]: Classifications are found on the Australian website and Crisis is supposed to be coming to PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: because this is on the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Before we get the final thoughts, I want to thank you once again for listening to Orange Launch Radio and supporting us over these nine years of our program.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, we're here to do it every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you've never come out for a live show, it's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight would have been a great night because many folks out there don't work on Monday.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, you know, if you have the time in the future, please do consider joining us for a live show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We do tape live at All Games Radio, allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sunday nights at 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern, right after the Bobby Buffett Show.
[SPEAKER_07]: You always say specific.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Choo is the sound that What's-Her-Name makes in Space Channel 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: La la.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's Choo!
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh la la.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh la la.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, Space Channel 5 Part 2 is on Steam for six bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I already have like two copies of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lots of good stuff to buy on Steam.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm telling you, BitTrip Runner, if it's still $2.50, is a great buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_10]: OrangeLodgeRadio.com, join our website, check the forums, all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: We really need to get the activity on the forums again.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got to really think about how we can get those going.
[SPEAKER_10]: But meanwhile, let's go around and get everybody's final thought for tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Loki, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to work in some more Earth Defense Force this weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: I had to play it for a few hours last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really need to play more of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought of the night is, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Vanille and Hope, they aren't that bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like 30 hours later, they aren't that bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_10]: Lesbians.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just looked at Alan's Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, what's Alan tweeting about lesbians for?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is his picture.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and don't buy, my other final thought, don't buy your games from eBay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unless they're, well, I guess the used market's okay, but just be careful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Buy or beware on eBay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just look at the feedback before you buy.
[SPEAKER_10]: that's it guys have a wonderful night thank you so much for downloading tuning in live however you listen to Orange Lounge Radio we really appreciate it thanks for joining us and inviting us into your lives for the past three hours we hope you consider doing it again next week have a great night
[SPEAKER_09]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_09]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!