[SPEAKER_05]: Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight, July 31st, 2011, Nintendo slashes the price of the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: The average price of an Xbox Live Arcade title is going up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And could the PlayStation 3 soon feature a doll?
[SPEAKER_06]: PinkBerry
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it's been about a week and a half.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why you feel disconnected.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then maybe we should end the show early and go get Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm down with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last week's show was a marathon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blah, blah, blah, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blah, blah, blah, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, say hello as well to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you feeling connected?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you on the grid this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm on the grid.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you've never joined us for a live show, it's a totally different experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really encourage you to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sunday nights, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, here at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we do have some folks in our chat room already starting there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see where we got here.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt says, this episode of OLR is brought to you by a higher debt ceiling.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope they got all that crap fixed but I hear it's still stalemate but I don't want to get too political because I'll just get angry because that stuff kind of has a direct impact on my life if that starts affecting the unemployment and all that like they're saying is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's try to move on to happier topics like games that keep us entertained when these things go wrong in our country.
[SPEAKER_06]: So DarkSakura, why don't you start us off with how is your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played WoW all up until the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was trying to get that achievement, the classic dungeon master, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, achievements weren't around when you first started playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think achievements have kind of, clearly they were just ripped right off Xbox Live, but do you think they've really added something to the WoW experience?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I mean, it's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I'll get like a wild hair and say, okay, I'm going to finish this.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then it'll give me an excuse.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because honestly, my favorite character to play is my 85 mage.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love my mage.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so it just gives me an excuse to keep playing her.
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead of, oh, I can't really do anything right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'll just, I guess, work on this other one instead of making another mage and leveling another mage.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know somebody, though, who has eight level 85 druids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, anything in the non-MMO universe that you've been up to?
[SPEAKER_06]: Groove Coaster.
[SPEAKER_10]: That game is fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I blame Shane.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's his fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Groove Coaster, of course, on the iOS, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's iPad and iPhone, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, 3GS and Apple.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming it'll work on the iPod, unlike Google+, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does not work on anything with the iPhone, which is a little silly, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: and the app really is not that great it's more stable than Facebook's app at this point you know I haven't updated Facebook app since they changed the photos oh really so I didn't update to that one because someone warned me so I haven't updated my Facebook app in like months nice
[SPEAKER_10]: and I'm not going to
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe tomorrow, on a Monday, maybe it got pushed back, who knows It's going to be very interesting when the games roll out Because it's going to make the two go head-to-head even more But right now, I think it's still too early to tell But I think a little valid competition And yeah, clearly everybody wants a piece of the social networking space But, you know, Facebook, or I should say Google Plus Has really succeeded at biting at Facebook's kneecaps In places where MySpace...
[SPEAKER_06]: Orkut, Buzz, even, you know, and other social networks have failed to do so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wait until Myspace rolls out their even better game service.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're coming back, baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, as things change ownership and things change hands and so forth, you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't ever count out somebody who's been gone for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, look at Origin, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Origin was an EA brand that kind of disappeared, unfortunately, because they used to make a lot of great games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the brand faded.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's back as a store.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could MySpace come back as a store?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, I just want to say the competition, I think, is a little bit healthy for Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know, they do say that festering piles of crap work as fertilizer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oendan, Elite Beat Agents
[SPEAKER_10]: but the lines keep moving and they'll sneak up on you and like the track will curve and that has a very vib ribbon type of vibe to it it really just made me think of playing vib ribbon except you know you're just pushing little you know you're tapping along and sometimes it's easy to figure out what the rhythm is but sometimes it's really freaking difficult I'm still kind of getting used to it but it's got the first Arkanoid song which was boop boop you know that was pretty fun and I actually got a little motion sick off of it
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know that I'd be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it is very light, seizure-y, you know, fast motions.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on the parts where it starts spiraling downwards.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then that's where I get a little motion sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing a lot of Groove Coaster this week, too, because obviously, you know, I love music games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a dollar.
[SPEAKER_06]: No secret.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still a buck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, definitely, if you're a music game fan at all, you definitely want to check out Space Invaders.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you can check out Space Invaders, too, but a groove coaster is only a buck.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what I love so much about this game, it's the perfect phone game, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's everything you want out of a phone game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except, you cannot sneak into the bathroom at work and play it unless you have your headphones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yes, there is that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I suppose there's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the thing about Groove Coaster is that you can play it in short little minute and a half, three minute boosts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's very pretty to watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's that kind of like audio stimulation, visual stimulation, little diversion for just a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you could sit there and play every song and be diverted for an hour.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no trans vibrator mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no trans vibrator mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think in some ways it's like just, it was designed very well with the phone audience in mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that's what's great about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because half of playing it is kind of just those visuals of going around the spirals and ooh, ah, I'm in a trance for three minutes and wasting my time.
[SPEAKER_10]: But coaster is a very good word because it really is like this massive galactic roller coaster.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it even shows you the track when you're done.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: See the path you've been on
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really had a good time with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I said, I've gotten up to the first Arkanoid song, which is like, what, the second stage?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or second set of stages or something?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's different, you know, I guess musicians that have worked on the tracks for the game, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then...
[SPEAKER_10]: Workin' it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, yeah, I'm doing cross-training now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, at some point, I'm going to have to loan you one of my Kinect games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys have Kinect?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I have a Kinect I haven't opened because I haven't had anything I want to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you'll have to try one of these fitness games that I was trying out.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might be into it if you're all about fitness and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really want to try the UFC game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: UFC trainer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard interesting things about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I want to train to be an ultimate fighter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just train to be it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes in these arguments, I've got to take Jamie out.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we had our company game summit thing So some of the publishers brought out things for me to try Oh yeah, you got a little slice of E3 at your door this week, didn't ya?
[SPEAKER_08]: Very small slice of E3 Alright, well what'd you check out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so I played the newest build of K'nex Star Wars
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's a couple things about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: One, they said that apparently they took development staff off of Dance Central 2 to finish polishing up Connect Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Harmonix makes Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but it's still Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Microsoft doesn't own Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they still have staff working on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a little... That seems a little... Well, it's just... Or is it one of those disingenuous things where we move some of the marketing staff?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has nothing to do with the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's development staff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same thing as... It's LucasArts making the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I understand that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that's what the rep told me.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just repeating what I heard.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little strange, but all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially... Different coasts, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: LucasArts is over in the Bay Area, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: And then...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know where their video game development house is I'm assuming it's North Bay like the rest of LucasArts but then of course Harmonix is out in Boston
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm saying I don't know, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd assume it's more than just maybe one development house working on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so, played a bit of Kinect Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had, of course, at Comic-Con, the new build had pod racing in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also they had the regular little demo thing that you go through.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, yeah, you know, it's alright, I guess, but once again, it's just kind of, you can tell how well it's gonna be just by looking at it in the videos and stuff, and it, right, for me, it plays okay, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You can knock it off either side, but they wanted you to knock it off the left side because it's a lot easier to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I ended up not knowing that, obviously, so I moved it to the right, trying to get it to fall off the edge of the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I got it to the point where it's literally sitting on the edge, teetering, not quite moving off the edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm at the point where I'm, why do I have to knock it off the edge?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's clearly like 20 feet of space next to it that I could run by.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since I'm a Jedi, I think I can be able to manage to fit my ego through that 20-foot patch of space there to get where I need to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or, I don't know, maybe because since my character can force jump anyways, I could have just hopped over the goddamn thing instead of knocking off the edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, the game wants you to knock it over the edge before you can move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm sitting there, like, pushing at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, tap, tap, tap, come on, get off the damn edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finally got the tip over, and then I moved on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: POD Racing POD Racing
[SPEAKER_06]: Parties and drunken nights
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not like... I mean, it's kind of on rails, sort of.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you can dash towards things and you can dodge stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, all the gestures are very basic.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, it's still very early.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the game right now, it's probably not even in beta.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's, you know, July and the game's coming out in November.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there's still plenty of time, you know, to polish it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's playable.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not something I would buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just something that if someone likes The Force Unleashed or something like that, they're not probably going to get a lot out of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's say Josh was 11.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you want to buy it then?
[SPEAKER_06]: He'd probably dig it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where I'm thinking this is going to.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is very much for the same audience that kind of supported The Connect to begin with.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't really the hardcore.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was more of the...
[SPEAKER_06]: LightSaber on!
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe you still could say lightsaber on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, that would be terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pod racing, though, I was slamming the walls.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I blame that probably a little bit on myself because I didn't know how to control a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, I went through the tutorial for the single-player regular game portion, but the rep just put me straight into the game for the pod racing, and so...
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess there's dual throttles on that thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was just like, full speed all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe that's not the greatest thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the game itself, the pod racing, it's very much like the movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if they get the controls correct, it might not be that bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do they have Greg Proops doing the announcing during the Star Wars sequence?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'll tell you, a shout out to one of my other favorite podcasts, Smartest Man in the World with Greg Proops.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was in Star Wars Episode I narrating the pod races.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was one of the two heads on the dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is he really?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same voices.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, that'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the other game I saw was Skylanders, which is the new Spyro game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, I was just sitting there with the two Activision reps and one of them I mentioned, I'm like, you know, it's like $70.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, really, you think people are going to buy this, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they think that it's going to sell well I mean it's kind of neat I guess for kids because you can just pop this little toy on there and you know away you go and you can play as that character and they're going to have I guess 30 characters that you can play in the game but the thing is that kind of sucks you need certain characters to go access certain parts of the game like you know if you want to go underwater you can't use a fire monster you have to use something else so they kind of want you to buy the toys which are fucking expensive they're like 8 bucks each
[SPEAKER_08]: and you know eight bucks for an action figure that's not so bad you know G.I.
[SPEAKER_08]: Joe's I used to buy those and that makes sense but these are like they're figurines they don't move they don't articulate at all they're just on you know not it's just mainly for the game it's like physical download content is basically what this is um
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's an experiment.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess you'll be right.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you're a fan of Spyro and you really want to play a Spyro game, I would check this out as a demo or something first.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, I will admit, I kind of got sick of Spyro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spyro just kind of got oversaturated.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I haven't played a Spyro game in so long that I think back to the original one on PlayStation 1 very fondly.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is not like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's like that in the world sense, but it's not... Spyro looks fucking angry in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spyro got more hardcore.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's like, what the fuck did you do to my games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so fucking pissed!
[SPEAKER_08]: He just has this angry look on his face.
[SPEAKER_08]: They made him emo-ragey.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're targeting a new audience.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're targeting angry people with money.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't get to play Just Dance 3 because...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I bet you're just torn up about that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Just Dance 2 was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is Just Dance 3 on all the consoles now, or is that just Wii?
[SPEAKER_08]: She was going to bring it on the Wii, bring a Wii dev kit because she had that, but unfortunately they had issues with syncing controllers or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ninja Gaiden 3 Ninja Gaiden 3
[SPEAKER_08]: Really violent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because every time you slash through somebody and you cut people in half and stuff, it goes in really close.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, they were saying that the theme this year was that they wanted to...
[SPEAKER_06]: I just convey the feeling of slicing somebody in half is what they're trying to go for alright I'm bringing up a YouTube here so I can try and see some of this here I'm just randomly finding a YouTube channel hoping there's no narration in the background here I don't want to hear this dude narrating let's see if we can find something else a little more
[SPEAKER_08]: I really don't want to hear Adam Sessler narrating over this stuff
[SPEAKER_08]: and of course theirs is timing out well this segment's going nowhere live radio boys and girls I'll just have to take Loki's word for it it's a pretty awesome game granted though that the difficulty was ramped way down because it is a demo and they don't want everybody to fail on it but there is going to be like I guess some sort of casual gaming mode or like an easy mode or something you can play so but you know just really over the top fun game though alright was that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: yeah oh did Ninja Gaiden 3 make you want to go back and play the other ones?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Ninja Gaiden's not really a game I would think that I need to play the other ones, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, if you were to play Ninja Gaiden 3... Yeah, but if you like 3, you might as well go back and see what you missed in 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, 1's, well...
[SPEAKER_06]: obviously there's obviously there's the old old old what there's the Atari arcade game and then there were the Nintendo NES games by Tecmo and now you know you had this new trilogy that started I believe on Xbox was because Ninja Gaiden was a huge exclusive for the original Xbox you know then what Ninja Gaiden 2 was on I think 360 in that yeah well and they also have the PS3 once the Sigma series right right so you can always check that out
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean... It's not really something I necessarily need to do, but... Going to our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com Doing Laundryman in our chatroom says, Chopping people in half?
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki finally gets to live one of his dreams.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, speaking... Not really the chopping people in half thing, but I did remember there was a few other things that I didn't get to play, but stuff I learned, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a little peek at, because, you know, I fucking love Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, you're just eating that stuff up with a spoon.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are so excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to be there at midnight.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, a couple things about Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_08]: One, I was looking at their, they had their kind of lineup of their advertising campaign.
[SPEAKER_08]: So everything they're doing up from now to launch.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of the things that's later on, not announced yet, is a new mode that they're going to have.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, all the other games have their kind of horde mode and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they're going to have horde mode, as in whores.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically when you turn on horde mode, random prostitutes will attack you on the streets.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just like, yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: This game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What game do I want to play today?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I want to get attacked by prostitutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just armies of prostitutes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they yelling things at you?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, but it's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's something they're going to be talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to have some sort of invite-only demo thing that my THQ rep says that they're going to try because I'm such a huge fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to try to get me into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh God, if that would happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what I would do.
[SPEAKER_06]: It almost sounds like you took that rep in the back alley and did what you had to do to get a sneak peek.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm probably the biggest Spyro fan here and I'm glad the game is like the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought the Legend series brought it down.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's see, Spazinator in our chatroom says, Agreed, I was just playing Ninja Gaiden 2 the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: The camera needs improvement, to put it mildly.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Actdeft is hearing you talking about Saints Row the 3rd saying, Best game ever, period.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hold on guys, the game's not out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: What you don't want to do, do not hype the game beyond your expectations because you'll only set yourself up for disappointment.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I'm just going to tell you guys now, Saints Row sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: It fucking blows.
[SPEAKER_06]: That way, if it's good, you'll be...
[SPEAKER_08]: Sonic Generations sounds like it's going to have a lot of fan service in it including I guess there's different things that you unlock by beating certain challenges in each level including some of the original games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can unlock Sonic 1 in there and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's see, Sonic 1.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many times has that game been whored out in the past few years?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see, we had the Sonic Mega Genesis collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could pay 400 Microsoft points and get it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now it's going to be an unlockable in another game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's not counting when we saw it probably back on the GameCube and every other collection known to man.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, how many times are you going to pimp out Sonic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Dead Rising 2, The Way We Meant To Do It
[SPEAKER_06]: I love some of the random comments our chatters make sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt in our chatroom says, I think in the Bizarro world, Bizarro Loki likes playing sports games, MMOs, enjoys eating steamed broccoli, and looking at tasteful porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: I enjoyed MMOs and tasteful porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: But fuck steamed broccoli.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, fuck steamed broccoli.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, moving on, My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a whole lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, I've kind of been focusing on many of the games I already have.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing those, including, of course, WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Been revisiting some old stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was randomly playing some Super Street Fighter IV this week, as well as Wipeout HD, which I finally looked at the Fury expansion, what, like two years later?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, well, since...
[SPEAKER_06]: In my household, there's two of us and we share a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I got two of the games and the Salacious Pop got two other games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he got the Wipeout with Fury in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I played the Bomberman game because it's free on PlayStation Plus right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And since I didn't cash in the PlayStation Plus until right at the end, I'm still on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Bomberman's free right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I played that and it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Bomberman was great in 95, and now it's something that's better left in my memory.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot I signed up for PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's some free games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't miss anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go get some trophies or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free until the 3rd or whenever it wears out, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: you can check that out also as far as other games I've been playing that are a little bit newer I talked about Bastion last week I said I'd only played the demo I did end up upgrading to the full version and I'm glad I did I'm still enjoying Bastion some things that didn't show up in the demo there's another weapon that I really like like a sword weapon that you can throw
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: I also checked out From Dust.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is just a demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: So again, these are impressions based on a demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had heard it was like the old games Populous, which I loved that game back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was all about ready to try this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I checked out the demo and it's very...
[SPEAKER_06]: The way it's presented, the presentation of the game is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, everything is very gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything is well done in the way it's put together.
[SPEAKER_06]: It felt like a disc-based game, honestly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really surprised they packed all this into an arcade release, although I think it was like a gig download.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, and some 360 games are like several hundred megs, so this is almost as big as a disc game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will say where I got frustrated though is that I honestly found the demo, I couldn't really get past one of the stages in the demo and I found it really frustrating because the way I was laying down the sand or something was just not right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean maybe I just need to approach it again with a clear head but it was one of those points of early frustration where I'm like well shit if I can't beat the demo then...
[SPEAKER_06]: I ain't wasting my money on the full game but I liked where it was going so I can't really say it reflects on the game negatively I think it's just one of those try this for yourself because it's something you have to experience but it's not really for everybody so that's the beautiful thing about arcade there's demos of every game so if you like those types of games like Populous I'm trying to think what else maybe Lemmings-esque
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of reminded of that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might enjoy this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really otherwise about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to get my classic game on next weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was talking to SalaciousPop about wanting to hook up the Dreamcast to play the NES emulator to go play some old games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I might do some of that this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot a game I played this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cadillacs and Dinosaurs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Old school.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where the hell did that come from?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wasn't that on Sega CD?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there was a version on Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there was a version on Genesis, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played it on my arcade cabinet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wanted to play a beat-em-up game that wasn't Ninja Turtles or something I'd played before.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Cadillacs and Dinosaurs it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's a character in there that looks just like Blanka, except he has a tail and weird eyes.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't we give you an S?
[SPEAKER_06]: You did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't have a lot of carts.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have some.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can, I was going to say, I'd be more than happy to do some games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that you can have the excitement of blowing into the cartridges.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: And then into the machine and then swapping them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to our chat room at chat.org.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some comments from our chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: BlackWolf, the man before us Sunday nights at all games, is in chat saying, Sky, take out the narrator.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Bastion still worth it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, but keep in mind, you know, every gamer's a little different, and I really like these isometric, platformy type of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, some of my favorite games going back to the NES and Super NES era are Solstice and Equinox and that series, and this game, to me, really kind of harkens back to those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's the sole motivator, but it just makes a good thing better.
[SPEAKER_06]: If that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: If only they had that narrator in Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then he decided to stand there and flip off the prostitute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Derek H in the chat says, From Dust is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll admit, I probably didn't give it a fair chance.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was late last night and I just kind of got fed up and I was like, I'm just going to go back to Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to approach it again a little later on because I refuse to believe that I wouldn't really get more out of this game considering I really used to like the SimCity, the Populous, and those types of games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I keep saying Populous because that's the one I am really reminded of.
[SPEAKER_06]: This really does feel like just an all-new version of that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much it for our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's move on to some housekeeping tonight, of which we don't have a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: We still have every show planned for the month.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think we have any shows planned off.
[SPEAKER_06]: There might be one at the end of August, because I'm going to be gone at the end of August, but that's a ways off.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are not going on any trips after all, so we'll be having shows for the foreseeable future, for at least the next four weeks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will be lonely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, nonsense.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why you have MMOs.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're never lonely.
[SPEAKER_06]: You will not be forever alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're feeling forever alone, DarkSakura, you should just hop into our chat room during the week and say, Iken has hug.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's people in there throughout the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll just say, hugs.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I challenge you to do that twice this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright Otherwise visit our website www.orangeloungeradio.com Of course you can always visit us on Twitter Twitter.com slash OLR If you have comments on the show as it's going tonight And you're not in the chat You can always send us a tweet And we'll get to some of your tweets later on in the program So twitter.com slash OLR for that Of course we are on Facebook as well Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio We're on Tumblr now I don't think we've been posting a lot there But it's there OrangeLoungeRadio.tumblr.com Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah it's there
[SPEAKER_06]: It's new.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know all the stuff now.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did we finally delete the MySpace?
[SPEAKER_06]: We might have.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's gone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe the MySpace is just rotting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It might be just an archive of old, old, old-ass clips from the to-go edition.
[SPEAKER_10]: We may as well just leave it there, like some treasure fossil.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be like something you discover in From Dusk.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like doing archaeology in WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, let's move on to some gaming news and obviously the blogosphere has been blowing up this week with chat on a few topics and I know you're all dying to know what Loki thinks of some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm dying to know what you guys think of some of this stuff in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, will you please do the honors of starting us off with the big news this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so Nintendo hasn't been doing that great with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: They cut their profits forecast by 82%, basically dropping their estimated profit from 20 billion yen, or about $257 million, to 110 billion yen, or about 1.41 billion, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or, I'm sorry...
[SPEAKER_08]: They dropped it down to 20 billion yen from 110 billion yen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is quite a drop.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, basing it on the fact that they're saying that the stronger than expected yen appreciation and sales performance of the 3DS hardware in sales outlook for the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: So they're going to be dropping the price, of course, of the 3DS on August 12th to $170 from its $250 mark right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I guess something similar is going to happen effective August 11th in Japan, dropping the system from 25,000 yen to 15,000 yen.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, there's no price yet in Europe, but I'm sure they're going to get some sort of drop.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, if you're having a little bit of buyer's remorse because you bought a launch system and you're like, what the fuck, you know, $80 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: What am I going to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Nintendo is actually going to give you some free games.
[SPEAKER_08]: They said basically anybody that signs into Nintendo's eShop before August 12th will be signed up automatically to the Nintendo 3DS Ambassador Program.
[SPEAKER_08]: and basically you get 10 free NES Virtual Console games on September 1st and I guess it's before the release of the games for everybody else and also some Game Boy Advance games also that's kind of their way of saying hey we're going to have an NES Virtual Console system on the 3DS and also going to offer Game Boy Advance games since this has never been mentioned prior to this um
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, in some of the games that they're giving away, I mean, they're not half bad, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's, you know, like The Legend of Zelda, Balloon Fight, Ice Climber.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, they're seeing some Game Boy Advance games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yoshi's Island, Super Mario Advance 3, Mario Kart, Metroid Fusion, WarioWare, Mario vs. Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, I guess... Let's stop there before we get to some of the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to dissect this a little bit because I've got to admit, when did this all come down?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was probably Wednesday or so when this was all announced.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've got to admit, I was reading the updates through Twitter and so forth and through my Google Reader and I was like...
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell is going on today?
[SPEAKER_06]: I feel like I've stepped into Bizarro World.
[SPEAKER_06]: What happened at Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, something huge went down there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this is just... Does this even feel like the same Nintendo from just a couple months ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: This screams of desperation.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, and when I told Salacious Pop about it, and I think he put it best, he said, Wow, Nintendo just totally ate shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they really did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like...
[SPEAKER_06]: What... I mean, clearly the 3DS not performing up to expectations, and there's been a lot of flack on that, but I honestly didn't see this coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's so much about this that's just out of character.
[SPEAKER_06]: A, they didn't announce a price drop today.
[SPEAKER_06]: They announced a price drop a few weeks from now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's usually not what you want to do, because that's kind of suicide to your sales right away.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then B, they turn around and announce this program with...
[SPEAKER_06]: 20 free games?
20?
[SPEAKER_06]: That is not... Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_06]: That is not something I would have ever expected out of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it gives people incentive to buy the system at full price to get the freebies.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does, and I see that perspective of it, but I still don't get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still don't get it being Nintendo, because I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have expected Nintendo to be like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, you know, well, we're going to cut the price and, you know, we're going to give you some free Club Nintendo points or we're going to let you have Mario Brothers 2 early or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was not expecting 20 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is a huge, like, in my opinion, is a huge admission of something on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, we didn't just fuck up.
[SPEAKER_06]: We fucked up big.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what's surprising about it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: To be honest, to be fair, I realize that if I buy something early, like a 3DS, it's very likely to get a price cut in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they had announced a price drop and they said, oh, you only get a Mario game, I would have been like, okay, well, you know, that's the price you pay for getting shit early.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki imported a 3DS and paid a premium to have it like a couple weeks early.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just what we do sometimes because we're sick.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to have the newest gadgets early.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have been perfectly fine with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now to hear there's like 20 free games coming out, now I'm not just like, oh, I'm not unhappy about this price drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I'm like, fuck, I'm really glad I bought one early.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, look at the games they're talking about on the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metroid, Yoshi's Island, these are like... Metroid Fusion's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not...
[SPEAKER_06]: There might be like half and half, half crap, half triple A titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do have a point though to make.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're glad that we didn't get one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because first of all, all of those games that are worth having, I already own.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bought them on my old system.
[SPEAKER_10]: Second, we're not going to spend as much money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, but hold that thought because, Loki, you gotta read this next bit then on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you're dying to give your impressions too, Loki, but I'm gonna make the listeners wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Loki, read this next story because here's where things get real fucking interesting real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: 3DS NES games will also include multiplayer following an update.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, you'll be able to play those virtual console games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess with other people now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure if that's over the internet or if that's just locally, but that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And here's the list of NES games that they've announced.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Mario Bros., Donkey Kong Jr., Balloon Fight, Ice Climber, and The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, five other unknown games right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, they added multiplayer into Virtual Console, and we don't know yet, but this possibly could be over the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're doing what they should have done with the Wii five years ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: Finally?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that makes these games a lot more... I mean, because let's face it, Nintendo is kind of sucker-punching us a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you didn't early adopt the 3DS and you do want to get these games, and let's say they do end up being multiplayer over the internet, you're going to have to buy them again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if you bought them for five bucks the first time on the Wii, you're going to have to buy them again.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for the early adopters, now you're kind of in this, well, I can't really get mad because I'm still going to get it for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: But DarkSakura, let's say the multiplayer thing pans out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's say it ends up that you can play it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now does that change your opinion?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or are you still like, no, at the end of the day, I'm saving 80 bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care about multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's just okay good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm glad for other people.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind how few times I've done any multiplayer game on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or I think the last multiplayer game I've played that involved a Nintendo system was playing Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then that I didn't really like it with the multiplayer aspect so because I was just like stop being stupid just let me play by myself you know I was just getting annoyed so I do not play well with others
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I want to emphasize, we don't know for sure yet if multiplayer means multiplayer on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're all forming a prayer circle right now that, for those of us that are into multiplayer, we're all forming a prayer circle that Nintendo's going to do the right thing, and they are going to open up the internet, because if the emulation scene's been able to do it for years, there's no reason Nintendo cannot open these games to play on the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, we should only expect that multiplayer means within the same room, which is still interesting...
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I would repay $5 for these games for that alone, but if Nintendo's going to hand them to me for free, I'm not exactly going to bash them.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: And then here's another interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently Satori Iwata, he's gone ahead and taken a 50% reduction in pay as a result of the 3DS's slow sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?!
[SPEAKER_06]: Who are you people?!
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo, I don't even know you anymore!
[SPEAKER_06]: You're taking pay cuts now?!
[SPEAKER_08]: Other representative directors, including senior managing directors Miyamoto and Shinji Hatano are taking a 30% pay cut and other executives will lose 20% off their salaries.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bet you anything that will not happen to Nintendo U.S.,
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they said Reggie's one of the affected people, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't pick up on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Doing something like that is honestly... It is the corporate equivalent of falling on your sword.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very much a Japanese thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: To take responsibility for the sake of the whole company.
[SPEAKER_06]: If only Congress would do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: In the scope of a week, we've gone from kicking Nintendo, fuck you Nintendo, Operation Rainfall for life, fuck you, I hate you too, oh my god, Congress needs to look at what Nintendo's doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: This all happened in a week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, every politician needs to take a look at what Nintendo's doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before we start talking about what Congress needs to start emulating from Nintendo, we're still not over the fact that they botched all this stuff up with the Wii and all the online and not bringing games over and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is a very effective diversion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony, they made a multi-million dollar...
[SPEAKER_08]: Error, if you will, in their online security, and I got two games for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo, to make up for dropping... You got four games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know you work the system, just like the rest of us did with the multi-accounts.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be fair, you got two PS3 games, two PSP games... I did not actually do it on my other... Alright, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, you know, we get... Okay, four games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: or our 20 free games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now here's the best part.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you really want to game the system, here's what you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: You go to a Best Buy or a Walmart or something like that just before August 12th.
[SPEAKER_08]: You buy a system for the full price.
[SPEAKER_08]: You log it onto Nintendo's network and then when it drops the price two days later, you come in and go, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why this drop in price?
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a refund.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they will refund you the difference in price.
[SPEAKER_06]: If these companies are smart, which I'm not saying they are, but if they're smart, they're going to put an exemption to their policy like just a couple weeks before.
[SPEAKER_06]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least one of these stores is going to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to say 3DS accepted from the policy from X to Y day.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to wait until right that first day that the refund... If it's like a 21-day window, they'll wait until... Well, I guess we would be in that window, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what the windows are depending on what store you shop at, but I bet some of them are going to throw up an exception.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe not something as huge as Walmart, but I bet you some of these other stores will.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the very least, if those games are interesting to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: So Loki, sometimes your thoughts on Nintendo really confuse the hell out of me because you imported a 3DS from Japan just so you could have it before anybody else and you were an early adopter of Nintendo and I know you were an early adopter of Wii as well but then Nintendo does things that really piss you off and you've screamed and you've yelled at them here on the show so surely you must have seen the news this week and gone, what is this?
[SPEAKER_06]: What is going on?
[SPEAKER_06]: What was your reaction to all the news this week and where are you at now?
[SPEAKER_08]: My reaction was like, wow, I'm surprised they're dropping it this early.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, I guess that's an admission that it's not selling well, which we all knew.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I wasn't angry about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only thing about these 20 free games is that it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least I'll have something that I can put on my memory card that I can play because I'm not fucking buying any of those virtual console games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not paying money for that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that's kind of cool that I'll have something to fill up my memory card with.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, at the same time, you know, dropping the price of the system doesn't make any of the good games come out any sooner.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, because, you know, what, they announced a couple games, you know, out this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: A new Mario, a Mario Kart, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, I've seen the videos of Mario Kart, and I was just kind of, eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: They added hang gliders in underwater.
[SPEAKER_08]: Big fucking deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's not that exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have something to download for free but it's definitely not going to get me to buy more things and it's definitely not going to get me to buy crappy games that are out there now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad I'll have a use to dust off my system.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I was looking at it sitting on the coffee table, not being charged or anything, just sitting there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go to our chatroom at chat.orangelandradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Technus in our chatroom says, right, Nintendo running America.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means they will just rehash the same laws and not make new ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that kind of what's happening now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like nobody wants to do something different?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where we're at right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, sorry, I didn't mean to get controversial.
[SPEAKER_06]: Salacious Pop in our chat says, what I want to know is, will DSi XL get a price drop too now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Very interesting that that is completely absent, but I would think logically it has to, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because isn't the DSi XL right now $179?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought they've already dropped the price of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know they did the regular DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: But even, I mean, logically, if the 3DS is coming down that low, XL and the rest of them, if they're not fading into obscurity altogether, are going to have to get some type of price cut.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, XL ought to come down to $129, if not less.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also a part of me that kind of thinks like, well, why wouldn't Nintendo just get rid of all the old DSs altogether and say, buy a 3DS or get GTFO?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, and could you really blame them for doing that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you would still have the current inventory on shelves now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll get their prices slashed to get it off the shelves and make room for more 3DSs, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo 3DS Launch Lineup
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's where I'm coming from.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm reading things on the internet that are like, oh, Sony was ready to give Nintendo Rumble and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm not trying to hate on the Vita, but I also don't see where it's in much better of a position right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the announced titles that they've got coming out right now aren't that exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's their one big, huge thing they got.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the other ones, like, I could give... I couldn't give a crap about whatever the hell that game, the puzzle game is, where they're, like, really showing off the back-touch stuff, or... You know, I don't need another fucking rehash of goddamn, you know, uh... Was it, uh... Well, LittleBigPlanet, for one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, yeah, great.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, LittleBigPlanet's coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it's I just think, you know, and don't get me wrong I want a Vita, I'm gonna buy a Vita at launch, I will, I mean, I just I'm a techno person, I have to have it all, but and there are a couple games on Vita I do want, there was that one music game that Miklatov was talking about on one of the E3 specials that I want to get, and then there's that dungeon game that probably won't be out at launch but I know down the road I'll want to get that
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: What won Christmas five years ago?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: What won Christmas last year?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Kinect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who was the target audience of both of those?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oprah Watchers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be the same story this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: The performance from March to now isn't really going to matter when it comes to the holidays and all the kids everywhere want the 3DS to play Mario and watch 3D movies on.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the 3DS...
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of has a lot going for it And I gotta think also that some people Well, a lot of people probably thought Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo's probably gonna drop the price of the 3DS Before holiday Because, you know, it's not doing that well Or, I mean, even if it was doing alright They still wanna, you know, incentivize people for, you know, buying the system I mean, I think a lot of people are like Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's not a lot of good games out right now I'm just gonna wait And waiting paid off for ya
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just saying, imagine you're a soccer mom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I know, just hear me out here for a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Imagine you're a soccer mom and you don't know anything about games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know there's this one system that's $250 that I guess does some type of back touch thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then there's this other system over here that's $80 less and it does 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mario.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has Mario on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which you remember some of your friends liking when you were in junior high school.
[SPEAKER_06]: which is where the soccer moms are at now, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, like, I'm not trying to, again, I'm not trying to knock the Vita.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be huge with the college crowd and the young 20s and, you know, more adult gamers, if you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll still be huge with them and the fact that it's a, you know, all-in-one in the pocket.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think when it comes down to the actual sales, I think what shows up under those Christmas trees and Hanukkah menorahs and so forth are going to be 3DSs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you put your presents under the menorah?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I get you guys presents because I know that you celebrate Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I like presents because I'm greedy.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And special.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going to our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Laha in the chat room says, I think the parents didn't like the 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something about not wanting to mess up their kids' eyes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what about, okay, look at the movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, Smurfs 3D is like top of the box office.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3D really bugs my eyes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate looking at the world in 3D.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really hurts my eye.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I will tell you something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know what Laha's referring to.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's those studies about the kids' eyes and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, the 3DS itself is not true 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's lenticular.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that can cause some issues with vision.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it gives me a headache.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't play a 3DS for very long without getting a headache.
[SPEAKER_06]: The first day it gave me a headache, but now it's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bridge Racer was unplayable it was just completely unplayable I've actually been using the 3DS a little bit as a Netflix device like it's kind of nice to just have it like you know when you're like lying in bed but you're not really ready to go to sleep like it's kind of nice to just be able to you know have the thing there to watch Netflix funny enough I have an iPhone which I could use but I don't know usually that's on the charger so the 3DS just kind of works
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you know, I guess they do have a point with the 3D thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's really gonna torpedo their sales.
[SPEAKER_08]: If only they had the forethought to, you know, put in a slider or something to turn the 3D off.
[SPEAKER_08]: If only.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Nintendo, maybe next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: And TigerClawInChat is correcting me saying Smurfs and Cowboy and Aliens are sharing the number one spot this week But the reason why the Smurfs is even tied in the first place is that it has those extra 3D ticket sales Because let's face it, no one over the age of 11 wanted to see the Smurfs movie I still want to see Cowboys and Aliens I'm very torn about the Smurfs movie because I really like Neil Patrick Harris But I really hate everything else about that movie
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Hank Azaria and he's Gargamel, but I am not fucking sitting through that movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: He does, however, look just like freaking Gargamel, doesn't he?
[SPEAKER_06]: I will give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why are we talking about the Smurfs movie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck this conversation.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: The Muppets movie, there's a lot of the cast from How I Met Your Mother.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck yes to the Muppets movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: 100% yes to the Muppets movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: 100% no to the Smurfs movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Smurfs is terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else is terrible?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Since we're on this tangent train.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Battleship.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, that movie looks a special kind of terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You posted the trailer on the Facebook, and I think my comment was, quote, this looks like shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, Dan showed it to me, and my reply was, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last time I played Battleship, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the way the trailer looked, like with the configuration of the ships, I was literally expecting Leonison to shout out, I-7-
[SPEAKER_06]: and Rihanna to go, girl, you shunk my battleship.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what they're setting up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like, well, our radar's out.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have this satellite imagery that we're going to use to plot where we fire stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the enemies, you know, whatever their missiles or whatever, they're the pegs.
[SPEAKER_06]: They spent money, lots and lots of money on that movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what really freaks me out is that they bought the rights to all these other board games too.
[SPEAKER_06]: They want to do a new Clue movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, no, no, no, no The one in the 80s was perfect It's a cult classic It's Tim Curry at his finest Second finest next to Furter Third finest next to Furter And Pennywise
[SPEAKER_06]: Fourth finest next to Furter, Pennywise, and whatever, and Annie.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, what about the demon in Labyrinth?
[SPEAKER_06]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, fifth finest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's just face it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tim Curry is always awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every movie he touches is amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even in The Worst Witch, he was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, don't make Clue like Battleship.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will cry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I just expect this scene of Miss Peacock walking these little squares in the, like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then all of a sudden aliens come from outer space and destroy everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Den doing Laundromat says, you sunk my battleshit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You sunk my battleshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and Ism said, you sunk my box office sales.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Frisbee says, you sunk my PT boat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Yahtzee movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good idea, Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, TigerClaw on chat says, you know, despite what you see in the trailer, it could be a fun popcorn movie if you ignore the fact it's based on a board game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go watch the trailer again and then come back and tell me that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it could be snakes on the plane.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe getting high will be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the first half of the trailer, don't get me wrong, I was like, okay, this is
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I just picture this trailer in my mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Monopoly?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just picture Russell Brand sitting in a top hat and a monocle going, I'll get out of jail free called.
[SPEAKER_08]: Monopoly, Ouija.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're doing a new Ouija movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it going to be like, what was the best Ouija movie ever?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe The Exorcist.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about Witch Board?
[SPEAKER_10]: That movie was based off of Ouija board.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about Witch Board?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, alright, I don't want to talk about these horrible movies anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although it is related to games, every single one of these movies will have a game tie-in to it, you better believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there will be something on the Wii that you can get for the Battleship movie that'll be, you know, Liam Neeson yelling, I7!
[SPEAKER_10]: I do, by the way, have to quote something from Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you watch The Exorcist Backwards, it's about a girl who's really sick and then eats some pea soup and gets better.
[SPEAKER_08]: shut up I'll bring it up later but I'm trying to find that list of movies that they have maybe we'll save it for like the afterbirth or something but it's terrible I know
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, can we move on?
[SPEAKER_06]: All this other news that just kind of showed up in the press releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the fact that original NES games were coming to virtual console.
[SPEAKER_06]: That just was kind of, oh yeah, well since we're giving them away, we're just going to throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to point out something to Laha.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a Dungeons & Dragons movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tom Baker was in it, however.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the kid from Serial Mom was in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a sequel, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: and just to let you know, the movie Krull that came out when I was pretty young I saw it in the theater, I'll put it that way was supposed to be the Dungeons & Dragons movie and they lost the license for it so Dungeons & Dragons has been done for the record though, I did kind of like the Dungeons & Dragons movie Dungeons & Dragons, you will believe that a Wayans can be an elf
[SPEAKER_10]: Super Mario 3D Land
[SPEAKER_06]: No further information still on Kid Icarus, which is also supposed to be this holiday, but they haven't exactly said when that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now there's a little bit of concern that maybe it's not going to make this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know the best part about Mario Kart 7?
[SPEAKER_08]: According to Kotaku, it's actually the ninth Mario Kart game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: What games did they forget?
[SPEAKER_06]: Arcade ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendo didn't really develop the arcade ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't Namco do those?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a Pac-Man movie, by the way, but it was animated.
[SPEAKER_06]: They would not be considered canon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would support calling it Mario Kart 7 because the arcade ones are not canon.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not as good, either.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're really not.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're okay for arcade games, I guess, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not the same quality as the home ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: And unlike Loki, I love me some Mario Kart and I am looking forward to this new one.
[SPEAKER_06]: As long as it's not Double Dash bad, then I am looking forward to the new one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did actually have to point out that just about everything that Lahaz suggested, there actually have been movies.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a Pac-Man movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was animated.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a Pac-Man TV show back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there was.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the same series.
[SPEAKER_10]: The movie was in the same series.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also Pac-Man Save Santa Claus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I watched it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what my two shows were when I was a kid?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Pac-Man and Q-Bert.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched the Q-Bert cartoon too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Candyland was also one of the other licenses that they had.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Monopoly Battleship, Candyland, and Ouija.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great, I hope Patrick Stewart stars in Candyland.
[SPEAKER_06]: set course for yellow square engage Spock is not impressed
[SPEAKER_06]: So, uh... Did they get Chutes and Ladders, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: How about HiHoCherryO?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about a story?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm gonna say why it's stupid after I read it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, the ESA wants $1.1 million reimbursement from the state of California for the law that failed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, it's for Brown v. EMA.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: and basically the whole point is that and this is a quote California persisted in defending a law that plaintiffs warned of the legislature was unconstitutional before it passed that was previously found to be unconstitutional by the district court and a unanimous panel of the Ninth Circuit and that is similar to at least eight other laws invalidated as unconstitutional prior to the time California sought seriatory in this case
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, you knew, but you pursued it anyway because you're stupid?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pay us.
[SPEAKER_10]: We spent a lot of money beating your ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, California did send a check for $282,794 for reimbursement for legal fees.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, we're broke in California.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, yeah, ESA kind of deserves it, but at the same time, we don't have the money right now, so you just need to... I'm going to tell you what's going to happen, ESA.
[SPEAKER_10]: Listen to me, representatives of the ESA.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is what's going to happen if you get your money.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to find another tax to raise or increase our tuition again or do something else, and it's going to hurt the people that pretty much fund your operation.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is so hard because I can see it from both sides.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ESA spent a lot of money defending something that should have never been a law in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were defending our rights.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so it's kind of like they should be entitled to that money.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I am with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know damn well that money is not going to come out of thin air.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's so much...
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't need to come out of thin air.
[SPEAKER_08]: It needs to come out of fucking Leland Yee's ass is where it needs to fucking come from.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's where the money should come from.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_10]: They need to take it right from the source.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would support that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I honestly think that any of these politicians that have basically brought up anything like this that have failed that spent our taxpayer dollars because you know he didn't pay anything out of pocket for any of this shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything that comes out of our pockets as taxpayers, the ones responsible for the failed law need to pay it themselves.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is actually something, because here in California, basically, we are pretty much a direct democracy here.
[SPEAKER_10]: We can vote on what we want.
[SPEAKER_10]: All you have to do is have enough signatures to put it on the ballot, and it can be voted on.
[SPEAKER_10]: and this is something that I would seriously sit back and pen and I've got friends that will review the legal side of it for me for free this is something that I would sit back and pen myself that a politician needs to be responsible for anything they do that fails if they cost the taxpayer money on a failed venture then it needs to come out of their personal pocket or they need to have a cut and pay
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to get too political, but you wouldn't want to scare off a politician from doing something that maybe they really should be doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a middle ground somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you're right, but you have to be very careful in how you word something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: is that the court should be able to find the person liable when gross negligence is shown.
[SPEAKER_06]: There needs to be something that the judge could do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You wouldn't want all politicians to have to suffer because of people constantly going after rights and things like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: They're still out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And again, we're broke in California.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have no money, even though we have some of the highest grossing income people in the country that live in our state.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they being taxed relatively any more than we are?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because of Republicans.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, but I'm saying that when you come to the point that we don't have any more money to pay on any of this, and they're still going and pursuing stuff that they know is going to cost us money.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, when is that going to stop?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to keep doing stupid shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just look at all the dumb laws they have in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they were going to try to ban circumcision.
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole circumcision thing that went on the ballot and had to be thrown out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was thrown out by a judge that it's not going to be on the ballot because it was just too ridiculous or whatever legal thing they decided.
[SPEAKER_10]: And besides that, it would infringe on religious rights.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I mean, it's just so... But it's like, who paid for that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Who paid for that whole process?
[SPEAKER_10]: They pay... The reason why I think it's so expensive to live in San Francisco is because they have a bunch of ridiculous laws that aren't necessary.
[SPEAKER_10]: None of us elsewhere have to deal with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just in San Francisco, they have this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I mean, I don't want to get too political here, but some could look and say, hmm, in San Francisco, everyone has health care.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, that's one I agree with.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm saying there's other...
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: We gotta not... I think Jamie needs a spin-off show that's political.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because then I would be hoarse and have a headache.
[SPEAKER_06]: Called Stitchin' Bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Back to gaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: GameStop is now prepared to offer downloadable PC purchases at retail, much like they do right now with digital purchases for DLC and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, great if you want to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, if you're trading used items for download content or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, much like I don't see the point in download content being purchased at retail, I don't really see the point of buying a digital PC title at retail.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, shit, if you're going to go to retail to buy a digital title, like, say, any game that's out there now that's...
[SPEAKER_08]: I think GameCroc's just trying to do what they have to do to stay relevant, but it ain't gonna work.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I guess that's cool if you want all those extras.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I know Steam does a lot of extras like that as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it's just really... If that's important to you, then I'd go that route.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you're just looking to buy digital stuff... I mean, it's kind of like the whole point of buying digital in the first place is so you don't have to go to the store.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I guess if you're young enough and you don't have a credit card or something like that, then that may be the only way to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: But whatever, you know
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what they want to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Power to the players, as they say.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be really neat if I could get into the used game market with this stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should be able to Steam revoke my access to a game and I get a credit to use on the store and then somebody else can buy the game at a reduced price or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that will never happen, but if you think about it, they could do something where the publisher would get a cut of that, and that doesn't happen right now in the retail stores.
[SPEAKER_06]: There could be a way, if publishers were smarter about the used game market, where they could get a cut of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm not just talking these $10 online passes.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of prices, Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you noticed something about the games on Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the points have been slowly rising.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, the cost of the games have been rising on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: so far in 2011 there have been 20 1200 plus games last year 27 of the 85 games released for the service cost 1200 points or more so we're already at 20 for this year so that was an 8% increase in itself over 2009 when 21 titles hit that price point
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, they are saying that, you know, well, we have to blame the fact that the quality of games we're basically making is a lot higher too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Limbo and Castle Crashers, they're as good as anything else that's out on the market.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that Xbox Live Arcade games are getting better and therefore they're worth the extra money?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or do you think this is just inflation when we're not paying attention?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's inflation.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a little bit of a mix of both I think yes it's inflation going on but at the same time you really don't see any more like just crappy lazy arcade ports ever since Xbox or Microsoft kind of banned those from the service like you don't see any more of this just re-release of an old ass game that's you know 400 Microsoft points most of the stuff that's coming out now definitely had a lot of development dollars put into it with mixed success some of it's really good some of it's not so good it just depends on what kind of games you're into
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's a little bit of both.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: They want to put out $20 games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you don't have to buy them.
[SPEAKER_08]: No one's forcing you to buy them.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're smart, you wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then sometimes when that game pops up onto the deal of the week, then you buy it for a cheaper price.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I still do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will say one thing I do love is that you still get the demos.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's something you can't always get at a retail store.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that is one thing I really like.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can really, really try a game before I buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Xbox Live Arcade, even though the prices are creeping up, as long as the quality stays good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's been a lot of good arcade games I've played lately.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, in other news, this actually is for our UK listeners.
[SPEAKER_10]: The shop game restarted its Play Now, Trade Later deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, you can buy a game and trade it in at a guaranteed amount.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you essentially end up paying five pounds for your game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the games that are included on this list is...
[SPEAKER_10]: UFC Trainer for Wii, Cars 2 on DS, Art Academy, Call of Juarez the Cartel, Hunted, The Demon's Forge, Harry Potter and Deathly Hallows Part 2 for Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's a number of games you'd have to check with your local game store to find out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, if you trade in any of those games for credit before August 12th, they'll effectively cost 5.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can use the credit on any future purchase.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's a good way to save money, especially if these are games that you got and you're kind of like, eh, meh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like a really weird way of doing like a demo or like a rental service.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, in February, they also had one where it guaranteed a 35-pound trade-in for shooters like Killzone 3 and Bulletstorm.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's a good way to basically refill stock.
[SPEAKER_10]: So.
Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll see how successful this is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: None of those games are making me go, ooh, gotta get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, granted, I live in the wrong country anyway, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, let's travel the world and talk about release dates and what upcoming games you could maybe get a five-pound deal or five-dollar deal on later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, not a whole lot this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least there's some games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a few weeks coming up here where there's nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starting off, Phineas and Ferb Across the Second Dimension.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love Phineas and Ferb.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming out on PlayStation 3 with Move support.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe $40.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you love Phineas and Ferb $40 much?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll just keep watching episodes off the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sesame Street, Ready, Set, Grover coming out on the DS and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: DS version has a funny little Grover stylus.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it might be that Kinect game that they were showing at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, that got delayed.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the Wii version you get a Grover fuzzy Wii remote cover.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, wait, you said that really quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: That got delayed?
[SPEAKER_06]: Delayed to when?
[SPEAKER_06]: Next year?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just in the fall.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like October.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I guess I thought that was when it was always set to come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was August at one point.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Bleach Soul Resurrection for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is going to be kind of like a Dice Warriors type of game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, you get three free episodes or the anime episodes on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get a voucher for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sniper Ghost Warrior Extended Edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's coming out on 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the enthusiasm in the chat room shown by Sterlok at chat.orangelunchradio.com Sterlok says, Yay Grover!
[SPEAKER_06]: He was my favorite when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Him and Cookie Monster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back in my day, Elmo didn't exist on the old school Sesame Street back when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which we like to refer to as the good old days.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Breakman says, I preferred the Muppets.
[SPEAKER_06]: I liked Muppet Babies, but it was always about Fraggle Rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know about you guys, but anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fraggle Rock is awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, going to Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of a slow week over there as well, but on the Xbox 360 this week, you get a couple of price reductions, including Assassin's Creed Brotherhood Special Edition and Tropico 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both move into the Platinum Collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's on the 4th of August on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going over to the PlayStation 3, we have Assassin's Creed Brotherhood there as well, and then another game getting a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_06]: This has a whopper of a name.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's
[SPEAKER_06]: R Tonelico 3 Sekai Shuin no Hikigane wa Shujou no Uta ga Hajuku gets a price reduction this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no idea what game this is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's R Tonelico.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a role-playing game and of course it looks like you can dress the little girls up as bunnies in the game and I can see a little item shop in some of these pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, the game looks kind of cool but I don't think we have this here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not number three, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have number two at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: What game is this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's R Tonelico.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I didn't know that was out here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's out here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on to other consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if Nintendo has anything on their lineup, but I will check.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I can do the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do have a couple games there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have Storm Lover, Summer Love from D3, Toriyoko, Gourmet Survival.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is that, like Iron Chef or Dai?
[SPEAKER_06]: Gourmet Survival!
[SPEAKER_06]: Man vs. Beast
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what that is.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's on the BSP this week as well as Yusha 32nd from Marvelous comes out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder if that's a version of 32nd Hero or Half Minute Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Half Minute Hero Part 2 comes out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: That could be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's on the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And going to the Nintendo Wii, Epic Mickey gets a release in Japan this week, finally.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they must have localized it for Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know Disney's pretty big over there, so they probably took a little while for them to localize it all.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had to add Duffy to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Duffy is bigger than Mickey in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, Duffy is pretty big.
[SPEAKER_06]: Family Fishing as well on the Wii and lastly on the Nintendo 3DS this week, Nazo Waku Yakata Oton no Aida ni Ade ni comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: This looks like, is this a Professor Layton game?
[SPEAKER_08]: It would appear so.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's Professor Layton's Haunted Mansion or something like that on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_06]: As I horribly butcher the names as I always do.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Europe, two things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Limbo for PC and Insanely Twisted Shadow Planet on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks monochrome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's got a unique art style to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's insanely twisted.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's talk a little bit more about earnings and lack thereof.
[SPEAKER_08]: THQ is disappointed in their earnings for Fiscal Quarter 2, including Red Faction and the performance of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're thinking, of course, Quarter 3 could be its best.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm sorry, it was Quarter 1 instead they were pissed off about.
[SPEAKER_08]: These Fiscal Quarters get confusing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, they were saying sales of Red Faction Armageddon and our licensed kid titles were below expectations.
[SPEAKER_08]: The late release of UFC Personal Trainer also adversely impacted the quarter.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know...
[SPEAKER_08]: THQ, I mean, you had a Kung Fu Panda game come out and you decided to make it U-Draw only.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a good choice, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, they're saying that the net loss of $38.4 million and most of the losses are from deferred revenue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, revenue that the company's not counting yet because it's going towards their online services for its games.
[SPEAKER_08]: and of course Q3 for them is going to be Saints Row the 3rd, WWE 12 and the UDraw tablet for the 360 and PS3 among other things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red Faction did so poorly that it will not be continuing on in any meaningful way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it is done, fortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Breakman is crying in our chat room over the death of Red Faction.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you feel about it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Weren't you a fan of that series?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I just didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not that I don't like it or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it looked cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Volition.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love Volition.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's part your fault that the series died, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's because I didn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you are mad about the death of Red Faction, just send those cards and letters to Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, it just didn't do that well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you would have thought, you know, a game with a unicorn that shoots rainbows out of its ass, that it would have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, by the way, I hope to God that they bring that weapon over to Saints Row III, because that would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: and then of course one of the things that they were experimenting with starting with MX vs. ATV is releasing a game for a lower price point and then hoping to make that money up back with download content so they did try that with MX vs. ATV Alive
[SPEAKER_08]: They put it out at $39.99 and their idea was of course to come out with a robust product at $39.99 price point, build a large install base more quickly, and then monetize that install base to wrap it in a large number of DLC drops.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, it didn't work.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only problem is the game didn't move enough units to turn, or in turn, move enough download content to make the experiment a success.
[SPEAKER_08]: So the key to learning was that it was not a successful experiment.
[SPEAKER_08]: The $39.99 price point, while good, gave us good acceleration of sales, but that wasn't enough to drive the install base where we wanted it to be, obviously.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just wasn't working out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Breakman in chat is calling you Darth Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's very upset about this whole Red Faction thing, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who you need to blame?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know who put their logo onto that game?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be SyFy.
[SPEAKER_08]: SyFy Channel had a fucking movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was SyFy Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to talk about someone putting out a poor product, that would be SyFy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that's who you need to blame.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at least, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can guarantee that quarter three is going to be amazing because fucking Saints Row the Third, that shit is going to sell like crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, I got to... There's part of me didn't want to talk about this next story, but this next story just really makes me angry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, there's so much to hate in this next story, and I apologize for bringing it up, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: This should piss you off too because you have the power to change things.
[SPEAKER_06]: and as you guys know if you ever watch a television you know that there was a horrible horrible tragedy in Norway this past week and you know you had this just crazy asshole that and I'm not even gonna say his name I'm not gonna show you his picture because he doesn't deserve to have it shown he's a crazy asshole and he blew up a building and he shot a bunch of kids at a camp
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and what happens when a horrific situation happens?
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to blame something.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to blame someone, you want to blame something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So why am I bringing it up here on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess what got blamed?
[SPEAKER_09]: Video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Norwegian retailers have pulled World of Warcraft and Call of Duty after the shooting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of the big retailers because I guess this asshole wrote some manifesto that either talked about the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he had actually said he learned how to shoot or whatever in Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_06]: which I don't know why you would take what a crazy asshole says at face value but whatever I mean this just infuriates me because it's like don't pay attention to this stupid asshole by banning these games I feel like you're validating what he says and that's the last thing you should do in a situation like this it's so irritating
[SPEAKER_06]: Warcraft provided a useful cover story for the time he spent in seclusion plotting his terrorist attacks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then playing Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 was a way to keep his skills honed.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the retailers Co-op Norway and Plate Companyet, I can't say these Norwegian names, but something like that, they pulled the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are saying it's a temporary removal, but as far as I'm concerned, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't validate this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Irritating.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, we will say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: SpaceWorld is another retailer.
[SPEAKER_06]: They refused to pull the games, saying it saw no connection between the games and the tragedy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quote, we have never seen any research that games alone have led to such incidents.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you live in Norway, that would be A plus SpaceWorld, F minus these other guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, shame on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then, of course, it doesn't end there.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if that's the word I would choose to use, but I guess that's what this article is saying here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Clinical psychologist Christopher Ferguson, a leading expert on video game violence and mass killings at Texas A&M International University, said video games aren't to blame for the tragedy, nor is Doom, nor is Quake, and so on.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, he believes that placing the blame on video games whenever a white male is guilty of a killing spree is racist.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird, but I can't say he's totally... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Keep in mind, keep in mind, and this is something that needs to be defined for the entirety of America.
[SPEAKER_10]: Racism does not mean white against black, white against this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It means one race against another.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it's making a judgment... Based on racial factors only.
[SPEAKER_06]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this time he's saying because...
[SPEAKER_06]: White males commit heinous acts Instantly blaming video games is racist
[SPEAKER_10]: I would say bigoted.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a better word.
[SPEAKER_06]: Racist just isn't the right word for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it is sort of profiling.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good word.
[SPEAKER_10]: Profiling.
[SPEAKER_10]: But racist?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that had to be used for lack of a better, or maybe just for shock value.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it really is profiling and a bit of bigotry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: and the doctor goes on to say mass killings are going to happen and there's nothing anyone can do about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: fortunately they're not going to happen very often but they're like lightning strikes let's see quote I know it's a little controversial to say but there's a certain type of racism in place of these killings when shootings happen in an inner city in minority populated schools video games are never brought up when these things happen in white majority schools and in the suburbs people start to freak out and video games are inevitably blamed I think that there's a certain element of racism or ignorance here
[SPEAKER_06]: people really want to know what kind of boogeyman we can hang this on and video games are still the top choice when it comes to any type of tragedy if you want to read more on this you can go to blog.forbes.com and read the full article there let me read another quote from this
[SPEAKER_06]: really interesting for lack of a better word there are groups out there who are going to blame video games on everything they're like ambulance chasers really I think it's irresponsible and thoughtless to try to make political gain off of someone else's tragedy but they're going to do it
[SPEAKER_06]: that's what they do but even those groups have been much quieter with the Oslo tragedy and you know we had another follow up story in our show role that I neglected to copy the link for but in a nutshell some crazy religious group is trying to get the games banned here in the US because of the Norway shooting and that quote I agree with these guys are like ambulance chasers to push their own agenda and they are exploiting a disgusting scenario to promote their own agenda and that is sick
[SPEAKER_06]: In that part, I agree with.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, really fascinating study.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Draw your own opinions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Choose your own words.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you know what the whole thing is?
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is my little commentary on the whole situation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop looking for something to blame other than the people themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kaishudo in the chatroom says, Rob, don't jump on the side of one nutcase that goes against another nutcase's view.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not totally with this guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, I get what he's saying, but I don't know if racism would be the word I'd use.
[SPEAKER_06]: Profiling, like Jamie said, I think is maybe a better word to use.
[SPEAKER_06]: But when he does talk about the ambulance chaser and how people will use these situations to promote their own agendas, I will say, yes, I agree with him on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Weren't we just talking about politicians and the whole Supreme Court thing earlier?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, wasn't that all kind of promoting Leland Yee's own political agenda and continuing to promote his own?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that part, I am with him.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a certain Lord Voldemort wouldn't have done this in the past at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and that's really, again, I think a failing of society in general.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I think that if you look at things maybe a hundred years ago or look into another culture.
[SPEAKER_10]: People were more likely to own up to what was their mistake.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was considered the mature thing, the honorable thing to do, to own up to your own mistake, to put the blame where it was, to not make those who were circumstantially a part of it pay for it, but those who were specifically responsible for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care what they did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care if they played My Little Pony while wearing mantis and doing ballet in a little pink frilly tutu.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do not care.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't care that J. Edgar Hoover was a transvestite.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was a bastard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Him being a transvestite had nothing to do with being a bastard.
[SPEAKER_08]: All those things, by the way, that she mentioned before are able to be done in Dead Rising 2 off the record.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Capcom has your weird, sick, twisted fantasies.
[SPEAKER_06]: The word Capcom is still... I have a bad Pavlov's response to that word this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: But my point being is that whatever they did in their private life, whatever they do on the side, has nothing to do...
[SPEAKER_10]: with their final action.
[SPEAKER_10]: It may have been, okay, well, I've done all this and it's led up to this point, but really, it's what goes on in the head.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they're not right in the head, they're not going to do something right to begin with.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they're crazy, okay, yeah, maybe they'll get some pleasure out of playing a video game for a little while, but they're going to need something else a little bit later.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_10]: A bump on, you know, a ripple in the ocean, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little pebble in the pond on the way to the big boulder falling in and damming the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_06]: It does, but I'm just, this whole thing is just, it just irritates me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just sick of the blame game.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a big problem with society.
[SPEAKER_10]: People need to freaking grow up and also have the maturity to put the blame on who it needs to be put on, which is the person who did it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't matter what else they're into.
[SPEAKER_10]: They could be into latex fetish porn.
[SPEAKER_06]: He could have been a concert-trained piano player.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, the guy in Japan who was the cannibal?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm using him as an example.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was a cultured, respected person.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was smart, lived a very good life, but he ate some chick that he went out on dinner with.
[SPEAKER_08]: He just gave in to the temptation of flesh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which, by the way, now he's actually a paid lecturer, just letting you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I hear he's eating up all the attention.
[SPEAKER_10]: But my point is... Fired!
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, here's another example.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm not just saying this because I'm Jewish.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hitler.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Failed painter.
[SPEAKER_10]: He failed his entrance into a prestigious art school.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he joined the military.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was a vegetarian!
[SPEAKER_10]: You would not assume vegetarian and painter would lead to mass murderer.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going to blame all vegetarians and painters now for being potential mass murdering fuckheads?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, vegetarians maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, vegetarians and pita maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, pita is just psycho anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, Jamie, you really murdered that onion in your salad.
[SPEAKER_10]: But my point is, you know...
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't matter what their hobbies are.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't matter the walk of life they come from.
[SPEAKER_10]: Crazy is fucking crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you blame the person.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't see anybody blaming vegetarians for, you know, 100,000 people being killed.
[SPEAKER_10]: You see them blaming Hitler.
[SPEAKER_06]: Legend of Zaku in our chatroom says, Jamie, you have to accept that playing the blame game ever since the Salem witch trials.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you see what happened then.
[SPEAKER_10]: A bunch of innocent people died.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'd think we'd learn from history.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, because people are stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: There may have been some witches in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: On that note, Loki has effectively killed the conversation.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's change things up a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need some happy, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week here on the show, DarkSakura takes a trip down memory lane and visits a classic video game that she says, Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to be playing this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: One thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do have to repeat what William Murderface said.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: The fallacy of correlation equals causation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, can we do the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: StarTropics.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least you picked a really good classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I actually didn't really play that game all that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but it's been such a cool... But I remember playing it and enjoying it when I did... I just never... I just got lazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's... My best friend in fourth grade and I stayed up all night playing this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's a lot of people's favorite games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's like, why shouldn't I bring up Star Topics, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it was an action-adventure RPG.
[SPEAKER_10]: It came out by Nintendo in 1990 for the NES, and it was never released or intended to be released in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: It only came out in North America and Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it was designed by Japanese designers who lived in the U.S., written and directed by Genyo Takeda of Nintendo Integrated Research and Development, who also gave us Punch-Out!!
[SPEAKER_10]: And it came out on the North American Virtual Console on January 7, 2008, and on the PAL region on January 11.
[SPEAKER_10]: and, of course, I had a sequel, which was Zoda's Revenge, StarTropics 2, in 1994.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the year I'm not telling people what I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you start off as, I graduated high school.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mike Jones is visiting his uncle, who is named Dr. J, and he lives on Sea Island.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he finds that Dr. J has gone missing, and Babu, his assistant, who also sounds a lot like Baloo from The Jungle Book,
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's Mike use the submarine to basically go look for Dr. J. So it starts off all of his adventures.
[SPEAKER_10]: He thinks aliens are involved.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically he finds Dr. J by the wreckage of an alien escape pod.
[SPEAKER_10]: So they think it's the Argonians.
[SPEAKER_10]: So he has to go to the mothership and do open stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then Zoda comes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm not going to say anymore because there's more stuff to the game than just what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's also children adoption involved too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just thought I'd mention that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you don't adopt the children.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't adopt children.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically it's a 2D top-down perspective kind of like Zelda in the dungeon areas.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it is linear, consistent storyline and the story progresses basically with talking to NPCs and doing certain actions.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then you have to go to your little dungeon-y areas.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it switches mechanics there where it has a zoomed in type of perspective.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically you get weapons and items, baseball themed in many cases, and you basically, well you also get baseballs but they're called wonder horse hides.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Clates known as Spikes and Bolas and Shuriken and Slingshots and Mirrors and different types of stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: But basically you get all kinds of things to help you progress through the game and fight all of the various baddies.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you get a life meter of 22 hearts, kind of like Link, in fact it looks a lot like the Legend of Zelda life bar.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you can find big hearts that are, again, like the heart containers in Zelda and you can get vitamin X that fills up all of your hearts even though, um, you know, you will lose, of course, health when you take damage.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, uh, you can also get try your luck signs that, um, are, you know, basically can give you extra lives in the game you only start off with three and if you lose all of your lives at the beginning of a dungeon I mean, in a dungeon then you'll have to go back to the beginning
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, so basically you've got, you know, your boss characters, it's RPG stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it, you know, like I said, I didn't get to play a whole bunch of it, but I know a lot of people liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We gotta talk about the letter that came with the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, yes, there was a letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: My friend and I, we had no idea that this was, oh my god, it was the coolest fucking thing when you were like nine or ten.
[SPEAKER_10]: You get a parchment letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: and... It actually came with the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's not talking about something you get in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a tangible thing that came in the box.
[SPEAKER_10]: Made of parchment.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically it has a letter from Dr. Jones addressed to Mike.
[SPEAKER_10]: And by the way, I actually did have a copy of the letter because when I rented StarTropics back in the day, they included the letter with the rental.
[SPEAKER_10]: But basically, it's like you intercepted the letter and were being invited to play the game on Mike's behalf.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you get a message from your uncle, Evil Aliens from a distant planet, tell Mike to dip my letter in water.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you have the letter, the original letter, then you could put... What was that thing with the water?
[SPEAKER_10]: They have a secret message?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the letter, the visible ink or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It had a subcode in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and I think it was supposed to be able to do it without damaging the letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, oh yeah, you could do it without damaging the letter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but you had a secret message in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it had like, if I remember right, there was a spot, a very specific spot where you would drip the water.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally recall.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I'm going to see if I can find a picture of the letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember the code was 747.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it's actually on here.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they actually... Like an airplane.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo Power was asked the question enough because people that rented the game or sometimes their letter would be damaged or missing in the package.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Nintendo Power actually printed it after a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I had to call into the hotline because I bought it used.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's kind of one of those things that like in retrospect, it probably wasn't a very good idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like Ubisoft, don't pay attention to the letter thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you imagine that coming back as rights, copyright protection?
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember back in the day on the, sorry, Jamie, but on the PC games, like the old school PC games, we'd have to like thumb to page 26 of the manual and read the symbol that's on there or get the plastic card that came with the game and
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, all this insane copy protection back in the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of what this sounds like.
[SPEAKER_06]: The wheels.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this one was cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now, for Virtual Console, the letter is included in the digital manual.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it has an image of the letter and a bucket of water at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you click on the image and the letter dips into the bucket and the code shows up.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the European release, though, it just has a click here link at the bottom and the thing will pop up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's kind of neat that, you know, you dunk the virtual letter.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cute, it's cute, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm gonna see if I can find a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll link it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised they haven't remade that series yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of surprised, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, they did have a sequel to StarTropics, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, it was like... Zoda's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't Zoda's Revenge, like, the last NES game they made?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or no, that was Wario's Woods.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was right at the end, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Wario's Woods was technically the last NES game they ever made, but Zoda's Revenge was right at the end.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we've got the letter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's a bad image.
[SPEAKER_10]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I am going to put a link to that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: If anyone wants to see, it's actually, and I love the name of the website, SocksMakePeopleSexy.net Why don't you just put it on Tumblr?
[SPEAKER_06]: Put it on the Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, but I'm just going to say it to you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: SocksMakePeopleSexy.net
[SPEAKER_10]: Go check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: This guy looks like a Rob the Robot, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: This Navcom guy in the little ship that you navigate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks just like a Rob the Robot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: StarTropics.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of my favorites, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good call, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though that wasn't one that maybe you remember as fondly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a classic game for the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are a few games I haven't played or haven't played a whole lot of, but that doesn't mean that other people haven't played them.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we're going to take a quick break, guys, but when we come back, there is plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio to come, including some rapid-fire news, the FUs of the Week, the Mailbag, of course, your Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR, and, of course, more phone calls when we get back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are live, of course, with our 422nd episode on this July 31st of 2011.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, we're into Part B of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to start off Part B, as we always do, with some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Loki, start us off with some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: To celebrate this, Harmonix is actually hooking up 30 people in America with 100 songs of their choosing, either on Xbox or PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, that's 3,000 songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's different ways to enter via Twitter, Facebook, or the Rock Band forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully, someone out there is going to enjoy those 100 songs if you win.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, of course, as of us recording this, it ended about a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, uh, so much for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you didn't enter, then it's news you lose.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot to enter too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, if you don't win the 100 songs, there are some other things coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Including, and these are all individual songs, they don't have any packs this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make Some Noise by the Beastie Boys.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be $2.
[SPEAKER_08]: No Sleep to Brooklyn, also $2.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's also from the Beastie Boys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Barracuda by Heart.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's $2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Superbad Parts 1 and 2 by James Brown.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's also $2.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Tell Me Something Good by Rufus featuring Shaka Khan.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can get some pro bass and pro guitar expansions for Barracuda and Superbad Parts 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not time for that yet, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it's funny because Duke Nukem still thinks it's popular, but Duke Nukem Forever is going to be getting some new download content, new multiplayer modes and maps this fall.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to have a Hail to the Icons parody pack and it's going to have several parodies of different games, including they've got a parody of...
[SPEAKER_08]: Team Fortress 2, that's going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two Forts, One Bridge, that's going to include hats.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, it says, Duke doesn't need no stinking hats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give him a minigun and he'll beat off all corners.
[SPEAKER_08]: Inferno, Time Machine, Engage, Duke does combat in a hellish landscape of lava and teleporters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who turned on the 16-bit graphics?
[SPEAKER_08]: More importantly, where did this DFG come from?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha, you're parodying Doom, a game that's how old?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, as old as your last game, because that's how long it took to get it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sandpit, player's take role of mini-Duke in a giant sandbox with two bases on either end made of child's toys.
[SPEAKER_08]: This map features sticky grenades and Call of Duke.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gee, I wonder what game that is parodying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Duke engages in modern combat in a war-torn city foes don't stand a chance against Duke when he spams him back with the noob tube
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, and they're also going to have freeze tag, which I guess is going to be, players will be able to freeze and shatter their opponents in huge succession for points and combos.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's going to be the new mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what the funny part about it, about all this?
[SPEAKER_08]: All those games that you're parodying, way better than your own game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha, joke's on you, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that'll be coming if you bought Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: By the time all this download content comes out, I bet you the download content will be priced higher than the actual game because it already got price dropped, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did it really?
[SPEAKER_08]: $3,999 happened this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a good sign.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, when you drop something really quick, that means it's selling well, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: No?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, and yeah, uh, Operation, uh, Rainfall, uh, apparently still not working out too well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, Xenoblade Chronicles is not coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, of course, you know, this week, Nintendo released their upcoming software list, and Xenoblade Chronicles, mm,
[SPEAKER_08]: No way near to be found.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is still scheduled for release in Europe, however, on August 19th.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, you know, the game has been subject of ongoing campaigns by disgruntled American RPG fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they're kind of pissed off that it's still not coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seeing as it's being localized into languages that, you know, us Americans speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you'd think it'd be easy to publish it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Nintendo doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't they just put it on their downloadable service?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't really have anything like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they have the Wii store, but... I don't know if you saw it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They announced this week that, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to now start offering download content on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard about that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, way late to the party.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, didn't the Wii do that too?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the Wii had Rock Band, and you could download some stuff on there, so I don't think it's exactly earth-shattering to hear that Nintendo's supporting DLC.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really just a matter of when.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's just not coming out yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's like they haven't built the infrastructure into the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no games worth it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, now what would be interesting is Nintendo saying, we are getting on board with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would truly be something new.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be like Bizarro World.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now that is something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mario Kart with new downloadable tracks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is the story to wait for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that what Nintendo's talking about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because then that's news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, moving on to some other news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Street Fighter X Tekken is obviously on everybody's radar, especially if you're into fighting games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But fans of the characters Dan, that might be DarkSakura, she's a fan of Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're a fan of Dan or a fan of Anna from Tekken, you might be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both of them have been announced as not in the roster.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, they were booted out of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: The series producer Yoshinori Ono has said that those characters won't be in Street Fighter X Tekken because he was killed by a Tekken character at Comic Con last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think the real reason is, quote, as much as I personally wanted to have... Oh, I'm sorry, this is about Anna and Nina.
[SPEAKER_06]: As much as I personally wanted to have a cool Nina and Anna tag battle, the director was against putting Anna because we already had Nina in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, of course, Dan probably isn't gone for real real.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would, at this point, knowing Capcom, wait for Street Fighter X Tekken Super or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Honestly, I think Anna's going to be a palette swap for Nina.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Some soundtrack related news, quite a bit of it actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a Raiden music collection that's due out on September 28th.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Team Entertainment is the record label, a four-disc compilation of music from the Raiden series called The Lightning Strikes Back.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will have music from Raiden the Arcade from the 90s, Raiden 2, Raiden DX, Raiden DX PlayStation, Raiden 3, and Raiden 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: for coming out September 28th in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also in soundtrack news, The King of Fighters 13.
[SPEAKER_06]: The pre-orders will come with 15 years of musical history, a four CD soundtrack compilation.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what Atlas is putting out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try and get folks to pre-order The King of Fighters 13.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also supposed to be some exclusive game modes in the console version of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: A story mode that will have new visuals and animations, a practice mode, a tutorial mode, and other stuff that wasn't in the arcade but you would expect to see in a console release of a fighter.
[SPEAKER_06]: One other soundtrack news, Rhythm Heaven on the Wii is getting a four-disc soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's already out in Japan, Rhythm Heaven Wii, but it's coming out here as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: A 4-disc CD soundtrack coming out in Japan August 24th for 4,800 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: 150 songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perfect and extended tracks included.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly on the plate tonight, not in soundtrack news, but in sequel rumor news, TimeSplitters 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rumored that there is a version of that coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess this is because of the official PlayStation Magazine UK's rumor machine section.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a rumor that says, quote, Gun-wielding monkeys are finally making a comeback.
[SPEAKER_06]: A fourth TimeSplitters title is to be announced soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, it is coming from the rumors, but when you consider it's the official PlayStation Magazine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love me some TimeSplitters.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I bet you're excited about that, so we will see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not until they actually announce something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they've been talking to TimeSplitters for a long time now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: In other news, we have the Endermen.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're coming for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're actually a new Minecraft mob.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they're just little black stick figures with... Like everything in Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they're all black.
[SPEAKER_10]: They actually remind me of... Do you ever remember in Mario Galaxy where there were the little black guys that were standing on top of the world but you couldn't get to them and they would just watch you?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what they look like to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they're just there to be scary like they're there to terrify you so that's all they're there for and they're going to be in the next Minecraft update it's based off of I guess a character that was made on the something awful forums Slenderman which I watched they have this ARG it's called like Marvel something I forget what it's called and really creepy really really creepy
[SPEAKER_10]: The Slender Man's also been thrown in a number of other video games too, just in background stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very creepy.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll basically stand still moving blocks around stuff, but if you move your reticle over them, they'll stare at you and then they'll charge at you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they can teleport and kill you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm actually going to link a picture in the chat room so they can see what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, moving forward, we also have something from Disney.
[SPEAKER_10]: They want to buy UTV Ignition for $454 million.
[SPEAKER_10]: This actually news comes from Develop, and it says that Disney already owns 50.4% of UTV, and they're wanting to acquire the whole thing for its Bollywood films and TV shows.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: But they own Ignition, so that means there might be some issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: And last but never least, and related to Disney a bit, Toy Story download content is coming for LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: There will be, and actually it's going to be on August 3rd in the UK.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to be 4.79 or 5.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's nine Toy Story themed levels with two cut scenes, five levels and two mini levels.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two new music tracks, one new interactive music track, one new level background, five materials, ten decorations, six objects, and 149 stickers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the costume pack, which is going to cost the same, has Buzz Lightyear gloves, helmet, legs, teeth, and body.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then there's Slinky Dog set that has the feet, ears, hands, nose, skin, body, and tail.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's Ham, which is a head, skin, and body.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Rex, which is the claws, head, skin, and body.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you can also, though, download each set individually for 1.59 or for 1.99 euro.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, if you enjoy Orange Lounge Radio, do check out another show that we produce here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth at www.hordehouse.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's myself and my buddy, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this week we had special guest, Ferare, one of the guild leaders for Extifer's guild on Talking Smack About WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some really good Firelands and raiding discussion this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you're a fan of WoW, check that out again, hordehouse.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: One more day.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's one more day?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you get your last Firelands vendor, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know you get a new mount from that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know!
[SPEAKER_06]: You get like a little firebird thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know!
[SPEAKER_06]: Salacious Pop got that the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll be getting to ride a flaming bird.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, the third podcast is probably delayed a little bit considering there's some personal stuff going on and so forth, but we are still eyeing that at least by Labor Day, no later than that.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've already got things definitely in motion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, more hints coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of you have been begging me on Twitter for more information about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, all I will say is that, you know, certain components of this show, if you like it, you're going to really like the new show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Otherwise, oh well, you still got this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's all free, so don't complain.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they might learn a thing or two.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, you might.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I want to say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: A new segment coming to OLR, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how we have some segments we like to do on the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, a lot of things you're very used to.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Twitter topics, the Skype line we do at the end of the show, Classic Game of the Week and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've kind of talked amongst ourselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: We like to mix it up once in a while at OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: While we have a formula that works for us, once in a while we want to mix it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing we want to feature more on the program is indie games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we're going to have a new segment starting soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't say exactly when.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just depends when I can get some folks on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're actually going to spotlight indie games.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have a name for the segment yet, but we are going to have  or I guess I should say invite developers onto the show to talk about their passion, their game, and share our space with the indie developers.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've had some on in the past in more full interview capacity.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: so if you are a developer that wants to have your indie game featured on the show I would like to keep it to relatively new releases but in the beginning I won't be too picky but something that's been out in the past few months or so do drop me an email you can email me personally rob at orange lounge radio dot com or you can always drop the general email bag as well mailbag at orange lounge radio dot com we'll get you in touch with who you need to get in touch with so that is coming to the show soon whenever we get enough stuff in the pipeline where we have some things to feature we're going to spotlight that here in the show
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just think about it like the classic game of the week, but now it's going to be the indie game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: The new classics.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess you could think about it that way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it won't just be DarkSakura telling you about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: We want to have a discussion with the developer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although if a week goes by where maybe we're having a hard time getting somebody, we'll talk about something that caught our eye.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: but it's so adorable and all the characters are little 8-bit characters and they look so cute and they have their little bit books that they update and you know what I really love?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's one called Tiny Zoo.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I love about Tiny Tower?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me tell you this about Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_06]: What I love about it is that yes, it's free to play and they have these whole tower bucks things and if you want to buy the tower bucks you can do that and move the game a lot faster but
[SPEAKER_06]: but you don't have to because once in a while and more so than in most free-to-play games you'll get tipped a tower buck or you'll get tower bucks as little incentive rewards and so it helps to move the game along a little bit and what I also love about it is that if you forget to check your tower for three weeks
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well, the lights were dark for three weeks and you didn't make any money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your citizens don't move out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't burn the building down in protest.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, you know, it doesn't require your tender, loving care all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want to play it every day, you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to play it once a week, you can.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is good design, in my opinion, and where the freemium model should go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I do know people that have spent money on Tiny Tower.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't, but I think if people want to, they can.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so I'm looking at our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com and it does look like some folks in chat are excited about the whole indie games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talking about that segment coming up.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Actdeft there says, Woo!
[SPEAKER_06]: New OLR segment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Breakman in chat says, How will any of you ever have the time to actually play games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Talking about the third podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will say this much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I'm not working.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Adding a third podcast to the plate is going to be something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not going to be a long show and it's going to be something where we can record several of them in a day and produce it regularly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the way it's going to be done.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think you guys will get a kick out of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is going to be myself, DarkSakura, and Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki is, of course, always welcome whenever he wants to come on, but he's got other stuff he's got to do, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Dan, of course, is going to add a whole new element, especially when we tell you more about what it's about.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll be great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Breakman in the chat says, Xbox Live Indie Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those devs need to call OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: So please, again, get in touch with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob at OrangeLawnsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who wants to be first?
[SPEAKER_06]: and let's see Misty about Tiny Tower in chat says hey protest burning might be funny once anyway at least I do agree it would be nice to see them do like a little more with some of the events and so forth but the game is still early in its life and I'm sure there'll be update patches and so forth now that's iOS gaming done well I'm gonna tell you what iOS game blows
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely blows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Capcom Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: You check this out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Capcom Arcade, you can play classic Capcom Arcade games like 1942 and, I don't know, what else is in the... Ghosts and Goblins and Street Fighter and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can play those.
[SPEAKER_06]: The deal is you can play like three games...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and I was like the music kept going so I knew that the emulation was still running but the game itself just froze and I was like did anybody fucking test this or did they just decide to just put this shit out and see who'd buy it because it seemed to me like option B so yet another strike from Capcom this week that Capcom Arcade needs to be tested better it sucks
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's my iOS talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get back into some other news.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we'll do some long news with Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, and since we were talking a little bit about Capcom, and they made an errant judgment, if you will, back with Resident Evil Mercenaries, where they said, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to make it impossible for you to erase your game to save.
[SPEAKER_08]: And everybody was pissed, and hopefully we figured that maybe people learned by that lesson.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pac-Man and Galaga Dimensions from Namco also features a problem where your save files are permanent and unable to be reset or erased.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, they put this out, and according to Wired's Game Life blog,
[SPEAKER_08]: There's simply no way to erase a save once it's been written to the cartridge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've looked all over, even going as far as to ask a Namco Bandai representative, and it doesn't seem like there's a way to erase a save game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um, you know, basically saying that the design doesn't just affect earned in-game awards, which can't be deleted, but also high scores, meaning that the most recent high score is the only one that the game records.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, though, Namco, they have come to an explanation for it, and they're saying that... Here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pac-Man Tilt.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says the plus high score from the EX Level 1.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says it needs to open 10 medals.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't really see what the high scores are here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Score ranking keeps one of each of the top scores mentioned above to submit to online ranking boards.
[SPEAKER_08]: It keeps the gamer's name in which the player can input via on-screen keyboard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it doesn't really say why they did that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just shows how it's affected.
[SPEAKER_08]: They said they confirmed that players have the option to share high scores online, but using the same cartridge in different DS main posts to score twice.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Namco Bandai didn't comment on the decision-making process behind it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like no decision was made.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sounds like just bad design again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, other than, you know, it says, but they were the copy, Capcom's response would say that it was an attempt to preserve the game's arcade-style feel and it would never do it again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm, you know, here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 3DS, okay, you've got very little penetration for the 3DS out there right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you really need to hinder sales of any game on that system?
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, Pac-Man and Galaga Dimensions, I don't know about you, but that's not really at the top of my list of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they're great on Xbox Live Arcade, and it sounds like that's where they're going to remain great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but it's just like, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: You thought that was a good idea?
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing that concerns me here, I mean, and I would say, I might have been interested in these games if the price was right, but again, this whole save file thing, I can't support this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The excuse they're giving just fucking doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're really talking us in circles.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they didn't really have an excuse.
[SPEAKER_08]: They gave no excuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: This concerns me because we have two companies that have made the same mistake that's very fishy.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's the whole used game market, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's really fishy to me that we have two companies that have now done this.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do understand people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is this a trend?
[SPEAKER_08]: This isn't going to stop you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, yeah, it will stop used game sales.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know how it's going to stop used game sales or at least hinder it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop new game sales?
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, because people aren't going to buy the new game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if you're going to buy a game, which, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: GameStop may decide, hey, you know what, we're not going to take it back because you can't erase a save game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Granted, they haven't made the decision permanently so far.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did at one time with Resident Evil where they said, oh, we're not going to take it back, and then they changed that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, if they do this, then, you know, a consumer that realizes, you know what, I'm going to play this game for a while, then I'm probably going to get sick of it, and I'm going to sell it and get some money for something else...
[SPEAKER_08]: If they can't sell it back, they may not buy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just skip buying that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll wait until another game comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just... It's dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really a dumb idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: And why you should be limited... Why even at all games should be saved to the carts that they're on instead of your system?
[SPEAKER_08]: Your 3DS, which has a goddamn SD card in it,
[SPEAKER_08]: everyone comes with one not even something you have to buy separately like on most PSPs and you can save to that I don't understand why you can't do that that's stupid you know with the DS it made sense because there was no saving whatsoever to the system there was no storage of any sort whatsoever but this is the 3DS come on jump into the century where you know what we can store data to these cards
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like Namco could have heard what Capcom did and then made the decision.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both of these companies made this conscious decision to design the saves this way months ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that is weird to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's almost like somebody put them up to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what strikes me as just really weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, I hope this trend stops.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yet again, another game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this one, unlike the Capcom game, this was one I was legitimately like, oh, I really do love Pac-Man Championship Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't mind a portable version of it, you know, if it was like 1999 maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now, nope, not going to do it because I'm not going to support this type of game design.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though I do tend to buy most of my games new, and I don't sell a lot of them back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very rarely do I sell games back.
[SPEAKER_06]: The last game I remember distinctly selling back was Top Spin 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just a handful of GameCube and old first generation Xbox 360 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, more news about the Xbox 360 anyway, since I brought it up there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Free-to-play games apparently are inevitable on the Xbox 360, at least according to one publisher.
[SPEAKER_06]: Todd Harris of Hi-Rez Studios, who makes the game Tribes Ascend.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a multiplayer first-person shooter coming to the PC and hopefully someday the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Todd Harris says quote at least from our conversations both Sony and Microsoft are moving there strategically but there are still some things to be worked out on both the business side and the technical side of the certification side that's a tongue twister regarding frequency of patches
[SPEAKER_06]: Those issues just need further advancement before we would be comfortable putting a release timeframe on the console version.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not the case of never, but we know all those things we can handle on the PC, so that's why PC is first.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I remember hearing something about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doesn't Microsoft limit you to the number of patches you're able to do within the release?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you have to pay for that or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe that's why, because free-to-play games...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, that's the sad part.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, and Breakman comments in our chatroom at chat.org.com Xbox has already had free-to-play games.
[SPEAKER_06]: One versus 100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Too bad it didn't last.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: One versus 100 wasn't an MMO per se, but it was a free-to-play game, sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Microsoft-backed, for one, but everybody, well, at least a lot of people I know miss it dearly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a freemium game, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know, though, that Marvel's MMO is going to be free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, I remember hearing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: With Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not going to be on 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be a PC game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but still.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week you guys email us at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we read your emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Live here on air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I gotta say this live.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is really funny, just live.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had a little net split live.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you've ever been in IRC, you know what a net split is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess Loki's on one side of the net split and I'm on another.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I could see that Loki just left the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's me on an island with Black Wolf and Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and everybody's back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, just reconnected.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, internets.
[SPEAKER_06]: You never cease to amaze me.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, mailbag that thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we got two.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to double check and see if we got any more real quick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope, just two.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the first one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just wondering, do you know of any smaller Xbox controllers?
[SPEAKER_10]: The current ones are so big, and the way the buttons are situated, I can only play for about 10 minutes because I also have arthritis.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's really irritating as I bought Dragon Age 2, but haven't been able to really progress because I can't really do the attacks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the ones I can do really bother my hands.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks, Holly D. Well, they all come with a smaller...
[SPEAKER_10]: Out of the bag, broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: What about like, I mean, I know she might be thinking smaller, but what about thinking bigger?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like what about an arcade stick?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what my suggestion was.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have, I've had hand surgery twice on my right hand.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it gets really stiff really easily and my fingers will lock up because I still need to have one of the finger worked on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, like, for example, I can play Dragon Age 2 just fine because I use my thumb and forefinger for a lot of stuff and neither of those are ones that have problems.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I cannot play fighting games very well because I'm moving so fast and my hand will start cramping up.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what I found is that using the joystick, you know, like we have the tournament stick and we've got the Xbox joystick, which you can probably find at a used game store somewhere for cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no problem so something like that will work a situation like that is tough too because you really need to get your no pun intended you need to get your hands on a controller to actually try it before you buy it so I would really suggest you head out to something where they tend to have those things out for you to try like maybe Best Buy I know Fry's but they're more west coast Fry's always seems to have that kind of stuff out at least the arcade sticks but I know they don't have those everywhere
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully there's a store near you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe even an independent store might be a way to go where they would have some of that stuff out for you to try it and see how your hand takes to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, speaking of the controllers they have out at Fry's, they have a six-button PlayStation controller that's third-party but supported by Sony that's super comfortable.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, maybe see how that likes and then see if the same distributor makes another pad like it because I found that to be really comfortable and it was just a six-button fighting stick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was playing Super Street Fighter 4 with it at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was that email.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the last one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just two quick unrelated questions.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, is there an online multiplayer game that varies the audio of voice chat or availability of text chat based on proximity?
[SPEAKER_10]: A character closer to you would sound louder, while players across the map couldn't be heard at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't gotten my feet wet with it, but I suggest World of Warcraft would do something like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it does.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does not.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the voice chat that's built into WoW kind of has a reputation for sucking.
[SPEAKER_06]: They tried to build it so that people wouldn't have to get what's called Ventrilo servers or TeamSpeak some people use.
[SPEAKER_06]: But folks tend to rely on the Ventrilo servers.
[SPEAKER_10]: With characters though?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, your proximity does change with NPCs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but... If your sound drivers will support it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, but not other people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he's thinking like a person-to-person game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what game comes to mind to me for some reason is Halo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't Halo do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or specifically Halo 2 and Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but he says a character.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's not saying... Oh, he said a character.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, WoW does that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, WoW does that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um... WoW will also pan left to right, depending on your sound card.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: I know that area noises in Portal 2, and also the loudspeaker in Portal 2, based on where you are, the loudspeaker will project a different way depending on the texture of the walls and where you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you remember that?
[SPEAKER_10]: So the echo will be different.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and when you're talking to, I don't care, spoilers, it's been out already.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you're talking to Potatoes through the glass wall, she's a little quieter than when you're actually right in front of her.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, a lot more games are doing that, but really a lot of it also has to do with your sound card and playing stereo versus mono.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the second question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Real quick, Tiger Call on our chatroom says, they still use Ventrilo?
[SPEAKER_06]: Ventrilo harassment comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I've seen those YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: For the record, on Star Trek Online, which by the way also does the distance based, I use TeamSpeak.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't do any of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like Ventrilo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ventrilo for Ragnarok For the record, I do prefer Ventrilo versus TeamSpeak
[SPEAKER_10]: What tense is used in phrases such as will have happened?
[SPEAKER_10]: Future Perfect
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll have happened.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you're referring to anything that is a future event happening, but in that future point where it has already happened, it's future perfect.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought we were a video game show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, he asked.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know this shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's from Robert M. What?
[SPEAKER_06]: add it for the emails then?
[SPEAKER_06]: yeah if you want to get in on the email bag mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com but now's the part of the show where we could rant about lack of emails if we would like CFU's of the week
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, you know, I did have one at the beginning of the show, and now for the life of me, I can't remember what it is, so... Fuck you to not remembering.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know the memory's the first thing you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um... Fuck you to Whole Foods for being too damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go to Sunflower instead.
[SPEAKER_09]: All the same stuff, and it's cheaper.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some big cheese wheels that I really wanted to buy.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're probably like $300.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like me my parm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really have a whole lot of FUs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Things are pretty good otherwise.
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to weekends not being three days long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll do something a little silly like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's get back into some news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Haha, I'm not able to say that FU.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a 3D weekend this weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, let's talk about some more retarded DRM.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm saying that because it's Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Ubisoft learned their lesson with the always-on DRM that they had with Assassin's Creed and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no, they're back with the always-on Assassin's Creed-type DRM for Driver San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, the PC version will require a permanent internet connection.
[SPEAKER_08]: No word if that's going to be loosened or not, like it was with Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_08]: or I believe Prince of Persia was the other game that used that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, the console version has the stupid Uplay Passport now, the one-time use code that will unlock multiplayer access.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: I get to play some multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_08]: How generous of you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, FromDust is getting the Ubisoft DRM as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then, to kind of add a little bit of the icing on top of their stupid cake, they have come out and said that, guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Our Always On DRM is a success!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a success in pissing everyone off!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, it says, Ubisoft has seen the clear reduction in piracy of our titles, which required a persistent online connection.
[SPEAKER_08]: And from that point of view, the requirement is success.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because everyone went further underground to get around your DRM.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they really think that people aren't going to find a way around it again?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what exactly is considered success because...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, less people are pirating your game.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: The number of people pirating your game before versus the number of people pirating your game now that you say it's reduced, does that actually equal out to more sales?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because those two numbers are independent of each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have nothing to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, whether people are interested in downloading your game or not, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone may not have been interested in downloading Assassin's Creed 2 on PC or Splinter Cell Conviction on PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe they just didn't want to pirate the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ever think of that?
[SPEAKER_08]: And not to mention, though, that the previous games, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: The DRM was hacked within a few weeks anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I wouldn't exactly go out and shout at the top of your lungs that it's a great success.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because all you're really doing is affecting the people that legitimately buy the game and now they want to play it offline or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say you take your laptop with you and you want to play it at...
[SPEAKER_06]: A friend's house or something and you don't have open wifi Or say you're a serviceman overseas serving our country and you want to play a game to relax on your break Can't do it Thanks Ubisoft So Yeah, it's stupid How is that a success?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's offensive The only people that this hurts is the people who bought the game legitimately That's who this hurts Pirates will still get their game and you're an idiot if you don't think they won't
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: So, who's going to win in that?
[SPEAKER_08]: The pirates, because they don't have your crappy DRM anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's this about?
[SPEAKER_06]: They denied the rumored cracks?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, this was back in March.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had, of course, their new DRM, and I want to say it was for... I'm trying to remember which game it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: It wasn't... Maybe it was Assassin's Creed 2, but there was another game that they had coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess they...
[SPEAKER_08]: Pirated copies of various PC games from Ubisoft are apparently making the rounds online, sparking allegations that the DRM has already been defeated.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ubisoft spokesman reported to Edge stating, "...this rumor is false, and while the pirated version may seem to be complete at startup, any gamer who downloads and plays the cracked version will find that the version is not complete."
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, not completing the fact that you don't get, I don't know what it was that they didn't get access to, but it was something really stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, oh, you don't get access to our wonderful customer service.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't get the Uplay features.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
Woosh!
[SPEAKER_08]: You've just thrown gasoline on the fire, you dumbass!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, speaking of adding fuel to the fire, there's obviously a lot of pissed off people that Mega Man Legends 3 got cancelled.
[SPEAKER_06]: What does the internet love?
[SPEAKER_06]: Petitions!
[SPEAKER_06]: So, an activist group has called themselves 100,000 strong for bringing back Mega Man Legends 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: they're trying to get 100,000 members and they are trying to get them all on their Facebook page so you can go over there and like them if you are so inclined not exactly they are doing that but there's an actual official petition which you have to do is sign up for the dev room stuff for the Mega Man Legends 3 project and you sign up there and then you go to the forums and you make a comment and a thread well it also wouldn't surprise me if people are just trying to reach out however they can
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's basically that's how they're doing it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I signed up for it and did all that stuff just because, you know, I'd like to play Mega Man Legends 3 and, you know, I'm not going to beg them to release it, but I'll support the movement, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, right now they're up to 36,428, so they're about a third of the way there, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, no word on what happens when they hit 100,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, Capcom hasn't said.
[SPEAKER_08]: Capcom will go, thanks for your support.
[SPEAKER_06]: Capcom will say, wow, that's 100,000 people that are getting this game still.
[SPEAKER_06]: DeadRising2 DeadRising2
[SPEAKER_08]: Tronbon's in there so we love the Mega Man Legends series but there's no Mega Man characters at all so they put in there you know oh there's alternate DLC because Legends never die and neither does like fashion or something like that it's like I know that's literally Capcom giving the finger to that group
[SPEAKER_08]: I really need to find that quote because it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: While you find that, let's go to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he has some more hilarious stuff for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, the Skype line is coming up as well as your Twitter topics in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is, it's kind of, I'm, you know how people are always finding little Easter eggs in games much later after the games have been out?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, sort of like the blowing on the Famicom speaker to make the pulse voice disappear and all that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently Bomberman will eat your dust and lick your crack.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll break your fucking head with a ratchet!
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll break your fucking head with a ratchet!
[SPEAKER_10]: but it has I'm so fucking proud of you I could just shit you should play that one, that one's great if I can find it I am so fucking proud of you I could just shit eat my dust and lick my crack there's like oh my ass and there's one that says I'll slap you down and shit that's right there tits
[SPEAKER_10]: The one after that is a little funnier.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're fucked.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I mean, there's like multiple sounds.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right there, sweet tits.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's right there, tits.
[SPEAKER_10]: You talking to me, shitheel?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, this would be a great soundboard for OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: Talk to the fist because the face is pissed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next time Loki and I get in an argument about Nintendo, DarkSakura could just say, Would you guys cut out this macho shit and hurry up?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't make me come out there and stomp both of your asses.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also like my ass is killing me, I need help.
[SPEAKER_04]: My ass is killing me, I need help.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one after that's funny too.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's really funny in like a second grade way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my ass.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, don't fuck me.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're gonna put out Mega Man Legends 3 after all?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will tell you something about this, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that you could actually go into the sound files in the game and make your own vocal macros for the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I think, I mean, I don't see why this is reported on now, except that, you know, I think it's freaking funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Pop a fucking dirt nap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds kind of like Bugs Bunny saying that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of funny that they made all these really sick things and they were just never found, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the last one.
[SPEAKER_10]: You talking to me, shitheel?
[SPEAKER_00]: You talking to me, shitheel?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no!
[SPEAKER_00]: Fuck me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll break your fucking head with a ratchet.
[SPEAKER_10]: That one's great, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xenicorn chat says, sounds like the Jerky Boys did the audio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_10]: These are the... Well, you know, another game had unused voice clips.
[SPEAKER_10]: And actually, I was reading a little bit more about this.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not a story that kind of has something, you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you know in Portal 2, what's his name that did Cave Johnson?
[SPEAKER_10]: I can never remember his name.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know who he is, but I can never remember his name.
[SPEAKER_06]: The guy from Spider-Man.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: He refused to do certain lines because it sounded too much like a rape scene.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I read that this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I had posted something about it on my Tumblr, but you can find Ellen's lines, who was the voice of GLaDOS and Carolyn, saying, no, I don't want this.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: But there was one line that I wish they would have recorded because I would have loved to hear it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's after she gets put in GLaDOS, says, I'm awake and I'm going to kill you all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I found that actual, that quote, and it was from the DLC for Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, all alternate costumes for Guile, Blanka, Dhalsim, Gen, and Feilong are included in this pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Show everyone that legends never die and never go out of fashion.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to which, you know, the 100,000 strongs for bringing back Maybelline Legends 3 go, seriously?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_06]: And the chat room is lighting up a minute and a half later because of the buffer.
[SPEAKER_06]: J.K.
[SPEAKER_06]: Simmons is who you're trying to think of.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Salacious Pop says he's fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple more stories for you guys and then the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony soon enough will be saying, show me on the doll where they touched you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they actually have patented some creepy looking doll thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know if this was the crying baby out of the PlayStation 3 commercials or what.
[SPEAKER_08]: But apparently the patent was filed back in 2008.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has only recently been publicized.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a plush toy that's packing, I guess, like a wireless receiver.
[SPEAKER_08]: It means for reading storage medium and even a processor along with both USB and Ethernet ports.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would act as some sort of buddy for kids who can pop a disc into their PS3 and have the console communicate with it telling it to act surprised, throw its arms up, or at a certain point, you know, at a certain point during gameplay or viewing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Weird and creepy looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wasn't there a controller like on the Wii for some type of game that was a doll and you put the Wii mode up its butt?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's two games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what this sounds like, kind of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not one game, two games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, actually, it was funny because I think one evolved into the other.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was My Baby and Me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was from 505 Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: and that came out in Europe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that came out over here, but we got Babysitting Mama also developed by the same studio that put out My Baby and Me.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the baby was actually cute and not disturbing looking like that picture.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, to be fair though, it was a holster that you could put on your baby so you could holster the remote that way instead of shoving it up its ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: This thing is kind of creepy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I can see some interesting implementations to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say you jailbreak your PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: The PS3 can send a kill signal to the doll.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they can attack you in your sleep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play fun pranks on all your family.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm reminded of that one Halloween episode of The Simpsons where it was like, I'm Christy the Clown and I'm going to kill you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Little dolly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is creepy though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you play a game that involved a doll as a peripheral Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Would it have to be murder dolls or something like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would have to be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, one more story for you guys, and then we'll get to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is about Connectimals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Guess what was announced?
[SPEAKER_06]: A sequel of sorts to Connectimals.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can think of it as Connectimals Plus, or more formally, Connectimals Now With Bears.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, that is exactly the name of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Connectimals Now With Bears.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have to throw them onto a trampoline?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyhow, you can download the download content for $15 or there will be a new retail release called Connectables.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now with bears!
[SPEAKER_06]: Grr.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: That does it for the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is open now at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can call us right now and we will talk about whatever you want to talk about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any news stories tonight or what have you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Meanwhile, while we wait for some calls, let's go to the Twitter and get some tweets to read here in between waiting for some phone calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I've got another screen capture.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to put it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, what'd you find?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do I want to know?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a couple of bears.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, probably gay bears, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: They have ears.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wearing assless chaps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they have cute little ears.
[SPEAKER_06]: CD Thunder CD Thunder
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a couple things I want to discuss.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: The two newest games that are out, Duke Nukem Forever and L.A.
[SPEAKER_07]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, what about them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'd like to start with the Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, first off, yeah, I agree with what you're saying, that the graphics aren't really that great.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Duke still has its...
[SPEAKER_07]: um sarcasm that's made it that's made the games great over the years and and only in this could and only in this game could you kick a monster's eyeball and consider it a field goal so you kind of like the potty humor in it I mean there's no shame in that potty humor's funny once in a while I do like the wall boobs there you go I mean I but what about what's up with the girls giving him a blowjob in the very beginning because he's Duke and
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and they're acting, in the game, they're acting like he's actually playing it, and he's got the controller and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because what they're trying to do is, like, imagine this is you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Hot Chick's giving you a BJ while you're playing this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that awesome?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I actually wouldn't mind that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Point made.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's some pre-order bonus right there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_07]: I like how it's set in the 40s and everything with all the classic cars and everything, but it's not really set.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can tell it's not a complete 40s game because they usually don't use that language, all the F words and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But besides that, it looks really fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the F is for fun in this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, forget it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, this game's... The thing is... If you like the toilet humor in Duke Nukem Forever, my understanding is that you get full-on beaver in L.A.
[SPEAKER_06]: Noire.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, it might be a dead chick, but still...
[SPEAKER_07]: I like how it integrates where you have to interview the person and you have to figure out on your own if they're lying or if they're acting doubtful or if they're flat out telling a lie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and from what I understand in the game, when you guess correct, or like, you know, you have to guess if they're telling the truth or lying, and then a little chime sounds, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what they should do is they should, instead of, like, just a dumb little chime that should sound, you should get rewarded with more pussy shots.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you get it wrong, you have to look at that bear picture that DarkSakura just posted.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you're not, they should just, like, edit it, like, have a little blur there or something, maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: there you go alright well anything else on your mind tonight CD Thunder oh let's see what other games are on your radar to play soon
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't actually played those two I just mentioned I was just looking at playthroughs of them but I haven't been able to listen to you guys lately because I've been working but I'm glad I've been able to tonight you guys have made my evening and rock on don't forget there is always the podcast you can take us with you in your pocket every week
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you say something?
[SPEAKER_06]: I couldn't hear you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, just plug in the podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_06]: OrangeLawnsRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: More information.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can take us in your pocket with you and listen to us whenever you want, not just Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, CD Thunder, thanks so much for the call, and enjoy the potty humor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hee-hee, poop-poop party.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, let's go to another call since our phone's ringing off the hook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, let me turn down my computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, this is Kai Judo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Kai Judo, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, they had to like fix those dolls because yes, like some girl got their hair caught in it or something, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a lot of girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the news report had me cracking up because like if you're a fan of horror movies, you know, there's always like some type of instruction on how to kill the monster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you know what I'm talking about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so on the news, they actually had instructions on what you would have to do if you caught the Cabbage Patch Doll.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the game you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now it's our turn, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're the last show of the week, so it's our turn, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yogi, like the bear, or the brand of tea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it comes from some type of Japanese saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: It means to read, like it's supposed to read your opponent's mind or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has some kind of mystical...
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to Google this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Google Yomi and the website is Serling Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it Yomi?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yomi, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, not Yogi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking Yogi Bear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Yomi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The guy who invented it, he's some type of high-ranking street fighter player.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's done a few of those, whatever the hell you call them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, this looks kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm looking at all the cards.
[SPEAKER_06]: The artwork looks very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's surlingames.com apparently sells this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Japanese word for reading and reading the mind of your opponent.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a competitive card game that simulates a battle between two characters.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a fighting game, but a card game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what I like about it best is it's not technically a trading card game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a set amount of cards that you get
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like you don't have to collect any more cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: There aren't any like rare cards that you have to go out looking for and spending tons of money on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a complete card game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what else is interesting about this is that I noticed every card has traditional card stamps on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the dodge card can substitute as a three of hearts and the flame arrow is a jack of spades.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like that's, that's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, every character is a deck you can actually use as a deck of playing cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: It comes with a complete, I guess, what is it, 52 playing cards in the deck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so that's pretty much the game in a nutshell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's a download version that you can, I think it's like $14.95.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get that, it's called Print and Play, where I guess you just print it out from your printer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get little card sleeves and you can play it that way, or you can go the super expensive route and get it for like $100 to complete the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'll take the cheap route.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but I did the math on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to take up all your time, but I did the math on it because it looked pretty expensive.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when you do the math on it, like if you buy the deck separately, each deck comes with two characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're getting like two decks of playing cards, and that's like $24 in change.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you bought them loosely, you'll actually be paying a little bit more than what you would for the full game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not entirely...
[SPEAKER_06]: you know what though, 100 bucks doesn't seem so bad when you consider how much I spent on magic back in the day and the website to play it online free, I'll put it in the chat room but you need to try that that I can do, free, I like that word you should have started with that alright, Kaishudo, thanks so much for the call and for the heads up on a new game alright, later I want to do tweets but we keep getting calls and I definitely want to hear what the callers have to say hi, you're on Orange Silence Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: Happier thoughts?
[SPEAKER_03]: Video games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Take our mind off of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good lord, video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried getting back into some games that I passed over because I wasn't sure how far their reach would be.
[SPEAKER_03]: But since I've been on YouTube for the past two months almost non-stop, I finally decided to try out both of the Defense of the Ancient Clones, League of Legends, and Heroes of New Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: League of Legends, yep, I know those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it depends on the time of day you're there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially, it seems like these games took off more in Europe than they did here.
[SPEAKER_03]: So while you're still getting European players, everything's calm.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're in a newbie room and there are actually newbies playing and if there's more experienced players actually trying to help the people learn.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the moment the afternoon comes up and all the US comes up
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty much like, get the hell out you noob left and right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I hate that shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish games had a better structure for noobs how to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know one game I randomly played this week I forgot to mention in my top of the week was StarCraft 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just randomly was like, I want to play Star Jeweled again because I love the Star Jeweled add-on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That made that game ten times better.
[SPEAKER_06]: And part of me was like, I should learn how to play real StarCraft and then go online and play.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then I'm like...
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm too scared, because there's nobody like me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody that plays StarCraft Online is already really good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's pretty much the truth.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried getting back into a game here, and of course I'm still in the Bronze League, but now Bronze League is quite seasoned, so you really have no hope.
[SPEAKER_03]: You gotta play your buddies, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's about the only way to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about some of the upcoming Defense of the Ancients?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like there's a Blizzard DOTA coming to StarCraft 2, speaking of which, and then we have actual DOTA 2 from Valve soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not holding my breath.
[SPEAKER_03]: The game is not going to change at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's going to play almost exactly the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even like with Heroes of New Earth and League of Legends, the only thing they really change is the functionality of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And switching from one to the other is painful.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get set up for the way one game works and it messes you up for the other.
[SPEAKER_03]: You pretty much got to pick your flavor and stick with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So who do you think will walk away victorious at the end of the day?
[SPEAKER_06]: Blizzard, Valve, or one of these other games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope they all drop, to tell you the truth.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to work on something more original.
[SPEAKER_03]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I told that to a Blizzard headhunter while I was in school.
[SPEAKER_03]: I called him out on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, why does Warcraft 3 play like Warcraft 2 and Starcraft?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, everybody was in there like, ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they sell gazillions.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why they all play the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it's the same damn game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I heard he actually wanted to talk to me after the...
[SPEAKER_03]: after the headhunter briefing he was doing at the school, but I think I already left in disgust, so I didn't get a chance to give it to him directly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows, I might have missed that on the job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, good luck.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope maybe you'll get a second shot with Blizzard at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't mention that all the games are the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I got one final thing for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Has anybody seen the Comic-Con coverage for the Star Wars MMO?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not extensively.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't been really watching this carefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of just waiting for when the game gets really closer to release.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I know a lot did come out of Comic-Con.
[SPEAKER_03]: Based off what I saw, because they showed the first part of an instance adventure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And any WoWhead that played this game, I don't think you're really going to see any difference.
[SPEAKER_03]: Based off what I saw in the video, I mean, it's up on YouTube now.
[SPEAKER_03]: But based off that footage, you still have the same tropes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You still have the same player classes, the same structure.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about what Star Wars laid over it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was really hoping for a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where can I find that video?
[SPEAKER_03]: YouTube.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll see if I can dig up the link for you and put it in chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do that for me and I'll check it out here in a minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much all I had.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd say wait until you see more footage on the game before you make a decision to do the initial investment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll see how much it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I definitely won't get that collector's edition, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially if they cut the price as fast as they did on Rift.
[SPEAKER_06]: I definitely have no excuse not to check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but this LucasArts stuff, they're not cutting that price anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, Xenocore, we're going to let you go, buddy, so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, I'll dig into that link for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks, bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game Addict 20 killed by deep vein thrombosis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently a 20-year-old died from a blood clot because he played his Xbox for up to 12 hours at a time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And his parents, of course, were stunned by it, saying, quote, As a parent, you think playing computer games can't do them any harm because you know what they are doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kids all over the country are playing these games for long periods.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't realize it could kill them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, 12 hours at a time though?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just excessive.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was not a good way to do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the parents not interfering and saying, hey, you need to slack off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or maybe your kid was obsessive and you should have put a stop to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That too.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's see, going on to more tweets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ramaditya Knight tweets us saying, Hi OLR, have any of you played Action 52 for the NES?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is another one of those multi-cart games, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think I have.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me look it up real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see what this is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does that sound familiar, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know a lot of the old school stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I never played multi-carts.
[SPEAKER_08]: I recognize a lot of the names just from ROM sets, but I haven't really played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why bother playing a multi-cart when you can play the actual game?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am actually looking at the multi-card.
[SPEAKER_06]: It did come out in 91 and then it was also out in 93 for Genesis consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: They say a lot of the titles had major glitches in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me get to the next call and we'll talk more about this in a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Sterlok, what's up, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just wanted to say well-played Nintendo, well-played.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, I was hoping somebody would call in on this.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you think about all this Nintendo news this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's both, you can tell, you know, they were desperate because the 3DS hasn't really been selling well because they really should have waited like another year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or at least tell the holidays.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But at the same time, the way they did it was just fucking genius because everybody wins.
[SPEAKER_01]: People who have waited, which is probably a lot of people because people are waiting for your actual games to come out and for a price drop.
[SPEAKER_01]: And people who have already bought the system
[SPEAKER_01]: They're getting 20 free games and some exclusive stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's good for everybody.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, it's really good for Nintendo because they've really made sure by doing this that the 3DS is probably going to end up being the number one Christmas gift this year with the price drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I could see, though, to be fair, as much as I pretty much agree with you on all these points, to be fair, I could see where somebody could still be pissed off at Nintendo because maybe these 20 games, maybe Virtual Console just isn't really interesting to them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, you know, they already bought them all on the Wii, so they don't really want them on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of like, $80?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that's still a steep cut.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe getting free stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, they could have just gone, eh, yeah, we're not going to
[SPEAKER_01]: We're not going to throw you a bone.
[SPEAKER_01]: And look at Apple.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just the price of being an early adopter.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's not even just with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's with games in general.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, Loki just mentioned the price of Duke Nukem Forever dropped already.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game is maybe two months old.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't get nothing for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: No free hats for being an early adopter.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, this is just the nature of the beast.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I think it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought it was brilliant that they put the spin on it that they did because yeah it was a desperate act but it's going to I think it's really going to save them in the long run because you know like eventually like well the like the DS launch was kind of shitty too
[SPEAKER_01]: That didn't have very many good games for a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: But look at it now.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing it had going for most of all was the Mario 64 port that was on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now it's the best-selling handheld, like, pretty much ever.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like the original Game Boy, but it's doing well.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, well, any other thoughts on your mind tonight before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll crack your head with a fucking ratchet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gee, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish I still had that soundboard up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have played something in response to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on our Tumblr.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, I don't have the Tumblr up.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, that's going to do it for the calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to get through the rest of these tweets.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys for calling tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry if you didn't get through, but you can always send us an email, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com, or you might be able to get a last-minute tweet in real quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at the suggested retail of Action 52, $200.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it really was, I guess, like 52 different games that were in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were all different games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure they were all shitty.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, one of them, I guess, crashes right when you start it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Going on to more tweets here at Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: MNZiba tweets us about, you know, we were talking earlier in the show about WTF Battleship.
[SPEAKER_06]: She tweeted us the Monopoly parody movie trailer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I want to play this whole thing, but we can start in the beginning here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Richie Benjamin never followed in his father's footsteps until one day when all that changed.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is where your father left you.
[SPEAKER_08]: A board game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks a lot, Dad.
[SPEAKER_06]: He threw all the houses on the ground and then of course the house shook.
[SPEAKER_00]: In a world where money matters...
[SPEAKER_08]: You lost, kid?
[SPEAKER_00]: Who are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: For the first time in his life, Richie is taking a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to teach you all about the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And rolling the dice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's got strippers.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is already better than the Battleship trailer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Never fall in love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless it's with money.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a community chest.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I love her.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Love her more than money?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't care what you think.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because now I have the monopoly.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, son, don't you know?
[SPEAKER_00]: Only I can win this game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do not pass out.
[SPEAKER_00]: You didn't pay the luxury tax.
[SPEAKER_00]: Go to jail.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do not collect $200.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should screen that at midnight at the shadiest looking theater in town.
[SPEAKER_06]: After Rocky Horror, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft tweets us something that somehow we missed in our news feed tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Age got removed from Steam because of DLC issues.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically EA has a lot of sand in their vagina and it basically has to do with Origin.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I guess what they're saying is it has to do with the whole...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's that whole thing where Steam wants to control the download stuff, but EA really wants that in their own house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Herpaderp.
[SPEAKER_06]: EA says, Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Age is a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, Dartituya is tweeting us saying, WonderCon 2012 moved from San Francisco to Anaheim just for the next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, that's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Wondercon New York Comic Con
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, but they're saying now, there are some updates saying nothing has actually been confirmed about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess Anaheim is in discussion right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's don't freak out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, maybe it's don't freak out yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkTetsuya is saying, wonder what the holdup was for the worldwide release of La Mulana?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Germany!
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess La Mulana has been held up for release in Germany.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Trying to read here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ratings board of Germany, the USK, Nigoro, who developed the game, submitted the game for review to the ESRB, the OFLC, and the USK two months ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other two boards have the game ready to go, but the USK has not finished yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they can't release it until it gets reviewed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry, Joe.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you're a big fan of La Mulana.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spazinator giving us an update on the PS3 saga.
[SPEAKER_06]: I sent my PS3 in for repairs this past Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: I figure that I'm likely to get it back early next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We will see.
[SPEAKER_06]: SSJ100Matt tweets us saying, The only way to defeat China is to attack their productivity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Coming soon to China.
[SPEAKER_06]: Angry birds.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Angry Birds is coming to China.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess in order to prevent knockoffs and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was officially launched in May through a partnership with Chinese mobile games network Downjoy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But so far there's been all these knockoffs and pirated versions on jailbroken iPhones.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now Rovio has teamed up with the ad network Madhouse to try and expand the game's presence.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still say Angry Birds isn't really all that and I don't understand why so many people are so losing their shit over it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_06]: TigerClaw sends us a tweet here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Samsung is going to be manufacturing the PlayStation Vita CPU.
[SPEAKER_06]: The core processing unit or central processing unit of Samsung's upcoming portable will be, excuse me, by Sony's upcoming portable will be done by Samsung.
[SPEAKER_06]: These are from Samsung.
[SPEAKER_06]: These are from online reports out of Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was on the website of Japanese industry paper, the Semiconductor Industry News.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot of further context besides just that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Samsung will play a role in the actual development of the Vita.
[SPEAKER_06]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to get in your tweets in the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, did you hear about the last sales reports on smartphones?
[SPEAKER_10]: Motorola's dipped way down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blackberry's going out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all Androids and iPhones now.
[SPEAKER_10]: The top three is Apple, Samsung, and Nokia.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think BlackBerrys are still big in the corporate world.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've gone way down.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not in the top three.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, before we close out the show tonight, I've got to go to Loki and ask if there's any last-minute stories he wants to tear through.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: We covered quite a bit of everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess so.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll work on more last-minute stories for next week, but I guess we've covered everything so far tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you think we missed a topic, you can always email us, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com, and we'll bring it up on next week's show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys, of course, as always, for downloading our show and supporting Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, we do the show for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't play commercials.
[SPEAKER_06]: All we really ask, help spread the word about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get more butts in our chat room on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell a friend about the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if you're like, I don't really know who I could tell about Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Help spread the word on websites.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's people that put signatures on forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: or just as simple as leaving a five-star review in iTunes really goes a long way because that drives the popularity rankings and helps us get exposure to more people.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's been some reports on the internet this week that I've seen come up on Google Plus and all that of people linking stories saying, podcasting is dying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, to that I say...
[SPEAKER_06]: because maybe corporate podcasting is dying but people like us were never really in it for the money anyways and we were doing this since before podcasting we're not going away anytime soon we're awesome sauce but we can still use every piece of word of mouth we can get and we'll continue to provide this show for your work day and whatever else so there you go but we can't have call it a show until we get around and get everybody's final thoughts so Dark Sakura what's your final thought tonight
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we're going to miss Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, this makes me sad, but we'll do it another time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I would like to do a tiny little plug.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look on Geek Life tomorrow, geek-life.com for a special Geeks in History that has to do with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: A Nintendo geek in history.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, your last minute story tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have any last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fortunately, today is both very sad and kind of happy tomorrow, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sad because it is the two-year anniversary of the twins' death, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_08]: We lost two babies two years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: However happy news though, Josh's first birthday is tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: So happy birthday to Josh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never realized it was in such close proximity to each other.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, everything is on the 31st of the 1st.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, looking forward to Josh's first birthday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm looking forward to seeing pictures of the mess he's going to make.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we've already fed him that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is there anything like Extifer's nephew in that party?
[SPEAKER_08]: We actually had professional pictures taken of him and he's eating a cupcake and that was funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_10]: We had a picture of my brother Matthew when he was, one, sitting in his high chair with a cake in front of him and half the cake demolished by...
[SPEAKER_10]: Smash, smash, smash, smash!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there's a picture like that of me out there somewhere, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll never see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's having his birthday party next Saturday.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a pork-themed party.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we all have a little piggy cake then.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do want the leftovers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tomorrow we're taking him to... At least I do, maybe not DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're taking him to the Galleria to go on the merry-go-round.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: And maybe have some ice cream.
[SPEAKER_06]: my final thought tonight is there may not be time for Pinkberry but there's always time for tacos yes that's going to do it for another episode of Orange Laundry thanks again for tuning in and spending your day with us your past three hours or what have you we really appreciate it and guess what we're going to do it all again next week goodnight
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_05]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!