[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight, July 17th, 2011, another company is set to charge for online passes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could an old MMO be coming to the PS Vita?
[SPEAKER_07]: And PopCap Games finds a buyer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is July 17th, episode 420 of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just kind of leave that over there and let the jokes write themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are here to talk about video games on the show where every gamer has a voice and you can join us live every week, Sunday nights, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern at All Games Radio, right after the Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.allgames.com My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you with my co-hosts First off, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers Hey, how's it going, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I'm allergic So wasted
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm high on coffee right now that DarkSakura brewed for me before the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a special blend.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I make excellent coffee.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will tell everybody, it's half hazelnut, half chocolate macadamia, which is decaf.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then marijuana.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: A teaspoon of Hershey's cocoa and a little bit of cinnamon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is coffee going to make me fat?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because keep in mind, cocoa does not really have any sugar in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is regular, like, the can of cocoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this an episode of Orange Lawns Radio or am I watching, like, Cooking with Paula Deen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you are from the South, after all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: That woman is frightening.
[SPEAKER_03]: This woman... What's your problem with Paula Deen?
[SPEAKER_03]: They photoshop her anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just, she just likes butter.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, okay, look at every magazine cover and advertisement that she's on.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's always...
[SPEAKER_10]: This one, same smile.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like they take different pictures of her and just plaster the same face on her in Photoshop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was looking through my Facebook pictures not that long ago and I had kind of a similar smile in a lot of my pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I tend to do that whole like, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're not Photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're right, I'm not Photoshopped.
[SPEAKER_04]: To look like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm naturally that beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: She looks like a wax sculpture.
[SPEAKER_04]: She looks like she belongs in, what is it, Madame Trousseau's House of Wax or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But her sculpture would be made out of butter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe butter is a good preservative.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, look, we gotta also say hello to the one and only Techmaster, Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know Loki knows a thing or two about cooking with butter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's the best way to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So how are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your dinner of choice tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: The listeners are dying to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pepperoni pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pepperoni pizza, good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: I ate some.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just craving pizza the other day because, well, we were talking about pizza and I was like, hmm, I want pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to our chat room at chat.orangelandreda.com You guys can always join us and have your say in what's going on on this program Starting off with Breakman tonight Obviously the chatters are making their own little jokes about this being episode 420 And Breakman says, most podcasts don't last this many episodes You know, not to sound cocky, but you're right, a lot don't I mean, granted
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: There's definitely some that have made it there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any show that can get past 50 is a great accomplishment, if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes dedication to get that far daily, weekly, no matter what you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're happy to be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys for joining us in chat every week, as you always do, whether you're high or not, to be listening to this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys for always supporting us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a wonderful, wonderful feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still having some warm fuzzies coming off of Under Sedation Live, which is another program here at All Games Radio on Saturday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was a guest on their 10th anniversary special, which aired last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for those that don't know, that was a show I was on before Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura was a guest many, many times.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can go back and check out the archives of that show over at their website.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, it was a lot of fun to just sit in on that, just like good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some folks that were listening to it said...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: I played WoW but really only to do my dailies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two more days and I'll be at another 150 marks in the damn world tree.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the whole new Fireland patch they put in that gave some good single player content.
[SPEAKER_10]: One item level away from being able to do Firelands.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: So hopefully I can get one more good purple item and I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also played a lot of Peggle on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just out of pure boredom and that, and every so often when I need something brainless to do, I play Peggle I also, what was it I was playing on Steam?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was playing actually some more Droplets Because it's, again, another thing that I can kind of not really think about while I play And I'm not really all that great at it anyway, but it's kind of fun And then I played, crap, what else was it I was playing?
[SPEAKER_10]: PS2 One is better.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Are those initial D-games on PS3 kind of faithful to the arcade?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's exactly like the one we have at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have to know a lot of Japanese to play those games?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_10]: However... Because I'm not very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there like translations on game FAQs?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Dan has an FAQ and it even has the whole story mode translated and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: But when he got it, he didn't have any of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And thankfully, I could read just enough of it that I could say, okay, this one means you want to replay this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but you had a couple years of Japanese in college, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I had just enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, I read like a retarded five-year-old in Japanese, so I had just enough in me that I could say, okay, that's what that says, that's what that says.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then we sort of figured out, because I could read like half of some of the kanji in the tracks, so I was like, okay, that one's Irohazaka, that one's, you know, Akina, that one, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to say this in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Dark Tetsuya's in there saying, Rob, you mean Eurobeat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I called it techno.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, the thing about Initial D especially is it has a very unique style of music that plays in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've never heard Initial D music before, it sounds something like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't that make you want to run over people?
[SPEAKER_10]: You've been in the car with me, driving to L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: While you're going 105 miles an hour, it is frightening.
[SPEAKER_10]: In my old Lancer?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, now we had Dan driving, and guess what he wanted to listen to?
[SPEAKER_10]: Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is something about Eurobeat that makes you go faster.
[SPEAKER_10]: Emo Para Emo Para?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's goth dancing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Exactly, but Para...
[SPEAKER_04]: Now see, I'm a little partial to the music in Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune because it's not really Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more like just, I don't know what you, techno.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's racing music.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just makes me want to drive fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what my song in that game is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, kind of trance.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it Destination Blackout?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or that's another Carpool song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then of course there's F-Zero music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh God.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I miss F-Zero so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo, why do you hate me?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I have just loaded you up with old school Bimani Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Including some Parapara.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be skipping that folder.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I put in like a few songs, but I'll also give you some poppin' music stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can get your Desro on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never got into the poppin' music soundtracks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fun to drive to Desro.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, any other games you've been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been playing, apparently I've been playing Kick Dan in his sleep.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you earn points in that game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Whoever wakes up with the most bruises, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and I swam.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a game, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, especially going outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's definitely not a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played just basically two things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Auto, you know, typical stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still playing through ranked death matches and the Battle of Gay Tony and kind of getting back in the groove of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that didn't take me long.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I've already got all my co-workers very frustrated at me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I, of course, played a little bit of Earth Defense Horse Insect Armageddon because it's just awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still kind of grinding my way through that.
[SPEAKER_04]: How long is that game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you beat it in a few hours or is it a long story?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not very long.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot less missions than the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first game had these really stupid missions that kind of repeated themselves almost.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had like 70 missions.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one has 15.
[SPEAKER_05]: But each mission is much longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember how long it took me to beat it, but it wasn't that long.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could probably beat it in 10 hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, not even 10 hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably a lot less than that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: Guess what folder I just found.
[SPEAKER_10]: All of Loki's old mixes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, all the remixes he used to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: He hasn't made a mix in years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we don't want to deviate too much from games right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then yeah so that's basically it was just playing those sweet yeah my gaming week let's see games I've been playing this week I'm still playing Final Fantasy 13 making my way through that I finally beat chapter 11 which I find is the point where most people say this game is awesome or a lot of my friends kind of got to chapter 11 and they're like this game opened up way too much and now some of the monsters can actually kill me I quit but
[SPEAKER_04]: But I found Chapter 11 to be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the trick is, folks, if you're stuck on Chapter 11, don't feel like it's like the rest of the game where you have to fight every monster you come in contact with.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, many are better left avoided until you way level up your characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of those Seath side quests that you can do, you really shouldn't do until towards the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of comparable to Emerald Weapon from Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really weren't supposed to do that until after the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, that was a badass cinematic.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kicked off Chapter 12.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to spoil too much of the story, but you'll figure out pretty quickly who the Eidolons are.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like the Summons.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are all involved in the opening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine Summons mixed with a scene out of Tron Legacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the opening to Chapter 12, and it was so hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to fan myself after it was over.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've gotten to that point, but I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really far in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You would remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an amazing cutscene.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, now I'm at that point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that before the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's way after it opens up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chapter 11 will take you as long as five chapters did from the Kukui stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, maybe because I was wasting my time just doing all the side quests because I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh yeah so that was uh that was you know Final Fantasy 13 I'm probably poured like 40 hours into that now I know I've been talking about that game even though it's like a year and a half old like the past four weeks but I understand I you know can only put so many hours in in a week and I just recently picked it back up again but I'm hoping in the next couple weeks I'll have it beat
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I was playing on the 360, a couple new games that I picked up Best Buy was having a buy one get one sale on Kinect Games So I got a late birthday present from Salacious Pop of Child of Eden Finally got to play that game And Your Self Fitness, I think, is that the Ubisoft fitness game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Your Self Fitness, that's what it's called, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: The most well received of the Kinect Fitness games is the one we got
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be my own bad, but the game also didn't explain it to me very well how I could really make sure I register that on the beat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the good thing is you can play with Kinect or controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: So after playing it a little bit with Kinect, I switched to the controller and played through a couple stages.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I like the controller responsiveness quite a bit more.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the game itself, it's basically Rez, but I'm going to admit I didn't like the music quite as much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that there's more elements to the game, and I think the game is very...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, otherwise, I think as a Kinect game, it's certainly a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's one I would show people.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, that sensitivity, music, firing mechanism thing, I would love if there was like...
[SPEAKER_04]: A clicker or something I could hold in my hand while I'm doing it to allow something tangible that's more precise.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't really know how you would do that, and it kind of takes away from what the Kinect is all about.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know how when you're using the Wiimote, you at least still have a button in your hand?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to say it, but I almost think this game might be a little better with the Wii controls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was just my thoughts on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So then you would probably want to play the PlayStation 3 version with the move controls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the move might actually be better for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, I am very much about I need the precision with a music game, and I don't feel like moving my hand forward or flicking my hand, especially when the Kinect is not a perfect system.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're not playing it in the perfect environment, it doesn't recognize you always.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was some of the problems I had with the other game I played, your self-fitness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like...
[SPEAKER_05]: But it may work better though now with that new accessory that's coming out, the Kinect Zoom thing from Nyko.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be better.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it might, you know, again, at least the Kinect is better than the iToy was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the iToy, my God, that technology never worked right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I feel Kinect is like, it's still a step above, but it's got a long way to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: The technology isn't perfect, but these games are still pretty early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orangelunchradio.com, Zether says, I heard that Child of Eden didn't sell good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it only sold about 30-some-odd thousand copies, which didn't really even put it in the top 20 of games that were sold last month.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, maybe Loki knows more about what sales ultimately mean and so forth, but I honestly think what probably scared a lot of people off were these reviews talking about
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a 90-minute game, and you're paying $60 for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping that this game will sell much more when it gets discounted, because I think it's one of the better Kinect games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a niche game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, Rez and stuff, that was a niche game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And unfortunately, it's a niche that we like, but it's a niche game, and that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's just like Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_05]: Earth Defense Force didn't sell...
[SPEAKER_05]: that great either but if Child of Eden had Britney Spears music in it it was sold 10 times as many copies right it would have been stupid though and then actually no I don't think it would have sold 10 times as many copies I think still people wouldn't give it a chance and even less copies would have been sold because people have been like you know like us but I'm not touching that shit what the hell is this um but yeah like Earth Defense Force it sold uh
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they estimated like 65,000 to 90,000 copies worldwide, which is fine because the launch quantities of that were only about 200,000 per platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're expecting to sell much.
[SPEAKER_05]: They know going into it what they're expecting to get out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a game like Child of Eden...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think, development-wise, it didn't cost as much money to put it together as, say, a Modern Warfare game or something like that, where you have to sell a lot more to make up the money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that they had really huge expectations for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, true, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'll quickly talk about the fitness game I played.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your Shape Fitness, Your Self Fitness, I don't know, one of those fitness games.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I really liked the idea of the whole tailored custom to you individual workout thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like how the Kinect, again, doesn't really recognize you 100% of what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this game grades you pretty rigidly on the exercises you're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you're not perfect within the box that it has, and your arms go way too out, you don't get credit for stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it can be very frustrating, especially when the exercises are kind of kicking your butt a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was having me do these squats.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the other thing I'm going to actually say I thought was terrible about this I truly think it was a bad decision to do this in a fitness game is when it was doing the calibration stages and having me warm up it did not start with a stretch activity and I think that is a very poor thing to do in a fitness game actually you want to warm up before you stretch
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, actually yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you have to warm up the muscles before you stretch or else you run a risk of pulling a muscle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if you saw what this game was doing though, some of the high intensity exercises it was doing, it's one thing to put a little flash card up on the screen saying, you should stretch before using this device.
[SPEAKER_04]: I honestly think a smarter little thing would have said, okay, let's do some swaying in place, a little jogging.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we're going to stretch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we're going to have you do the intensive squats and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do they have a stretching portion at all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I ran into, but keep in mind this game kind of kicked my butt before I got very far into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been sore in my legs for four days since playing, and it's because Stupid Me didn't stretch beforehand.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was a little bit upset that the game should have... I mean, I should have known better, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to totally blame the game, but I just think it was a bad idea to...
[SPEAKER_04]: to not encourage me more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remind me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not everyone knows that you need to stretch beforehand.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I didn't think it was going to throw me so far into it with the calibration where I'm doing some squatting and things that are going to hurt my legs before telling me, hey, maybe we should do some yoga first.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: And I just, and again, I want to clarify before, because this might show up later in the game, so I want to be very careful on what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going through an initial setup calibration mode, but it was having you do exercises as part of the calibration, like a full routine type of thing, and it did not have me stretch beforehand, nor did no reminder come up at any point.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, maybe after the calibration, when you get into the actual daily stuff, you'll see more of that, but I'm not going to, if I didn't see it beforehand...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: It makes all the difference with how well you can keep up with the exercises too if you've given your chance to warm up and then stretch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this comment from Kai Judo in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do the stretch when you try to get the game out of the shrink wrap.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of those shrink wraps are pretty terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my arms don't hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my legs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you guys, for real.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm a teacher, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a kid teacher, but an adult teacher.
[SPEAKER_04]: I teach in a corporate environment.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I use classrooms full of computers, and I walk around and look at adults on their systems all day long, making sure they're following with me and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I have to walk around the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: The day after I did this Connect exercise, I couldn't walk as much.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm having to explain to my class,
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sorry guys, I was playing Kinect yesterday and you know, those things are pretty rough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how embarrassing is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fool, you should have known to stretch.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, it used to happen to me when I would go play DDR on my lunch break.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'd come back, my knees hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like, I had to... Walking upstairs was not a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Walking downstairs, oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I felt like a little old lady clutching to that railing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should have used the elevator.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like you're doing squats all over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's easier to lift it than to drop to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was traumatic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to give up and I'm not going to say a lot of negative things about the game because of that one thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll know next time to stretch, but I really think the game should have incorporated it better.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I missed it, and I consider myself a pretty smart individual, if I missed it, who knows who else is missing this and hurting themselves.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, not about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually something that came up in my video game week that I didn't get to play because of a certain something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just occurred to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the last game I wanted to talk about.
[SPEAKER_10]: The arcade that had Parapara Paradise is out of business.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Arcadia budding games or whatever it's called, the kind of crappy ghetto.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the little crappy, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they had the Parapara machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not surprised at all they went out of business.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really was a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to go play Parapara because I don't have Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their location really was never that good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we should buy that place and open up the actual Orange Lounge arcade in batting cages.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bet it's dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, going to our chatroom at chat.orangeloungevideo.com Derek H is in our chatroom saying, Rob is correct.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even Carmen Electra's aerobic striptease workout DVDs have an extensive stretching section.
[SPEAKER_04]: See?
[SPEAKER_04]: And even if your pole dancing classes tell you, I don't know why Derek H. knows so much about pole dancing classes, but I'll just assume he does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if they're getting you to stretch.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know that these games need to make sure they are incorporating that into their customized workouts.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for our Gaming Weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quickly, housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make sure you follow us on all those great websites around the interwebs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR or Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kick businesses off of Google Plus right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we are not on Google Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can follow...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, we're starting off with a comment from, uh, one of the Sony Network Entertainment execs, the president, Tim Schaaf, who, uh, spoke to, uh, or spoke at GamesBeat, uh, 2011, uh, about the PlayStation Network downtime.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they said,
[SPEAKER_05]: So, just goes to show you, all those people are like, you know, they're done for.
[SPEAKER_05]: They ended up selling a lot more because of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it says, of course, you know, the downtime cost Sony approximately $171 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, they would not like to do it again, obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said one time was enough, but it was a great learning experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: We agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a very interesting choice of words.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a learning experience, but once is enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that isn't the most politically correct statement about the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: He had to explain a little bit because his first quote was, it was a great experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's not exactly how you would describe that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: A humbling experience might be a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know how many times in my day-to-day job I use a phrase like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, because people make mistakes all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, it's frustrating to make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to, especially when you're at your job, you want to do the best job you possibly can.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of times people make mistakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a learning experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to learn from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we make mistakes in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very funny to hear Sony kind of use that same phrase.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was a learning experience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they are planning to invest some money to make sure that the PlayStation Network is secure.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're committing $20 million, and they're also seeking out independent developers to create games like, you know, PixelJunk, Sidescroller, and the Papoio Boku stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're also saying that they're going to be...
[SPEAKER_05]: doing this pub fun to bring innovative different and unique gameplay to the PlayStation Network so they're kind of trying to beef up their content on there because it could use a little bit of beefing up so that's kind of cool
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm glad they're kind of bringing in all that extra support.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I think all this talk about how Google was going to go under, or I'm sorry, not Google, excuse me, I'm still thinking about Plus and all that, but how PlayStation was going to go under and all that after the hacking and all that, it seems to be...
[SPEAKER_04]: A distant memory at this point, and I'm looking at a comment in our chatroom from Blender, says Uncharted 3 beta had 1.53 million players, by the way, and I do remember reading about that on the internet earlier this week, and I think a story had said it's the biggest PlayStation beta that's ever happened, so it certainly gives the impression that people have pretty much forgiven Sony, and we've all moved on with our lives, and we're back on PlayStation Network, but
[SPEAKER_04]: There's also, I guess, that sense of fool me once, shame on you, fool me twice, shame on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like if something bad happens again, I think you'll see a lot of people really mean it this time and leave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, it also helps that, you know, it's Uncharted 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a huge game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, of course, it's going to be one of their largest betas they've ever had.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: David Reeves said,
[SPEAKER_04]: That there is a resurgence in people buying the generic PSN cards in retail stores rather than putting up their credit card details.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think in the future they will make more non-generic cards like game branded ones such as Street Fighter or FIFA or even Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the generic ones have done well.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are playing it a bit safe at the moment because the hackers will be back.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my personal opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean they will right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's really the best thing to be saying there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, shut up, Capcom.
[SPEAKER_05]: We see that they're buying more generic cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, hopefully they're not buying your games with your crappy DRM shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, your games didn't work during the whole PlayStation Network outage, or at least your two PlayStation Network games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are awfully pretty good spirits to be in when you consider they missed out on all those weeks of sales, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of surprised it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, that might be one quote out of a much larger interview, but still.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because they need them more than Sony needs them, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because if they, you know, stop supporting Sony, then their sales kind of get cut about half.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whereas if Sony loses them, eh, there's
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't really wanted anything else, but Dan got the freebies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I got the freebies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I've bought anything on PSN.
[SPEAKER_05]: I try not to buy anything on there, not because I'm afraid of my credit card information being hacked, but because I don't want to spend money on their network.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that goes for Microsoft, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really want to buy anything, because I got into the habit where, oh, I gotta buy all the Xbox Live Arcade games, and I did that for a while, and
[SPEAKER_05]: How many of them do I play now?
[SPEAKER_05]: None of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: The last thing I bought on there, I think, was the Pirates of the Caribbean expansion for LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the last thing that I purchased on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, I don't see myself really purchasing anything else for there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I'm going to purchase download content for something, most of the time I'm gaming on my 360 anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I've bought anything since the hack happened, but I will say that Salacious Pop is strongly encouraging me to get the Arcade Super Street Fighter Arcade Edition expansion there on PlayStation Network because that's where we own Super Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may have to buy something in the near future.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I have some Ubisoft news.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have confirmed that there is going to be an online pass to be used for its games.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called the Uplay Passport.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's $9.99, basically $10 for access to the online features of many of their core games when bought second-hand.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, if you bought the game, you have a registration code that comes in it and it has exclusive bonus content and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the first game that's going to be using this is Driver San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_10]: No UK price yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Loki, aren't you excited to hear about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's just another company jumping on this horrible bandwagon, and I don't see the point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was trying to find... There was another article that actually had their press release for that in there, and I really want to find that so that I can... Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they can read you their PR spin on this, and it's just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's what gamers want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamers want that premium experience that their $10 goes to help.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to find... God, I really wish I had it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, they spun it as, it allows us, it's extra content, like online multiplayer and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, if I'm buying a game that has online multiplayer in it, and that does, because it does brand new, so therefore it should use, I don't understand why I should have to pay extra if I'm buying used.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I've heard people make, and I gotta say the most...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: All used games start off as new at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, they've made their money for that game to fund that online network.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to be devil's advocate and give you the counterpoint, but if the game wasn't being sold used, then that would force someone to buy it new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not necessarily, because some people might not buy it
[SPEAKER_05]: They may just skip it altogether.
[SPEAKER_05]: And whereas if you got a used sale, you may have the chance that other people might enjoy that game and they may later on decide, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go pick up more games from this developer or whatnot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on top of all that, people say that the developer doesn't get money for used sales.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it doesn't matter because the developer already got paid when the game got pressed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they get some kickbacks for sales and stuff like that, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't matter...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chat room for some comments at chat.orange.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sterlok says, cool, more games I'm not buying.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya says, they fuck us over and for whatever reason people still step up to defend them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, I'm not necessarily defending this here, but I have to...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of this news story I just kind of roll my eyes at and I'm like, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I really do buy most of my stuff new.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like either I'm going to buy it new or I'm going to get it on one of those rental accounts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there are very few games that I would play online that I wouldn't just buy new.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most games I want to play online with friends I'm excited about and I want to buy them right away.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you're not seeing the writing on the wall, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: You see, if you give them an inch, they're going to take a mile.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you start thinking that this is an okay thing for them to do, then everybody jumps on board and they start doing this for multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Then they start going, hey, you know, we're noticing that it seems that our used game sales or whatever, our new sales, aren't really being impacted enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to make sure that this is really something that people are going to want to buy new by adding more content for this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, you can't wait until later on when they're like, oh, well, it doesn't matter because I buy a lot of games new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, until they start saying, oh, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We can make a lot more money by charging for online multiplayer by having it download content or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say it does piss me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is interesting because I do kind of have different opinions depending on what system it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think the PlayStation 3...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: and I refuse to support it on Xbox and I will take Microsoft to task for that because Microsoft's allowing it to happen by selling it on their store and I'm sorry that's double dipping you're charging me twice for the same thing and that is to play my game online so I honestly think the company that needs to put their foot down is Microsoft Sony
[SPEAKER_04]: they're providing a free service it's harder to get mad at them on that side because you aren't paying for online over there the whole infrastructure is free and to say that to charge $10 for maintenance you can get away with that a lot more on that end than you can on Microsoft's end
[SPEAKER_04]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_10]: For the record, just because Eason wanted to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: OBJECTION!
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, and then, I mean, it's like I've said before, and you know, no one seemed to care then, and it's happening more now, and yeah, it doesn't really bother me too much because I don't buy Wii games, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of Wii games out there nowadays that, you know, maybe music games, maybe, you know, I don't know, just some other type of game, but where they're charging $60 for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No one's saying anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is something that's now commonly happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, like, for example, and, I mean, not that, this is definitely not a game I'm buying, but, you know, like, that Spyro fucking game that's coming out, the, the new Spyro Skylanders Adventure bullshit thing, that they're selling some S-
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, those horrid things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listen, kids are starting out stupid early on, and they just become stupid adults.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope Richard Gere doesn't own a Zuzu.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's just dumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're trying all these different tactics to get money for things they really shouldn't be getting money for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Developers getting money for used games?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You shouldn't get money for used games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a market.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a market that was created by people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it doesn't even have to be necessarily that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's say, for example, Rob, I loan you a copy of my game and you want to play it online.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to pay $10 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, because it's someone else accessing their network.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've already paid for that on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: They just use the more subscription model based thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm telling you, I've been an Xbox Live member for like six, seven years.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they allow this shit to continue, I'm out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: There will come a point probably where there's a game I'm going to want to play online.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be pissed that I'm double dipping and I'm canceling Xbox Live when that happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: If Sony is doing it, if Ubisoft is doing it, EA is doing it, THQ is doing it, Warner Games is doing it...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not going to be long before everybody jumps on board with this, and hopefully not Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting comment from Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Microsoft did it, now they need to be called out if that happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma in our chatroom at chat.org.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if you're patient enough, you can buy the games as new when the price drops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that serious to get the game on day one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd rather wait a few weeks for the game to drop to 30, 40 new than wait a week and buy it used for 45, 50.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: That is technically a way to get it cheaper, but people want their games right away.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, the way I look at it is if you're buying it used anyways, you're probably not getting it day one anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: So just wait even longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: In a game like Driver, I mean, let's look at Driver.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, the pedigree of Driver hasn't been that great.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first one was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Second one was alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Third one was terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the fourth one, eh, kind of terrible as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the fifth one, eh, I wouldn't be surprised if it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's definitely not a game I'd be playing online anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on with some other topics here before we make Loki's head explode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: No mention of Final Fantasy XIV That just doesn't exist But Final Fantasy XI Their only online game In the Final Fantasy series Will be Possibly ported to the PlayStation 8 Their only online game?
[SPEAKER_04]: in the Final Fantasy series.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they just totally forget about Final Fantasy XIV?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, that's my comments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I see, I see, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: XIV doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's just, it's kind of interesting though if they did that, but I think it'd be kind of cool because think about it, you know, MMOs haven't really come to handhelds, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, not that I can think of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phantasy Star, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, but the Phantasy Star portable games contained little single-player games.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were a lot like Universe's single-player mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, I'd like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd welcome that, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hear Final Fantasy XI is still going.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still improving.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did graphical improvements.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're a PC player, you got some new graphic textures this last go-around.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think that's kind of rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's really possible to put XIV on a portable platform because despite the fact that everybody criticizes it for being poop it was a really good looking game and the Vita probably just doesn't possess the power graphically to pull it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: but you know 11 was a game that was made for the PS2 and that's the biggest drawback to 11 is that everything they do on 11 still has to support the PlayStation 2 because a lot of folks in Japan that's how they adopted it was on the PS2 so until there comes a day where they say well we no longer are going to support the old platforms I just don't see them being able to do that I think that's what 14 was trying to do but failed miserably because they didn't make the they tried to change the core game
[SPEAKER_04]: and they took out the goddamn auction houses which every MMO like needs so I don't, oh my god and they kept the same races but changed the names that's just stupid
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, I think it's a neat idea to have, especially considering the Vitas are supposed to have 3G in them and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's kind of a cool use.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be curious what other types of MMOs come out of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not just ports of old stuff, but some new ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially because isn't part of the whole Vitas thing supposed to be finding gamers around you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, you've got GPS built into them and all the different little services that they have and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it just sounds like a neat thing to kind of integrate the GPS stuff into MMOs somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com Spazinator says, Final Fantasy XI would be a system seller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to love it on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tigerclaw says, MMOs on a PlayStation Vita.
[SPEAKER_04]: I sense you can do some sort of transferring type of stuff from the PlayStation 3 to the Vita with MMOs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very hard to play Final Fantasy XI on a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could do it, but you have to have the exact right model of PlayStation in order to be able to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not even just the backward compatible ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one that has some type of port that the hard drive attaches to because I don't think you can use PlayStation 3's hard drive.
[SPEAKER_04]: For 11, can you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember No, you can't at all because it's a 3.5 drive versus a laptop SATA drive And it's an old IDE drive So you would have to clone Well, I think they had something that you could download off the PlayStation Network That was basically the cloned hard drive information, I think, for the Final Fantasy XI stuff
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a curious comment from Spazinator in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are the Vita launch games really that bad looking so far?
[SPEAKER_04]: How old is Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about as old as this show, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it came out in 2002 in Japan, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a nine-year-old game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Launch titles right now are pretty sparse.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't really said what they're launching with yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Other than Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uncharted is a big title for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there was that neat looking dungeon game with the whole PlayStation 3 integration I thought was neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't really said yet what a lot of launch games are going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still really early, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vita, Naughty Dog, Crash Bandicoot
[SPEAKER_04]: But saying a pretty big slam that's pro-Sony and anti-Nintendo In an interview with Now Gamer, Justin Richman said To be honest with you, the idea of it is very, very cool Speaking about the Wii U But there's nothing that the Wii U has that the Vita and PlayStation 3 doesn't You know, it's an interesting piece of technology And I'm interested to see how people use it
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not completely sold yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That the screen isn't multi-touch, that's a little weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems that there are some very strange holes in it, but to be fair, last time I was skeptical of the original Wii, and look at how that did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure the games they make for Wii U will be amazing."
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, I'm seeing that whole observation in the mainstream media that, hell, not even the Vita, but the PSP in the PlayStation 3 was kind of capable of that same technology of having a portable screen in your hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he brings up a point I forgot.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Vita has a touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is going to be just like the Wii U. I mean, granted, it'll be between a PlayStation 3 and a Vita way more expensive than a Wii U most likely will be, but he's got a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ports would be a little weird on the Sony end, but you know... It'd be like something like, here's some really optional way to play this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not like right away, but what about further down the line?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or what about a game like, I don't know, Arkham Asylum is supposed to be on the Wii U, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So... That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be out on the Wii U a year after it comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it'll have some stinking bonus feature, something that everybody has to have.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my curiosity is, couldn't they release a similar game of the year edition, quote unquote, on the PlayStation 3 that could optionally bring up the Vita to do whatever the Wii U screen is doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it could, but people would just shrug their shoulders and say, I'm not buying another fucking $299 system so that I can do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: True, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's an optional and not a mandatory enhancement, does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be like if Gran Turismo 5 was coming out, say, next year, and you could buy the Vita and use it as a rear-view mirror.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would someone do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, I'm sure there's someone out there that would do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is what they had showed off that the PS3 was supposed to do in 2006.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, is that necessarily a good use of your $299?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens when the games get a little closer to coming out for the Wii U and when the Vita comes out, exactly what types of technology we see beyond what we've just seen at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there is a dream come true for many, many people in West Virginia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, first of all, I will rewind.
[SPEAKER_04]: People stop making jokes about West Virginia?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, we're in West Virginia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, Konami is going to have the Childhood Obesity Summit in West Virginia this month.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then they're going to have a DDR tournament for school-aged children in West Virginia.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hear that's going to be a cool summit, except there's going to be a lot of fatties.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: At any rate, it's going to be held July 27th and 28th in Charleston, and it will have representatives from the President's Council on Fitness, Sports, and Nutrition, the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Department of Health and Human Services, Dr. Michael Danzinger from The Biggest Loser, and they will also have the West Virginia University Extension Service and West Virginia Public Employees Insurance Agency hosting it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There will be prizes, mainly scholarships, and they're hoping that they can just get kids more active.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will also be a technician on hand to maintain the DDR pads as they keep breaking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: There will be no technician to tech those pads.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wish I had DDR at my gym.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything that gets kids motivated to exercise is a good thing, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: We shouldn't be making fun of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you have to admit, the idea of an obesity summit, doesn't that seem the slightest bit condescending to you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, anything that gets more DDR machines out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like the parents telling the kids, you're going to summer camp.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: What camp are we going to?
[SPEAKER_04]: Camp Thin and Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I really think that it's a good start.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a good thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: But really, a lot of it is going to start with parental education.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got to look at what the influences are on the kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can buy all the DDR you want, but at the end of the day, it has to be the parent that says, no, you can't have a donut until you have mowed the lawn, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or eat your vegetables first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we'll see what comes of that, and we'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll let you know how big of a score the winner of the DDR tournament racks up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's travel the world and look at some upcoming release dates and games that are coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not a whole lot this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week it's basically Call of Juarez the Cartel on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also Captain America Super Soldier that's coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii DS, and actually that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then also the Smurfs, in case you forgot.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have a movie coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's the Smurfs on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And because Ubisoft loves their dancing games, Smurfs Dance Party, which I saw a YouTube clip out there with one of the Smurfs songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who let the Smurfs out?
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to stab a needle into my ear.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seriously was terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I also believe that just Dance Summer Party will be coming out as well on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, do you know what I have stuck in my head thanks to the whole talk about going to fat camp and going to summer camp?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I have stuck in my head now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you going to salute your shorts?
[SPEAKER_11]: We run, we jump, we swim and play
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a great idea for something.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is just totally made me think of it for some reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't it be awesome if they had some sort of social network thing where you could basically create your own TV stations that people can watch actual programming, actual TV syndicated programming that you can basically design the lineup for and have that play and people would favor it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't that be awesome?
[SPEAKER_10]: Doesn't Hulu have like a playlist?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: and he got me an invite to the service and it kind of looks like iTunes kind of mixed with Napster but one of the big things is that you can build playlists and then like share them on Facebook and anybody can call up your playlist and play the songs because it's essentially kind of Napster.
[SPEAKER_04]: in that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: New Napster, not old Napster, but the new one that's subscribed to the service and get everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's free for right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's limited to 10 hours a month or something like that on free, but it's a good way to get exposed to some new songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But kind of what you're describing to me sounds like that with TV, because you'd be making a television playlist, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: 80s commercials for like products you know you could just have like the Lysol commercial whatever from the 80s but still advertising products that you have now or if people you know have products out there right now that they want to make an 80s type commercial for that'd be pretty awesome
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently there's this, you know how they used to have the Nickelodeon Game and Sports channel?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's around anymore, is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It used to show the Legends of the Hidden Temple and Guts and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now there's a Teen Nick channel that might have replaced that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's been around for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, I guess Teen Nick has a whole now 90s segment coming back, and they're going to show all the shows from the 90s.
[SPEAKER_04]: on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you know I'm going to be camped out in front of Teen Nick.
[SPEAKER_04]: My 33-year-old ass will be camped out in front of Teen Nick when they do the marathon for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_10]: I totally watched the crap out of that show.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what have any of these people done since it's set for her?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't she on a show on ABC Family with Joey Lawrence or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's done a few things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those poor parents probably don't get recognized for anything else than, Hey, it's Clarissa's parents!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: True story, did you know that they made a pilot for a CBS TV show that was like Clarissa Grows Up or something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was something about her becoming a journalist.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really had nothing to do with the old show, but it just was her.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would have been cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but it didn't get picked up, so she went to do Sabrina instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: That worked all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, there was another show that was on Nickelodeon when I was probably 19, but it was called, what was it called?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was like some soap opera that they tried to do, like the teenage soap opera.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, 14.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it wasn't 14.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or 15.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, 15 or 17 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: 15, I think, was the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember all the British programming that they used to have?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just remember you can't do that on television.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the greatest show ever on that network.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing that they did was introduce me to one of my favorite shows of all time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up, Moose.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Tomorrow People.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which actually was a BBC program.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a full serial, and the series had been around since the 70s.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I loved that damn show, and I watched the entire thing, and I've downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let me move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it was out on DVD, I'd freaking buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Release dates for Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do we get from release dates to Clarissa Explains It All?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360, some games coming out very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alice Madness Returns in Japan as well as Fear F3AR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIII International Edition comes to the Xbox 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: will only set you back about half as much as it did before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alice Madness returns there as well, as well as F.E.A.R.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the Final Fantasy XIII Ultimate Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: F.E.A.R.
[SPEAKER_04]: is Fear 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fear 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's F.3.A.R.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's that whole stylized... I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like how Scream 4 had a 4 in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No More Heroes, the Red Zone Edition, also on the PlayStation 3 this week in Japan, and Sniper Ghost Warrior this week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sengoku Basara Chronicle Heroes Capcom
[SPEAKER_04]: brings back the two-on-two battles and all the famous scenes from the previous six installments.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess this is a long-going... It's like Dynasty Warriors.
[SPEAKER_04]: ...series in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Try to bring out Nintendo, see what's going on in their world, if anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Devil Rhythm
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I've seen this girl in other games before, this little character.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen her before.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Gabrielle's Ghostly Groove is what's coming out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a 3DS version of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's on WiiWare right now if you want to check.
[SPEAKER_05]: WiiWare or DSiWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then next week Super Pokemon Scramble comes out on the 3DS so it's a Pokemon game even though it's not like an actual Pokemon game it's a Pokemon mini game thing I guess it looks kind of cute actually I'd check that out if it comes out over here there it is your Japanese release dates let's move over to the old kingdom DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Not a whole bunch.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the 22nd we have Calvarez, The Cartel, and Cars 2, The Video Game, and Earth Defense Force, Insect Armageddon.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised it's coming out over there as Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_05]: They used to call it Global Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to double check.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it says Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they not like the word Earth over there or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it was the fact that they were localizing it from Japan, so they called it Global Defense Force over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It never really came out over here on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's our fault for calling it Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_10]: There were a lot of other series that were renamed just for censorship issues, like Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm also thinking about, you know, what comes to mind is the whole fact that Captain America's coming out in some countries as the first Avenger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, it's Captain America's a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm totally serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Certain countries are getting it as the first Avenger.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, just a couple more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least they're not giving it the Hetalia treatment where he's making, you know, he's eating cheeseburgers or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple more news stories for you guys, then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I'd be willing to see, like, you know how they have Italian Spider-Man?
[SPEAKER_05]: Italian Captain America.
[SPEAKER_10]: Japanese Spider-Man is freaking hilarious, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there is a new model of PlayStation 3 coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually now, I believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's to conform to a new thing that was passed back in December.
[SPEAKER_05]: The, what was it, the...
[SPEAKER_05]: and the AACS Final Adopter Agreement which basically is some sort of DRM that they have standardized that all media companies must adhere to and this means that they need to only support Blu-ray playback high definition Blu-ray playback
[SPEAKER_05]: Only over HDMI because it's the only way this kind of DRM works.
[SPEAKER_05]: So these new systems will be unable to play HD Blu-ray movies over Component.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's only going to be available through HDMI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Games are fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Games you can still play over Component but you will not be able to play over Component for Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not something Sony is necessarily doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's something that everybody has to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: If Microsoft has a new system coming out, say that supports Blu-ray later on, they will not be able to have Blu-ray playback over Component.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you talking about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just because Sony's a bunch of cheap bastards.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why this is happening, because they are cheap bastards and they want to cut out the things that they're putting in the boxes for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you mean cut out things that they're putting in the boxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I read on the internet, so it must be true.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's what initially everyone thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on, I wouldn't put it past them.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've done things to cut out power usage and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really just saves them money on components.
[SPEAKER_04]: So instead you're telling me that Sony just waited until the last minute to implement their own standard for Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, not even really the last minute because I don't think this goes into effect until 2012.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they kind of just said, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're just going to do it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And before the Xmas rush.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing, though, is they didn't ever explain it to anybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't think there's anything on the box that calls out... Well, I don't see Sony putting out a press release going, guess what, we've taken a feature away from the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they don't have to say it like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They could just say, due to blah, blah, blah, playback of high-def Blu-ray movies can only be facilitated through HDMI.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be clear, though, you can still hook up your PlayStation 3 through component cables.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will only play the games and the movies in standard def, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: My old TV didn't even have HDMI.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to hook up through Component, and it was an HDTV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully, I do have HDMI on my TV, and I am hooked up through HDMI for my PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: But once again, I mean, because HDMI cables are so damn cheap, I don't understand why they don't throw one in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wait, I know why.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they sell HDMI cables for $40 when anybody can go out and get them for like $3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucks, but that's life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: This has to do with a new Bomani game.
[SPEAKER_04]: For you fans of DDR and Beatmania 2DX, there's information about a new game that is being tested at Leisureland in Akiba, Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is called Sound Voltex Booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not vortex, that's voltex.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like volts, like energy.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some video that has hit the internet that shows this game in action, and apparently kind of what this game looks like... That's the little fuzzy music you hear in the background...
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of looks like, imagine like a Beatmania screen that's more like Guitar Hero, I guess, looking like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it looks like not only are there buttons, but there's some type of tilt mechanism in this game too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you'll notice as the song goes on, the guy kind of has to drive and tilt the thing a little bit before he starts hitting buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it looks like it kind of incorporates both those features into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Location Test
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami has trademarked some names Sound Voltex Booth and Sound Voltex Floor possibly localized versions of the game I don't know, I guess it would depend on how well this one does so, we'll see anyhow, it's time to take a stroll down memory lane in a segment we call the Classic Game of the Week
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week here at Orange Lounge Radio, DarkSakura dives into the vault and pulls out a classic game that she thinks, hey, why aren't you kids playing this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enough with your newfangled crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy this old classic for a change.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is Tekken 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: I figured since I did Soul Blade last week, I'd do Tekken 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because this was my favorite fighting game for ages.
[SPEAKER_10]: It came out in the arcade in March 1997.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it came out on the PlayStation in 1998.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a simplified arcade version that came out on PS2 as part of Tekken 5's arcade history mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the PlayStation version is probably considered one of the greatest ones ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the first game on Namco System 12 hardware, and it was the last one that came on the original PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is such a fun game.
[SPEAKER_10]: This game came out when I worked for Namco Arcade and I played the crap out of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: As far as the characters that were in it, it had basically, you could unlock all of the classic characters later on, but it had its own new characters too.
[SPEAKER_10]: The ones that returned at the beginning were Paul Phoenix, Nina Williams, Yoshimitsu, and Lei Wulong.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also you could unlock Anna Williams and Heihachi.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the new characters that came in were Jin Kazama, Xiaoyu, Hualrong, King2, which is the wrestler with the mask, Eddie Gordo, who is every masher's favorite.
[SPEAKER_10]: and ForestFlaw.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you could also unlock Kuma and Panda, Julia Chung, who was my second favorite person to use in the game, Brian Fury, Gunjack, Mokujin, Ogre, True Ogre, and Tiger Jackson, who was the swap for Eddie Gordo with the Fro and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the character I loved right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hwarong.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love his music.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can turn it up a little bit.
Hwarong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, in the PlayStation version, you had two other characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had Gon, who I don't know if anyone's ever heard of the comic, and I will link something in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gon is a little dinosaur, and there is a manga, a big manga series, and honestly, his ending and everything was pretty...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: and also Dr. Bosconovich, who was actually supposed to be an unlockable in the arcade version, but he ended up being a bonus in the PlayStation version.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there was another one that was for Bleemcast, which was a boot disk for the Dreamcast that you could boot the PlayStation version of the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've got it, and it really just enhanced the resolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: It made it look a lot better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: But it also did sort of screw up some of the background images versus the stage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of almost how it did in... You remember the Japanese version of Tekken Tag Tournament?
[SPEAKER_10]: Where it would do that weird thing between the ground and the backwards stage?
[SPEAKER_10]: Where they would separate?
[SPEAKER_10]: It kind of did that number.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, this is lauded by lots of people as one of the best PlayStation games ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It got a 96 out of 100 on Metacritic, and it's ranked the number two on their list of greatest PlayStation games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, this was the music I really liked.
[SPEAKER_10]: Forrest Law's music.
[SPEAKER_10]: His ending was funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yes, I have beaten him, but never the one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, this is actually a little bit of fun trivia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tekken 3 was the first game to get a 10 on EGM's revised review scale, saying that a game no longer had to be perfect to get a 10, and the last game that got a 10 was Sonic & Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it honestly is...
[SPEAKER_10]: One of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I have to say it is a masher's paradise, especially with Eddie Gordo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I loved him.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, I would only use him to play Tiger, because Tiger was so freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the game had great music, and I'll tell you one thing, actually, and this is actually fairly common with me and the Namco games when they bring them home and have their arranged version of the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: I always preferred the arcade soundtrack, except for a couple of cases in Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not Soul Calibur, but Soul Blade, because I like Cervantes' arranged music better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: But I would always watch the Japanese forums to see who was going to be the next character to come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they actually had a different release schedule for the US machines versus the Japanese machines.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I would sometimes be able to guess, because they had this little screen pop up that says, guess who or who's next or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I would usually be able to accurately say who was the next character coming out.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_10]: and we were talking about just seeing how far it could go and I said, there's going to come a day where you're not going to be able to tell the 3D from the real thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now they've even got different types of motion capture so advanced that you really can't tell the difference unless you're really looking for it, you know?
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: But as far as this, it is, I think to this day, my favorite Tekken game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I really loved Tekken 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still pissed off about... What was that game, that company, that I gave the bad Better Business Bureau review to?
[SPEAKER_10]: because they sent me the Asian version and not the Japanese version and I specifically asked for the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of those, like, was it Toys?
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't Toys and Joys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Toys and Joys has always been good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was like, import something or... Yeah, I know what you're talking about, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're long since out of business, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: The other good thing about this one is that, like I mentioned, it had a mode called Tekken Force, which was a kind of side-scrolling version, a beat-em-up like Streets of Rage, and it was one where you would go through different stages, and if you beat the minigame four times, then you could unlock Dr. Bosconovich.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had to beat him first, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then it had another version that was called Tekken Ball that was like beach volleyball except you had to charge the ball so you had to use a powerful attack to try to hurt your opponent or hit the ball so that it hits the ground and then your character would get injured if it touched the ground or the opponent's character would get injured if it touched the ground and
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was super fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can still find it, you know, and if you get Tekken 5, it's in the history mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the best games ever, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there it is, Tekken 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I like this character.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other one ran out.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what's funny in the intro, though, on the PlayStation version?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is what Namco was doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Look how we can render individual hairs!
[SPEAKER_10]: And it looks so unnatural.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, jeez.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well that's going to do it for the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't go anywhere because Orange Lingerie is going to be right back with Part B of our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have some rapid fire news for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some news about PopCap got sold.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to talk about that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk about some news around EA's camp when it comes to server shutdowns.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some...
[SPEAKER_04]: Discussion topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, tonight the news is a little bit light, but we're going to talk about is good parenting better than a violent video game ban?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure that'll get everybody riled up here in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And stop hating on sports games, says one writer.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about all that when we come back with more tonight of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we're going to get back into some gaming news, including rapid-fire news, as well as your tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is your last chance to get in those Twitter topics, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, I want to just give a quick plug for other projects and things that we're working on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth is a Warcraft podcast that I host with my buddy, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_04]: for more information you can visit www.hoardhouse.com sadly there wasn't a new show this week so there was some other stuff going on but we should be back next week so this would be a great time to catch up on the 31 some odd back episodes there are of the show and listen to our potty humor in talking about Warcraft but never too seriously I have a new impression by the way what's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: What is nature's call?
[SPEAKER_10]: I get sick of hearing it every time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that one of the chicks in Warcraft when you get a quest?
[SPEAKER_10]: Avrila?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: The centaur girl?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh, uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, the great outdoors!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, I know exactly who you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Screw her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ow!
[SPEAKER_04]: Very carefully.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just gotta get those hind... never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I want to plug a guest appearance I did this week on Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, it was their 10th anniversary show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I talked about that at the top of the program, but fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of the chatters were saying it was a very different side of me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was on that show, and I'm just saying, well, I just...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not really about games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was the old Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was still me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't go in there with a different mindset.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just I don't have to worry about... It's not my show, quote unquote, anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're different when you're not facilitating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm not facilitating.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not in the MC role.
[SPEAKER_04]: And plus, I realize on that show, conversation will go anywhere and anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show, I've got to make sure after a 20-minute tangent, it does get back to games eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that show...
[SPEAKER_10]: I was in the same boat when I was running the gig when Tiara guested.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just a different role.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you have to be moderator.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like Julie Chan on Big Brother versus Julie Chan on The Talk for those that actually watch daytime TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: because they discovered robots have emotion now yes apparently she got her emotion chip put in she can learn DarkSakura I don't know if you can plug the stuff you've been guesting on it's actually the podcast that Tiara and our friend Weasel do for Geek Life it's called Pop Culture Parlay if you go to geek-life.com I am going to be on the next two episodes so yay awesome
[SPEAKER_10]: and it was a very interesting discussion and there was some Pyramid Head mentioned.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So by the way, it sounds like I didn't even realize this, but the chat room is telling me my audio cut out for a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's the mic or whatever, but there was audio issues.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you hear me now, chat room?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob was talking about how he likes to do things in the dark.
[SPEAKER_04]: How sad I'm giving the plug for Under Sedation Live and it cut out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob was on Under Sedation Live, guys, and it was epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Listen to Horde House, listen on your station live.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there was diarrhea involved.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Should I go check on your coffee?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if that's a good thing to bring up right after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, can we move on, please, with some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to... And, by the way, Brad from PodCulture in the chatroom says, Big difference between innocent and not guilty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to get too political on this program or what have you or talk about controversial stuff because, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll let, uh, what's her name, uh, God, what's, what's that chick on the CNN show that, oh God, Nancy Grace, that's, that, I'll leave that discussion to her, but fine, I stand corrected on, on my earlier comment Uh, let's get to some rapid fire news though, Loki, why don't you start us
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well there is a rumor that apparently during Comic Con they're going to announce a new Marvel vs. Capcom kind of iteration, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Marvel vs. Capcom 3 to be exact.
[SPEAKER_05]: The actual announcement is supposed to be Ultimate Marvel vs. Capcom 3 and it's supposed to include a roster update including, I think, 12 extra characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: are supposed to be added to the roster and it will be sold for $40 retail.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the rumored characters, of course, Doc Doc, because I guess there were some files that referenced him in the ISO that was floating around out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, there is a panel for Marvel vs. Capcom 3 at Comic Con, so it makes sense that they would maybe make an announcement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they just want to give out tips.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's hard to believe that it wasn't that long ago that the game came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, February.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Street Fighter 4 and Super Street Fighter 4, kind of the same thing happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: 12 characters is a lot, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, that would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: movie could have been a lot better.
[SPEAKER_05]: And some of the earlier drafts, I guess, of the script actually had it a little bit more traditional to the actual Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: game.
[SPEAKER_05]: There actually was supposed to be some sort of epic boss fight over lava and stuff with Koopa and a lot of, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_05]: The scenery that you would see in the game will actually kind of take place in the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I guess Koopa's flying around in a giant floating pirate ship.
[SPEAKER_05]: But unfortunately what we got ended up being some sort of weird Mario Judge Dredd movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: You mean that executives came in and fucked the whole thing up because they thought they knew what people wanted?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never heard of this happening before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's what they did.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then finally, I guess this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually had a dig at Capcom in Ms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Splosion Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's during one of the levels that looks very much like the Star Road in Super Mario World.
[SPEAKER_05]: and they're all, who does this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, this is completely ripped off.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this, a Capcom game or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, going to some other quick stories here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's an epic mod on its way out for StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called StarCraft Universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might have known this previously as World of StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this was all back in January when that whole thing happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now there is a trailer out with gameplay from the alpha version.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess in a press release that the dude sent to Kotaku, he wanted to update everybody on the mod's progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, kind of interesting that it's going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me play a little bit of that trailer here in studio so folks can see what that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this looks like an epic mod for StarCraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some cinematics there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see if we can get some gameplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you look at the gameplay, it really does kind of look like World of Warcraft, but in the StarCraft universe, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Complete with the hit points for numbers and the whole kind of first-person-esque 3D environments.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the creator of this actually left school to work on StarCraft Universe for full time.
[SPEAKER_04]: He says, at this point, I'm learning way more creating StarCraft Universe than I ever would at school.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of my friends trying to get into creative industry find themselves having to grind out a massive portfolio to find any work after four years of college.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is very true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard would be dumb not to hire him if this ends up being a pretty awesome thing here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to see how that works out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, other news stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Incubus, you know the band, they're getting their own video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Incubattle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a beat-em-up that's very similar to Scott Pilgrim vs. the World in that whole retro style.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what that reminds me of actually more so than that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the Linkin Park game that they put out in like iOS or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very much like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can pick one of the band's five members and you go on the streets and fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who do you fight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pirates trying to steal the band's latest album.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is seriously who you're fighting.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: No indication on what, I mean, you can click on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this a Flash game or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it looks like a little Flash game you can actually play there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm not going to play that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go cause physical harm to pirates because they do physical harm to my wall.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if they have the whole hats and the eye patch, that's actually kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Arkham City's collector's edition has announced some pre-orders.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop and Best Buy both priced the collector's edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's see, Best Buy actually went ahead and priced the collection at $99.99 and explained the content saying, a premium statue, an art book, Gotham Knight animated material, and, interestingly enough, early access to download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: It all comes out on October 18th when the game is set to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, we actually have a new Incubus single apparently has released to promote the new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would have known that this is coming out?
[SPEAKER_04]: But here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take a little listen here.
[SPEAKER_00]: You say, I'll just make a copy for me and a friend Then he'll make one and she'll make one and where will it end?
[SPEAKER_00]: One leads to another, then more And no one buys any dish from the store So no one gets paid and they can't make more The posse breaks up and that's close to store Don't copy, don't copy that floppy So let me break this down for you
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't copy that floppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The hot new Incubus single that's going to be in that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: As you fight the pirates.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hell about some different news.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an interesting new sound for them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, here's some good news.
[SPEAKER_10]: For Sonic Generations, guess who's going to be there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Metal Sonic!
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's going to be old school Metal Sonic and he's going to be one of the rivals.
[SPEAKER_10]: I freaking love Mecha Sonic so that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was actually my favorite part of Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Konami again.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're giving us a choice.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually up on Xbox Live Arcade and PSN where they're going to let basically the people who subscribe to these services choose the next game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's on their Facebook page.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's a question there.
[SPEAKER_10]: In a perfect world, what previously released Konami classic would you like to see next on Xbox Live Arcade or PSN?
[SPEAKER_04]: Simpsons Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I want YY Konami World.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, last but not least, Child of Eden is going to be on PlayStation 3 on September 23rd.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's basically going to also have revised versions, I believe, of some other games, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: there's Call of Juarez the Cartel on the 16th of September World Rally Championship 2011 on October 7th and Connect Party Rabbids Alive and Kicking on 360 in November also Far Cry 3 and Brothers in Arms Furious 4 are going to be on 2012 the end
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get to Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week we invite your tweets at twitter.com slash OLR, because after all, it is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes you want to ask questions, or you want to make sure we touch on a story at some point during this show, or you just have an opinion you want to share.
[SPEAKER_04]: We read your feedback in 120, or excuse me, 140 characters or less.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ramaditya Knight tweets us, saying, what is your favorite NES multi-cart?
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Duck Hunt Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Duck Hunt
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a good one, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking Donkey Kong Jr.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Donkey Kong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really wish I'd played more of those pirated multi-carts because they had some Final Fantasy 7 and the Titanic game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some amazing garbage in those cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Ramaditya Knight gives you some ideas there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Vision 110 in 1 and Super 190 in 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: My favorite multi-cart?
[SPEAKER_04]: Short Order and Eggsplode.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were power pad games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyone ever play those?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them was whack-a-mole with your feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Eggsplode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: More tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt, SSJ100Matt on Twitter tweets us and says, Hey, Toys R Us is having a $15 sale on all Tony Hawk and DJ Guitar Hero bundles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great deal.
$15?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an awesome deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you don't own DJ Hero, you might want to, like, consider that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, shit, I would love to just pick up an extra guitar controller, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: guitar hero bundles for real hold on i'm going to the source here he's linking us to a thread on cheap ass gamer uh it works on the bundles but not the super combo bundles for guitar hero on tour combos would be ridiculous guitar hero 5 and guitar hero warriors of rock holy crap yeah the super bundles i mean those are basically like you know the all the instruments
[SPEAKER_05]: I might have to do that, that's a pretty damn good deal I gotta tell you this much, we were clearing out some old inventory We had $50, I could buy you the DJ Hero 2 party set on the Wii Two turntables and a microphone at a game for $50 Is that where it's at?
[SPEAKER_05]: If I play it on the Wii, man, that's an awesome deal
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on, Tigerclaw tweets us a few things.
[SPEAKER_04]: One is a story about how Steam apparently has improved its content delivery system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Defense of the Ancients 2 will be making use of the new system when it comes out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: But apparently, yeah, it has to do with the fact that when new games come out on launch day from Steam...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: for those that have ISPs with monthly bandwidth caps Steam will no longer force you to download unnecessary data when a game is updated you will just download whatever's been changed rather than the entire files can't believe they weren't doing this before but that's a great improvement help cut back on some of the bandwidth overall
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can also get into download scheduling, bandwidth throttling, and the ability to prioritize the order that games are downloaded for updates and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all coming to Steam very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, not everything on Steam will be able to use this right away, but Dota will be the first game to use it when it comes out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting that they're pegging that as a game to use it soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had no idea this game was...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: And it has to do with Hideo Kojima.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he says, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have time for a new Snatcher game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if someone else wants to do it, great.
[SPEAKER_04]: So might be kind of opening the door there to a new Snatcher game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was in an interview with PlayStation Blog when he was asked about games like L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire and Deus Ex Human Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to make a new Snatcher game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Kojima said, quote, L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: Noire is a game that I really like, but unfortunately I have not played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it is coming out in Japan today, so when I return, I intend to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The idea of an open world in 3D is very good, and I would love to do something like Snatcher, but I do not have the time or the means to do so.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if anyone else would like to develop it, I would love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Team Bondi, you might need to give Hideo Kojima a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might not even have to work 100-hour work weeks to get that game done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to get your tweets in for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, back to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your phone calls in about 30 minutes here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: The mailbag's coming up soon as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: FUs of the week and all that stuff you love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA bought PopCap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, thank God it wasn't Zynga, which they were in the running, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA purchased PopCap games for $750 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then also, of course, there are some bonuses, including some performance bonuses, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job, PopCap!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that is kind of bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Plants vs. Zombies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Name me one thing you can't play Plants vs. Zombies on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe an old Nokia phone and an Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I would bet somebody's probably tried to port it to the 2600.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, yeah, you can play that well because there's a Quest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Peace Bloom vs. Ghouls I have my Peace Bloom They'll remove that quest from a while I'm keeping my Peace Bloom You better not take my Peace Bloom I don't think they will I love my stupid singing flower I actually hate those fucking flowers that sing You'll be walking through Stormwind
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a torch to set those things on fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why couldn't they give us one of the plants that look like Audrey?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a zombie to eat that plant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I digress.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess if it's a good business thing for PopCap, then yay, winners.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's always going to be that part of me that's a little bit nervous.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit nervous about what the future has.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakroom in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com If Zynga bought PopCap games, I would still be crying.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw says, you know EA is going to be milking those PopCap games.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw says, Peggle Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it'll get that bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think EA just kind of wants something to fall back on if their games, you know, it's not like EA doesn't have a humongous library of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if, you know, it's nice to have some proven winners in their hat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that would maybe be the best news out of all with this is that if EA knows they've got a winner in their back pocket, then maybe they'll experiment with some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the other hand, I mean, I'm sure that's just wishful thinking on my part, but forgive me for being a dreamer.
[SPEAKER_10]: People say you're a dreamer, but you're not the only one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not the only one, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, this is another story that's kind of about Zynga and it's about EA.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting how these things come full circle.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is about the NBA Jam creator, Mark Turmel.
[SPEAKER_04]: He created the NBA Jam series that recently came back last year, although it kind of came back with a... Hopefully the arcade ones this year will be a little better.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has left EA Sports.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know where he works now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zynga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so he now works at Zynga, so who knows what he's gonna create for them over there.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was assimilated into their collective.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was the senior creative director at EA when he left.
[SPEAKER_04]: NBA Jam is not the only thing he works on, but some other projects as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently there were rumors about a return of NFL Blitz when this guy worked at Midway.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then EA bought the Blitz property when Midway was going out of business.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know if that'll happen now or maybe it'll just happen without this guy overseeing the project anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA has confirmed his departure.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word at what exactly he's going to help design at Zynga.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know like I'm really trying to look at both sides about Zynga but don't does anyone else think Zynga's days are really numbered and it's not just about the whole like fact that their games are laughably bad when it comes to things like Farmville and so forth despite the fact that tons and tons of people play them but I feel like if Facebook goes down Zynga is fucked
[SPEAKER_04]: Zynga has yet to establish.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I know they like to say in their press releases, well, people could just come to Zynga.com and play.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one's going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not going to be nearly the company you are thanks to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if Google Plus rolls out games and says, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Since we don't like the Zynga games ever either and we've become the safe haven for nerds, we're not going to partner with Zynga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zynga is not allowed to put their games on Facebook or on Google Plus, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: or maybe Google Plus will come out and say sure we're going to have games but it's not showing up in the stream or it's not going to do the same thing that Facebook did where it shows up in feeds.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll be like how I think how Yahoo games were.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just its own section.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can go to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it'll be how most people I think would prefer to see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't keep it off my stream but you can have some cool games in their own little game section.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played Lexiolus for the longest time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's why I'm also glad to see PopCap didn't go with Zynga, although for Zynga's benefit, that would have been a huge win for them because at least PopCap can prove that they've done a bunch of other stuff in the other place.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's at least that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so let's move on with another story.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what I have is actually a little bit more...
[SPEAKER_10]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: EA is going to be doing another bit of online service shutdowns taking down a bunch of multiplayer games and demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Army of Two, bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: TheDemo, Bye, Battlefield 2142, Bye, Battlefield 2, Modern Combat, Demo, Medal of Honor Airborne, Medal of Honor Heroes 2, NASCAR 09, NCAA Basketball 10, NCAA Football 10, Need for Speed Most Wanted, Need for Speed Undercover, Skate for PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Tiger Woods, PGA Tour 10 and 11.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those are all going down on August 11th And on October 1st, Madden NFL 10 and NHL 10
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucks to be the guy that paid $10 to play those games online yesterday.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously those games were out well before the whole $10 thing took off, but can't wait to see when the inevitable next wave of server shutdowns comes out and something that you paid $10 because you bought it used a couple years after the fact to play online suddenly shuts down.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll go over real well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, at least most of those games are like old sequels, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like they're old games and series that have newer sequels.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they probably have a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one's playing those games online anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're not exactly, people are going to cry over them, but it's going to be very interesting when we get to the $10 games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I hate when they shut down stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I haven't really ever played this in the arcade, but I'm definitely familiar with the music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune is coming to arcades, number four, that is, in December in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm assuming we can expect more of the wonderful music in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the stuff that they are going to be adding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Connected Ghost Battle Mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'll be able to battle ghost records around the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can challenge the top ghosts in the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're also going to have a team function.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can create your own teams.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put team-specific stickers on your cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not sure if that's going to make the international version.
[SPEAKER_05]: New cars, including the Mazda RX-7.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mitsubishi Starion, Nissan Skyline Coupe V36, Infiniti G37 Coupe, RUF CTR Yellowbird, RUF RGT, Subaru Legacy B4 5th Generation, Toyota Crown 13th Generation, and yet unannounced car.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also some new courses, Yokohama Line and Yesu Route.
[SPEAKER_05]: 830HP
[SPEAKER_05]: so uh that's kind of cool I mean I don't know I I know that there's definitely in the arcade scene nowadays it's all about racing games um I mean that's really popular so it'll be kind of cool hopefully this stuff makes it over here yeah it'd be nice uh as I was saying at the top of the show that's a pretty awesome racing series so I do hope we see that show up over here
[SPEAKER_04]: Charles Smith, Professor of Family Studies, Kansas State University
[SPEAKER_04]: He says that there's this big hysteria about violence in video games, but it's context and the type of game that's important.
[SPEAKER_04]: The type of child is important as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a quote.
[SPEAKER_04]: A child without a connected parent relationship, one who doesn't have respect for their parents and plays a violent video game over a certain length of time, would worry me.
[SPEAKER_04]: But banning video games completely isn't the right answer either.
[SPEAKER_04]: He goes on to say that banning games might make them more attractive to children.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quote, the realism in video games is changing constantly because of technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: This causes more realistic violence and video games are becoming more and more immersive in terms of their nature.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's talking about how, you know, the technology is always changing and this can kind of be a concern.
[SPEAKER_04]: But ultimately, at the end of the day, he says that parents, they need to be educated, they need to be aware about what games they're letting their children play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Without that parent-child relationship...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: He knows what he's talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need him to go against Leland Yee in what is needed for kids and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on with the mailbag and see what offensive things you guys are going to email us this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com is the place to email us every week and DarkSakura will dive in head first and read some emails for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have some.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have four emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, four?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: But first of all, person, you misspelled Voltaire.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's V-O-L-T-A-I-R-E.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you're going to quote somebody, which, quoting Voltaire is fine by me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Make sure you spell it right, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mailbag, hi, we haven't spoken in a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to let you in on this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I came ahead quite a bit since I started a week ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just have a read.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that a spam email?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you that's a spam email.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to watch out for that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We get tons of spam in the email box.
[SPEAKER_10]: well I I should just ignore bad grammar anyway okay hello comrades I'm sorry it's funny that that still was signed with something that they're quoting a philosopher I find that funny I'm sorry three emails hello comrades I hope that all of you are doing well firstly I wanted to thank you for the great show very entertaining just like shooting an AK while intoxicated just joking I don't drink
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you guys think of the future of GTA?
[SPEAKER_10]: Will the next installment be as serious and realistic, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_10]: gray and muddy as the previous one?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or will it perhaps return to a much more hilarious style like San Andreas with much more customization and humor?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is really a Loki question, if anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, I know you're rocking out over there, but Grand Theft Auto, what would the next one be like?
[SPEAKER_04]: Would it be serious or whimsical?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that they're going to try to bring back what they did in San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, kind of keeping it grounded a little bit, but have a little bit of extra fun stuff like the miniguns and the parachutes and a little bit of ridiculous stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think they've got to step it up a little bit as far as whimsical and crazy because of Saints Row the Third, but I still think they're going to try to keep it a little bit somewhat realistic, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you're definitely going to see kind of like a Sandra is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hope they get rid of the I kind of call it like dating your friends where oh hey let's go bowling or hey I want to go play air hockey I don't want to fucking play air hockey with you I want ho mode DarkSakura I'm with you I want more hoes I want ho mode where you play as a whore I think there needs to be a mode where when she says I want to go play air hockey you should say shut up bitch and suck my dick
[SPEAKER_05]: See?
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is why Saints Row, in some ways, is a better game than Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Saints Row 2 does have whore mode, where you can play as a whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can be a man whore, and you can go... Oh my god, why am I not playing this game?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of the side missions you can do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played the first Saints Row and I was like, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you need to play Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I borrow it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to be a man-whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a fucking awesome game.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can borrow it when you lend me Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up, bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I'm practicing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey-ho.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you play as a man-whore?
[SPEAKER_05]: Big Bang Bar A Little More To The Left
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's seriously, they have scenes where they have a mode where, I don't even remember what the hell it's called, it's basically you in one of those bunny suits, you know how they have the bunny suits, Intel and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right in ATV, on fire, and everything you run into explodes!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just such an awesome game!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: If this game convinced Loki to get a gold star in man-whoring, I've got to check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll loan it to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the third, man, the third's going to be even better than this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't fathom how awesome this is going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was there more to the email?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, there is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're stuck thinking about hosts.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also want to inform you guys of this great game I played as a kid.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's called Dark Earth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, I want to see how old this is if he said he played it as a kid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it links to something in archaeology.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll find it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Post-apocalyptic action adventure game for the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: When did it come out?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was canceled for PS2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dark Earth, 1997 September 30th, 1997 You were a kid in 97, shut the fuck up I'm not reading any more of this Don't be mean to the emailers It featured an amazing story and the graphics were pretty impressive at the time If you have the time, check it out, you won't regret it Stay frost, comrades, Stanislav
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm reading up on this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually never played this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a PC only game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember this game actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen it before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I never played this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Third person game centering around item collection and weapon based combat.
[SPEAKER_04]: The environments of the game were pre-rendered with 3D modeled characters moving atop them like Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will have to check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email comes from... Thanks for the game, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: The next one.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I was saying thanks for the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I read the damn email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did any of you see the Forza 4 trailer on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched it and it starts with this claim.
[SPEAKER_10]: All in-game footage.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then, unless I'm wrong, it shows you the CG render intro to the game followed by footage from the game which I'm not sure looks any different than Forza 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: CG renders are not in-game footage even if they are part of the game media.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only way that could be in-game footage is if there was a special car viewer section that does nothing else.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder if that is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that the one that blasted the Kanye West song when you watched the trailer?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't watch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Racing games always have, at least these days, have pretty impressive graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of it goes by so fast you can't really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also have to paste how Rob signed his email because you'll only get it if you know DOS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh God.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And to read it out for the listeners, 10 print, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: 20 print, B.
[SPEAKER_10]: 30, go to 20.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, that's basic, not DOS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have an icon that says the home sweet home one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I spent a lot of time on Commodore 64 Basic in my youth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, you kids were playing Dark Earth.
[SPEAKER_04]: When I was a kid, I was typing.
[SPEAKER_10]: What were the commands?
[SPEAKER_10]: Run, quote, game, quote, comma, eight, comma, no, asterisk, A, asterisk, B.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Earth Dark Earth Dark Earth Dark Earth
[SPEAKER_10]: I used to have one of those that you play games on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, last email.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dun, dun, dun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, gang.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Ramaditya.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope I said that right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I spoke to Rob earlier, and as a blind gamer, I would like to give my personal thoughts about one of the topics brought up in the last show.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is about an invention that can help blind persons see, use, and connect as assistive device.
[SPEAKER_04]: I asked for an email like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, because my English vocabularies are somewhat limited, I'll try to explain it as best I can.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope you can catch what I mean.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is what I understand.
[SPEAKER_10]: In order to make the connect work, it needs to recognize the visual objects it points to.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, if I want to know that there is a glass in front of me, I must point my connect to it, and an audio message will tell me there is a glass.
[SPEAKER_10]: It means that my connect must have proper information about the object so that it can recognize it properly, so the object must contain something special that the connect can recognize.
[SPEAKER_10]: With this aid, we are faced with the circumstance that visual objects are a lot, color, shape, letters, etc.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it is probably impossible for the device to recognize all of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, if I stand in front of the mall, it will be difficult for the device to identify various activities in front of me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Walking people, running children, moving trolley, etc.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the device may not be able to replace working eyes, but there is still a way to make the device useful and more effectively.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need a specific object that can universally be recognized.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a coincidence that the idea came from Rob himself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, QR code can be one.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's basically QR code usually contains text or number, and those are universal, e.g.
[SPEAKER_10]: the numbers are number 9 is the same around the world, letter A is also the same, and many other examples that you can make yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we use the device like a reading tool or transportation recognizer, and it's like what Rob told.
[SPEAKER_10]: When it scans the QR code attached to the bus, it would speak, bus to Canada goes at 7 a.m.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another example, the inventor can install a small GPS so that it can help blind people navigate easily.
[SPEAKER_10]: You are facing north, the device says, and when you walk straight, it finds a QR code embedded at the next exit door that will read, northern exit, go south to Dunkin' Donuts.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to implement Kinect as a gaming device which is accessible for the blind, perhaps bodily movement can be considered as a universal target that the device can recognize.
[SPEAKER_10]: Perhaps when you play one-on-one lightsaber battle, both players can face each other and use Kinect like a lightsaber, and the device held by the blind player can inform the position or movement his or her opponent makes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Combined with the sound effects from the game, it can be great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Another possible implementation is to use the device in card games like, well I forget, but there was that one PS3 one which came out with the physical cards.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have judgment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the one where you all bet if I could sell one million and Loki must dress as Tingle?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, correct.
[SPEAKER_10]: The physical cards must contain label or QR code that tells Kinect which cards the player holds so the player can use it properly based on information given by Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, this is dragon card facing up, this is golem card facing down, etc.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, that's my personal thought about the topic, but I do support whatever result may come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, before I conclude this email, let me give you my YouTube video.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's me playing Frog's Theme with my recorder.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope you and all you listeners can enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't he send us a recorder link before?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I remember this guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to copy it to you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll bring it up here real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, first off, I think if I understood the point of the email correctly, it was that I'm a genius for my idea with the QR codes last week, so I totally agree with the email 100%, might I say.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're so awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I do have to say, if English isn't your first language, you still did a fantastic job.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, you did better than some people who email us.
[SPEAKER_10]: You did better than people who have grown up here all of their lives, so thank you for being awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me bring this up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that because you know he's got a deep appreciation for this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I want to say the last video I saw of him playing the recorder was like Scars of Time, I think it was.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: So clearly this kid loves his chrono.
[SPEAKER_04]: He played it with the music and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, he loves his chrono.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's great that even though he's blind, he kind of has that appreciation.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it's hard for a lot of us to understand sometimes what it's like in that position.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But certainly, I can also agree that kind of what he says at the end of the email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, anything that will help is a good thing, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, see, this is kind of actually... It's funny because I was actually having this thought about the use of QR codes to provide...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: or even like an iPhone app that you can hold up your phone, read the code, and it'll have a speaker attached to it that says so-and-so or record voice signal or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we have all these technologies now, like the QR code.
[SPEAKER_04]: GPS is so cheap to implement in devices now, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we're just a matter of time away.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to tell you, though, and I'd actually like to get some of our blind listeners' feedback on this, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I watched a special probably a couple years ago about using audio location to be able to tell distance.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a guy blind from birth riding a bicycle down a street that had cars all around, people crossing the street, and making clicking noises.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he was able to tell his location and what was close to him by the clicking sound.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I was thinking, you know...
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Crazy thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, just real quick, some folks are requesting the video so that they could watch it at full volume.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's a link right there in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I put that there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to those folks that are listening on the podcast feed, but you'll just have to do a search for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was it labeled as?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me see what it's labeled as real quick here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that the last email, by the way?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that was the last email.
[SPEAKER_04]: The name on YouTube is Ramaditya Skywalker, R-A-M-A-D-I-T-Y-A Skywalker, S-K-Y-W-A-L-K-E-R.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can look that up, and I'm sure, I think he probably has, it's 61 videos, so who knows what else is in there, but I'm assuming there's a lot of recorder stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see, yeah, Tin Whistle, Ship, yeah, he's got some other videos too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a Tin Whistle.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have two of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm not any good at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I should learn to play my melodica.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe we could do a YouTube duet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do a duet?
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it for the Mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to send in your emails for a future week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, let's get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would like to say F you to my skin for not getting quite as much sun as I wanted today.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I am happy to say that I don't have skin cancer yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to people being sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh my fu of the week goes to this microphone because i think it's dying and i really don't want to buy another microphone but fine if that's what i have to do i will uh and um fu to i don't know my skin too my skin sucks too like i have the whole like this is gonna be gross but i have like the whole like flaky thing going on in some parts this is gross i hate it i know i use i use similar stuff i do but it only lasts so long and then it's like
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the reason why I'm actually, and I hate to plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: An F you to the outro playing right there.
[SPEAKER_10]: To plug, you know, because they're not paying us clearly.
[SPEAKER_10]: But since I started using, I'm using the Hoofmaker stuff, and it actually made the eczema on my knuckles go away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny enough, my hands are fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: My hands, never a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I get a lot of compliments on my hands.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I've started using it on my knees.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it, I'm just saying, it helps.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, anyhow, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple quick stories for you guys in the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just watching video for some of the Saints Row 3rd stuff just because it's fun watching the video over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: They announced their Hyper Ordinary Pre-Order Pack, and this will be included with games that you pre-order, I'm assuming, anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, it...
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe just certain outlets.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's Professor Genki's Hyper Ordinary Pre-Order Pack.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets you a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Professor Genki suit, which Professor Genki, if you don't know about the game, it's this weird...
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A catapult.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's a manapult.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can suck pedestrians up into the cannon and fire them out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, of course, there's a weapon that's an octopus gun that fires octopuses that land on people's heads.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if that's not crazy enough for you, they have the platinum pack that's available, which I'm seriously considering buying this, that comes with a headset that auto-tunes your voice automatically.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of worth it in the price of there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as well as the soundtrack, and I'm sure some other fun bonuses in there as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, the headset does not work with Xbox Live or the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it does, but you have to buy a little adapter.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still worth it to have a headset that auto-tunes your voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might be worth it just for this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could do a whole show auto-tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's funny that the subject of Auto-Tune came up on last night's Under Sedation Live, and you've got to check out this app on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Songify, and it's an app where you can make instant songs out of whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I don't want to rip off the bit from USL, but I feel like now I have to demo it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here's Songify, and what should I sing about?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell me what to sing about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sing about hemorrhoids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not going to sing about hemorrhoids.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's gross.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sing about... I'll sing a song about Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sing about Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'll sing a song about Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki went to Round Table Pizza and got a pizza with cheese and pepperoni but no bacon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so now it's going to do its thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did it wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't recording that whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, live radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki went to Roundtable Pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: He didn't get the bacon pizza because bacon makes you fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki went to Roundtable Pizza He didn't get the bacon pizza Because bacon makes you fat Pizza He didn't get the bacon pizza Because bacon makes you fat
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, went to Roundtable, Loki, went to Roundtable Pizza So obviously it's not perfect because, you know, it kind of cuts out a little bit there, but this duo is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Songify, you said?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Songify, it's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Download it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the way they make money is you can download other add-ons and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like for instance, I just got one that says, sounds like you can sing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you tried La Di Da?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rumor is Kesha uses it to sing better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cute little things like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I have to tell you.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know how we talked about the blow video?
[SPEAKER_10]: I found out who the director was and he did some other videos that are freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_10]: This guy is like amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, well, that was the director.
[SPEAKER_10]: We found the director's other videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, anyway, I had to say that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was me and Becky and Susan in here just watching the hell out of these.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was so funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, one more story for you guys here, and it has to do with sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more of an opinion piece, but since we're a little short on news tonight, I thought I'd... By the way, I'm loving these comments in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: People trying to vote for that song in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't vote for that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop it.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_09]: Songify?
[SPEAKER_04]: Songify.
[SPEAKER_04]: S-O-N-G-I-F-I-Y or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why you should stop hating on sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an opinion piece that came from VentureBeat.com and talks about why sports games, you know, a lot of the masses tend to hate on sports games because it's roster update and it's another fucking Madden games coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who buys those games anyway, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a sports guru for Electronic Arts says as part of this story, quote, "...the point of our games is not reenacting throwing a football, but the spirit of the sport and letting gamers fulfill their sports dreams.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are real players.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are real events, and there is real angst.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to reenact reality."
[SPEAKER_04]: The opinion piece goes on to talk about how sports games have a role in driving forward innovation for the entire video game industry, and that's why you should take them seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess goes on to talk about NBA 2K11, the game that reenacts some of basketball's finest moments because that was the one that brought back Jordan in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess saying that some people were too young to experience that back in 92, but the video game helps them relive an experience that they actually missed the first time around.
[SPEAKER_04]: The games include tons and tons of commentary from people that actually commentate on sports in the real industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I think a lot that kind of went through this as well and it talked about that I thought made a good point is having to re-up the reality of these games every year the opinion piece from VentureBeat.com says sports games are a main source of revenue for electronic arts so a lot of the innovation in terms of graphics and realistic physics happens in that department and trickles down to other games
[SPEAKER_04]: EA, for example, uses the collision engines originally built for Madden in games like Battlefield 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Each year, those teams build and rebuild physics and animation engines for their in-game characters, and then other games reap the rewards of those engines.
[SPEAKER_04]: Physics and animation in our very core games has been very driven by sports games since the inception of the technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: that physics and animation had to be in a sports games for many years shooters didn't need it and then it goes on to talk about artificial intelligence is a big part of that as well when you play against sports teams and then the sports franchise did start this whole once a year cycle but World of Warcraft does the same thing Calls of Duty, Modern Warfare DDR I would throw out there again and
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that you have to appeal to everyone's fandoms.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not every guy out there is going to like to play the RPGs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not every girl out there is going to like to play adventure games.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got a market there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sports especially, well actually really all over the world.
[SPEAKER_10]: Football is such a big thing in Europe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm talking about real football, not the shit we call football here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an opinion, young lady.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, and I'm talking about an opinion piece, so I'm giving my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fine, fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't judge me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Judging a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Counter-judge.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's important, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: First of all, it's a source of revenue.
[SPEAKER_10]: That means that for every Madden game EA puts out, we get another Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's a necessary evil.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have to like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chatroom at chat.orange.com, TigerClaw says, So all the nerds are complaining about sports games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't they realize that some of the most beloved video games are sports games that nerds enjoy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Blades of Steel, Mario Kart, anyone?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I posted about this to my Google+, and I got some really interesting comments.
[SPEAKER_04]: And because I didn't say that I would read them on air, I don't want to read them verbatim on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will just kind of summarize.
[SPEAKER_04]: One comment that I thought was very interesting was about
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody who said, you know, I really enjoy the sports games, especially the football games And why I like them is that I can't really play sports games Or I can't play football IRL I can't play professional football because I'm a tall skinny dude I'm not built for professional football These games let me live out that experience And that kind of ties into what the beginning of that article said How, you know, it's about letting folks kind of
[SPEAKER_04]: Reenact an experience, I guess you could say.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I could see the same thing with basketball.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you have to be a very certain body type to be able to really play competitive basketball.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the same reason why people do fantasy football and whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I still think, though, they're dodging the actual problem with sports games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not even just going to limit it to sports games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can be a lot of games that feel that they need to release a new title in the franchise every year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the fact that they don't change very much year to year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that still didn't address the fact that when people call it just a roster update, they tweak a few things to make things more realistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why does that justify another $60?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I don't really think that you went back to the ground level and rebuilt the whole game from scratch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that you're just tweaking it a little bit to make it a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Tweaks like that can be done to older games and then patched in.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't understand why you need to release a game every year.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about the idea of just throwing it out there that sports games set the bar so to speak that other games end up using?
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole physics and engine being used in Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I've seen... Well, the guy from Electronic Arts said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's not biased at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Electronic Arts, a company that makes a ton of its money off of sports games, and they have some of the largest sports franchises out there, would totally not be skewed towards sports games at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's going to say, well, you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our games aren't very realistic at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Every bit of game research, no matter the type of game, can benefit.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, if you want a realistic...
[SPEAKER_10]: Physics, for example.
[SPEAKER_10]: A sports game actually is a really good judge of doing realistic physics.
[SPEAKER_10]: For example, you want to know how fully inflated basketball is going to bounce on a certain type of floor with a certain type of push.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to program all that in.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, say that you take that into, like, for example, Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they do, suddenly they have, like, you can play basketball in Sims.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, say that at the same time you take, like...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: No one can jump like 50 feet in the air and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, there's a little bit of fantasy there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I mean, if they really want super realistic games, then why aren't they building Madden in the Crytek engine or Unreal 3 or something like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell, there was Backbreaker, a game that had really realistic physics, and that sports game didn't sell very well at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think that...
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, people, yeah, I understand there's a lot of people that, oh, I can't play real sports, so I'm going to play this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't drive a race car, but I'll still drive a car and a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't go murder people, but I'll still play a game like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me read some comments from chat because the chat room is lighting up on this story and I think there's some really excellent comments in the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_04]: From all sides of the spectrum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xenacore says, Rob, that's bull crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: The updates they do to the engine are no better than patches.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really don't get your money's worth if you keep up year to year.
[SPEAKER_04]: How often do your other examples charge full price for an incremental update?
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakroom in chat says, I couldn't play in the NFL because I would pee myself if I saw some guy like Ray Lewis looking at me like he's going to kill me.
[SPEAKER_04]: He just might kill me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every NFL game I have played has been different in some way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes there are slight differences.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya says, Yeah, that's why I love Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legally, I can't really drive, but I've always grown up loving cars.
[SPEAKER_04]: In games like that, let me imagine what it's like driving an expensive car I'll never own really freaking fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really good analogy there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Breakroom also says, I love Dragon Quest games, and I will buy the next Dragon Quest game.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much have those games really changed?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be fair, you do have a whole new story, new characters, new environments, new maps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I really follow the DQ analogy because they're completely different stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's talk about sports games here.
[SPEAKER_05]: NCAA football.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the big updates this year was all the pre-game rituals, like the different mascots coming across the field and the little tweaks and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All stuff that you would say, yes, lends to the experience, but not necessarily the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that the fact that the mascot looks realistic and does whatever the mascot does normally in the game lends itself to playing a better football game.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'd say the same thing with Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that they really need to release a new game each year.
[SPEAKER_05]: To their credit, though, at least there's a new storyline that goes along with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's a little bit of something.
[SPEAKER_05]: But sports games, though, you don't need to write a new story for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a sports game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless it's wrestling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the gaming community rejected music games doing this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our opinion with DDR and such is a little bit skewed because those were games we really loved.
[SPEAKER_04]: But games like Guitar Hero failed because the market was too saturated with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band, essentially Harmonix has said, you know what, we need to take a break from Rock Band because Rock Band 3 unfortunately didn't sell well because there were just so many Rock Band games coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think sometimes these yearly update games get rejected by the marketplace.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I want to read a couple other comments from chat and then go to our phone lines because I'm sure folks want to call in on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Quickly, DarkSakura, before I go to chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well I was actually, there is an exception to the rule when it comes to the sports games and I really think it's the wrestling games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that makes sense to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let me go to the chatroom at chat.orangelaunchery.com for a couple more comments.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Dollar Bill in our chatroom says, I can't drive real cars, but doing it online was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, and flying sims are fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I gotta say, even though I might talk about, eh, I don't play a lot of sports games I don't play a lot of Madden because I'm not super into football I don't play a lot of basketball games because I'm not super into it Although it is the sport I probably enjoy more than most others And I do love NBA Jam, the old one I'm not as big on the new one, but I'm curious about this whole arcade one they're putting out, you know
[SPEAKER_04]: Super high impact But one thing, one game I love are racing games I love a lot of those racing games But I usually like the arcade racers more than I like the realistic ones Like I can't do Forza, I can't do Gran Turismo But I loved Blur, I like Mario Kart I really loved F-Zero I will always love F-Zero What about Initial D?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sports games have been around since the first arcade game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically tennis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, let's see, one other comment.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did I want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Break Room says, I love sports games, but when I have ever tried to play in real sports, I was never any good.
[SPEAKER_04]: A skinny white guy doesn't line up well in high school sports, but give me a controller and it's fun to pretend.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt says, Listen, I've been a hockey fan for most of my life and used to play when I was younger.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the game of hockey so much that I gladly pay for the yearly update NHL games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoy playing the game because it's the closest I can get to playing with my favorite players and favorite teams than I can possibly ever get.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would gladly pay the yearly $60 cost to play the game that I truly enjoy watching, playing, and being a fan of.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, we're going to go to the phone here, but while we wait for the calls to come in, I will ask Loki quickly if he has any last-minute stories he wants to share with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if there's anything that came up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it was a very busy Newsweek.
[SPEAKER_05]: We might have hit on it all.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is a... There may have been one thing or two that we hadn't hit up on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to remember how long they were, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking it up real quick here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there was something that we missed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you know the story that Loki missed.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, it's coming up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a story.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I do have a last minute story, but we'll wait until after this call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, let's do the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yo, guys, it's Xenacore from the OKC.
[SPEAKER_08]: How y'all doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Xenacore.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's it going in the OKC?
[SPEAKER_08]: Man, I'm pissed off, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went off to work, I set my DVR to record the World Cup, and of course it stopped recording right before the shootout.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I know how it ended, I didn't get to see how it ended.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, you missed the... It's so funny about soccer games that come down to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That whole five minutes is like the entire game right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: It gets right before they start running out on the field, and it's like, this is the end of the recording.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, oh, you bastard, I'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, how is OKC these days?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a city I haven't been to since I was 17.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hot, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel like going through the whole Good Morning Vietnam rant about it being too hot in Vietnam, but I'll tell you the truth.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, after you've been in 130, 100's nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, I guess we should bring it back to games, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's on your mind about the gaming world today?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been sort of preparing for Dark Souls the best way I can.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I put Demon's Souls back in my machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a game I need to go back and play more of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Demon's Souls is so unkind, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game is just not nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this time I'm backing myself up with the wiki.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Demon's Souls wiki, they put so much information in that thing, it's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now there's a plan.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now all I have to do is survive it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you want to play a game like Demon's Souls?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that game is too fucking hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you a masochist, sir?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, because you have to struggle to truly achieve anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: And most of the games nowadays just hand you the ending on a silver platter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_08]: All you have to do is, oh, I played it for 50 hours.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm almost near the end now.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no challenge in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't have to get better at the game to see the ending.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sir, I think that might have been a dig at Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not quite sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, this is gaming in general, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm covering the whole scope.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you hope they improve on in the next incarnation of the Souls series?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only thing they could really improve on is maybe if they could get the whole environment into one gigantic streaming level, like just a big-ass castle.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that way, although you can teleport to different areas of the castle, you can actually walk the whole thing from one thing to the other.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would actually be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: You calling and asking about that game makes me really want to go back and play it, because I'll tell you, I didn't get very far, even though I spent hours...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you got to talk to Pandit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of everybody in the all-games community, I can think of, she's probably the one person I know of that's actually finished it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, finished?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, she's got a character that's like level 120 or something, so you know you have to put some time in to get a character that high.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's dedication.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anything else on your mind this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just that and the whole thing about the incremental updating for the sports games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, if it was on a PC, you'd just get patches now and again for all that information.
[SPEAKER_08]: Granted, the fans who want to pay it just so they can have the updated team rosters, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they'd just be just as happy if they got it in a patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't a lot of that crap also DLC?
[SPEAKER_08]: it could be DLC too like for instance yeah an updated Rouser cost you three bucks or whatever they wouldn't have to release a whole new game it would be nothing but profit they wouldn't have to reprint or anything else like that you know now that the DLC has been pushed out there I could see them easily doing that but I don't think they want to like most of the executives will do don't mess with the money you know so keep it coming the way they're used to paying for it and maybe we can keep that money coming in the way we want it alright so I'm going to let you go so we can get some more calls but thanks for your call
[SPEAKER_08]: No problem, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can take it easy.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Zeether from the chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zeether!
[SPEAKER_04]: I recognize your name, but I think you're also a first-time caller, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I'm a first-time caller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Long-time listener, first-time caller?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, Zeether?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I was just, you guys were talking about Wonga on Maximum Tune.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that was really, I was really hyped for that because I've been following it ever since it was announced and they had the trailer put out and the music already sounds really good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, the trailer just has like a little mix of the various songs, but it sounds fantastic.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really hope they release like a soundtrack CD for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, like they did the other games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, those soundtracks are awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever actually driven to those soundtracks?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, actually I did.
[SPEAKER_13]: I used to drive from high school and back while listening to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how fast did you go?
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't make me drive faster though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'll tell you, some of that music makes me just want to drive faster.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will say nothing about the LA trips.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, and, oh yeah, have any of you guys played the PS2 game, the Wangan PS2 game?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was like Tokyo Extreme Racer, kind of.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have not.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was one on PlayStation 3 that Loki imported, but it was not like the arcade games at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of bad, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wangan Midnight.
[SPEAKER_13]: just Wangan Midnight was the one there actually was one on the PS2 and it was released in the arcades as Wangan Midnight R and it was basically like a Tokyo Extreme Racer type game and the music in it was different from like the standard trance music it was more orchestral
[SPEAKER_13]: Yuzo Koshiro
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Last time I played Streets of Rage was on the Sonic's Mega Genesis Collection or whatever for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I have the PS3 one actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's got like Streets of Rage 1, 2, and 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a great deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Along with a shit ton of other Genesis games.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, any other games we should be looking out for this week?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, nothing else.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was just calling about Wongun because I'm a pretty big fan of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Initial D. Initial D.
[SPEAKER_13]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, those are the games that are kind of keeping some arcades afloat right now with actual arcades as opposed to kiddie gambling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you go to the local Golf Land here, those are really the only games that made me stop and go, ooh, I kind of want to actually spend money on this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there's so much crap now, you know, that spit out tickets and so forth.
[SPEAKER_13]: The sad thing is the newer initial D games, like versions 5 and 6, they have not gotten proper English versions because Sega probably just gave up on localizing them.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the good news is the PlayStation 3 is region-free, so hopefully this new game that they're releasing in the arcades, maybe we'll get a decent home version of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if it's only in Japan, at least we can import it over here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I've been considering getting a PS3 because of the initial D game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've watched all of the anime, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are really into these games, then, if you've gone so far as to watch the anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we've got to let you go to get some more calls, but thanks so much for your call, alright?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: and here's a hint, don't go driving down a barren freeway to the soundtracks of one of those games because you might not realize how fast you were going.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, let me have you work on your story real quick here before I go back to the phone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, the story is actually that the creator of VVVVVV made a Super Meat Boy tribute, sort of.
[SPEAKER_10]: He did a Super Meat Boy flash game that's in the style of his own game, VVVVVV.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's actually available at distractionware.com slash games slash flash slash meat boy And he says it's only a couple of screens long and very broken I can't wait for the next team meat game, just saying Let's go to the phones and take another call Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Spazinator Hey Spazinator, what's on your mind buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: A couple things, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: To touch on what we were talking about a few minutes ago with the whole EA constantly releasing new games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, in fact, you had mentioned, I believe, why don't they just release yearly patches instead of releasing new games.
[SPEAKER_01]: To use an analogy, I'll ask a rhetorical question.
[SPEAKER_01]: How much did DarkSakura pay for the 4.2 patch in World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, nothing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, that kind of illustrates the point that you can't really charge for patches.
[SPEAKER_01]: They can update the...
[SPEAKER_04]: Madden 20 billion times you know with patches but you can't really make $60 off patches let me play devil's advocate here for a minute though you could say that she got the patches free but you could also say she's paying $14.95 a month to get the patch because you know MMOs are kind of their own little beast because you do pay a subscription fee for most of them now granted some are free to play but they just make their money in other ways
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_01]: Perhaps I really picked a really poor example for my analogy.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: But even if you had, let's say, Uncharted 1, the patch analogy would apply because there's no monthly charts for Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: But now...
[SPEAKER_01]: If they were to release, you know, the yearly increments in Madden on desk, you know, with the, you know, then, yeah, they can make their 60 bucks every single time, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of like, I don't know, why kill the goose that's laying the golden eggs, or at least gimp it anyway, when they can keep it nothing healthy and kill all the golden eggs, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's kind of like making sequels to movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't release those for free, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, one final note before I do let you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a quick update as to what's going on with my PlayStation 3 thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know everyone's kind of asking about it, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, right now, Game Repair is temporarily on hold, if only because of bureaucratic red tape with my Social Security Disability Payee's offices.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have put in a request.
[SPEAKER_01]: for the extra funds for like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's a money issue right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just real life economical money stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And basically, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently I need to have her do some paperwork and I have to find data.
[SPEAKER_01]: They got taken care of.
[SPEAKER_04]: But to be fair, these are all things that have nothing to do with Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but to make a long story short, hopefully I'll have the money to have it repaired this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: and once I get the money, I'll get the ball rolling and get everything repaired.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well you'll have to let us know how that repair process goes once you get that taken care of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well Spassinator, we're going to let you go to get some more calls but thank you for your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good one and good luck with the PlayStation drama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1877-GAME-OLR or use your name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call and we'll talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, does anyone else have other stories they want to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: I do want to say that I've put some more stuff up on our Tumblr, including Gon's ending in Tekken 3 and some of the playthrough of Tekken Force Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should also do me a favor and put up the recorder video that we had talked about earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will do such a thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, I guess we have time for one more call, so let's go back to the... Whoa!
[SPEAKER_04]: There is feedback.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, caller, can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, gotta let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you check your connection?
[SPEAKER_04]: Echo 123, remember, is a good thing to call?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, I apologize to the listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was driving me bonkers.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit out of my control, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's try another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, what's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Kai Judo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Kai Judo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to make two points as far as the sports games just being an update roster type of thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not the biggest sports game player.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, every once in a while I'll pick up the NBA 2K series just because I like that series.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what I do notice when I do pick it up, maybe it's just because I wait a couple of years before I pick it up, they do add a lot more to the game, especially on the multiplayer side.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like right now in the NBA games, you can actually play like you and four other people can actually play five other people in line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like you'll be like one entire basketball team.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you could go up against another team of five, which I think is great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish they would put that in a baseball game, actually have nine versus nine in a baseball game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why they haven't done that yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure they can do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: but um you know they they they're pretty innovative is basically what I'm saying is that they they do add stuff other than just updating the roster you know what's interesting though is I do notice a common theme between what you're saying between what Matt's saying and between what I think I'm going to say for us and our support of DDR over the years even when a lot of people didn't get it and that is you know in chat SJ100 Matt said you know I pay 60 bucks a year gladly because I love hockey and this is
[SPEAKER_04]: How I Get Close to Hockey.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for you, it just sounds like it's replaced basketball with hockey.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for you, even though the rest of us might look at it and go, they don't even update anything in those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You look at it and go, oh my God, there's all these awesome new features that make it more realistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I kind of right here?
[SPEAKER_04]: That maybe not everyone gets it because not everyone is necessarily a huge fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas we look at DDR and we go, oh, but they've introduced, now you can do Marvelous as opposed to Perfects as well and it's a new thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not everybody gets that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just has to be your thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just have to be into it to really notice some of the subtle differences and the major differences that they do make in a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they do improve the game a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, the updated roster thing is kind of like a crazy argument.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the other thing I wanted to point out was sports games do actually have a story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you have to create the story on your own, just basically using your own imagination, kind of like an old D&D tabletop type of a game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there is story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, especially I can remember...
[SPEAKER_06]: I was playing Madden back in the early 90s when I was in my teens.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me and my friends had stories.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had rivalries going.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had tournaments going.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were playing with a lot of emotion behind those games because so-and-so beat my ass last week, so now I've got to come back and beat their ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, you know, it's just a lot of fun to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't want to fucking lose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, those are my two points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think those are fair points.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm weighing on my prize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you know what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a little slowed down.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have it sitting here and Loki has to sign it because we got folks, he ran out last week before I had a chance to have him sign it, but we're hoping to get that out to you Monday or Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, look out for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take your time.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, good night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye
[SPEAKER_04]: and see what we end up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, I hear it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Caller, are you there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like the emergency broadcast system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just, I can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to send in your thoughts, send us an email at mailbag at orangelaundry.com or you can, of course, always leave us a voicemail or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We try to get to those throughout the week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or send us a tweet, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, we're going to go around and get everybody's final thought before we wrap things up tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Loki, what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is... I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and DarkSakura, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Gon is pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: and my final thought tonight is even though I had a quesadilla today, now I want a taco.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want the complete Mexican food day.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I want.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jimmy Chunga.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's going to do it for another week here of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and staying up late with us if you're listening live or letting us be a part of your work day or evening or whatever it is you do when you listen to the show on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you just for spending the time with us and getting through all two and a half, three hours of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Help spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how we've done it over the years and have built our family up.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably how you found out about OLR was by somebody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: So please help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, we'll be back to do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another episode of Orange Lounge Radio with the latest in gaming news and most importantly, your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_07]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_07]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week!
Thank you.