Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Strike one down and another two pop up in its place
That's the story of how PUBG has banned 13 million accounts and counting
Cheaters and scammers know no bounds, but we've got better news of new content coming soon
Stay tuned for this and plenty more starting right now on the show, wherever Gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet, welcome back
It's another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Live tonight, episode number 747 for this, October the 7th, 2018
My name is Rob Roberts, joining you here in Sacramento, California
Studio N7, where our show is based
Live for the next few hours, talk about video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
With you guys in our live chat, as well as my co-hosts here in studio, say hello to Loki
Hello
How are you, Loki?
I'm good
Good, you're eating Korean BBQ on the show tonight
Yes
Yes, which is not something you usually get, because I thought Korean BBQ was very expensive
It is
There must be something very specific you were craving tonight
It's the bulgogi beef, but the problem is though, the bulgogi that you get with Takeout
Is not the same as the bulgogi that you cook at a Korean BBQ
It's like, it's thicker, it's covered with tons of barbecue teriyaki sauce
This was dry
Thankfully I ordered an extra side of teriyaki sauce
Thank gosh, thank gosh
So
That's funny because you had Korean BBQ, I had bulgogi BBQ
So it's like BBQ city tonight
And then a couple nights ago, I had Lucille's BBQ, the more southern BBQ type of stuff
Mmm
BBQ
We've just seen a BBQ fusion restaurant
That's right, there's BBQ with some orange entrees tonight
All of the BBQ
All of the BBQ, anyway
Dark Sakura, she is still out on leave
She'll be joining us a little later in the show for the Classic Game of the Week
But we do have someone else here in studio with us tonight
To help us along with Dark Sakura's absence
I'm very happy to welcome him to the show because I know he's been listening for a while
And he has a show of his own which is fantastic
And he came a very long way to be here
So all the way from Toronto, say hello everybody to Delvin
Hello
How are you?
I'm really good
So you have a show called Video Game Realness
That is correct
Well it's not your show, you're your friends
Yeah, it's a group of friends
It's a group of friends that all do it together
Tell us a little bit about Video Game Realness
So we started about 5 years ago I want to say now
You see a boat
And so, yeah, 5 years ago it's me, one of my old roommates Cameron and my two friends James and Michael
We just shoot the shit talking about video games because we used to do it all the time
Going to dinner and stuff
One day we just decided let's just put this on tape and record it
This sounds so familiar
Doesn't this sound familiar, Loki?
Yeah
So yeah, we
No, I love it
We just get together, talk about video games
It's usually quite random and quite stupid and silly but that's just how we are
Yeah, actually I loved, you know, again I would encourage folks to go listen to Video Game Realness
Although I notice your episodes are kind of sporadic
Yes
You just kind of do them when you feel like it
Yeah, we're on a regular schedule but, you know, life gets in the way and now we just do it when there's something to talk about
I respect that, I respect that but I will say, not to give away all your jokes
But on the most recent episode, something that had me rolling, you already know this
Was you guys were talking about the new Switch game that's coming out, Starlink
Yes
Which is Ubisoft's game
But we keep seeing all these in the trailers and in the Nintendo Directs
They're like, Star Fox is in Starlink
Yeah
So finish this joke here
So basically, every time Nintendo talks about the game, they pretty much promote it as a Star Fox game
Right
And I don't know what the game's about
I mean, they might kind of say it by Ubisoft, you know, they just kind of like skim over the details
Yeah
Yeah, so there's this comic out there, James had shared it with our group
I don't know the origin of the comic but basically it's like in three parts or whatever
Where someone had basically, was handing something to someone saying, I made this, right?
And then, but the person takes it and then says, no, I made this
So basically we considered this the same situation with Starlink
Right
Where Ubisoft has made the game and Nintendo has now just taken it and said, no, I made this
You made this? I made this
Yeah, yeah, just slapped Star Fox in there and now it's just Star Fox
That's right
Like, who knows what the game's about
The question is, is the game any good?
Who knows, who cares, it's a Star Fox game
It's a Star Fox game now
How dare you, don't ask these questions
Because all of the Nintendo tie-ins have been successful, you know, just like they did with what, the last Skylanders game
Did you buy it because it had Nintendo tie-ins in it?
No
No, no, I didn't
Because no one gives a shit about that
I sure did
And this is another choice of life game with a Nintendo tie-in that
You know what else I didn't buy was the one with Gamelan on Philips CD-i
So not every Nintendo crossover is successful, but some are kind of cool, so you never know
We'll see where this one goes, but I think it's pretty much a Star Fox game
Yeah
With some other characters
I made this
You don't know
I'll let video game realness hold the joke, I'll stop stealing it
They could have one of Gamelan, Link as a, you know, echo fighter in the next Smash Brothers game
I just, I think there's like a sense of pride that would never be violated by doing that in Smash Brothers
I really think so, I think Nintendo would really rather forget that ever happened
Or Linkette
Stop it right now
Alright, anyway
Go to our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Because like I said earlier, we do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice Geeks Network
vognetwork.com
6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
And going into our chat room, Tigerclaw says
Starling on the Switch is basically a new Star Fox game
That's exactly what Nintendo wants you to think
It's not
Please, stop making excuses for them
They need to make their own Star Fox game
I made this, I made this
However though, I'm completely fine with them not making their own F-Zero game
Because when it was Nintendo and Namco, that turned out just fine
Oh, that was the Triforce, that was Sega as well, wasn't that too
Yes, because Sega and Namco both know racing games, Nintendo, they have F-Zero
Nintendo makes great characters, alright anyway
Tigerclaw says what's interesting though, in the cutscenes that show Star Fox, or excuse me, Fox with a human
Fox is pretty short, he looks to be about 4 feet tall next to a human
And S.J. 100 Matt is calling out a few minutes in and Loki is already going after Nintendo
And which I oppose is sorry I'm late
Anyway, Delvin, I don't mean to take the spotlight off of you and video game realness
So you've been listening, I know, to OLR for a little while, which you know, thank you very much
But we got connected back when GamerX was kind of like coming up
Correct
Because we were trying to find other LGBTQIA plus, you know, all the colors of the rainbow
We were trying to find people to kind of connect with to propose a podcasting panel at GamerX
Which we did end up doing, but sadly you guys didn't make it to GamerX
Yeah, we couldn't make it out to the
But at least we still got connected, so that was the important part
That was the win in that situation, which was really cool
Yeah, so that was a while ago now
Because they did four years of GamerX and the last GamerX was like two years ago
So that was like six years ago
Crazy! So awesome
Tell me a little bit about why you're a gaming fan
What do you remember early on that like a gaming memory that made you a gaming fan?
Well, I got into gaming from a very young age
I think I was five or six
I got the NES for Christmas
And my sister and I, we didn't really know like what a Nintendo was
We'd kind of seen it in commercials or whatever
And then we got it for Christmas one year
And so my parents had this one box that we couldn't open
And so they left it there, and then they gave us this one box to open
If you open that box, Santa's gonna burn down the house
Yeah, kinda
So they gave us this one box to open and it was a joystick
And so we were like, well, why are you giving us a joystick?
And then we looked at the box and we just started clawing at it
And we were screaming and going crazy
And so that was like the moment when gaming started for me essentially
And they're like, no, I told you not to open it, now you don't get it
And it turns out the joystick was for a lawnmower that was in the box
Now go do the chores
No, it was a Nintendo in there
So at that time it was just NES games
We only had Mario
But my aunt, who lived in Texas at the time, had sent us a bunch of games from the US
Because they were a lot cheaper here in the US than it was in Canada
And one of those games that she sent was Mega Man 2
Which is my most favorite game of all time
I was gonna ask that because I know you're a big Mega Man fan
Like so much that Mega Man appears in your online presence
Correct, my gamertag, Mega Man X400
So tell us a little bit about this Mega Man love
Where does that come from?
It really just started from Mega Man 2
And I've always enjoyed the Mega Man series
It took me forever to actually beat Mega Man 2 as a kid
And then when I finally got it, it just clicked with me
And then that evolved into liking the X series
Which is my favorite of the Mega Man games
Which I've played through all of them
And they're just really fun
And they have great replayability and great challenge
You can play it in any which way you like
To make it more difficult if you want
You can try to speedrun it if you want or just play it for shits and giggles
I gotta ask you your thoughts on Mega Man 11
Although you probably haven't really had to play it yet
Because you've been out here, right?
Well I did play the demo
I played the demo at Fan Expo
Which is a big convention in Toronto
And so that was a lot of fun playing it there
I did get to play some of it on the plane right here
And it's great
Honestly, I think they did a really good job of this game
It was long overdue
Long, long overdue
I'm glad that they didn't go in the direction they did with Mega Man 9 and 10
With going back to the old retro design
They seem to have found a nice hybrid
Maybe it's not retro, but it looks like the old game
They didn't try to make it ultra fancy or force 3D in it
No, it has a good style to it
It's still in the original Mega Man series
But it is not the old Mega Man 2, 3, 4 style
With the NES 8-bit style
That they did with 9 and 10
Which I didn't quite like
It now has 4 different difficulty levels
Which I think is really good
It has super beginner, casual, normal, and then hardcore
Wait a minute, so you got hardcore for ultra
Is that going to be your mode at some point?
No, I'm just normal
So then you have slightly irritating
Which is normal
That would be your mode
So then you have casual
And so then we even have below that Bobby Black Wolf mode
Beginner
No, it's ok, he's in on the joke
It's fine, it's fine
The most basic of basic levels was made for Bobby Black Wolf
And it's fine
So basically what happens in beginner mode is
You almost take no damage
And if you fall, a little bird comes and picks you up
And puts you onto the next platform
So you can just get through the level
Oh my god, I love it
It's super easy
Ok, that's awesome
I know one place maybe some of the OLR listeners may have seen you before
If they don't participate with video game realness right now
They may be familiar with your Twitch
Because I know you and I have done co-streams
We've done Mario Kart
We did Mario Kart and we played 20XX
Which is not Mega Man
I remember when I streamed that game for the first time
You came into the chat and you were like
What is this?
I had no idea about the game until I saw you play it
And I purchased it immediately
And it is a really good game
And I generally don't like the
Roguelike style of gaming
Where you have to start all over again
But they do this one in a really good way
That incorporates the Mega Man style of playing
In with a roguelike
Which is really good
So tell us a little more about your Twitch
You're streaming right?
So I do stream rather passively right now
Because there hasn't been very much games to stream
But there's a whole slew of games coming out
Between now and when Smash Brothers comes out
So you'll be seeing me stream a lot more
On twitch.tv slash vgrealness
Nice! Love it
And by the way Bobby is speaking up in chat
He wants us to know
I didn't even beat beginner frown
There was this one platforming section
That was an autoscroller and I could never get through it
It was the one with destructible blocks
Oh yeah I had that trouble too
Because our Switch controllers
My kids busted them
Well they're not busted
But they occasionally drift
For no reason
No it's not even
I don't even think it's the kids that did it
I think it's just their controllers are pieces of shit
Is what it is
I've actually seen a lot on Twitter about like
Cleaning those controllers
How does dust get in there
In a way that affects analogies
Because I don't have this problem on any other controller
Oh and then the other thing that was fun
Is my kids wanted to play
Super Mario Party
And so you know I thought
They had some nice little additional pieces
That they have for the joy cons
To make them add the little wrist strap
And stuff like that
Those fuckers are nearly impossible to put on
And take off
I don't use them for that reason
What poor fucking design is this shit
Even when you put them on correctly
It's just impossible to take them off
They're pretty tight
Alright anyway what else I want to ask you about
New games that you're into
So we know about Mega Man
What else, I mean I'll get into your gaming week
So we can talk about specifics because you know we do that here
But like in a general sense what are some of the
Recent games you've really enjoyed
The one that I've
Played through the most recently was
Octopath Traveler
Which I know a lot of people
It's kind of a love hate game
Where you either really got into it because you like that style
Of game
But it is lacking in terms of a continuous story
And character development
I think it really did
Have the design sense
Where it was going to be
Made for a mobile game
That you would purchase in packages
Based on the characters that you purchased
I think, was that your show that got into a discussion
On that because I think you guys are apps
I heard that on a podcast somewhere about this game was very
Clearly designed for mobile
And I think that is like on the money
I think it was on the money
And they made efforts to kind of
Make character development later on
But it was very tapped on
But that being said, I do love the battle system
That is where the heart of the game is
And how you can
Do the battles and customize your
Jobs
And you get like advanced jobs later
Which just make it even like super easier
And just even talking with friends and like
Finding out how they beep certain bosses
Versus how I did it and just
There's so many different ways in which you can skin the cat
Basically
Well don't do that
But it's really great
And I'm pretty sure Square Enix will make
A Octopath Battle 2
It ended up selling like
It was the best seller that month in the US
So I'm sure that game really
Exceeded expectations in the US
Specifically
So there's gonna be like a Deca path
I mean I know Deca is 10
But I think we got into this in a previous episode
But there's going to be a sequel
And that will be good because it will give them a chance to really perfect
Now this formula I think
And the only thing they need to do to make a second game
Good is just a story that continues
And keep everything about the battle system
The same because it's
That we know is not going to be piecemeal like in the story
Correct
Make it a joining story and not just eight
Individual stories about people that
Don't connect
Makes sense
Awesome
Please chime in throughout the night
Tell us what you think about the news
And we're just really happy to have you here
Any social media shout outs to give while you're here?
You can follow us on our Twitter channel
Which is at VG Realness and of course I mentioned
Our Twitch channel
Twitch.tv slash VG Realness
We do have a YouTube channel as well
Which has like some of our old playthroughs
Because sometimes we would play games
Together as all four of us
Or together
Sometimes me and James would be playing
Final Fantasy 14 so all of our old
Video clips and stuff are on our YouTube
Channel as well which you can just search
Video game realness and it's on there
They are
I like to think so
I'm curious though
Am I the first guest you've had
From Canada?
In studio
Yes
I'm pretty sure we've had a Skype guest
From Canada
But in studio
I think we had guys from Vancouver
But as far as in studio
Yes
I'm pretty confident in saying yeah you're the first one from Canada
If I'm wrong
Dark Tetsuya will correct me shortly
Because he knows this show better than I do
Which is fine
That's why we have a wiki
Alright I appreciate that
What is the number one thing
People in the US should know about Canada
We don't all say A in a boot
You kind of did though a little bit
You definitely said A
Ok not all of us though
Maybe I did
But not all of us
You know what though good point
Now that I'm thinking about this
I have interviewed people at conventions randomly
And some of them may have been from Canada
But actually sitting in on the show
You've got to be the first
So SJ100Matt says Canada is great
I'm going up to Toronto later this month
And says poutine is the one thing we should know
I'm actually very thankful
That you actually brought with you
Ketchup chips
Oh yeah that's right
No no no
Why not they make sense
You put ketchup on french fries and hash browns
And other potatoes why not put them on chips
I get it
But you know what's funny
I was explaining this to you last night
We just had this hilarious
All these stupid differences between the countries
But right now for some reason
They're selling all dressed chips
Which we don't usually have in the US
But Ruffles or whatever is doing this
Random ass promotion
I should have also brought you Smarties
The chocolate candy
Not the little tart things
That we associate with
So we have Smarties as something different
Completely in Canada
And then I think the things
That you call Smarties we call pop rockets
Or something I can't quite recall
Because I'm not that candy person
Alright good to know
D'artizia in chat is confirming
I'm pretty sure he's the first Canadian we know
That's actually on the show
The ambassador to Canada
Delvin is here with us tonight
Yes queen
Alright let's get into our kickoff topic tonight
Which has to do with movies movies movies
Like this week it just seems like
All these video games suddenly
Want to turn into movies
Loki you want to tell us a little more about
What's going on this week with Hollywood's recent
Obsession with adapting more video games
When, correct me if I'm wrong
Video game adaptations
Like some have done okay
You know like Resident Evil
They've made how many of those movies
Because I think they do very well on Blu Ray
And home video and you know cult type of things
You know with the horror crowd
I know there's definitely a huge fandom of Resident Evil
And so forth so I think those movies have done
Okay but like I'm not thinking of like
You know how like when there's a big
Big movie like let's say Titanic
Right then suddenly Hollywood is like
What are all the other disasters in
History we need to suddenly make
A movie or or um
Titanic did well well then we need to remake
The Poseidon adventure right away
Right like Hollywood has this
Obsession with if one thing is big
So I'm trying to like
They have this obsession with we run out of ideas
And so now let's
Yeah we gotta remake everything
Scrape that barrel until there's no barrel left
Although I'm gonna get this off my chest
Right now because while many of you were
Seeing Venom in the theaters this weekend
My ass was there opening night to see
A Star is Born with Lady Gaga
The fourth remake of that movie
And all I'm gonna say is
Yes queen
Well all I'm saying is yes I am
Seeing Venom next week
No I don't really care to see it but it's a
Free movie my dad wants to hang out so
Sure
There's nothing else playing he's like
So you don't wanna go see A Star is Born like no
It's so good
I cried so much
She's queening out
Anyway no but my point is
Not every remake
But the thing about
Not to get too far this is a video game show but the thing about
Star is Born is that
The one in the 50's is about
Hollywood acting this one is very much about
Music making because obviously that's what Gaga
Does so it's like Grammys
But anyway
I can save that for another podcast
Let's talk about my point with this whole thing
Was why is Hollywood suddenly obsessed
With we've gotta make a video game
Movie because we have so many of them just coming out
I think because they're doing like well this
Is kind of Konami a little bit you know they're
Doing I think they have had some
Success with Castlevania as a series
And so now they're like yeah sure
You can make our properties into
Things so like first off we've got Dance Dance
Revolution being adapted
To something
What is there to adapt? Look
Well here's what they're saying and this
This is gonna be like
Real quick real quick cause I wanna address the
First question before we move on about like what is
Hollywood's obsession right now with this
Tigerclaw says movies based on video games are
Usually a hit or miss it depends on the source
Material some video game movies are better than
Others because they're closer to the source material
Than others Tomb Raider for example
That was a good video game movie I forgot
That was pretty recent but I didn't think that
One made I mean I didn't see the movie
I heard it was actually like decent
It was like it didn't it didn't like
Make a tragedy of the game or anything like it was
A good adaptation but I don't think it made
Shit tons of money
Like I don't even know if it made its budget back
But anyway like that's
Like a kind of a recent thing that
Came up so anyway sorry so
DDR where are we going with this
No we're good
Unfortunately so basically
Here is how
They summarize it
The project will explore a world
On the brink of destruction where only
The only hope is to unite
Through the universal language
Of dance
Fucking stupid
Um and since I know
A lot of people playing the home game are probably
Shouting various other movies that
Have been about DDR in the past
We have things like DDR the movie so we have
The FP La Machina
De Bailar a failed
DDR movie script floating around for the 2000s
That's what Rama says in chat at live.vognetwork.com
Um so this isn't necessarily
The first movie about DDR
But I mean here's the thing like
I I'm gonna say something y'all might
Not like but those movies even though
They're DDR inspired they're not
Dance Dance Revolution the movie
They're more about you know
Community DDR is kind of a plot device
So to speak
And I'm fine with it being a plot device
And honestly this sounds more like something
That would you know lend itself better to like
An animation or something like some
Some kid wants a
You know make it to like the
Grand chan- who cares make the stakes
Lower and just like you know
Talk about like the community
Or something but like instead they're going with
Fucking apocalypse it's always a
Fucking apocalypse of some sort and
This doesn't it doesn't lend
Itself you can't have like
Hey guys you know what
The step up series is doing fucking great
Let's make a movie where we
Save the world from an apocalypse with
It's fucking stupid it sounds
Stupid with an established franchise like that
And now we're gonna do something different
The only way
That Emmy could save the world
Was to get a triple A on
Brilliant to You
This is what I'm gonna
Say there's no fucking story in
DDR so I don't understand like why they're
Gonna do movies so in my opinion
And that's my opinion is that
If they're gonna do a DDR movie
It needs to have two things
It needs to have some scene where
Arrows go up the screen if arrows do not
Go up the screen at some point in the movie
Fail. Number two that
Soundtrack better be the
Cheesiest fucking 90s euro dance
I have heard in my entire
Life because if skill
Rex is on that album throw it in
The garbage
My guess is that with
The uniting of the world
With dance is that it's gonna
Incorporate different types
Of music and dance and then the arrows
Will be the language in which they speak
So there will be arrows
On the screen but they'll
That will be their way of communicating
Will the arrows make a heart at some point?
Yes and a giant heart
And then it will save the world
Sailor Moon style
Like the only way that this is like
Sounds any like a plausible
Thing like to use like music to
Save the world type thing it sounds like
Matt Cross 7
Or 2 or I don't remember which
Matt Cross series they had where I think it was
7 where they had like the rock band and
They were fighting actually with music and stuff
Matt Cross 2 I didn't watch any of those I just
Remember the figures for them
So that's the only way I could
See that something like that if you want to fight
With like music or something but other than that I just don't
See how this could be a thing
It's gonna be garbage
It's a movie called Dance Dance Revolution
That might have like
One throw it like do you remember
When they made a battleship movie?
With Rihanna in it
I've talked about this on a show before
I know I have it was fucking terrible yeah
That's the thing I said if that movie
Did not have a scene with Liam Neeson
Going you suck my battleship
Then it's not a battleship game
And they have the pegs they have the pegs in there too
And that was great I saw it in the trailer
I'm like this is stupid but that's the thing
You know it's stupid and that's what you
Go to see is stupid and guess what they're
Delivering stupid so
I will say
Dance is kind of big right now like
That World of Dance show on NBC
Have you like seen some of that like
Like I gotta say like some of the
Like cause you know I love
Emotional porn on Facebook right
Like I will watch those auditions
With like the little girl that like
Breaks this on and then all the judges start crying
And then I'm crying and we're all crying
And it's like 1 am and I'm not in bed yet
It's not gonna be that
But I'm saying dance is big right now cause that World of Dance show
Is actually has a lot of that
And then what just tonight
They've got Dancing with the Stars with
Little kids for some reason
I don't know with Honey Boo Boo
Dancing with the Stars is tonight
Oh wait is she actually on it?
Yeah Honey Boo Boo is on it
She must be much older now
Like what is she grown up all the way
Yeah but you know gotta get those paychecks
Still rolling in like you know
That show went off the air how many years ago
So gotta pay for college
That kid will go to any college she wants
So anyway
Dance is big right now so why not
I just don't have high expectations
Whatever the hell they put in the theater so I don't really care
Sorry I gotta say Bobby Blackwoven
Chat after I talked about Honey Boo Boo
Bobby Blackwoven chats like
Delvin's like well OLR was fun but you
Got a TV right
I love it
I love it alright so enough
Enough Dance Dance Revolution so
That may be a thing we'll see
I think if it's gonna suck this
Especially since what? It's like
It's not necessarily like
This would have been like something to do
A decade or so ago
Like when it was like super popular
Now it's not super popular
You've missed your boat
Here's the thing and I want you all to know
I love dance you might think I'm excited
About a DDR movie I'm not
I love Dance Dance Revolution
This show wouldn't exist if it wasn't for
DDR in the community but when I heard
The movie the news about the movie and this
Whole plot and everything I'm that lady
In the matrix and you've all seen this
Youtuber gif I don't remember her name
But you see her and she's looking and she knows
About to get unplugged she's gonna die she's going
Not like this not like this
And that's how I'm looking
At this DDR movie not like
This is not where I would not like this
Anyway
What else is gonna get ruined?
Well let's see the next
Step on the list is
Monster Hunter the movie
Alright Monster Hunter that's a popular
Series let's see how we're
Gonna fuck this one up
Well the movie plot centers
On the leader of a UN military
Team named Artemis played
Oh but it's got Milaj
Um Jovanovich so
Milajovic Jovanovich yeah whatever
You know why she's in it
Because it's just gonna be garbage
Better than that who's directing it
Oh her husband
Yeah so
Whatever you know what it's fine I can see
This being like a schlocky
It's a great Hollywood love story
If we're gonna flop we're gonna flop together
So it's alright
It's transported into another realm populated by
Monsters where she meets a hunter
Jai
With two team
Or two of them teaming up to close the portal
To prevent monsters from attacking Earth
Doesn't sound like Monster Hunter
But you know what though
Yeah Darkest Season chat says are we sure this is a Monster Hunter movie
It's what it is
It does have the video game director
Doing it and it's got the name
So
I mean there's monsters in it and there might be
Four people trying to take down the monster
Honestly though but here's why
Like think about it this is why that they're gonna
Let them do this
Look at how much money Capcom probably made
From the Resident Evil movie franchise
And let's be honest the Resident Evil movies
They're not high caliber
They were just
They're entertaining popcorn films
That's what I see this as
Instead of it being zombies
It's just gonna be fucking monsters now
And it's the same shit
Because she's a
UN military person so it's basically
Her fucking character from
The Resident Evil movies
Just thrown into a whole other fucking universe
With CGI monsters that says
CGI zombies
I will say out of the movies
The games becoming movies Monster Hunter is the one that
Kinda makes the most sense
Honestly like if you're gonna make
It become a movie like Monster Hunter I'm like
Okay well that's not like DDR
You know that has at least a plot
Or like some sort of a story
Monsters being hunted okay
I'm with you
It's basic but I got it
Godzilla was a monster being hunted
Oh good point good point
Well Hollywood loves a monster movie
And of course since
Capcom's sense is hmm there's
Money to be made from our franchises
We tried Street Fighter that didn't work
Out so well a few times
We are trying uh we tried
Resident Evil that worked out let's go with that
Monster Hunter? Possibly
How about we fuck over Mega Man
Again he's not quite dead
Yet with the animated series
No because I'm counting the animated series
With that have you watched the animated series?
Absolutely not it's pretty garbage
It's not that bad
Our Resident Mega Man fan says
But it's not that good either
That saw that there's a tiny Mega Man
That's living inside of Mega Man's head
Yes I'm sorry that's it's terrible
It's fucking garbage
It's fucking garbage and like
They should do it in a way they're gonna do
An animated series of Mega Man and they wanna
Be silly like that then do it like the
Fucking Teen Titans series
I mean Teen Titans Go just do it like that
Where it's self
Referential and just silly
Oh wait were you talking about the new Mega Man
The new one okay sorry no
I was referring to the old one
Oh no no the old one
That's fine that was a long time ago we made
Our mistakes back then
Yeah I was referring to the old one
No I'm talking about the new Mega Man
No no no no
No new Mega Man series yeah
So they're thinking
About doing and not necessarily
An animated Mega Man series
A live action Mega Man
Film
That makes me very nervous
Based on the influential and globally
Beloved Mega Man franchise
Capcom aims to appeal
To a diverse audience
Including not only game players
But action movie fans
As well you know this
Is how we get this right here
Is how we get that prototype of Mega Man
That fucking was scrapped and you know the one that looked like
Bomberman Act Zero that bullshit
Oh yeah that's how we get this shit
Yeah I was still
Watch it though
Every day I hear about the Sonic the Hedgehog movie
I'm just like going
I will watch that because Jim Carrey's in it
And that's the only reason why
Is going to be a mess
I'm a little worried when they say live action
Because immediately I get the picture
The cover art of Mega Man 2
In my head
With the human Mega Man
And that just terrifies me to see that
But what if that human Mega Man is played by none other than
Nathan Fillion
Who's going to play Mega Man?
Oh I imagine if Mega Man is a boy
They're going to get a child actor to play Mega Man
And they'll probably humanize
Like I don't think Mega Man will look so
Roboty but Mega Man will look like
A little kid but maybe with like
An arm that shoots lasers
We'll get none other than child actor
Macaulay Culkin
He's in his 30s I mean like
He was a child actor at one time
That's still
That's like the whole thing where I'm like wait a minute
I'm still voicing Sora
Okay that's going to be interesting
Because Sora's going to be very much an adult now
Because Haley Joel Osment's
I don't know if y'all know
But since Kingdom Hearts
The last game was like 15 years ago
Haley Joel Osment is not a kid anymore
I don't know if y'all know
He a very grown man now
I don't know if y'all have heard
But a lot of those kid actors have grown up
Like that kid who played Anakin
In the first Star Wars movie
And he also was like you know what
Acting is not for me because people are fucking me
Because you know people were really fucking rude to him
Because they blamed
The failures of episode one on
What a seven year old boy
Because that's a rational thing to do
Anyway
Who knows it's George Lucas come on
Let's see
Looking in chat over at
Live.vog at Network.com
Dungeon Buster says I've seen artists try to make Mega Man
Look realistic
One box art did not turn out well
The only positive
I think there's a way to make Mega Man not look
He just won't look like the robot
Except maybe in like one scene
The only positive I have here
Because I'm a fan of his as well
Is that it's being produced
I guess
Along with Masaoka
Which was the guy from Heroes
That was the guy in Heroes
He's like kind of helping shape this
Okay you have my attention
He's kind of a geeky guy that I feel
Has probably actually played Mega Man
I played Mega Man
So I'm hopeful
Okay
Once again though
We'll put that in column A
I will see it no matter how garbage it is
Just so I can complain about it
I think it has potential
To be really good if they
Went the X series route
As opposed to the original Mega Man
But it would be weird for them to jump
To the X series
And not start at the beginning for people who've never
Played Mega Man before
So it's
Either here or there
I think it would actually be
Like you guys are going to disagree with me
But I think it would be very smart of them
Like if they want to make a good movie
They're going to really keep the references to the games
Very light
Like there will be a Mega Man
There will be a Dr. Light
And a Dr. Wily
But maybe it's not like
You just described the game
I know but like it's not like
Levels
It's just going to be like
Maybe it's like Scott Pilgrim
I would be fine with Scott Pilgrim
Type of movie
He's got to find these other kids that are actually
The creations of Dr. Wily
Yeah exactly
Now that I'd be okay with
Going to chat at
Live.vognetwork.com
And SS200Matt says at the end they will say
He is a Mega Man
Cause you know we all
Y'all love it when somebody in the movie
Says the title of the movie
Roll credits
Yeah got it
There you go
Three video game movies
Coming soon
Maybe not that soon
Eventually
Let's move on into some
How was your gaming week and the types of video games
That you've been playing this week
Loki we'll start with you
I played Forza Horizon 4
So I played through a little bit of that
I
Don't know what I'm
I'm probably training my
Dryvatars badly
Because I'm not on the roads most of the time
I'm just going everywhere else
But
Yeah it's a very pretty game
It runs really nice on my laptop
So I'm happy about that
Um
Then I did play a little bit of
DDR
Ace
I went to the arcades actually
I've been meaning to go over there and play for like a long time
But the problem is it's like so packed over there
Dave and Busters
That can never really get on the machine
Especially since there's fuckers that like to
Camp on the machine all day long
It's like don't you have school or something?
I mean like shouldn't you be
In a job? I don't know
But so I did that
And then you know other arcade games with the Golf Land
Because I had to keep my son
Away from my other son
Because my other son was sick
And so that means I had to take him out of the house the entire day
So that was pretty much
Saturday all arcade day
So we were playing different arcade games
I got to play the giant
Space Invaders game
Which meh
Mario Kart was pretty fun
Played a little bit of that
And very sad
That I saw the
DDR Max 2 machine
That's at
Roosevelt Golf Land
And it is a sad, it's off
And it's a very sad sight
I didn't take Delvin to Golf Land while he's here
For a reason, I was just like you know it's skippable
It's um
The golf course is nice
We went and played mini golf, they have it all decorated for Halloween
So that's kind of cool
The only way to fixing their machines up is
They don't give a shit
As long as the ticket spitters are working
Then they don't give a shit about anything else
But it was a sad sight
Do you have mini golf in Canada?
We do
Well then yeah, there's no point
And then what else?
So
Pokemon Go
And
Just
Yeah, that's pretty much it
I didn't get the chance to play Super Mario Party
Because my kids basically have been
You know, monopolizing the Switch
And
I didn't bother to purchase Spiderman
Because my wife's monopolizing the TV
To watch a stupid baking show that she could watch
Oh, the Great British Bake Off?
Oh good times, love that show
It's a great show, but I wish I could have the TV once in a while
Has she watched Nailed It?
Because that's another great one
You know what, I set up a TV in our bedroom
She's like, I want to watch Netflix in bed
Okay, cool, set up the old TV in the bedroom
With the Netflix box
Watch your fucking baking show in here
Then I can play on the 4K TV
That we bought with my nice 4K system
To play some 4K games
Nope!
Gotta fucking watch the goddamn baking show in 4K instead
It's like, ugh
We need to see every detail on those cakes
And they are fucking delicious looking
No fault of that show
It's just, it's
It's everything
Uh, Delvin, I'll let you go next
Because I know we have a little bit of overlap
So I'll let you, you know, I can always just talk about 4
How was your gaming week, Delvin?
Um, so
For the past week and a bit
Uh, I just recently got back
Into playing World of Warcraft
I'm back on my bullshit again
Of playing World of Warcraft
Uh, so
Any fans listening from
Video gaming will just know that I
Swore that I was not going to play
Uh
I'm right there with you
I swore, I'm like, nope, not going to play this expansion
I'm done, I'm not playing World of Warcraft anymore
And then
I blame Cameron
Because he started playing
And we're basically, we enable each other
One of us will start playing
And then enable the other person
To start playing
It's kind of like the friendship Shane and I have
And so
Not totally his fault, but then another friend
Was playing too, and I was like, okay, well, fuck
The band's getting back together again
So I don't want to be the one left out
Uh, so I got back
Playing about a week and a half ago
And power leveled all the way
To 120, and then started
Grinding through dungeons, mythic bluses
Raiding, and
I'm such a
Nerd that, you know, the raid
Resets are on the Tuesday
Right. So
Tuesday night, uh
I did all my raiding for one week
Because I was leaving
Yeah. Wednesday
So Tuesday I did
All of normal raid
And I did a bit of heroic with
My guild
And did some, like I did everything that I needed to do
For the week, I did the mythic plus, so I would get something
In my box for the week
And all of it
And so that was my gaming week mostly
Um, I also, like I did mention
Bonds006 says you did not want to be the diva
Holding out to get the band
Get together. Exactly. You did not want to be
Posh Spice. No. You did not want to be the hold out
Exactly. So I was like
Whatever. I've been playing for
Ten years, what's, what's another
Year? Right? So who cares?
Um, and uh
I did play some Mega Man
Um, and that, and of course Pokemon Go
A lot, uh, we've been playing over
The weekend. Yeah, we were hanging with Dark
Sakura yesterday actually, since obviously
She's not available on Sundays, so we kind of spent yesterday
With her so you could meet her. Um, and then we
Ended up, she did not have Mewtwo yet
And it was like, me, you, her
And Allen like all play, so I was like
Okay, we have four people together, where's the Mewtwo
At? And we're like, maybe somebody will be
There if we get there right at Hatch, and sure enough
We, and there was this couple, walked
Right up when we did, and it was like, oh good
We were hoping other people would be here, so like between the six
Of us, actually no, there was a seventh account
A mysterious seventh
Player. Possible Spoofer
But thank you Spoofer
Yeah, cause we took that one down, and then we did the other one
At the bridge. Yes. Which, like
The same thing happened. We're like, where are they?
And I looked over and I'm like, that dude's on his phone over there
Yeah. That's the other guy
So I, it's, so, it's funny
We're talking about the Mewtwo
I have done, probably about
Eight Mewtwo raids
Uh, between here and back in Toronto
And, not for the life of me could I catch
More than one god damn Mewtwo
So I did catch one here, and
So now I have two, but that's it
Yeah. And it's hard now to get
To find Mewtwo raids back
In Toronto because it seems like
Once the initial rush of
Mewtwo coming out was done
Nobody's doing raids anymore
I find that people still want to do them
I mean, it might be harder, especially in like
Less trafficked areas to find the people
But people still generally want to do them
Because they're really good experience
And it's the only way you can get rare candy and items
So you might as well use your free pass
For the day if you can get a group
You might as well do it, there's no harm in doing it
I did, I did join, uh
There's a discord group, uh, for the Toronto
Area for Pokemon Go
So, I'm gonna utilize that a bit more
Now that we're starting to get into the colder
Months in Toronto
It's a lot harder to get people to do raids
Unless you actually coordinate
Well plus, load up on Trashymon here
In California, and then when you go back
You could just be like, does anyone want to do distance trading
Cause it's, it's like 3000 kilometers
Cause like, when I open my Alolan
Eggs, I'm very particular
I will tend to, so like
This is why if you're on my friends list
And you're somewhere on the east coast, like I've been opening
Your presence a lot more lately
Like, if you're like Atlanta
Toronto, or I've got a little group
There's like some New York, some New Jersey, I'm like kinda
Figuring out who's where, I'm opening those gifts
When I have the holes in my inventory for Alolan eggs
Because if nothing else, if I get another fucking
Sandshrew or Grimer or something
I can trade it for a hella distance
And I think they're doing the same thing with my eggs
Because then the eggs in the west coast
You can at least trade for distance
And get that medal, which you know
The medal doesn't really mean anything, it's just EP
No, but for the people that are in those
Type of Discord groups, they want
They're full completionists, you know
They're checking their IVs, they're doing badges and medals
And things like that, so, it helps
Yeah, so, cool
Um, and then I think it's also fun to have
Pokemon from like, other places
Like, so now you have a Mewtwo from Sacramento
That will like, kinda remind you of that day
Oh yes, absolutely
Just like, my one and only Regirock
Is from Atlanta
So during Dragon Con, that was the only time I was actually able to
Capture Regirock, but then I also go
That was the time I got Bobby Blackwolf to actually
Do a Pokemon raid, so that's like
You know, like, woo, we got a little memory there
And then we traded Unknown today
And it became Lucky
Yeah, Lucky you
Yeah, he got the Lucky D
Because I gave him one of the Unknown, I got a Dragon Con
Because I saved like, you know, I basically
Don't have an Unknown yet here, here you go
You don't have one yet
Oh, really?
Remind me next episode, I'll get you one
So, then what left, you got the Lucky Unknown
But because you were like, what do you want
I'm like, my Contodex is done
There's like, literally nothing, just give me trash
So you gave me a Pidgey
I got a Lucky Pidgey
It's because you haven't gotten enough Lucky
Stuff yet
The first few trades you do
Like, first 10 trades are gonna be Lucky
So whatever I get from you is gonna be Lucky
So, yeah
Anyway, so that was, that was a little irritating
But anyway
Well, max out that Pidgey then
Yeah, you know what, actually because
When they're Lucky, they get good stats
And this guy is a 15 Attack
15 Defense
So I'm like, well, if nothing else, he might just
Be a funny Gym Defender
If nothing else, like,
Why not?
He'll be half price to level him up to
Level him up a little bit and throw him in a gym somewhere
Anyway, my game of the week, so I've been playing
Not just World of Warcraft
I'm not on the raiding thing
And I don't think I will be
But I just enjoy, like, the
World quests, just the leveling up
Experience, I started a new
Monk, just because I wanted to
Level up again, it seems like they fixed
A lot of the level sinking dungeons thing
Because when that patch first went in, I was pissed
I was not having a good time
But now it seems it's fine now
I did, okay, so the day that
Patch went in that rescaled
The old world where all the dungeons were 1-60
I went in and I got
Dire Maul or something, and it was
It was a shit show, because
People were not used to it the new way
And it was impossible to heal
So you could get
Dungeons that were
For level 60 at level 20?
No, they would still unlock later
My panda shaman
Was level 50, but we got that
But other people that were higher
Would get sinked down, like for example
I'm level 27, and I just queued for
Dungeon, I got Wailing Caverns at
27, but I was scaled down
To what a player in Wailing Caverns would be
Which is kind of like the 14 system
A little bit, it's this weird
Weird iteration of it, whereas like
14 just straight up level sinks you
It's a little different in a while
But anyway, I've been playing a lot of
Forza Horizon 4, I did a stream of that earlier
This week, and that game is fun
Forza is so extra
That's the greatest thing about it, and I love that
My character is named Potato
And they actually say, okay Potato
Do you want to go get some new influence?
Okay Potato, it's great to meet you Potato
Potato, we're gonna need you in a movie
So I just love that they call me Potato
Why do they call you Potato?
Because I ask them to
Because the game has
All these names loaded into it
They always call me Matt
Okay, here's the funny thing
I think it reads your Xbox profile
Because when I started the full game
They were like, do you want us to call you Rob?
And I was like
Let me see what the other names are
And the first page is all like
Quote unquote normal names
And they have a pretty impressive list
Of like 300 names
Sadly, not everybody's name is gonna be in there
Yeah, Delvin's not gonna be in there
If you have a unique name, it's not gonna be in there
Sorry, but if your name isn't in there
Then you go to page 2, which is
Nicknames
And there's all these different nicknames that they'll call you
So you can pick one
I don't know if they'll call you Mega Ma'am
I bet Mega is one of the names that they'll call you
And one of the names that was in there was Potato
So I was doing the stream
I was like
Perfect, that's a perfect name for me, Potato
Can I change that?
You can change it
You go into the menu and it's
Right where you pick your car
Wherever you customize your character
It's in the menu, it's not hard to miss
And you change it at any time
So if I feel like I don't want them to call me Potato anymore
But it's all voice acted
Like when I say they call me Potato
The voice acting says it
It's not just the text in the game
Naming your character in an RPG
Like butts, so that you make all the characters say
Get over here, butts
And all that stuff, right?
Anyway
But Fours is fun
I'm not quite in the open world yet
I don't really give my full thoughts because
I'm still making my way through the season
I didn't realize I'm not in the open world
I thought I was
There's like a pre-open world
So like you're still seeing everything
Like the other people and stuff
But I noticed today there were way less
People in there than there were when
The day the game came out
Because more people have gotten through it
So they're in the real open world now
I guess I should play through the game then
The seasons are on a fixed schedule
The schedule will change when you start
So it basically forces you to go
So the very first thing in the game
You play all the seasons in rapid succession
That's just to get you a taste, right?
But then when you start the game it's like, okay
It's autumn, go do this race, this race, and this race
And then it's gonna be winter
And then get this many fans
And it will be, you know, I'm assuming spring
And then summer
Once you get through all four seasons
Then you'll go into the real game mode
Where the seasons rotate like once a week
Like a real game week
So I think they had winter last week
So I would imagine it's spring in game right now
Or it's gonna turn to spring on Friday
And then that's when you're like racing
With other people and doing those events
Everybody's kind of on the same clock, so to speak
So, there's that
Yeah, gosh, I don't know what else to say
About Forza
If you think you might enjoy a new
Type of racing game, I urge you to check out the demo
I think Forza is one of the must-own
Titles on Xbox One
It honestly, in my opinion, is Microsoft's
Best exclusive right now
And yes, I'm including Halo
Fight me
So, Forza Horizon
Is Microsoft's best exclusive right now
And maybe I'll change my mind on that later
But these are must-have games if you own
An Xbox One
And even if you don't own an Xbox One, the great thing is
They're on PC
That's where I got mine, I don't need an Xbox One
That's the reason I got rid of my Xbox One
All the Xbox One games I wanted to play
Were all on PC, so I was like
Okay, well, time to get a PS4, and I traded it in
Yeah, so, I mean
Yeah, and I bought it
Digitally, so you get the whole like
I have it on PC, and if I want to
Play it on my Xbox One, I can't, which I did today
So you could watch a little bit, and see the game
You know, because my office is a little cramped
It's harder to watch me play on PC, so we
You know, did that a little bit, so
It's nice to- And your TV's bigger
Yeah, TV is a lot bigger, yeah, it's nicer, so
Anyway, um
Bonds006 says I want all Forza games on PC
Well, they probably will be in the future
Forza Horizon 3 was on PC, too
I don't know about Motorsport, because I don't follow
That series as closely, because I-
Seven is, I think
I prefer the arcade racers to the
Simulation racers, that's why you don't hear me talk
Like this about Gran Turismo
But I fucking love Mario Kart
And F-Zero, because those are arcade racers
There's a big difference
Burnout, I love that game, that's an arcade racer
I stand blur
Really hard, and I'm really sad that that franchise
Is gone, because that was more of an arcade racer, too
Um, so, that's
That's my thought
Let's see, what else, so we went to round one
I should quickly say, you got to have
Your first experience at round one
Yeah, I forgot to mention that in my, I guess as part
Of my gaming week
Oh, real quick, I just want to go back to Pokemon Go
Now, did you make sure to get one
Of those Pikachus with a hat, because they're
Very hard to find
No, they went away today
I'm glad you asked, Loki
I lucked out, I tapped the one on my house
Yesterday morning, not only was it a Pikachu
And a hat, it was a shiny Pikachu and a hat
So knowing that those, I mean, as annoying
Those little guys were, because they were everywhere
For like two days
Like, that makes that shiny
Really rare
So like, my Pokemon E-peen
Is really big right now, because not only
Did I get the shiny hat Pikachu, but I got
A shiny Drowzee today
My shiny E-peen is like
Real shiny right now
Real shiny
I bathed for you, anyway
Where were we? Oh yes, round one
Round one, speaking of shiny
In new places
So yeah, round one was amazing
It's huge, there's tons
Of arcade games in there
We don't really have
Very many arcades anymore
In the Toronto area
There was a place that opened up recently
Right near the CN Tower
And Skydome area
That has arcade in it
But it is a fraction
Of what is in round one
In terms of both ticket spinners
And arcade games
Like, round one
Just had a huge, a mass amount
Of games, so I was there
With you playing
I got to play some old fighting games
That I really enjoyed, they had Tatsunoko
Versus Capcom
Which I had never played, I had only played it on Wii
So it was fun to play that
I was playing some King of Fighters, I was playing some Street Fighter
And they had
Mario and Sonic
At the Rio Olympics
Which I didn't even know was an arcade game
And also Luigi's Mansion
I had no idea that
Yeah, they had one of those at Dave and Buster's
That was broken, aww
Yeah, I had no idea that these things
Were ever made as arcade games
And I'm kind of wondering why they're not more
Available
And rampant, but I guess it's just
Arcades probably aren't
As big money makers, why they have those
Stupid ticket spinners
Yeah, I got to play
The new BB&E 2DX
The Cannonball Rush, I think it's called
Which is a racing theme, I didn't realize that
But that's what they call it
And I actually played some of the new songs
Like, usually I'm really bad
Just ask JD, who goes to round one with me a lot
Like, when I go play 2DX, I'm really bad about
What's in 4 style that I can go back and play
So I, like, never play the new songs
But this time I really did play some of the new songs
There was some good stuff in there, it's just hard to hear in there
Yes, I was just gonna say
I was trying to do a rhythm game
I can't remember which one I was playing
To be honest
But it was very hard to play because I
Couldn't keep, I did not
Hear the music at all, period
I should have thought to tell you to bring headphones
And I didn't remember this myself, because a lot of people
You can put headphones in a lot of these jeans
Which is a great idea, because
Without it, you can't fucking hear shit in there
So, um, yeah
And I got to see Dance Rush, I didn't play it
Because the dance area was a little crowded
And I was, like, I'm gonna just keep it real
We had just had Lucille's BBQ
And so I was feeling very puffy
And I was not
I was not gonna get on
That was not the moment
And JD's like, come on, play, dance, dance
I'm like, you don't understand
If I get on that machine, it's gonna turn into
Dance, dance, fart
And none of y'all want that right now
Nobody deserves that kind of treatment
You don't deserve that type of treatment
The strangers don't deserve that type of treatment
It's not gonna happen
I am perfectly fine just watching
Although, there were people there who were doing
Their gym workouts there
Right?
There was a little bit of funk going on
They had their shorts and their little gym towels
Bottled water, like, they were full on
But then I think back
That's just how I played DDR though
I need those things in order to
Not be in your garage
I totally get it
Because if I don't have the towel
It's gonna be dripping all over the place
And then no one wants to slip in that
So, anyway
So I watched, and JD played
DDR, and he did go into
The retro mode, and he played
D2R, so I could see
The full background and how it emulates
DDR Extreme and all that, and it was silly
But in a good way
I appreciated the throwback
That was pretty cool that I got to see that
Anyway, very long
Winded answer to gaming week, but it was pretty busy
Because when you're here, I'm gonna take you to all the
Fun spots to play games. We never did make it
To coin-op, I was gonna take you there, but then I read
They didn't have a Killer Instinct machine
Which I wanted
Delvin needs to play Killer Instinct in the arcade
And I can't remember where around here has one
Maybe at that
Old arcade that's in Sutter
Street might have one
Oh, I always forget that place is there
Dang
Well, you know we might luck out
Because we're gonna go to Reno tomorrow
Which, that's a whole other story about why we're gonna go to Reno
But we are
And they have arcades there that time forgot
You might luck out and find it
Yeah, we'll go check them out
Oh, Pepper Mill
Has like that retro arcade
So, remind me
Go to Pepper Mill
Sounds like a plan
Alright, let's move on to some actual gaming news
And not casino talk
So, let's get into some gaming news with Loki
Starting us off tonight
So, since we're not gonna be talking about movies anymore
Yes, I know that you guys are disappointed
Let's talk about something else
That's coming soon
Rumored to be coming soon
A new model of the Nintendo Switch
According to the Wall Street Journal
Nintendo is gonna be introducing
A new version of the Switch
Next year
No word on what it is
Other than it will probably share some features
With the current version
And be compatible with existing Switch software
Well, you don't say
That's just a safe guess
Wall Street Journal
Nintendo is apparently
They're debating on what new hardware
And software features
To include in the upgrade
Here's an idea
If you don't know what to put in the upgrade
Don't fucking upgrade your system
Unless you have a plan
You don't need to upgrade it
If you have nothing to upgrade it with
And what do we really need to upgrade it with
I mean, the only thing I could see
That they could do
To add to the system
Really, is more storage
Cause 32GB onboard storage
Is fucking stupid nowadays
I'm imagining
This is gonna sound ridiculous Loki
But I think if they do
Like a 2019
My hope is that they would not segregate
Like they did with new 3DS and 3DS
Where you're gonna have shit like Xenoblade Chronicles
That only plays on new Switch
I would really hate to see that happen
This early in the game
Not that it's an impossibility
Because there is a potential that Nintendo might just go in there
And zhuzh it up a little bit
Zhuzh it up, meaning
Just a little more memory
A fancier screen
We're just gonna come in here and do a little makeover
Get the guys from Queer Eye to come
Get a little makeover
Just make sure Jonathan Van Ness
We're gonna patch out that taker chip
So you can't run that homebrew
Cause that's really what's got our knickers in a bunch
Make sure Jonathan Van Ness comes out and says gorgeous
This is a gorgeous screen, it's very gorgeous
We're gonna have a very gorgeous looking system here
So one of my theories
That we've talked about before
Is that
Pokemon is the big game that's obviously coming next year
Yes
And that still is a game that is geared towards kids
So
My theory
And thoughts is that
Whatever remake or redesign
Or upgrade that they're coming out with
Could potentially be
A portable only version
Of the Switch
That'll be a bit smaller for kids to use
And it'll be a bit cheaper
So that you're not giving your kid a
$300 handheld system that they'll
Throw around inevitably and throw on the ground
And whatever
So that might be the angle they're going
And then that will just be for people who only
Want to play the Switch on the go
They'll have like a better screen
Like a smartphone type screen
So for better battery life
Because we know that the Switch as it is now
Has poor battery life on the go
So I think that might
And it won't segregate the market that way
That's
An answer I'm comfortable with
That's a good answer
The Neon Family Feud, good answer
Here comes Loki
Here's why it's not gonna happen
The reason why it's only a 720p
Screen in the first place
Is because it can't run anything
Higher than that in portable mode
That's why it has to be plugged in because they're
Underclocking the CPU in that
GPU to be able to run what's on there
So
For them to put like a 1080p
Screen in there, it's just not gonna happen
Because they can't
Do it, so if anything
I don't
Really know, it's just an excuse
Really just to upgrade that chip so that
They can't have homebrew in there is really all
It is. I just hope if they do this
They take the 3DS out back
And shoot it
That also is kind of
My opinion segregating the portable market
Is that they still have these games like WarioWare
That are coming out on the 3DS
That we're not getting on the Switch now
Yes, I understand the WarioWare has like the
Blowing mechanics and some things that don't really
That don't really exist on the Switch
Right, like the microphone and everything
So I get it. There's a microphone on the Switch
Is there?
I think so. I don't think so
I think that's why everything had to go through a smartphone
Or you plug in a headphone or that whole thing
Because I don't think there's one built into it
There's no camera either like there is on the 3DS
So there's some things
So I understand why it can't be one for one
But like that Luigi's Mansion remake
That should be on the Switch
That should have been a Switch game
So I do hope if they're going to
Ask us to get this newer Switch
They really need to take the 3DS out back
And shoot it
They really need to have some pretty
Kick ass features that they're adding
To it to get people to want it
Because just look at all the
Refreshes that they've done with the 3DS
You know
Made it bigger
Added a little nub that no one wanted
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says
I see where Delvin's going
Make a newer Switch that doesn't have
Detachable controllers
Doesn't have HDMI out or any of that type of stuff
They can remove components which will make the system
Overall cheaper
Not having detachable controllers is going to be a big mistake
Because here's one problem
First off you got games like Super Mario Party
Oh hey you want to play that game?
Well you got to detach the fucking controllers to play that game
Because we don't work in handheld mode
Well but that's because of the whole laying the screens next to each other
Thing which is kind of magic
I will say yeah
It's stupid
It's dumb though that you need to have it just to do the motion controls and stuff
But I feel like that whole laying the screens
Next to each other sort of thing
There's more to that
We're going to see in a later game
I think that might just be one mode of the game
No no but I mean that
Technology, that concept
We're going to see it again
And what better way to perhaps do that
If more people have more of the portable
To go version of Switch
Potentially
Alright well I mean we'll see where we go with it
I mean technically it is a rumor
They may not do anything but
I wouldn't
I wouldn't put it past Nintendo to do it
Because honestly
I don't know
Why redesign it now?
Unless you fix your stupid
Online support
With the whole app
Why do a PS4 mini
Two years after PS4 launches
I don't get that either
Or PS4 Pro
It makes sense because it has
You can push better graphics with it
It has stronger processing power
But it's
Not segregating the marketplace
Because it still runs
All the same games and everything
I don't see what
We may also be overthinking it to be fair
Because then my mind also goes
They did do a new Xbox One
Like just a year and it was a gig
Instead of
They did a different color or something too
It's not that big a deal
So maybe this whole thing
Is not going to be that big a deal
Like you said in the very beginning
More on board storage memory to start
And then maybe some different colors
I think it makes sense because
Having these installs with different games
People are buying stuff
More digitally
The indie game marketplace is seriously driving
I think a lot of sales for the system
Because there's not a ton of games coming out
Especially mainline
Switch games
Yes and no
Because I think at this point the Switch has the backlog
Where when somebody comes to me and says
If I buy a Switch what game should I buy
I'm sitting there going
Did you have a Wii U
And at the end of the time the answer is no
So I'm like alright
You need to get Breath of the Wild
You need to get Mario Odyssey
You need to get Mario Party 8
Do you like Skyrim?
You might need to get Skyrim
There's a growing library of Switch games
Bayonetta
I always recommend Bayonetta 1 and 2
There's a growing library of games now
I feel like the Switch doesn't need to justify
We don't have enough games to play on the Switch
You're thinking
TL Shade
That was Microsoft's problem
They didn't have enough exclusives
You can play Rise Son of Rome
But everything else
Microsoft was offering
At that time was on
PlayStation 4
Which is why
I'm bringing this up again because you and I were just talking about this last night
We were having a little nerd out
Nervous Lumber Party
I said how quickly we forget
Never forget
The biggest news
Out of E3 2018
Is that Microsoft acquired
A bunch of fucking studios
They are laying this
They are laying out this path
To get them back
In the front of the pack
And that is going to be
When they unleash whatever their next system is
They're going to have all these games
Only playable on Xbox
It's just the question is going to be
Are you going to put out Forza Horizon
Crackdown type games
As exclusives
Or are you going to put out Rise Son of Rome
Because one of them
Will make Microsoft in the lead
At least in the US
One of them? Pack it up
You all know what I mean
Alright
But anyway
In Nintendo's case
We've always known this is Nintendo's
Thing that is going to always put them
In a league of their own
Nintendo is the
The underscore bolded
The best
Game maker
Making video games
True story
I don't know if that's the case anymore
Honestly
I don't
There's a long pause because I'm looking
I gave him that look
I get it
Super Mario Odyssey was a great game
But I mean
Other companies make great games too
Sure
I'm just saying Nintendo's the best
I think we're giving them too much
We're giving them too much
Well it's fine that you're doing this bullshit
Because you made Super Mario Odyssey
It's fine that you're doing this bullshit
Because you made Breath of the Wild
I don't know
Bobby Blackwolf is trying to summarize
What you're saying
In quotes here
I get it Nintendo makes great games
It sucks
Yeah they suck at everything else
And you know what
I understand that you think it doesn't matter
They make great games
But if you're running it on hardware that doesn't make any fucking sense
Or they have shit that gets in the way
Then that's going to be the problem
I get it when people are like
Why won't Nintendo just put their games out on the
PlayStation 4 that would fix everything
I get it
Exactly
Wow that would be fucking awesome
That would be like gaming would never be better
Than if like
If Nintendo made games
For the Sony PlayStation 4
And Microsoft did all of the online component
Like that would be the perfect thing
Oh that would be perfect
Not going to ever fucking happen
But I might masturbate to that later
Great theory
Great idea
Never going to happen
Well let's see
I have to wait and see what the system is going to be
I might like
With everything with Nintendo my expectations are low
Alright let's move on
Let's talk about Fortnite
You want to talk about what's fucking huge in gaming right now
It doesn't matter what system you own
Because now we got the cross play problem solved
So this game is literally
Everywhere
Fortnite
It's on the phones, it's on the Switch, on the PS4
It's on the PC, it's on Macs
It's everywhere
Everybody's playing it during the Emmys
Yes as we learned on RuPaul's podcast
This last week
Carson Daly was playing Fortnite during the Emmys
Apparently
So anyway, Fortnite is still going
And now there's going to be more encouragement
To try to kind of keep that Fortnite
Train going
Because you know one place where
PUBG is probably
PUBG lost a lot of steam
They were the number one, number two game on Twitch
For a long time
And it seemed like PUBG news
Was getting really light
And they started to kind of fall behind a little bit
And I'm not totally shading PUBG
But that's just
Facts are facts
Go look at the Twitch standings
PUBG is not number one anymore
Facts are facts America
Epic wants to keep Fortnite out in the lead
So here's an idea
Why not pay content creators
And this is
This is like
Interesting because I can't think of a lot of
Game makers
Because you know some game makers
Want to stop content creators
Maybe that's not
Completely fair but you know what I mean
Sometimes they hold them back a little bit
But Epic is launching a
Support a creator event
That will send real money
To folks on Twitch and YouTube
When gamers make purchases with
V-Bucks
So starting October 8th until the end of
18 if you put in the name
Of a creator in Fortnite's
Shop to reward them
When you buy a costume or glider
So you know
Guess what you're gonna start hearing on every
Podcast who knows maybe this one I don't know
It's gonna be use offer code
O-L-R at checkout
That's offer code O-L-R
Yeah that's right it's offer code
O-L-R
At checkout
Watch watch these content
Creators of Fortnite wait for it
And let's find our best content creators
Plugging their offer codes
That they're gonna put in at checkout
This is standard business nowadays because you know
You're not getting paid by YouTube
Or Twitch that much
I mean so you gotta make your money
Somewhere but this is interesting because
The only like
Qualifications for this you have to
Produce Fortnite related material in the
Past 30 days have at
Least 1,000 social
Media followers which sounds high
But social media like I have
That on Twitter like not to be that
Guy but like you know if you have
Been on social media and working
All that long enough and frequent enough you're
Probably gaining a lot of followers
So um and I
Didn't see if that is a thousand YouTube
A thousand Twitch I don't know but you have to
Have a thousand followers and you have to
Avoid illegal or toxic
Behavior so you can't be a jerk
Fair enough
It's not gonna be it's not gonna pay your mortgage
50,000 V-Bucks
That's about $500
The creator will get $25
So that's like 5%
Which I mean
It's not a bad
It's right it's better than nothing
Somebody like Ninja
Oh he's gonna be raking it in
Oh it is he's gonna be he's gonna fill a bathtub
Full of money it's gonna be like that scene with Demi
Morin in Decent Proposal where she's laughing on the
Bedroll that's gonna be Ninja
Okay it already is Ninja
Anyway
So yeah it's gonna incentivize
Content creators to move
And Loki yes in some ways
Like you know there's
Other ways that content creators can make money
Through like biddies on Twitch and subscriptions
And all that but you know what
Knowing that wow if I keep playing
Fortnite I can make a little more
Money is gonna keep people
Playing Fortnite it's smart
It even makes me wanna go
I have a thousand social media followers
Maybe I need to play Fortnite some night
I'm not gonna but I hope some other companies
It would be pretty cool if they follow up on this
It would be pretty rad
And then it's kind of a
Another way to keep
Fortnite popular cause
If Fortnite just stays on Twitch
Or YouTube as the number one most
Watched game
It just keeps it in people's face
It does it does
Here's the new mode here's the new stuff here's all the new
Crap you can buy on the online marketplace
For sure for sure anyway well let's move
On Loki
Alright
So apparently
For the longest time we've been asking
For the ability to be able to change our
PlayStation Network
User names
And Sony's always said
Oh yeah don't worry we'll have something worked out
Soon you know we're working on it we're looking into
It blah blah blah
Well that might actually be getting closer because
Apparently
There's been some game studios
That have been speaking anonymously
To different social
Media outlets and letting them
Know that hey
That they've been
Participating in bug fixing
And tweaking settings and stuff like that
To make sure that it's gonna be compatible
Their games are compatible with these
PlayStation Network name profile
Changes or user names
So they have like the option
To edit user name
They have like a guide
That they've been going off of to kind of
Work on it so it is something that is coming up
Um
We don't know when yet
I remember that they were originally talking that
They're gonna make the announcement at PSX
But that's not gonna happen this year so maybe
Around that time maybe the end
Of this year I don't know there's nothing to stop them
From just doing an internet press release I mean
That's the way you can do things now
So they've got that PlayStation blog
They've got a Twitter account
They dump a bombshell like that
And it's gonna run around the internet real quick
So that's something people have been asking
For it does seem ridiculous
That now it's like 2018 and we're still
Oh my god Sony might allow you the
Ability to change your name real soon y'all
I wonder what the reason behind that is
It's gotta do something with the infrastructure
There's gotta be something rooted in
Yeah I think it was their infrastructure where they had the
User names like the accounts were tied
To the user name it wasn't tied to like some
Number that the user name was like
You know tied to the account
Yeah so now they have to
Go back and rework all that shit so that
It's now tied to this universal number
That your user name is then tied to that
Account so you can change it
Or whatever it just it just seems weird
That it would have taken this long to get here
Because I mean and then again
I don't know as much about networking
And infrastructure so I will be the first to admit
Maybe I'm just ignorant to how
Hard this really is
But why wouldn't they have just
At some point
Taken Playstation Network down for a day
To say we're gonna run this thing
That's gonna change all your
User names behind the scenes into a number
And then that number is now you
But you won't see it because now you have your name
And then now if you wanna change your name it's fine
Cause we put in those numbers behind the scene
That's why we took Playstation Network down for a day
Like
Am I crazy?
Whenever there's a database
And someone's
Information is in there
That information is tied to an
ID and that could be a number
It could be a name it's just something that's
A unique identifier and they probably
Chose the user name to be that unique identifier
Which was a poor choice
Now that I know in Microsoft Access you always
Have your key field
So they
Basically chose the user name to be the unique
Identifier instead of it being
Some other number behind the
Scene usually a key that's like numbers
And letters and now
So if you change it it almost
Fucks up the account and then maybe
This would've prevented the hack because we would've
Never well no because I was like maybe
They would've only seen that random numbers of letters
And numbers and not you know the user names but
Actually no they would've still pulled
The other yeah yeah anyway
Alright anyway let's move on I wanna talk about
This because I think I don't know if this is gonna be
So much a game but it's like VR
It's gonna be Oculus
And HTC Vive
And I don't know about you guys but I'm
Super into it and this is
A new VR experience
I don't know if it's like a game
But knowing what it is
It's probably gonna be like
Like what is it anyway
It's Twin Peaks is what it is so Twin Peaks
Y'all know it was a show
Back in the 90's on ABC but then they
Brought it back recently on Showtime
And I was a fan of the old
Series and I loved the new one too
Even though there was a lot of like
Especially like
Here's the thing with Twin Peaks
The next to last episode like if they had
Ended it with that it would've been like
They kinda answered a lot of the questions
They kept some things open I love the way that
Next to last episode ended but then
In true David Lynch form there's a
Full another episode after that that keeps
Going that the entire thing
Is just what the
Fuck and that's
How it ends but that's
But you go to see a David
Lynch anything you need to be prepared
To be walking out of that theater going
What the actual
Fuck was that
And that was what happened when I saw Lost Highway
Years ago in the theater as I left out
What the fuck
Keske fuck
Anyway
So maybe that's gonna be the same thing
When you do Twin Peaks VR is that you're gonna be
Putting that going into that and then like what the fuck
I have never watched Twin Peaks ever
Really you should
Here's the thing in my
Personal opinion the first
Season that was on ABC that's
Only like 7 episodes or something like that
Is like a must watch
It is really fucking good and like
You see things
There that they weren't doing in TV
In the 90's that people are doing
Now the second
Season of the show like
If you like the first season and you
Want to get more of the story you should watch the
Second season only because it
Kind of continues it but it does get
Weaker throughout the second season
Because David Lynch didn't do all of it
The network put a lot
Of pressure to reveal Laura Palmer's
Killer before they really wanted to do it
And it kind of went downhill after they revealed a killer
But there are elements
In that that then come back
In Twin Peaks
The Return so if you're not gonna
Watch the second season at least read
The cliff notes read the spoilers read through it
And then watch The Return because
In my opinion The Return like
Is like there
It's crazy because like I said the 90's
Version of Twin Peaks there was nothing like it
On TV then The Return
There's nothing like it on TV
Now like there was a
Particular episode of that show
And any of you that watch it will know that I was talking
About that was like
40 minutes of just
Pure
What the
Fuck am I watching
But like you sit there at the end of it
And going I think
I understood a third
Of that
But it was really fucking brilliant
That that was art
I don't know what it was
But it was art
And any of you that have watched the revival series
Know exactly which episode I'm talking about
Anyway
I'm sorry I'm finally looking at chat over
At live.vognetwork.com
As Joe and Hunter Matt said I stopped trying to make sense
Of David Lynch after the 90's if you try to
You're just gonna hurt your brain yep pretty much
Anyway
So Twin Peaks VR
Where this whole thing was supposed to be started
So Twin Peaks VR is gonna put you in the Red
Room which is a very important place
In Twin Peaks mythology
This could be considered a minor
Spoiler but the Red Room
Is basically like you could think of it as like
A gateway to hell that's kind of like what I
Sort of look at it as is that the Red Room is like
A gateway to hell
So anyway
Twin Peaks also gets into this whole mythology
About that there could be doppelgangers
In the world that you may have
Somebody that looks exactly like you but they are
From this bad place type of thing
Do they have a goatee?
Um
Not necessarily
But I'll leave it at that
Anyway so
Twin Peaks VR is gonna take you in this Red Room
And you'll be in there
And you're gonna they say in the game
You wind up in the Red Room and
Fans of the series will follow in the footsteps of
Dale Cooper to try to make their way back
Into the life that they left behind
So there will be places and dialogues
From the original series and the sequel
It's gonna be made for the HTC Vive
And the Rift it's only gonna be available
On Steam we don't know when it's gonna come
Out but they are showing it next
Weekend at the Festival of
Disruption in Los Angeles
Which I believe is a David Lynch or at least
David Lynch has a large part of this
Festival thing going on cause you know
Katya is actually gonna be performing at it too
Random?
Well because no Katya fucking loves Twin Peaks
Like her thing
At DragCon New York City where you took a
Picture of her she fucking her set
Was the Red Room from Twin Peaks
And she's actually made outfits
Inspired by Twin Peaks like she's
She's a stan She's very into it
And that's why I love her cause she loves
That weird shit so anyway
Sadly
No word if it's gonna be on PlayStation
VR
Cause you know that would be a nice thing
So anyway
Do you get pie though?
No word if there will be a damn fine cup of coffee
Involved no word on that yet
Or if there will be random dancing to songs
Playing on the jukebox who knows
Anyway I think we should move on to other
Other weird television shows
And things that have spawned from them right Loki?
Yes like The Walking Dead
Unfortunately like The Walking Dead
We might also kind of compare The Walking Dead
To Telltale
Which is kind of Walking Dead
Of it's own
Being that they've laid off 90%
Of their staff
But that's not all because they're continuing
To lay off people as well
So
They had a skeleton crew
That was you know left behind to kind of
Finish up some of the stuff on The Walking Dead
And also
The interactive Minecraft
Series that's supposed to be on
Netflix well
Now of course with that
They're going to be letting
Some of those people go as well
Because now they have another
Team that's gonna be working on
The
Walking Dead series
So they said everyone involved is trying to make sure
Clementines story is told
I'm not concerned at the moment with
Telling that story
In the comics
They said that
As odd as it may sound 25 of us will continue
Foreseeable
I'll make further comment
In the coming weeks after today's events
It's not clear of
How many of those 25 will
Remain because they're not trying
To necessarily
Keep them around I guess since they have
Another studio going to be working on it
And so yeah with that there is gonna be
The series will be finished by
Another company so they've got
Skybound Games is gonna be
Completing season 4
Of The Walking Dead
And of course they made an announcement on
Twitter saying we're so happy to
Announce that we've reached a deal with Telltale Games
That will allow Skybound
To continue The Walking Dead final
Season more details
To come I want to say that they were
Trying to
They're working with the original Telltale team
To finish the story
The way that the fans deserve
Um
Still disappointing to see that they're
You know letting go all those people
Without severance and now they have another team
Working on the game that doesn't make any sense but
That's what they're doing
I don't know
I don't really
Follow the walking dead
Games I know that they're pretty good but
It kinda sucks cause you know
The quality is gonna be quite
I don't know if it's gonna be up there with the other
Games
Yeah this is really unexplored territory too
With the studio closing and a lot of people
Have very strong feelings about how Telltale
Has treated those employees
But yet at the same time
Telltale has created these obligations
To customers out there that they are
Also not gonna be able to follow up on
You know now they've got this whole exchange
But there's this whole like
Duality now where it's like okay
Well who is more important in this scenario
The obligation to the customer
Or the obligation to the employees
Because this is gonna be
Great in I guess fulfilling
That obligation to the customer even though
The quality may be who knows what
I suppose it depends on how many of those Telltale
Employees they get but it's not
Gonna really address the concern of how
To Telltale treat the employees
Sure some of them may be able to come
On but we know it's not gonna be all of them
Some of those folks have probably already
Moved on to new jobs
I don't know if like honestly if it were
Me you know unless you're really really
Passionate about like your job and stuff
Like I can't imagine like oh I
Got fired without severance yeah
And now you want me to work on that game again
That's very true and those
Employees have every right like even if they extend
This offer and say would you like to come finish the game
These employees have every right to say go take a hike
Like just I'm not interested
Because I have bad memories
With that are they being asked to come back
With pay or like just make it
The game well I would assume I would
Assume with pay if it's a new company that's
Taking on the obligation to finish it
The company this new company would hire
Them and do what they need to do
We'll give you some exposure yeah
Anyway
D'artitsuya in chat says
The Telltale news for sure sucks but at the very
Least the story gets to be completed
Not that I'm letting them off the hook and I guess
That's where my mind is at
Is I'm like okay this
Is going to help with half the problem
The obligation to the customers
Will get filled
Even though the quality is still
TBD we'll give them the benefit
Of the doubt and hope it's going to be a great
Maybe is that going to give them more money to
Pay these severances or are they just
Pocketing that that would be fabulous
And then maybe address some of the concern
About what happened to the other half
But unfortunately the realist
In me is like this new
Company has
No need
I mean has no obligation to pay
Another company's
Severance you know what I mean
And please please do not misinterpret
What I'm saying those people deserve to be treated
Better but that's not this
Company that's trying to come in and fix some of the
Problems it's not their problem
They're selling the rights to this company
To like make the game because
It's their series but maybe they're
Getting like a portion of that
You know those profits
Going back to their original telltale company
Because it's their game
Well and then I hope that money gets redistributed to the
Employees because the management
And the board don't deserve a fucking dime
But aren't they just finishing the
Stories for what people have
Already paid for yes so that
Means there's no new money coming in
These people have already paid for this
Game and what money they
Made already wasn't enough to pay severance
So there isn't any new money coming in
To finish whatever chapters are left
Correct so
Yeah no it sucks so this new company that's
Doing it isn't gonna get a dime
Really because people have already paid for the
Content unless new people come on
Later and buy
The whole thing but
For the most part they're just fulfilling back orders
Right yeah and that's why I'm like
The new company like even
Though I have a hard time saying yay
Everything is better okay I'm
Gonna get this new company is doing a good thing
I think it's good intentioned and they're trying
To fix some of the problem what
They can do fixing
This problem with the severance and everything I don't
Think this new company can do at least not
Now not unless a ton of people buy
This game and they made buku bucks but
At that point I mean how long
Before these games come out and turn a profit it's
Probably gonna take some time you know and
Even then these other folks hopefully will
Have moved on but likely add to new
Jobs it's just it's a shitty
Situation and it's telltale management's
Fault and it's unfortunate
I hope the industry
As a whole is kind of watching
What's happening to this and
Especially how pissed off a lot of people
Are getting about it and especially how
It's moving more and more game
Makers to kind of go you know
Maybe we do need to unionize
And it could be very interesting if this
Is gonna be the the straw that
Start or the what was
An analogy I can use here the rock that starts
The avalanche so to speak with that whole thing
So all right
Let's move on one more thing here before we get to the classic
Game of the week I want to talk about a beloved
Game from the past I don't know about you guys but I
Always love this game did you guys ever play a game called
Descent on PC?
Yeah it was pretty cool because it kind of came out
In that first person era when
Doom and Wolfenstein really started
Taking off but Descent was really
The first game that had the full
360 degrees of movement
Cause like in Doom you move forward
Back side side but in Descent
You were a ship and you flew
Around rooms and you really had
360 degrees of movement so they
Made a few Descent games within the series
Kind of went kaput well
Apparently a new Descent
Game is coming out next year
On PC and consoles
So it was announced by
Little Orbit who is a independent
Video game publisher and Descendant
Studios they are making
A reimagining of
Descent you will be going through
Twisting tunnels and caverns
Where again like the originals up and
Down is you know you're gonna
Move all over the place you have to be able to think
In 360 degrees
So anyway they say
This is actually a Kickstarter project from a long
Time ago so it took about 3 years
To get here but the retail and digital release
For PC, Xbox One, and Playstation 4
Is early 2019 the
Switch is now included in this so you can
Play Descent if you wanna you know throw up on the
Go by spinning in all those different directions
You can do that if you
Pre-order now you will get access
To a PC beta starting later
This year a custom version of the
Generation 3 Voila ship
With a new paint job
PC beta challenges
Multi-pass upgrade for multiplayer
Secret missions DLC
You know all the extra crap they tack on to games
These days so anyway kind of
Neat the Descent is coming back and
Always nice to see a Kickstarter come full
Circle and actually get its release
And be fully realized which sadly
Doesn't happen 100% of the time
But we're getting there
Would anyone want to check out the new Descent game
I'm curious about it
I love the old one
Sorry I was texting with my wife apparently they launched
A Falcon 9 rocket near by
You can actually see it outside
Really? Yeah
Yeah pretty close like
She sent me pictures she's like what the hell is that
Why are they launching rockets
Fuck if I know
Random
Delvin I hope your trip
To the US doesn't end in tragedy
Why are they launching no I'm
I'm obviously kidding but
It's neat that they bring back I remember we were talking about that
When they first announced that they were doing that
I mean I
I never really liked the original Descent
I had like the demo for it it came out like one of those PC gamer
Discs or something like that
Back when they used to do that I don't know if they still
Do those but
I don't know I just never really got
It was hard enough for me to control like
First person shooters let alone a
360 first person shooter
But
I never played the original
I never heard of the game so
I mean if there's a demo I'll
Check it out but other than that
Probably not cause is it kinda like a
Like a Star Fox type
I wouldn't really call it Star Fox like imagine if
Star Fox was Doom
Kinda a little more like that it's a little more realistic
I suppose than talking animals
Well no I'm not I just mean in terms of like
It's a flying shooting game
Yeah but you move like you might wanna go to a room
That's above you so you actually fly up
Where as like Star Fox was still kinda
Like on rails a bit
You know what I mean like this gives you the full
360 degrees of motion
So I mean it'll probably be like a very kinda
Competent space shooter game
Multiplayer was a lot of fun though I will say that
Because that was also the day when you know
Modems and BBS's you'd hook up through that
And you could play like 4 player Doom online
Or Duke Nukem
And that was a lot of fun too because you could
Hide above somebody
In a game like Descent so it might be neat
We'll see anyway uh
Let's move on to the classic game of the week you know
One of these weeks we'll have to do Descent
As the classic game of the week but I don't think
That is what Dark Soccer has in store
For us this week let's go ask
Jamie Summers what the classic game of the week this week
Will be
So we take a
Step back in time
Figuratively and literally
In the classic game of the week
Where Dark Soccer is here
It's magic you just appeared
Delvin disappeared and you appeared
Oh my god where did Delvin go
Well through the magic of space and time
He's actually not here yet
Right he gets to see me
As a nun but yet he's there I know
It's going to be a very exciting weekend anyway
Let's continue this exciting weekend
By talking about actually it's going to be way more exciting
For us because we're going to Reno
That's where the nuns go I saw that Whoopi
Goldberg movie Sister Act
Reno and Gamora
Nuns in Reno are nuns
Alright anyway
Girl
It's the classic game of the week Dark Soccer
Is going to take a trip back and walk into the vault
And find a game that she thinks hey
You should get to church
Or play this game
Or cry like the poor Oppa Oppa
Or I will slap you with a ruler like nuns do
Alright it's the classic game of the week
Dark Soccer what did you pick for us
Actually did you know you want a fun fact
Before we get into tonight's classic game of the week
Fun fact for the listeners
So we were having dinner earlier this evening
As people do sometimes
Dark Soccer and I went on a date
So Delvin was there too so it was a triad date
But anyway we were eating and we were
Talking about this segment the classic game of the week
And we were wondering how long is it
Until the classic game of the week
Can be the classic game of the week
Like is this segment so thanks to the
Wonderful people that maintain the wiki
I went back to the wiki and found out
This week October 7th
Was the first classic game of the week
So it's actually 11 years old
This week
So I'm doing the classic game of the week as the classic game of the week
I'm kidding I'm not
Do you know what the very first classic game of the week ever was that we did
I believe it was Fantasy Zone
It was Fantasy Zone
So tonight for our 11th anniversary spectacular
We're doing a sequel
That's Fantasy Zone 1-1
We're doing Fantasy Zone 2
The Tears of Oppa Oppa
Oh it's not Electric Boogaloo?
Or as it was called Oppa Oppa
Non Amida
Which basically means Oppa Oppa Tears
And I'm actually kind of doing 2 and 1
Because I wanted to do the System 16 remake
But to do that I have to talk
About the Sega Master System
Which this is one of the few
Times where the game has come out at home
And then years later they remade it
For the arcade
There's a lot of situations where that's happened
I mean maybe things like Street Fighter V
Question mark
Maybe
In modern times that really doesn't happen
Well at any rate
This was a Sega Master System game
That came out in 1987
Of course it was a Sega game
It was ported to the arcade
Ported to the arcade
Famicom and MSX
And then there was a remake
For System 16 hardware
population in 2008
It had virtual console releases
But we're going to
Go a little bit more
Into what this game is like
So Fantasy Zone 2 does play
Like the first Fantasy Zone
Where it's defender style
You have a continuously scrolling screen
You can go back and forth
And shoot down little bases
And it does qualify as a shooter
Not really fond of that term
But anyway
Now this game has such a fucking
Convoluted storyline
Oh my god Rob it has like three endings
People play this game for the story?
One of the endings
Spoiler
I play it because it's a cute shooter
Oh my god you're going to spoil a 30 year old game
Opa Opa turns evil
And kills the space Harrier
Opa Opa loses to his evil self
Evil self takes over
And the space Harrier
Which you know is set in the same universe right?
Opa Opa tries to go to knock his ass out
And Opa Opa kills him
Funny enough that was also the ending
I'm sorry to spoil this guys
But that's also the ending to A Star is Born
Is that Gaga turns evil
And turns into the evil leader of the planet
And makes everybody bow down and say
Yes Gaga yes
That's basically what it is
And then she interrupts my Fantasy Zone music
And then Changela comes out of the box
Yes Hallelu
Anyway
So basically the story of this
Is in the year 1432
Space year 1432
Ten years after
Fantasy Zone
Opa Opa has to go in
And save the Fantasy Zone again
So the mastermind of this
Is an evil version of himself
And then after winning
God Smooshy what?
Can we hear him?
I don't think he picks up on the mic
Mr. Smoosh is throwing a fit
He's screaming
Anyway Opa Opa's father comes out to
Comfort him
And Opa Opa cries
And so the evil Opa Opa vanishes
Mr. Smoosh is just playing along
And he's singing along
But you get to see Opa Opa's daddy
Which is a big ginormous Opa Opa
Alright well Mr. Smoosh's daddy is going to go over there and tell him to shut the fuck up
I'll be back
So anyway as I said
You play kind of Defender Style
Indefinitely
And you can travel freely
You've got different bases that you have to knock down
And you pick up coins
And you can go into secret shops to buy stuff
But now what's new in this one
Is that you get different warps that are hidden behind
Certain bases that let you travel to different zones
So you have three different zones
And when all of the bases have
disappeared and all three of the zones
Are available
Then you can go through a warp to get to the boss
Now the boss fights are just simply
Like the way that they were in fantasy zones
Where you have to kind of be
Sort of bullet hellish
You know shooting at big bossy things
And then
They are super huge and they change color
And then your last stage is a boss rush
Which is kind of a pain in the ass
So you get different types of attacks
You have a fire and you have a bomb
The bomb kind of drops
Like in an arc
But it is more powerful and has a shorter range
You get the shops like I said
You can get different weapons
Bombs, speeds, extra lives
You get the large wing
And the jet engine
The large one is probably one of my favorite ones
So the ones that upgrade
Over open speed are permanent
As long as you do not die
Weapon upgrades are time limited
And the bombs have a limited number
So here's where we get to the fun part
All the ports
So it passes into our cave
The first one is based on system A
So it is almost identical to master system version
It does have the radar that shows
The base of the destroyer pod
And of course
It has a timer because
Pretty much kind of like
Like those play choice games I guess
The internet
The Famicom version
That came out actually has
A kind of different name
It's called the teardrop of Oppa Oppa
So now we have the big one
Which really is the one that I wanted to talk about
So now keep in mind
The first one came out
In what did I say
2000 not 2000
1987 right
So in 2008
So 10 years ago
They
Re-released the game
They did it in the system 16
Which is
Basically the
Same original hardware
It was
It was developed by M2
And it's not really
They didn't want to modernize the older one
They wanted to do a hypothetical interpretation
Of what the game would have been like
Had it been developed for
System 16 arcade hardware
By the original staff
That's kind of neat though
It is
So instead of using the Sega console
R&D system
And system E board for the system 16
It was called a what if remake
And basically it adhered
Strictly to the limitations
From the time that fantasy M2
Was originally released
But with the arcade hardware
At that point
So M2 developed it on a real
System 16 hardware
Except that it had expanded memory
256 kilobytes
So it was called
They dubbed it system 16c
Well I mean that was pretty hot shit for
No yeah for that time
Now it's just funny like 256 kilobytes
It's like I have word documents
That are far bigger than that you know
It's crazy
On top of that it actually can be played
Via emulation
And on top of that it shows a 1987
Sega copyright and makes no mention
Of M2
So it really
And I played the system 16 arcade remake
I played it at
California extreme
I played the shit out of it at California
Extreme cause I fucking love some Fantasy Zone
And when I first looked at it
If I hadn't seen it say the tears of
Oppa Oppa I would have thought I was
About to play the real Fantasy Zone
And I was like oh wait shit this is
That one
So it's been nicknamed by fans
Fantasy Zone 2DX
Nice
So it follows the original one
Kinda loosely it has the enemies
Music locations and gameplay from
Master System game that has
New content and elements that went
With the original Fantasy Zone it's actually kinda why I like
This one better cause it's more like the original Fantasy Zone
So level structure is the
Same so instead of distinct zones that you
Have to beat you actually have portals
That take you into parallel dimensions
You have the bright side and the dark side
And they're comparable to the levels
Of the first Fantasy Zone
So you can destroy them in each dimension
Jeez okay
So bases
That are destroyed in one dimension will be destroyed in the other
So you can clear entirely on one level
Of the other but the dark side is more
Difficult but you get greater rewards
And points and money
The bosses are the same on either side
But they have a more difficult
Attack pattern on the dark side
It also has three endings
Based on which
On both whether the dark side levels
Were cleared and whether certain specific
Items were purchased so that's where
You get like the you know daddy comes
And helps Oppa Oppa
And then evil Oppa Oppa
Takes over and there's like one more
The music was done by
Manabu Namiki
Sorry Manabu Namiki
That uses
Some of the songs from
The original Fantasy Zone 2 soundtrack
But rearranged to fit more
Like Kawaguchi Hiroshi's
First Fantasy Zone style so
And there's a few original tracks
That were made for it
It's based off of some of the same
Games
The
Bosses there are some new ones for here
It's just sort of like again a loose interpretation
It's kind of like arena
So it has been bootlegged and re-released
To the arcades
As FZ-2006-2
By a Taiwanese manufacturer
Called ISG
As a 2006 copyright date
But it's directly
Derived from the Playstation 2 release
It also has the ROM data
From the PS2 version
Sega did
Actually produce
Real arcade units running the System 16
Hardware as part of the promotion
So there's a Nintendo 3DS
Port of this version
16-bit version that came out in Japan
In 2014 and internationally
In 2015 and it's called 3D Fantasy
Zone 2W
You also have
Another game mode in this one
It's called Loop Land
Where it's an endless survival mode
Starring Oppa Oppa's brother Oppa Oppa
Oppa Oppa and Oppa Oppa
Oppa Oppa
I just always laugh at Oppa Oppa
Because I don't know if his name is supposed to be a ton on boobs
Oppai
Or if it's like Oppa
You know the Greek cheer
I think it's also a Korean word for brother
Because I used to have a friend in high school
Random question
So there you go
It is one of the best games
Ever made Fantasy Zone 2
And as much
As much as I
I have a lot of fucking love for this game
And if someone wants to find me
The Sega Ages Fantasy Zone box
Will work something out
Alright
She'll go Oppa Oppa for it
Also
I'm mad because Dan guessed
One of the games I got him
And I can't lie
He guessed that I got him the treasure box
So when is his birthday?
It's November 29th
Oh gosh so are you making him wait?
I'm making him wait
That's what he gets
Guess what he got though for us?
On the 27th he got us tickets to see the
40th anniversary
Theater showing a superman
That's kind of cool
Very cool
Last game of the week Fantasy Zone 2
The Tears of Oppa Oppa
Poor Oppa Oppa don't cry
We're running long so we gotta wrap up
So any last words for the week Dark Sakura?
I like big butts
And I cannot lie
You other brothers can't deny
I'm kidding
I don't like big butts
Unless they're like rump roasts
I'm done
And we're back in the present
Where sadly Dark Sakura did not
end up coming out as a nun
Delvin didn't get to see that because unfortunately
I think she got a little sick before
we went out last night
I was taking Delvin around
I'm trying to think of how to give Delvin this Sacramento
experience because we don't exactly have
a lot. It's not like Disneyland
is in this part of California
Disneyland is like six hours
from here. It's a long way away
It's pretty far
So I was like well we'll go to Old Town
That'll be fun
We'll go to the Capitol
I actually taught Delvin a little bit about
American government today
Which is very confusing by the way
Especially if you've watched the news this past week
You're especially looking at it going
How did any of this happen?
It's so confusing
US politics is just very confusing
Canadian politics which I feel is a little bit more
simplistic in its design
But ask any of us to explain
Canadian politics and we couldn't do it
I doubt I barely could
I would bet there would be so many Americans that would be like
Justin Trudeau is the president of Canada, right?
Probably
Well, no
Prime Minister, but close
Close, as far as
delegations
It's got to be equivalent, but it's not the same
Anyway
To register participation for this
week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at
vognetwork.com, use the passphrase
Family
Speaking of like adventures and
being here in Sacramento
So you've listened to OLR sometimes
And now you're here, what should people at home
know about what
OLR is really like in person?
It's just what it sounds like
That's good
I guess that's good, that means we're authentic
That's good, alright, it's an authentic product
I appreciate that
Good, alright
And you're even getting to sit in Jamie's chair
I feel very special
It's the nicest chair in the room, isn't it?
That's why I picked it
Nothing but the finest for our out of town guests
Alright, looking at chat over at live.vognetwork.com
SSG100Matt says
I thought the Sacramento experience was watching
Lady Bird
You know, as
somebody who's lived here his entire life
I did watch that movie and I was
obviously I nitpicked some of the
little things, but I was like, yeah
honestly, they got it
They
really got it, and like the whole story
of her really spoke to me
because I too applied to go to college
back east, it's just
I didn't get in
Aww
My life turned out okay, it's all good
I also learned in college that college
wasn't for me, and that's what happens
sometimes, college isn't for everybody, so
Sometimes I just don't think people should go
college right after high school
I think that is, well that's a
big reason why community college is a thing
because, and some people have joked and called
community college 13th grade, but
actually I think it really is like a good
transition type of thing, so I think
community college is really underrated in
many ways, but anyway, it is not that kind of
show, although I
do associate, you know what I associate community college
with? The altered beast machine
that was at the cafeteria at the community college
I went to and took like one or two
classes at during the summer, they
had an altered beast machine, it was awesome
There you go
What? What?
I guess I live a primitive life up in Canada
Apparently, my god, you
really do all live in igloos with no power
don't you
Alright
Alright, let's move on, let's get into some
rapid fire news, Loki
So there's more rumors regarding
Microsoft releasing
a streaming platform
as a new console possibly
next year, they're
saying that
the rumors are that this
console quality game
streaming platform for phones and other
devices will be released
sometime as early as
quarter one of, or quarter two
of next year, and
they're saying that there's possibly going to be an
announcement at EXO
2018 in November
So I guess we'll have to
wait and see if that actually
ends up being a thing
They don't really have a streaming
platform
I feel like it's not a void they really need to
fill, because they have game pass
which is pretty rad, but
okay, I mean if they
But what if you could do game pass on devices that
if you don't have an Xbox
Yeah, I think that's the direction
Microsoft, and we've heard this rumor before
that the next Xbox
is there's going to be one super
Xbox, but then there's going to be a baby
Xbox that just basically does the online
Yeah, so I
one of the things that I think the direction
Microsoft is going, and probably
all consoles will be going in the future
is no longer having us
like a new generation
and then creating a segmented
user base, so
I think that they're planning to have
whatever next console Microsoft
comes out with the more powerful
and whatever the case may be, but those games
that come out for it will work on your
original Xbox, but will scale
in the same way that you
buy a PC game, and even if you
are playing it on your laptop with
no video card, it will still work
or just like
you have Pokemon Go
on your iPhone, and it will work
on your iPhone 5, 6
7, 8, it doesn't matter
it just scales correctly, so
this streaming method
might be one of the ways in which they
allow those more powerful games to
run on the older systems, you just
stream it. Well you know a story that didn't
make our show roll tonight has to do with the fact that
the Switch is exploiting, like Capcom's
looking at doing something like
Resident Evil 7 with maybe
more of their games, because you may or may not
know, but in Japan, there's more of these
streaming games on the Switch, and that's how
they've put Resident Evil 7 on it
and Assassin's Creed Odyssey came out
on the Switch in Japan. And Phantasy Star Online
2. Oh that's right!
Is a streaming
stream game. God that pisses me off.
That's not open, that can of worms.
I want to play that game so bad,
and they just refuse to release it in the US.
Sega, what's your fucking problem?
Like seriously.
I have so much fond memories of that
game, but I just want to play the second one
so bad. Same.
Anyway, sorry Logi.
So, I think
it's a neat idea on paper, but
like, you know, are
the United, you know,
North American
internet infrastructures
going to be able to handle something like this?
I don't, I'm
kind of concerned that, no,
they can't. I
would, well, okay, but remember
we live in Sacramento, and
one of the things that we're getting here, that
very few cities in America are getting because we're in
a test program, they just rolled out 5G here.
Now sadly, not where OLR Studios
is located, because this is in the downtown
part, and I'm not going to give out my address on
air, but I don't live downtown.
So, the downtown area is really
where a lot of this is going in, because they put all the
boxes on phone poles. So, I mean, 5G
is going to give you wirelessly
like what cable internet gives
you. So,
here's the thing, in five years from now,
Logi, the internet like that is only
going to get better, and 5G is going to roll out more
and more places. Will places like
rural Alaska
have that type of internet? Probably
not, but you know what?
I mean, they
were probably still on dial-up
up to a few years ago, but it's progressed.
It's not so much the speeds. I mean,
speeds definitely, we need improvements
there, but it's also bandwidth caps
for no fucking reason.
Well, I kind of think
that argument is going to have to
give a little bit as more and
more people start getting too close to
that cap, but cable is really
probably assessing the situation right now. Like, a
company like Comcast is
definitely going. Like, the days
of cable as a television
delivery service are limited. Like,
that is dying. You know,
again, maybe in rural parts
where there isn't as fast of internet and so forth,
maybe there's still a need there, but
again, a lot of those people have had satellite
for the longest time. But, you know, people,
more and more people are ditching cable
channels to watch their shows on
Netflix, or this is why
as much as people hate on CBS
All Access, it exists
because CBS saw this coming a long
time ago. So, they were trying to
future-proof against, you know what?
People aren't going to be getting CBS on cable.
They're not going to be getting it over the air.
So, we need to, you know, adopt
this Netflix-style thing, like, fast
because that is where it's going.
So, one of the things I
have noticed recently
in terms of infrastructure
and internet and TV and all that sort of thing,
all the,
in Canada, the providers now,
all the internet plans don't
have, most of them don't have caps anymore.
They're all just unlimited.
They just limit the speed at which you get
the internet now. Oh, hooray. Another reason
why Canada is better than the United States.
Like, as if everything.
Why can't we just live in Canada? I mean,
seriously. You can if you want to.
It's a bit of a process. Actually, do you know, I was like,
do you know how hard it is for an American to be going to Canada?
Because, you know, there's a lot of people this week
that are like, I'm going to move to Canada because fuck
this place. And, you know what?
I completely understand
that as a reaction. But when you
sit down and you really start to plot
it out, you're like, oh shit, that's really hard
to do. It's complicated. And
it's also one of those things, and I
don't want to get political, but it's also one of those where I also
kind of feel like, no, this is my fucking
country too. And we are going
to fucking fix this problem.
So that's also my kind of perspective, but that's my
I will get on that high horse at a later time.
So anyway. But anyway, so
the, uh, most of the plans are
trending towards no cap. So that's
one issue for this streaming service gone
out the window. Um,
the major issue will be the
cap, or so not the cap, the
bandwidth or rate at which you can
download it and upload. Because
if you don't have good up download, then you're screwed for the
streaming service. But I think it's more something
that is going to be as a premium service. So it's not
meant to be for,
you know, Tom in Alaska, who's,
you know, he needs to actually
purchase the game in order to play it.
He can't stream it. Which could easily be said
to for people north of you in Canada,
because there's a lot of, a lot of place
in Canada that probably don't have these fast Internet's.
Yeah, very, very true. Um, and
one of the things like you mentioned with the TV,
um, so one of the, uh,
television, major television providers,
CTV, uh, in
Canada did their promos
in all the subway stations for,
you know, the fall lineup and stuff.
Normally they'll say, oh, this
show is airing, uh,
you know, Thursdays at nine.
Uh, one of the key
things I noticed that they did, uh,
in their advertising is they said it is
now streaming at
such and such a time. Yeah.
They, they emphasize that
it's not something
that's live. It's available for
streaming at this time and this
date. Yeah. So again, trending in
the direction of you just now are just going to
get everything on the Internet. Yeah.
No, it's interesting stuff. It's
going to be really interesting to see where we are in the future.
I mean, to put it in perspective,
one other little tidbit that I think you guys, some of you
are going to find funny. When OLR
first started in 2002,
this was before VOG Network
was a thing. This was before All Games Radio
where we were at previously was a thing.
When OLR was a
station where this show was
the kind of centerpiece of the station,
that's what it was originally intended.
One of the pitches of our station
because we were kind of, and I'm using my quoting fingers,
competing with DDR
Freak Radio, but we really weren't.
Like we were two peas in a pod, right?
But our thing was
where as DDR Freak Radio was all high
speed, we were dial-up friendly
radio when we started.
So something to think about. When this show started,
there was still enough need out there
for there to be dial-up friendly streams
that you could listen to. And
there's a reason why I'm called Potato
because this show sounded like a Potato
if you go back to episode one, because it's saved
in that dial-up quality. But that's the
reality, is that the internet has progressed
that much, even since then.
And it will continue to progress even
faster, even in the next five years.
As far as this show is concerned,
even in the next three months, because
whereas we upgraded from
24 kbps,
the dial-up standard or whatever it was,
to 96, which we're using on VoG,
now we're going to be going to Twitch.
As more and more people now
can just watch video on their phones.
This is not something we could have considered doing
a few years ago, even.
You know what I mean?
So, again, with this streaming service, it's kind of
just, I guess, them setting the groundwork
and infrastructure for something that
will be more readily
available in five years.
Anyway, rapid-fire news, and we just spent
probably the longest on that topic, but that's alright.
It was good talk.
I love how you say sorry.
So, PUBG over the last
14 months has banned 13 million
users.
That's one way to get your
subscription numbers out. Well, most of
the people that were kicked off the service
were using cheat tools.
And then
apparently that's a common problem.
Well, I would assume so, if you've kicked off
13 million people.
They've, of course, been
patching the game to fight against these
tools, but then there's also
aimbots and whatnot.
But these were the numbers
that were coming out from Bluehole
and the Korean
PUBG Cafe board.
That's an
interesting statistic.
Yeah.
Maybe the rampant
cheating is one of the reasons why PUBG
has fallen in the rankings. I don't know.
But I don't play the game or Fortnite
enough to really get into that stan war.
So, but it's just, it's interesting
they've had to ban that many accounts, and is that really gonna
stop them? As Jason said in the intro,
one goes down, two more
come up, you know? Well, I think one of the things
that killed the PUBG
userbase was the amount of
people that they were banning
for stream sniping,
quote unquote, but weren't
actually stream sniping. Oh.
Remember that whole thing? Yeah, I do.
That really killed that community. Yeah, that was...
And that was right when Fortnite came out.
So, people were getting pissed off from one
and jumping right to the other. Well, but then the
other big thing was that Fortnite's Battle Royale
was free, and PUBG cost money.
And I think, honestly, it's really not much
more difficult than that.
I think for a lot, but you're right, that other
situation certainly didn't help. And the quality of
the game, it looks like too, like PUBG
it's not really as flat.
It's kind of like comparing, I guess,
like, you know, it's not Overwatch
where Overwatch, you know, has
this like really flashy
art style and everything that, you know,
Fortnite has, whereas PUBG's kind of
meh. It's
serves its purpose. It's trying to go a little more
for the realistic angle. Yeah, but...
To make success. Yeah, no, I get it.
I get it. Alright. Anyhow,
let's move on to some other rapid fire news
including a game that's several years old
at this point, which is interesting because
it's a remake of a game that's many years old.
But it's one of my favorite classics.
The game Shadowgate from the
Nintendo Entertainment System. Did you ever play Shadowgate, Delvin?
Never heard of it. Oh, and the music is really
good. It was like a PC game
they kind of put out on the NES.
Where, like, you use the
controller as a mouse, basically.
And, yeah, it's kind of neat. Anyway, they
remade it a few years ago and
I actually was a Kickstarter backer. It's one of the
very few Kickstarters I ever did.
But I was like, somebody wants to make a
new Shadowgate game? Fuck yes, take my money.
Because this was before we really started
learning about all the issues with Kickstarter.
And, you know what, to be fair, these guys
they did the game. They delivered on what
they promised. It's out there.
So, uh, and they're going to keep it going
because this new Shadowgate
version is going to be coming to the Nintendo Switch
this autumn. So they're putting out
the new Shadowgate on the Switch.
It is based on the newer PC version
that came out a couple years ago, but they're going to enhance it
with a new user interface and
a wheel-based command system, some other
new features and elements as well. So
that is pretty cool.
Also, speaking of the Nintendo stuff,
remember the Switch Online
Classic Nintendo library?
We knew we were going to be getting more games
in October, but we didn't quite know when.
Well, now we know. Those new games
will be arriving on October 10th.
So Super Dodgeball,
NES Open Tournament Golf, and
Sullivan's Key will be arriving on
October 10th. And if I were to rank
those, I would say probably Super
Dodgeball is going to be the best, especially with the
online play. That was a really,
uh, it's kind of the art style
of River City Ransom, and it has a very
particular name in Japan, and somebody
in chat will beat me to it. But, um...
You needed a multi-tap to play
that, because it's four players, wasn't it?
I don't think so. You could play two-player.
It might have supported the four-player
thing, but it was two-player. I think it did.
But it was like, imagine the River City Ransom guys are playing
Dodgeball, and it was really well done.
The definitive version is on the Neo Geo,
honestly, but the NES version
is not bad. Because they were playing,
thinking way back, they were playing
this on
stage when they were doing the
Nintendo World Championships
in the Oakland Coliseum.
They were playing the four-player version of
Dodgeball.
I remember when I was trying to do the
preliminary
trial thing, where you had to play the three games.
And then I would rank
number two as Solomon's Key.
Some people would probably put that in first place,
but I think that was a pretty competent puzzler game
that was on the NES. And number three,
of course, the golf game. Trash.
Sorry, just my opinion.
It is. It is.
Does Nintendo have Nintendo Golf on there already?
Uh, the actual NES Golf?
No, it is not there.
So this is what you're getting instead.
Oh, on the NES Classic
service, but there wasn't that
golf thing that they did, someone
Oh, it was, uh, that was
the hidden game. The hidden game was golf.
That was the Iwata thing that somebody
found in there was the original 8-bit
NES Golf. That's what you're thinking about.
That actually, for some reason, was not
put on the Nintendo Classic service, and they're
doing this instead, so I don't know.
This is a golf game from much later in the NES's life.
Oh, it's not that golf game.
No, it is not. It's a Mario golf game.
It's basically that, but insert Mario.
Which, to think about it, if I seem to remember
the original guy kind of looked like Mario,
but it wasn't officially him.
But there's a very different look to this game.
So, uh, anyway.
D'Artesia said, I assume that we won't
get original NES Golf.
I don't know. They may still do that at some point.
And D'Artesia says, I do
remember having Solomon's Key back in the day.
Actually, I owned it too, believe it or not.
So they're not gonna do the original golf because it's
gonna take so much programming stuff
for them to get to work. They can't just, like,
dump in a ROM or anything like that?
We're not doing this again.
I'm just checking, because it seems like
it's an awful lot of work for Nintendo.
Not today, Satan. Delvin is here,
and we are going to have
a good time, dammit!
Alright.
Let's move on and talk about what's coming
out in stores this week. Loki,
what will we be playing a little sooner than
NES Golf on the Switch?
And then the World Ends With You final
remix. Is it really the final remix?
Is it really the final one?
The final for now. Final for now.
Nintendo Switch. It's final, like, as in the
Final Fantasy for the
Nintendo Switch. And that
is what we're getting.
Alright, let's travel to Japan. And over
in Japan, they're gonna be getting a game called
Varnir of the Dragon Star,
Exodus of the Dragon
that comes out in a regular and limited edition.
Middle Earth Shadow of War
that's a price reduction in Japan this week as it
moves into the definitive edition.
Tactical Assault Commander
comes out as well, with a variety
of different little controllers and things like that.
And believe it or not, Call of Duty
Black Ops 4, you know, they're going pretty
hard in Japan with that as well, so they
get a release the same day we do,
as well as Europe, so that's all on the same
day. So Japan won't miss out on that.
But they're actually also getting a blue
camouflage dual-shot
controller as well. And then
there are new PlayStation 4 pros
in Glacier White and Jet Black.
I don't think these are Call of Duty themed, I think they just
happen to be the same day. But there's Glacier White
and Jet Black pros with a one terabyte
hard drive also coming out that day.
And there is also a brand new
PlayStation VR bundle in
Japan, so kind of
setting the stage for end-of-the-year
releases. Not really holiday releases in Japan
because Christmas isn't quite the same thing
that it is here, but I would say
end-of-the-year kind of positioning.
That is Japan. Dark Soccer
is not here for the UK, but maybe you can help out
Logie? Sure.
So this week we're getting Space Hulk
Tactics on PlayStation 4 and
Xbox One, WWE 2K19
on PC, PlayStation 4
and Xbox One. Goosebumps
the game on the Switch.
They're getting a bridge
constructor compilation
that's both the bridge
constructor portal and the original
bridge constructor that's on PlayStation 4.
A game called My
Riding Stables Life with Horses
on PlayStation 4 and the Switch.
Call of Duty
Black Ops 4 on PlayStation 4
Xbox One and PC.
And last but not least
The World Ends with You final remix on the
Switch. Okie dokie.
Well before we get back into some news
we're going to take some time out to read
some of your emails.
Every
week you guys email us. Participate at
OrangeLoungeRadio.com and we read some
of those emails live here on the air.
Actually we're pretty good about reading them all
unless they're just way way
way too long or off topic or something like
that, but we read them all.
You get to be here for a mail bag segment, Delman.
Isn't that exciting? Yes. And we actually have some
emails tonight. You ready for it? Alright.
I should have made you read them. That would have been fun. Alright.
Anyway, the first email tonight
is from DJ Rama S.
I've never heard of this guy. He must be
a new listener.
Long time listener. First time caller.
How about that? Alright. Obviously I'm teasing.
We love Rama. So the email
goes like this. Evening everyone.
I hope all is good. Two weeks ago
I tried to call into the show, but I just missed
the Skyplinas. I just got off the train.
So if you bear with me, I have a few things to say.
Number one. Telltale Games.
First of all, I feel really bad about
the employees losing their jobs like that.
It sucks that this seems to be the norm in
the industry when it shouldn't be. What
bothers me is how upper management surprised
everyone about it. How do you go from
hiring people to firing people in a week?
I really think that upper management
has been finageling
the books. But hey,
what do I know? I have
this really weird feeling.
Give it about like six months
and there's going to be a lot of those employees
who are going to squawk. And we're going to
like there's going to be books written about
the fucking ups and fucking
downs of Telltale Games.
Because, seriously, open Twitter.
And they're already
like there's just a lot. I got something
to say. And you know what?
And I'm not making fun of it. Like
I bet there's a lot
of things that have built up that people
have wanted to say. So I'm very let
it out. Let it out y'all. Someone
needs to make a docu-series about
the gaming industry in general of
like past employees. And
one of them that I want to hear from, of course,
is Kojima. You know,
I would love
to see some type of documentary
that's very real about the game.
I'm sure there's been some, you know, if
you can think of it, it's been done, I'm sure.
So I'm sure there's documentaries on YouTube
and things like that about the gaming industry. But I would
like somebody who's like really a renowned
like documentary filmmaker. And I'm not thinking
about like Michael Moore because he's a bit partisan.
But he's very well known for his documentaries.
But I'm thinking maybe a little more like how
do you remember when you saw Super Size Me?
I don't know if you ever saw that movie. What was that guy's name?
Spurlock made that movie.
And it really opened people's eyes
to like, wow,
this is why I'm fat.
And just how McDonald's was really
pushing a lot of this stuff and the industry
in general, you know, not to pick on McDonald's, but maybe
a little bit. And it even made McDonald's change
some of their policies that they no longer
would ask, you know, you want to super size
it. And I think eventually they got rid of that and that
whole thing. And you've even commented on this before
about how like a medium drink here is like a large.
Yeah, it's crazy, right?
So anyway, the reason why I say that is that I would like a documentary
like that, but about
what really happens in the gaming industry.
How a game is really made from start to finish.
Yes. And I want it to be
something that I could be comfortable saying.
I 100%
support anybody starting
a gaming podcast. I want
voices to be out there. I want everybody to be
heard, but you need to
watch this documentary first
before you just start blindly saying this game
sucks. These people suck. All this
sucks. Like I want a documentary
that I'm going to feel comfortable saying
I support you doing this, but
first, you need to put your shoes
in, or you need to put yourself in the shoes of
somebody who's really in this. You know what I mean?
So anyway. Give some perspective to the gaming
internet. Yeah, for real.
Anyway, actdeft in chat says
granted super size me was kind of a hoax.
Okay, look, I realize there's always going to be
controversy with documentaries. There's always going to be
is it part, is it, was this lean one way or the other?
I think you all see the real point I'm
getting. I'm not saying make a copy of that, but I'm just
saying that movie love
it or hate it had a social impact
and I want to see something that
powerful about how we're treating people
that work in the game industry. Does that make sense?
Yeah, absolutely. Okay. Anyway,
um, number two, the PlayStation classic
in Rama's email. I too
had wondered why the PlayStation classic isn't coming
with dual shot controllers. They're going with the
generation of games that didn't need them. From
the reactions I saw, it seems that a lot of people
forgot that the PlayStation originally had
standard controllers. I also understand
why people were taken aback at the price tag of
$99. 20 games,
each disk about 650 megabytes.
All of the games are going to need at least
13 gigs of space at minimum,
at least 32 gigs tops.
Even at that price, I don't see
myself investing in one.
PlayStation emulation
seems to be pretty well,
so I should be able to play them on my laptop or
Surface 3 with minimal issues.
Also, if you notice, the controller ports aren't
even USB. To be quite
honest, I feel that Atari has the
right idea with their retro console.
USB, you can make your own games,
add your own extra storage.
To be quite honest, I'm seriously considering
to build my own mini retro box.
We'll see.
So, there you go. Uh, lastly,
oh, I'm sorry, no, there's a few more here. Skype
versus Discord. Uh, because I've said
on the show,
openly, I'm considering switching to Discord.
Uh, honestly, stay with Skype.
A few episodes back, we tried
to do our show on Discord because of Skype 7
being discontinued, and Skype 8
was buggy as fuck. Honestly, it did not
work. There were too many audio dropout and
lagging, so we switched back to Skype 8,
and we haven't had any issues since.
But what's interesting is that my other podcast I do
over Discord is fine. I think because
we're also streaming audio out, that could be the
issue, and I look forward to hearing updates on
the new studio streaming PC. Also,
I've used my Surface 3 to record my
podcast at conventions, so it's a great
little device. I
have considered the Surface as
an option. It's a good choice.
I've considered it. Is that what you use?
No. No. You have a different thing.
Um, I just need to make sure it can do
Twitch and everything. I have a Surface
3 Pro. I might want to bring it over.
I might want to check it out a little. If you don't mind me poking
at it a little bit. You can get them cheap.
Mine was only, like, 400
used, and it came with everything.
Anyway, anyway, I'll get in that later.
Anyway, for what you want to do, I highly
recommend a Surface Pro 5 or 6.
We can talk offline for more details on that.
Might as well just get a laptop for that price.
And then lastly, you know
Rama's got something to say about Bowsette.
I know you're
tired of the meme, and I know this has crossed
deep into your neck of the woods. For what it's
worth, it's gone deep into the anime
and cosplay fandom. I'm seeing
some great cosplays from this, with cosplayers
doing many variants, and I love it.
I know I busted your chops about it,
but it's all fun and games. Just
let us, the anime fans, enjoy
this. Here's the thing.
I'm not going to tell anyone what they can or can't
do for fun, as long as they're not hurting anybody.
I might argue that this
is hurting my eyes.
But jokes aside,
y'all can have your fun, but I
am going to sit there in my rocking chair,
and the minute someone in a Bowsette cosplay
comes up, I'm going to say, get the hell
off my lawn.
Give me that, alright?
Love and hearts
and XOs, I mean it. Alright, anyway,
back to the email. That's all that's been
on my mind. Enjoying the show. Thankful for
the podcast. Keep it fabulous.
From the East Coast, the York of New
Rama. There you go. Thank you
for the emails. Great email.
Alright, going to
another email from YYR,
who says, hello LR.
Don't worry, I don't have a laundry list
of complaints this week, but I did have
a question for Loki.
This is for you, sir. I'm listening.
Week after week, you mentioned that you've
been playing on your DDR Extreme cabinet,
but as a long time DDR player,
I'm personally interested in hearing
about your progression. What level
are you up to now? What songs have
you been working on lately? Now that you're
playing constantly, at what rate
have you been improving? Are you playing
double, or just focusing on singles
for now? You know, here's the funny part,
is I'm not improving.
That's the weirdest thing. I
always play doubles, unless
my, you know, kids
or something want me to play singles, and actually
it's weird. Playing doubles,
like, I could be used to that,
and I can play it for a while, and then I go and play
singles, and it actually really hurts my feet
to play singles. Like, it's just different.
I don't know. It's...
But, no, and sadly, I'm not really getting
much better at
it. I have been noticing
lately, though, that the machine needs to be tuned up
again, because I'm starting
to get some misses on my upper arrow on the
left side, but that's probably because
it just needs to be cleaned out again. I never did clean
the right side of the stage, either,
so I probably should do that at some point,
but, yeah, sadly,
I haven't really been progressing too much further.
I've tried to play harder songs.
I guess that's not necessarily
true, because when I started playing, I couldn't really play a whole
lot of hard stuff.
I've been kind of hanging around,
like, I
always do, like, the random Caprice stuff,
because it's just, you know,
random songs, and they usually would just play them on the
standard difficulty, but then I've been
lately been mixing it up when, you know,
DDR tends to be nice,
and throws in, you know,
hey, let's do a Legend of Max, and then followed
by, you know, Paranormal Survivor Max
on a random Caprice. I'm like, fuck
that, and I go and play something else.
So, I've been trying to play, like,
around, like, six to eight,
but I find, like, the eight-footer song, especially in doubles,
can get really tiring,
and also the hard thing, too,
is, like, after I come home and play DDR,
it's after I've walked for, like, three to
five miles that day already,
and so I can tell when I'm getting tired
because I start missing stuff more,
so I don't really care about as far as, like,
perfect attacking anything. If I pass the song, cool.
That's it.
But, yeah, I haven't really noticed that I'm, like,
can, like, all of a sudden play Max or something
now. I don't, I don't think I'm as
good as I was before.
Do you notice your stamina improving at all, though, that, like,
you know, that you were really winded in the
beginning? Because I would think that if I were to get back into
DDR every day, which I really, like, I just
really wish I could. I wish I had a
situation where I could have a DDR machine in this house.
It's just not financially
the thing to do, and we don't own this house,
so it's just not, you know, something I really want to keep here.
And even to go out and play at an
arcade, like, A,
it, I hate to say it, it's a little weird that I'm
40 years old when we have these, you know,
you know, younger kids that are playing the game. It's gonna look a little
weird. Like, am I a predator? Honestly, no, because
after, like, watching the people play
Ace, they're, like, fucking hugging the bar
on standard difficulty shit. I'm like,
I'm not judging, but I'm
judging. Well, that's a whole
nother thing you're gonna get into. But anyway,
my point is, really, though, all
that aside, I mean, you guys could tell me it doesn't matter
all you want, but the reality is, there just isn't
a machine conveniently near here.
Yes, we have machines in Sacramento, but we
have this thing called rush hour traffic,
and it's gonna change your mind about a lot of things,
too, about what's convenient to get to an amount
of time. And just the area, town
I live in, just, there's nothing convenient.
Like, sure, if there was, like, a DDR machine in
an arcade, like, right up the street, I'd probably go there
all the time. But anyway.
Alright, and then, I want to
continue with YYR's email. I can't
speak for everyone, but since a significant portion
of OLR's audience came out of the DDR
community, I'm pretty sure I'm not the only one
interested in learning more about your progress.
So I hope you'll give us regular updates as you
pursue your personal goals.
Well, funny enough, I've been thinking, actually, the last
few times I've been playing, of setting up a Twitch stream
setup. I think you should.
I've been looking into it, but, like, it's gonna
be complicated to do something like that.
Um, because I want to do, like, a
multi-camera setup type thing, but...
Well, here's my suggestion.
Start basic. Like, I know
you want to reach for the stars, and you know you want it
to be fucking primo on day one, but I'm
gonna also keep it real. OLR's
gonna convert to Twitch soon. Don't expect
it to be what we really want it to be
day one. Day one is going to be camera
pointed at us as we do this show,
like it used to be on Justin TV
all those years ago. Then, we might
start to grow more and more, but again,
I want to make, and I'm stressing this,
especially for my podcast people out there, because I know
there's a lot of you. I don't want to change
it into a video show for those of you that
are listening on audio. It's still Orange Lounge Radio,
it's just that you can watch
us do it on Twitch if you want, but, you know,
that's all gonna grow with time, and so forth.
So anyway, my point is, that's
great you want a multi-camera setup. You don't need
it day one. Right, I know that.
And it's just, um,
and not necessarily
multi-camera, like, I would just want, like,
you know, a camera and a
screen capture type thing, you know,
just so you can see that, but, like,
I don't know who would want to watch, like, me,
like, you're fucking tired,
you know, oh shit, look
at me, I barely passed the seven-footer,
ooh, you know, it's like,
yeah, but, you know,
I'm fucking tired, because I've been
exercising all day. Okay.
So, here's the thing,
here's the thing.
I streamed Forza Horizon 4 this week.
Number one, I'm terrible at Forza Horizon 2.
Forza Horizon. Number two,
I still love it. Number three,
Travis Donovan decided to crash my game,
because that's what Travis Donovan does, and as
I was driving off a cliff, he fucking pushed
me off of it, live on stream, he drove
his car into mine and pushed me off the cliff.
Now, as much as, so, it was
honestly, it was terrible. We weren't progressing in the
game at all, it was just, but,
damn it, Loki, it was the funniest
fucking thing. Like, even I had to look
at it and go, okay, this is funny, because, like, I can't
get up the hill, and then Travis comes and pushes me off the
fucking cliff, and it's funny.
So, you know what, you don't always have to be good at the games.
So, so, honestly,
Loki, just title your stream
Old Dude Getting Back into
DDR, and, like, people aren't gonna give
a fuck. Well, it's like, was it the one dude that, I don't even
remember the guy's name, but, like, he was in the Kotaku
article just this week, or something, about,
like, how he lost 125 pounds
playing DDR. It's, like, pretty much
just what I'm doing, except he's been
doing it slightly longer, like, he bought a
DDR machine, he's losing weight,
he's also eating dieting, he's lost
weight, and it's like, god damn it,
that's just the shit I'm doing, you know, so.
Document it all.
And then, make a YouTube channel, and
now you have a sponsor, and so on and
so forth, you never know. Let's not get crazy.
Alright, um, S2100Matt also
points out, you're doing something that he doesn't
see on Twitch, you're playing doubles,
most DDR people do singles.
And most people perfect attack, and I
am not gonna be perfect attacking on my machine.
It's okay, you don't have to be the best.
Because that machine
ain't capable of perfect attacking,
I think. This is going to sound
shady, but I know he would
support me 100% in this statement,
so hopefully he's out there listening still.
If Bobby Blackwolf can stream,
you can stream.
I'll consider it.
I would not have said that in a bitchy
way if I know he didn't 100% support me.
I have been thinking about it, and I've been like
looking at my garage, and like, how would I set this
up? I need to replace some lights and stuff
because it's really dark, but
I have been considering it. I may do it.
And it would
like, get me to
play even more.
But I mean, I just shit, like, fucking
the other day I walked five
miles, and then I come home and I play
DDR for like, 30 minutes.
And the problem is, like, you know, after you've walked that long,
you know, during the day, it's like
hard to play for an hour.
So.
You can get your kids involved, too. That could be fun, too.
That could be fun.
Yeah, I guess, yeah.
But there's also weirdness about putting your kids on video like that.
They don't really know how to play.
I mean, my one son's sorted.
That's the entertaining part.
Beginner mode, but then they get bored with it
pretty fast.
Alright. Anyway, and ActEftInChat
says, I think Blackwolf acknowledges his lack
of skills when playing most games. He probably doesn't
mind as long as he's out of fun.
Exactly. I do need to get into it. I just need to
buy all new gear because I don't have
anything. Exactly. And that's why,
and honestly, he's not as bad
as games as he thinks he is. Especially when it comes to
using games and stuff. Well, the other thing I've been looking to is, I've
been seriously considering
changing that over into a set medium machine
because, um,
I don't know. Because
I'm just getting kind of
bored with this all of a sudden.
Hold on. I just realized something because
what I really think you need to do
is you need to talk to
NameRedacted, but I'm gonna show
you this text message here. You need
to talk to NameRedacted
about
this on your machine.
And I bet that's something
you could do. Oh, I already know how to do that.
Oh, okay. Yeah, that I can do.
I just have to buy a new drive for that.
Alright. Yeah, and that's, and I
have, I already have that image to burn
that, but it's just, and I
thought about doing that. Alright.
But maybe, I don't know. Anyhow,
YYR concludes, that's it for me this time.
Not every email I write has to be a novel.
Well, every discussion
has to be, apparently, though. We spent like
five minutes on the email. That's alright, no.
Just almost every email.
Enjoy your week and happy gaming.
Love, YYR. I inserted the
love in there, but, you know, he'd probably
be okay with that.
Alright, let's move on. We got some
more news to get into, and then we're gonna
get to your calls at Orange Lounge Radio, all one
word on Skype. Loki.
Alright. Um, so this is
kind of interesting that
it's a thing, but
um, I'm glad it's a thing, actually.
So, what's happening, Seattle Police
are launching a new anti-swatting
program, because, you know, swatting
is fucking terrible, and
people have been killed because of it,
and it's, it's really not
a great thing. So what they've done now
is they have this registry that you can basically go
and sign up on
it, and letting them know that you have
swatting concerns. Um,
then that way that they will get that
when there is
you know, a call into
the swat or whatever, saying, oh yeah,
this person's got a thing, that message
will pop up, and they're like, oh, okay,
well maybe this is, you know, a
streamer or something, and they'll proceed with, you
know, a little bit differently than they would if
they didn't have that sort of message.
So, you know,
what they need to do, I guess,
if you're in the Seattle area, there's a website
you can go to to actually do
that. They have an official swatting
resource site, and
you create your
profile, and then flag yourself as having
swatting concerns, and then what'll happen
is they say a 911 call taker
receives a report of a critical
incident, while ensuring
the first responders are dispatched to
that call for service as quickly as possible,
the caller, uh, call taker will
simultaneously check for whether
or not swatting concerns have been registered
at that address. If swatting concerns
have been registered, this information can be
shared with the responding officers, who will
still proceed to the call.
So that at least gives them kind of, like,
you know,
this is the situation I may be walking into.
It's, um, it's
an interesting solution. I'm not sure
it's a perfect solution, but
I mean, better than no solution. Exactly.
Like, at least we're trying
something to fix this problem,
so I'm like, alright, let's see, it's one
city, let's see how it goes, because if
it ends up doing well, maybe, and you know,
Seattle is a pretty big tech town,
home of Amazon, home of Microsoft,
Nintendo, right, they're all in Seattle
area, so, you know, if this does well there,
you know, maybe other, uh,
cities will take notice, and maybe this can be something
that helps, um, you know, because we know
somebody got fucking shot, that
shouldn't have been shot. Yeah, they're completely
wrong housekeeping, so, yeah.
Yeah, uh, Pooba, that wouldn't have, this
wouldn't have prevented that, unfortunately, because
No, but, at least
again, it's something, we're trying to move somewhere.
Uh, Pooba in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
says, damn, why don't we think of this sooner, smart
on the PD for this. Yeah.
It's about time, right? Yeah.
Alright, um,
moving on, let's talk about Amazon, actually,
because Amazon is having to put up
with a, uh, leaked, uh, YouTube,
or, excuse me, not YouTube, actually, it's very much
not YouTube, but a leaked video that went up
of their new MMO. It was
2 hours and 11 minutes
of streamed footage of their project
called New World.
Now, we know New World exists,
they've talked about this project before,
but what's interesting about it is that, uh,
it was, uh, originally put out
there as a Google Drive file.
The video then went to Pornhub
as backup in case
of removal, because you know how, like,
interesting things end up on Pornhub
sometimes, right? Like,
not just the obvious,
but you know how sometimes people will
put, like, legit video on there,
and some have even joked that,
like, the company that could take on
YouTube is Pornhub. 100%.
I wholeheartedly agree,
because they own, like, a lot of the
streaming services, like the different
porn streaming services,
so they, they own
a lot of them, and, I mean, all they have to do
is put out one that's not a porn service
and, boom, they've got the infrastructure
for it. Yeah.
Anyhow, the footage did get taken down
from Pornhub, aw, but, uh,
3800 people viewed it, and
you know, of course, now
it's spreading throughout the internet. Now it is on YouTube,
and, or, excuse me, there's, like,
an edited version on YouTube. Some
YouTube users took the footage and kind of, like,
compressed it down to, like, 11 minutes,
and have done their own, uh, thing.
So, anyway, what we learned about New World from the leak,
it's a third-person survival MMO.
There's resource gathering, crafting, action,
combat. Uh, the concept behind
it is that you are settling a new world, and you
join forces with other players, uh,
to form companies. You could be mercs,
prospectors, craft people, architects.
You claim territory and fight against
raiders. So, it's kind of like
a civilization-esque type of game,
but mixed with, like, I don't know,
DayZ or something?
I don't know, like, a survival type of thing.
Anyway, um, Rust.
Also, what should be noted,
speaking of PornHub and the fact that
interesting videos go up there, in 2015,
there was leaked Fallout 4
footage that made there.
Um, because, I guess, it, uh,
it takes a little longer for copyright
strikes to hit on PornHub.
They're a little slower to act, because they don't usually
get this type of stuff, whereas, like, YouTube, you know,
tends to put stuff down,
even if they maybe don't necessarily need to.
So, anyway,
kind of interesting. I don't know if we, I don't think
we have a date for New World. I think it's something that's
still being worked on. Um, it is
being made, um,
um, who is making this game?
I thought that Amazon had
a studio, but all I see is Amazon's
game. Anyway,
alright, well, let's
move on. Loki, uh, let's talk
about the next story. Yes, so, the Switch,
of course, you know, has been hacked, and
with that, RetroArch
has been added
to the system, so, they've got,
um, development now of it, I
guess, has been going on
for a while. Now, they have the
latest version that runs on the Switch,
and, of course, for those not familiar, RetroArch
is a multi-system
emulator, and
so, you can do all sorts of things, like, they have
the PSP, you know,
you can do, um, Super
Nintendo, Nintendo. In fact, actually, I run
RetroArch, um, my, um,
SNES Mini.
So, but,
it's interesting to see, though, that they have
all sorts of things running on there. Legend of Zelda,
Okuri, and Tine, they have the screenshot of that.
Um,
Ridge Racer, they're saying, you know, you can
even do split-screen Ridge Racer
on that, each person has a controller.
Um,
lots of cool stuff, but,
I don't know. I mean,
I'm not surprised that they have emulators
running on a system.
I mean, it's capable of it, which is, you know,
makes sense.
The real question is how long before Nintendo
shuts it down, but I guess they can't, right?
It's like a permanent, which might
also be the reason why they're putting out a new thing in 2019.
Exactly. Yeah.
Um, here's another reason that they might want to do that
as well, because not only are you going to be
able to run your emulators,
but you can also run mods in
Skyrim. That's right.
So, they have a tool called the Skyrim
NX Toolkit that allows people
to port over mods that were made
for other versions of the game
for the Switch now.
And, of course, the more popular mods
that are working with that,
are body mods!
So, the big-breasted naked chicks.
Hooray.
Going into Skyrim,
because that's...
Everybody wants sexy Skyrim.
Well, not everybody.
Oh, sexy Skyrim! Okay, yes.
Well, they also said,
the sexy mods have triple or more
downloads than everything else.
The other thing that they have is the intro skip mod
that they uploaded about 37 times.
Oh, a practical, useful thing.
Yeah. But nobody cares.
Sexy armor, and
all sorts of other skeleton mods.
And speaking of Skyrim,
and then previously Pornhub, I'm surprised
the amount of Skyrim porn that exists
out there. I did not know that was a thing.
There's a lot of, like, everything
porn out there. Like, there's, like, Zelda
Breath of the Wild porn. There's, like, you...
I mean, again, you think... No, but I can, like,
made in the Skyrim engine.
Oh, that they actually made it in... I think I've seen
Skyrim. Like, they made porn.
They do a lot, yeah.
In the engine, that doesn't really
lend itself well to the engine,
but they do have mods with sex
in them, and then they also have,
I'm sure,
I don't know, a lot of people use, actually, funny enough,
Source Filmmaker for
porn stuff.
Like, they'll use that to make stuff.
You know what? As soon as Super Smash Brothers
Ultimate comes out, within, like, two days, we're gonna have
Super Gangbang Ultimate. Like, it's just
a matter of time. Just wait for it.
And then, within three days,
Bowsette will be there, even though she's not in the game.
Yeah. Speaking of which, I saw there was a version
of Mario 64 that someone
modded Bowsette into, and you can play as her.
Granted, she looks
a little bit more, um, Bowser
than Bowsette, but, you know.
Moving on, let's talk about Castlevania.
Uh, there's a new Castlevania
portal. That's right, Konami,
not the portal game, sorry, meaning, like, a web
portal. Konami did launch a
Castlevania, like, website, basically.
Um, because if you go to this Castlevania
portal, you get to see a whole, like, timeline
of the series.
Uh, there's a big gap between 2014
and 2018, which is, you know, sad,
but that's the way it is. Uh, we do see
the rebirth of
Castlevania with the new, uh, you know,
Requiem that's coming out on PlayStation 4.
Um, but anyhow,
thanks to the new Castlevania series
on Netflix, thanks to Simon being
in Super Smash Brothers Ultimate, uh,
more people are getting, you know, re-interested
in Castlevania, I think. So,
Konami's created this website to, kind of, educate
people a little bit on Castlevania,
but there is a section called
New Product.
Hmm. Oh, boy. I, I,
I can't wait for the new Batista
lot machine. Oh, God.
Of course, of course. So, uh,
who knows, maybe there'll be a Castlevania
new game in the works,
and hopefully it's as good as,
like, maybe when they redid Bomberman,
because I know when we think of Konami
lately, we don't have a lot of positive feelings,
but, to be fair, the Bomberman
game was a'ight, so
we'll see if the Castlevania thing
is good, too, hopefully.
That's more Hudson, though, but, you know.
Yeah, well, maybe, maybe they contracted with another
studio to do it. Who knows? We'll see,
I guess. Well, Castlevania
Requiem is not going to use the
original localization for
Symphony of the Night, so be warned.
If you were looking forward to some of the
infamous voice acting, it's not
quite the same, because, uh,
the PSP, uh,
English version is the one that's going to be
in there again. So, if you were waiting
for the What is a Man? Nope.
You're gonna get the redone voice lines
from PSP's Dracula X Chronicles.
That is also the
same for Rondo of
Blood. So,
um, well, that's too bad.
But, um, not surprising either,
especially after the Silent Hill remake, so
there's clearly something going on with the voice actor
rules and all that stuff, so.
Alright, a few more stories for you guys, then we're gonna
get to the Skype line at Orange Lounge Radio,
all one word on Skype. But first, Loki.
Yes, but first we have to talk about the
final conclusion of what,
you know, fighting games are going
towards. So, you may notice
that with each fighting game that comes out,
we're pushing the boundaries of
outfits and
what scantily clad,
you know, outfits
the characters have and the boob
physics and stuff like that.
Well, it's only a matter of
time, and the time is now,
that a game should
exist called Naked Fighter 3D.
And it is a one-man project.
A one-man indie project, you may
will. It's a turn-based
fighting game where you
fight naked people
against naked people.
That's right. You can
fight women against men, against
transsexuals, whatever you
want. With a custom
character creator,
I don't know. It's a unity
thing, I guess, now, but
if you want to check it out, they've got a demo.
And they have, like, skill trees
and stuff, and there's- Boy, I can't wait.
It's just-
Is there a dong slider? There is a
dong slider for both male and female.
Okay.
I'm just gonna let the internet
have its thing. It can just, the internet
just, it can exist.
Well, they'll make, inevitably,
Naked Bowsette.
I'm curious, like, how a turn-based
fighting game works, though. Like, how's
that, you mean?
I'd be curious to see how that plays.
But this is weird.
I guess it's like a Final Fantasy type,
you know, fight, select
option, slap,
kick. But if you're
interested, they have a Patreon.
So Patreon.com slash Naked Fighter
3D. For more information,
you can go download that demo, and
go check it out.
Bobby Blackwolf asked, why didn't you download the demo,
Logie? Um, I did.
I haven't played it, though. Hey,
I got to. I gotta try it.
For research purposes only.
Gotta see what it is.
I'm curious, like, how a turn-based fighting,
like, how- I mean, I'm curious, too.
How do you make a turn-based fighting game?
We're all a little curious.
I mean,
I've already seen the videos. The videos are
goddamn ridiculous, you know, with the sliders
and everything, but, um,
yeah.
It's a thing.
Alright, uh,
anyhow, one more story for you guys before we
open up the Skype line, and this has to do with
Steam, uh, and the removal
of minigames. Speaking of, like, porny games,
Steam has recently removed
179 games,
uh, and this is probably from
the whole, like, if you're trying to troll purposely,
it's nice to see they've finally
maybe gone back a little bit on the whole, like,
well, things on Steam should offend you
and that whole bullshit thing that they were-
their line was recently.
But anyhow, uh, apparently,
about 179 games have been removed in the past
few weeks, including such titles
as Make Border Great Again,
Big Dick,
Milf, Hentai Sisters,
Putin, Boobs,
and Trump. I mean, I was looking forward to
that one myself. Uh,
Logan versus KSI,
which is, I don't know what that means,
and my life is probably better for it.
Um, Logan Paul and KSI, they
did a boxing match. No, okay, I got it.
They're two YouTubers.
Uh, 31 different games that have some
variation on the title Achievement Hunter.
So, anyhow, now we have an
idea what Steam means when they
say trolling,
basically. So, I guess
that's nice. Anyway,
ugh.
Yep, Steam is kind of a garbage
dump, uh, of games sometimes,
and, uh, yeah, I-
I think they might need to curate their
stuff a little better, but at least they're making some
attempts at it by, uh, scraping a lot of this
bottom-of-the-barrel stuff out of the store.
So, there you go.
Siya Tabiri in our chat suggests,
Professor Layaton and the Mystery
Box. No, that's-
I might actually play that.
That sounds like a porny title, like, you know how, like,
they might do, like, a porn
take on a big, like,
like, Lord of the Cockring or something, like,
it would be- Saving Ryan's Privates.
Yeah, Shaving Ryan's Privates, yeah.
Yeah, exactly. Anyway,
let's get to the
Skype line at Orange Lounge Radio,
all one word on
Skype. Um,
I'm trying to think, um, cause you know I run-
and the Skype line is open.
Uh, since we're talking about funny porn titles,
you know, I run with the Rocky Horror Crowd
and they know some weird shit, so I think the funniest
porn thing I ever saw was
Beaver and Buttface,
which was Beavis and Butthead, and I
swear to God, one of the actors goes,
huh, huh, I think I'm gonna cum or something.
It was ridiculous.
Anyway, Skype line is lit up,
let's get to it. Uh, and then
wow, those calls I was trying to take
just straight up disappeared.
So,
so, the chatters are yelling at
me, Poopa says, Rob, no, I'm
sorry, but if I had to see this
and had it seared into my brain for all eternity,
guess what, so do you.
And Dartasuya says, I'm pretty
sure Bowsette already has a porn
parody. She does. Yes, unfortunately,
that crossed my desk this week
and went
immediately into the trash
receptacle. Alright,
I'm trying to get some calls, dang it, Skype
cooperate, here we go. Hi, you're on Orange
Lounge Radio, who's this?
Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio,
who's this?
Perhaps we have a connection
on Orange Lounge Radio. Oh, sorry, I don't know
why my headset was muted, but it
was. That's alright. Hi, who's this?
This is Eric RPG. Hey, Eric RPG,
what's on your mind tonight, buddy?
Um, just wanna talk about, uh,
two open world games I've been playing and
they're polar opposites of each other.
Okay, what's the first one? The first one's
Assassin's Creed Odyssey.
Oh, yeah, I was curious about
this game, but I was- I hate
this thing. Really, because
I, it looked really interesting, but
I was really turned off
when I heard that they were selling in the
store this $10 thing for double
XP and just, and that, like,
double XP was kinda like what you needed
to really progress through the game.
There's a part of me that's like, just
tack $10 on to the
price of your game, stop being a coward,
this is what you wanna do,
just do it. Like, charge what
you're really trying to charge for the game and stop
all this other bullshit. But anyway, what are
your thoughts? The experience that you get for doing quests
is not as much as
you could get in Origins, and even
Origins kinda felt grindy,
but, like, it wasn't nearly as
bad as this game. That's unfortunate.
Because I didn't mind doing the quests then.
But, um, I don't have the kind of time
the game demands for me, and it
is sorta like, like, like a pay-to-win
game where you, where they basically
are cajoling you into paying
for the experience booster.
Which was, which
is something that didn't exist in a previous game.
But, um, that
along with the fact that the game is very
repetitious to begin with,
like, sure, there are some unique
quests that you can do that, like,
give you decent rewards, but most of
them are pretty much, go
here and kill a lot of dudes.
Or
steal something, but you end up
killing a lot of dudes anyways, because they're in your way.
Well, that's unfortunate.
I haven't heard quite as negative
of a reception of the game as a whole,
except for the microtransactions part,
but I gotta admit that- That ruins it, though.
Yeah, no, I hear ya.
In the, everything else I just
mentioned.
It wouldn't feel so grindy if you
just got double XP out the gate.
And then there's
a game like Spider-Man, which I also
played. It's like, I ran in
the other game from Redbox
because no other Redbox had Spider-Man.
It's like, I'll do this over the weekend, because
I'm taking Monday off.
And, um,
I tried playing it for
most of Saturday, and then I just returned
it on Sunday against Spider-Man today.
And how's Spider-Man?
Spider-Man is everything
that an open world game should be doing.
I mean, it still
has a lot of that, like, stupid
fetch quest stuff that's more
busywork and doesn't have any real
significant story content.
And there's a lot of collectible
junk, but, um,
it's a lot more fun game,
tight controls, and,
like, even on my
base PS4, I mean, I did experience
some issues, but I think that has more
to do with the fact that I probably need to, like,
defrag the hard drive.
Because that happens after a while,
after you've downloaded a lot.
That's very true. It's something, uh, sometimes
I even forget to do. But you can't defrag
a solid state drive.
Yeah, I'm just using
a standard drive. Yeah, I hear you.
But I probably should just
get an external.
So, you mentioned you rented
Spider-Man. Do you think you're gonna end up
purchasing it, because you like it so much?
Um,
I'm probably gonna beat it to completion,
but I might just decide to
not do that and return it tomorrow, because
I can get it later, hopefully on a
Black Friday sale.
Because I'll probably be playing it even after I
beat the main game. Yeah.
Alright, well, I'm very curious
to check out Spider-Man as well, and I'm happy to
hear you don't have the same microtransaction stuff, but
I don't get quite as into the Marvel
stuff as other people do, but,
like, or DC, really,
but I did, I mean, even, I say that,
but I did buy, like, Arkham
City or whatever, what was the one, the
open, big open world one, and it was
really good. Arkham
Knight? Yeah, that might have been it. Um, and it was,
it was good, so I hear a lot of
the, it's basically that with Spider-Man,
and I'm like, okay, I'm into it.
Yeah, um,
I didn't like Arkham Knight as much as
Arkham Asylum or Arkham City,
because, uh, they put it in the
tank sections, and I was like, this is
not a Batman game anymore, why is this here?
Maybe it was Arkham Asylum,
I thought that was the first game, but anyway,
but yeah, that's, uh, that game
was really good, and then I hear a lot about the Spider-Mans
really good too, and I see all these screenshots
that look great, like, the game just looks like it's really
pretty, so.
But other than that, I've been playing
Mega Man 11, which I think is
probably,
I'm gonna put it above 9,
just a little bit. Okay.
As, like, one of my favorite Mega Man games,
my favorite being the third,
and then 9 being
number 2, that would be,
this would be a number 3.
How many games are in this series?
Um,
11, plus the side games,
like, uh, the spin-offs
like, uh, X and
all that stuff.
But, um,
so those are my top 3, and
um, I do think
that, uh, the game has
a little bit of, uh,
it's kind of, it's kind of like
barebones, but, um,
I guess that
Capcom did essentially
what they needed to do, and
didn't try to overreach, just to
prevent themselves from screwing it up too much.
But I could
yell at Capcom for also doing the same thing that
Ubisoft did with
Assassin's Creed Odyssey that they're going to be doing
with Devil May Cry 5.
Basically the same thing.
Where they'll charge you money
to pay for extra boost,
experience boost, so you can get more red orbs.
Yeah, I just wish, if game
companies want to do this, they just
make the game $70 already,
and just give us the right proper
balancing in the game, because this is
just, it's just getting ridiculous.
And it's just, it's, I realize
games are expensive to develop, and they need to
make their money back, but,
like, you're shooting yourself in the foot
by making the money back in this manner.
Yeah.
One thing I will comment on in regards to
that, at least Capcom did well
in terms of Mega Man, is that
it is not priced as a full pop
game, so even though, yes, it is simplistic
in its offerings, it is
not charged at, you know, a full
$59.99, so I believe it was,
I don't know what the Canadian, the Canadian
or US price equivalent is,
but it was a $39.99 in Canada,
so I think it's probably $29.99 for you guys.
Probably, yeah. So, there's that
at least. Yeah, there is that.
Alright. Well, Eric RPG,
I'm going to let you go so I can get some more calls,
but thank you for your thoughts.
Yeah, and maybe you could tune
into RP Grinders'
podcast, where me and
Breakman have been doing
Mega Man Retrospective, but
we'll have a final episode soon
and we'll probably have our reviews
of Mega Man 11 up then.
Alright. And we tend to go
live around Wednesdays
at 7,
no, 8,
yeah, 8 PM Eastern.
Alright.
Check that out, RP Grinders. Alright.
See you later. Take care. Bye.
OrangeLoungeRadio, all one word
on Skype if you want to get in.
You can try to get in right now.
Meanwhile, while we're
waiting for, what?
As fast as I talk, it lights right back up.
Let's get to another call. Hi, OrangeLoungeRadio,
who's this? Hey, what's going on, everyone?
It's Rama. Hey, Rama. An email
and a call tonight. Two for one
special. Alright, what's up, buddy?
Okay, in response to that
naked fighting game, I just
have one thing to say about that. What's that?
Excuse me
while I whip this out. Oh,
please don't.
No, thank you.
Hard pass.
They have groin kicks in the game.
They have what? Groin kicks.
Well, that seems appropriate. Oh, boy.
Is that what you wanted to talk about, was
naked fighting, Rama? No, I
did that two weeks ago, but that's the story for another
time, another show, and so on and so forth,
et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
Oh, righty then.
Oh, okay.
You're the one that brought up Folsom
Street fair. Hold on, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Delvin, could you go get me the
brain bleach? It's in the other room.
Because
my brain hurts right now.
It was too much.
It was just too much. No, I'm kidding. Alright,
what's really up?
I gotta throw my two cents in about this
DDR movie. I mean,
I'm picturing
the final stage,
the final part of the movie,
since you brought up Scott Pilgrim. They're in his
warehouse. The bad boss is on the
left side. Our hero
is in the
bathroom, just getting
motivated, and it's like that whole scene from
8 Mile, and you see him come out in
the hoodie, and they just do
max 300,
1.5, skip.
That's not gonna
make a fun movie.
That's not gonna be a good
movie. It might.
I'm just, in reference to earlier
chat, me and Bob Coffey were talking about, they have
been animes with similar
plotlines,
and it worked. I mean,
fuck, if you've
played, um,
Elite Beat Agents is basically the same thing.
I just feel like the
DDR movie is gonna be You've Got
Served, too. I really just feel
like that's what it's gonna be.
I mean, well,
if it's anything like La Machina de Baja,
I will be in the front row watching it.
I guess I need to give it a chance
and see what they turn, but I just, you know, again,
DDR doesn't have a
story. Like, at least Monster
Hunter and Mega Man kind of, like, have
stories, but DDR just, like,
doesn't have a story, and that's okay.
It doesn't, like, it's
a great game. It doesn't need
a story. Well, there
was a DDR manga that
came out sometime back.
It was not an official one.
It was a fan. A friend of mine did
call the 10K Millennium.
It was, it was really cool. It was basically
a DDR tournament. It was
a cash cow.
Hahahaha.
But I tell you what,
this current idea for a DDR
film is a hell of a lot better than the
supposed one that floated around back in
2000. I never saw that one.
What was that supposed to be?
Well, according
to what was supposed to be with that
script, it was about
a boy teaching a girl
English through DDR.
Are we sure
this wasn't, like, DDR Freak fanfic?
No. Alright, are we
sure? I'm positive.
Alright, just making sure. Are we very sure? Hahahaha.
I'm very, very sure. I remember
if I could've sworn this was
discussed on a show back in
the day. No, it probably was
and there's a really good reason I've forgotten
over the years.
What's funny is that
I may not remember certain things
at work, but I sure as fuck remember shit like
this. I know. I know.
Whereas I can't remember what happened on this show
last week, but that's why you guys are all great.
Like, some of the, I swear to God, some of the,
some days I feel like RuPaul around here.
And I say that joke because, and Delvin understands
this, and some of you out there too, if you ever
listen to, like, RuPaul's podcast and stuff, like,
you learn, like, just, like, he is
such an old man.
Like, he does not, like, he, like, seriously,
Michelle's like, yeah, Carson's been playing Fortnite
and Ru's like, what's a Fortnite?
No, no, Rob, I
can tell you exactly what happened on last
week's show. You had a mimosa
and you went total B-Arthur on everyone.
I had a mimosa last week.
I don't remember that.
We do.
No, seriously, I didn't have a mimosa.
I'd remember that. Now,
last night,
well, I had a lot to drink.
That's a different story.
But we're not that, what had happened was,
no, we're not gonna talk about it on this show.
Alright.
Anyway, I'm gonna let you go, my friend.
But thank you for the call, except for that one
part that I will have seared in my brain
for all time. But,
you brought it up, I'm sorry.
Bye.
Alright. That's gonna do it for the
Skype line tonight. Thank you guys
who were able to get through. If you didn't get through, though,
please feel free to send us an email.
Participate at OrangelaungeRadio.com
is the place where you, too, can send an email
and have it read on a future episode.
But, for now, we're gonna
proceed to wrap up the show.
As I always say at the end of the show, if you
enjoyed what you heard here at Orange Lounge Radio, please tell
a friend or five about the show. Help us spread
the word, because we are the show where every gamer has
a voice, but if the voices aren't here,
then how can we air them?
So, tell a friend or two.
A nice five star review in a place like iTunes
goes an awful long way, and we
excuse me, we would really appreciate
those. Delvin,
all the way from Toronto, Canada,
thank you so much for being here tonight.
Thank you for having me. I am so
happy you finally got to actually be on
the show. You came all the way to Sacramento,
just to be on OLR.
There wasn't, like, work involved in San
Francisco or anything. You came all the way
out here just to be on OLR.
Oh, and just to see you and Alan, of course.
No, I love it, I love it.
Come back any time.
It might be a while,
but yeah. And hopefully when I come
to Toronto, you can actually do
an episode of Video Game Realness and I can be there.
Oh yeah, absolutely. Okay, work. That sounds awesome.
Anyway, give us the social media plugs one more
time. Where can people follow you if they want to see more of
Delvin and company?
So you can see the pod, or listen
to the podcast at videogamerealness.com
You can follow us on Twitter
at
vgrealness
and we're also on Twitch, twitch.tv
slash vgrealness.
Please send all our best to your
co-hosts over on Video Game Realness. I know there's
really four of you there. It's not just you, but you know.
Absolutely. I appreciate you representing
the show tonight. I'm here.
All right. Where are they
though? Where is she though?
Where is she though?
All right. Oh, and we always ask
at the end of the show, of course, if you have any final thoughts.
So do you have any final thoughts you'd like to leave
our listeners with tonight?
Eh?
Perfect.
Thank you. Oh, I love
that song. It's my favorite DDR song. Okay, anyway.
Uh, Loki, how about you?
Your final thought tonight?
My final thought is we didn't do
last minute stories, but I
had one thing real quick I want to talk about.
Okay, fair enough. Toys R Us.
Should we talk about Toys
R Us? I mean, we can,
but I can't believe that they're
now thinking about coming back?
After they've fired all those people, sure.
Well, technically, I think it's a company that's
selling the brand as Toys R Us.
So it's not really Toys R
Us. It's somebody who cut up
Toys R Us and is now wearing them as a dress.
That's a Toys
R Us skin suit.
That is what is happening, yes.
Okay. All right.
My final thought is
I'm still trying to work on
game development stuff.
This hasn't helped that I've been tired
or had a headache for two days, you know.
But I've been
working. The thing, the problem I have is
that I keep starting stuff and then
running the roadblocks of what I can and
cannot do by myself with my
current knowledge, and so that's kind of
why I keep jumping between projects, because
it's just like, I get into this thing where I
have to, like, research a bunch of stuff, and it's like,
I want to make progress now, and I'm
impatient with that.
All right. Figure it out.
My final thought is I need my
Pokmon storage increased to 2,000.
I need it. I need it. No,
I don't have a problem keeping three of every
type of Pokmon. You have a problem.
I was just going to say, I was like, maybe you should keep
three of every goddamn Pokmon.
I don't have a problem. You have a problem.
You have a problem. Good night, everybody.
You've been listening to
Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is a production
of OLR Studios.
To join us for a live show,
tune into VoGnetwork.com
Sunday nights at
6 p.m. Pacific, 9 p.m.
Eastern. The views and
opinions expressed in this program
do not necessarily reflect those of the
staff of Orange Lounge Radio
or VoGnetwork, but you know
they were all still true.
See you next week.
Thanks for watching!