[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_09]: To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: And welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are live on this 4th of July weekend, except it's actually the 6th of July now, in 2008.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did everybody have a good 4th of July weekend?
[SPEAKER_13]: We have a lot of people in the studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you haven't listened to Part 8 yet, we have tons of guests.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you guys all have a good 4th of July?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we had a couple encounters, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: A couple encounters?
[SPEAKER_13]: What's that mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: Random encounters.
[SPEAKER_13]: Random encounters?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like you are suddenly attacked by a gray slime?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and just substitute unexpected fireworks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh yes, good times.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, 4th of July, you're from New York City, Ranma, so the 4th of July in a cow town like this one is a little different from what you're used to in Brooklyn, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Even out in Brooklyn, it's very suburbanite.
[SPEAKER_14]: Out in New York City, we look forward to the Nathan's Hot Dog Eating Contest.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the big thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do people go shoot their guns off in the middle of the street for 4th of July?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, that's more up in the South Bronx where I used to live.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're confusing that with Texas.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, well, we hope everybody had a safe Fourth of July.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unless you're not an American citizen, then I hope you had a good Friday.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like to say in a very cryptic fashion that thank God the end of my headache is over, you know, and I can continue on with the work that I have been working on for a few weeks now.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I'm not mistaken, Loki will be unveiling something big on next week's show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cross your fingers, cross your toes.
[SPEAKER_13]: The funny thing about the 4th of July, though, really quickly, because I went to the extravaganza at DarkSakura's house that she had, stupid me thought, I want to bring something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to contribute to DarkSakura's thing this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to be a leecher.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I brought fireworks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I went out and bought $40 worth of fireworks and brought it to the party.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: And only to be upstaged by all the more awesome illegal fireworks that were present.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, our neighbor put in money for the legal stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: For the fuck show?
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_13]: In the garage.
[SPEAKER_12]: That wouldn't be right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do it now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our void says now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think that's going to happen, sir.
All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a 6th of July party.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, kick it off.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, no fireworks right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we talked a little bit earlier, actually Rob did during his release dates for Japan, that Persona 4 was going to be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Persona 4 is also making its way to North America as well, just not until December 9th.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that should be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was teased on, I think, a new trailer for Persona 4.
[SPEAKER_12]: So December 9th is when you can get your Persona 4 on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, and it says also that each game will be bundled with the soundtrack CD as well with select music from the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there are many RPG fans going squee!
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it come with a free spirit gun?
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's cool, though, that they're still cranking them out for the PlayStation 2, quality games for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not just a budget system.
[SPEAKER_13]: They've still got good stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's cheaper to develop for, and if they want to jump to the PS3, they'll still sell probably...
[SPEAKER_12]: What they would sell on the PS3 with the PS2?
[SPEAKER_13]: Gs68 calls them fuckworks.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: and cooler looking, in their words, suave version of the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to be coming out in India first and then Europe.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to be coming out on October 28th in India.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what that means?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Ben Heck will be able to make an even cooler PS2 portable system.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Economic Times, who reported this initially, also says there will be no more external AC adapter.
[SPEAKER_13]: The price will still be the same, about $162 American, because this is in other countries.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you mean, no more AC adapter that's external?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm assuming that means the plug is built right into it, so you don't have to plug in an external adapter now.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's built right into the system, I would imagine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Power Supplies
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, in other news, there is a list that was released by Hideo Kojima, who said what his top five favorite games are.
[SPEAKER_06]: And he was actually speaking to a newspaper, Yomiuri Shinbun, and he listed Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: series, Outer World, and Xevious as being some of the most memorable and influential games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Portopia, Renzoku Satsu Jinjiken, Metal Gear Solid Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alba World, Xevious
[SPEAKER_06]: Hideo Kojima Talks, You Listen
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: That I've bumped into him enough times that I think I should.
[SPEAKER_13]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, there's some interesting stuff coming out now.
[SPEAKER_12]: PlayStation.com, I guess, was hacked according to a security firm's reports.
[SPEAKER_12]: The IT security firm Sophos reported that someone has been messing around with the official PlayStation site, the US one.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I guess some of the messing around fits in with fake ads on the SingStar and God of War pages.
[SPEAKER_12]: And trying to, I guess, I don't know, put viruses or...
[SPEAKER_13]: Spyware or something Were they trying to install spyware on people's computer?
[SPEAKER_13]: Were they trying to say, haha, we pwned Sony, or what?
[SPEAKER_12]: It says basically that the bogus pop-ups prompted people that saw them to purchase I guess what turned out to be bogus antivirus software Dope Oh my god, they put Gator on PlayStation.com Wow Apparently though, Sony's already fixed the problem, but you know
[SPEAKER_12]: That still sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would say, if there was ever a list, and maybe we'll have to do this as a list list someday, even though it isn't directly video game related, but if there was ever a list of the most evil things to ever hit the internet, like the worst things to ever happen to the internet, Gator would be in the top three.
[SPEAKER_02]: Banzai Buddy would be also in the top three.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't get me started on Banzai Buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: YouTube.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, this is sad news in the Sony department.
[SPEAKER_13]: You cannot have Kratos in Soul Calibur 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: That news was announced one up, actually revealed in their most recent podcast because they've been playing the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like you bastards.
[SPEAKER_13]: They actually have the game there in studio because certain media people are more special than everybody else.
[SPEAKER_13]: And so they've got it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they've been playing the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3 versions and no Kratos to be found anywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unless it was some type of last-minute addition, but let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you think a big character like Kratos was going to be in a big game like this, do you think it's something that would be a last-minute addition?
[SPEAKER_13]: Download content?
[SPEAKER_13]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_13]: That could be, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I still say slim to none are your chances.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cratos in Soul Calibur 4
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, I know you and Hubby were debating which version of Soul Calibur 4 you were going to get.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you finally come to a consensus?
360.
[SPEAKER_13]: And why is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Xbox Live is better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you think if Kratos had been in the Sony one, do you think that might have tilted you in the other direction?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not at all?
[SPEAKER_13]: Not a Kratos fan?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really, honestly, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did anybody check out Soul Calibur on Xbox Live this week?
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't hear anyone mention it during their gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: I only checked out the demo.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't feel good enough reviewing it based on the demo alone, but it just seemed like the Dreamcast version.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but not that that's bad, because the Dreamcast one was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rip it open!
[SPEAKER_13]: What do we got?
[SPEAKER_06]: We've actually gotten a crap ton, so I'm very sorry for some of the emails that I am not answering.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to get to ones that I haven't really read before, so... Yeah, let's hear from people.
[SPEAKER_13]: No offense to the people who email us all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's hear from people we don't often hear from.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dear OLR team, my name is Zyman and I live in Sweden.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a first-time writer to the show and I've listened for about three years.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to tell you, you are the best and ask a question.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, I live in a time zone where I can't listen live, so I have to make do with the podcast, which, by the way, is the best podcast on the web.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, why is Part 2 released so late in the week nowadays?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get Part 2 until Friday night, and most of the other stuff you talk about by then feels kind of outdated.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I don't enjoy what you talk about, but is there a reason why it can't be released on Tuesday or Wednesday instead?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, it's been kind of my fault recently, because I've just been so busy on Tuesday and Wednesday nights, specifically, because it's kind of in my... the ball's in my court to get that thing released, and with my birthday on the 4th of July, especially these past two weeks, it has just been a madhouse, so I apologize, that's not usually the plan.
[SPEAKER_13]: The reason why we don't do it in, uh, well, first off...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: 24 to 48 hours out from part A, though, and that's just because that way a lot of RSS audio grabbers will skip a file if you haven't already grabbed it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, let's say there's two new shows on the stream, it will only grab the most recent one, and so people miss out on half the show if they're not updating every day.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we try to space it out about 24 to 48 hours to make sure people are getting each and every part.
[SPEAKER_13]: and just so that you have something spread out throughout the week because most game shows release on Sunday, Monday but much fewer of them release on Wednesday, Thursday so that was kind of the whole point about that so that's why we did it that way so sorry it isn't a popular decision but you never know especially with our 300th episode coming up and talk of already changing some other things about the show you never know, it might be one big show in the future we'll see
[SPEAKER_13]: We reserve the right to change things as we want.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm also not reading part of this email though because it is directed towards somebody else.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is thank you for an excellent show and take care.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one's from Resimo who I don't think I've read an email from.
[SPEAKER_13]: The name sounds familiar but it's been a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I beat Metal Gear Solid 4 a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone used the word epic to describe the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's because there's no other word to describe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's one of the best games I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sick of people bitching about games' cutscenes and not talking about how great the actual game is.
[SPEAKER_06]: With so much diversity in the actual gameplay, I find this alarming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to know if any of you actually played it or just watched a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm curious to know what you think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lastly, a couple of questions for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you watch any of the TV channels preceding the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're bizarre.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, and did you see the one where David Hayter experiences the interview from hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you did, fangasm much?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't watch television.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think, is it something like you leave the disc in and you see this random Easter egg stuff?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no, no, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I can.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, I thought that the game was very diverse in the things that allowed it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's also, I guess this is up on YouTube, but no, never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: PS, I sent you guys a video months ago with my goddaughter playing my great 1000 mile rally arcade machine since then I've purchased a Street Fighter 2 machine and I'm now eyeing a pinball table I played a lot of pinball in my youth but don't remember many of the machines one of my customers owns a pinball boutique and suggested either a Black Knight or Addams Family machine as the best ever
[SPEAKER_06]: The Black Knight isn't too banged up, but it needs a bit of work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Either one will cost me $2,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've heard you rave about Black Knight pinball, but can't remember you talking about Addams Family one.
[SPEAKER_06]: What says you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for getting me through this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, there's a Black Knight and a Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if it's Black Knight 2000, it's worthy.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I warn you, the game's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's hard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Addams Family is really, really, really fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love Adam's Family.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to find out the user group that my husband goes on and try to get you in touch with his group because Dan started off on a really banged up machine and worked his way up.
[SPEAKER_06]: $2,000 for an Addams Family?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: at least as far as I've heard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just, you know, check.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to have to go ahead and start, you know, investing in rubbers and plastics and, you know, get carnauba wax for the boards.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do I use that for?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, pinball.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the actual boards themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make sure you've got Goo Gone handy and acid-free stuff because, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry if I didn't know you were talking about pinball.
[SPEAKER_13]: This would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_13]: I live in the gutter.
[SPEAKER_06]: just email me later anyway
[SPEAKER_06]: Next email, and this actually is somebody different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, Dan Shadow here.
[SPEAKER_06]: While I was growing up, I had a lot of adventure and puzzle games to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of my favorites were the Monkey Island series, Loom, thank you, Loom is great, King's Quest, Before 3D, Toonstruck, The 7th Guest in the 11th Hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the most part, those games were just point and clickers, but they all had great dialogue and good puzzles that fit into the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, Insult Swordfighting was the best.
[SPEAKER_06]: My question is a two-parter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Aside from games like Professor Layton and Hotel Dusk, will we ever see a return of the good plain fun adventure game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Part of the greatness of the 7th Guest in the 11th Hour was that they were of a much darker tone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you ever play Phantasmagoria?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I did play Phantasmagoria.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: My second question is if we do ever see more adventure games, are they fated to be just childish games that will work for all ages?
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I would love to see another Phantasmagoria.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't that be awesome?
[SPEAKER_13]: Seven CDs that game was.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was epic.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd love to see another Monkey Island.
[SPEAKER_13]: Only because the emailer isn't saying it, I would hope to, gosh, you already know about it, but Sam and Max, seriously, if you're not playing it, this game was made for someone like you who loves these old 90s puzzlers.
[SPEAKER_13]: And just the cool thing, and I hate sounding like a salesman for this service, but I do like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I honestly do.
[SPEAKER_13]: GameTap has all these old school PC games, a lot of the ones you're talking about on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which is cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: You fight like a dairy farmer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Justin sent me an email that reminded me that the song I was trying to think of was Lab from 2DX8Style that had the hearty Hadouken.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play some while I'm looking.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll have to dig it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: 8Style, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to take me a minute.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got an email from Sauce.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says, Hi, Sois, which is my online nickname of the Saucers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sky, Otherguy, and DJ Ranma guest.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Drew, if he's there, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seeing how I know DarkSakura thoroughly enjoyed reading my lengthy multi-paragraph review of the Iron Man video game released by Sony, I thought it only be fair to review another game, Lego Indiana Jones.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as to be kind to her vocal cords rather than writing the review up here in this email, I've written it up in my own blog and provided a link to paste in the chat room, which I will in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: The journal, though, is marronmarvel.livejournal.com It's M-A-R-R-O-N-Marvel
[SPEAKER_13]: And she will soon be writing for Orange Lounge Radio when we get our new website done, which is the next big task here at Camp OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is part of a project I'm working on for the OLR website.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dubiously and aptly named project.
[SPEAKER_06]: Update the website so more content can be added.
[SPEAKER_13]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: But for now, the review sits on my own blog until Skye and I can get together and work something out.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura has another dozen or so emails to read.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the great work, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sincerely, your friendly neighborhood sauce.
[SPEAKER_13]: Friendly Neighborhood Sauce.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love that she's dedicated.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need someone like that to keep poking me going website, website, website.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm really glad there's enthusiastic people.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I don't like sharp things.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, me no likey.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if you keep poking me, then I'm not going to give you...
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey guys and gals, I've been listening to this show for almost four years.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is also the first podcast I have ever listened to, but I have never been able to listen live because of school, family, etc.
[SPEAKER_13]: Abandon them all!
[SPEAKER_13]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love this show and keep up the good work from Taco4Brain, which is my gamer tag, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Imagine Babies would have been a lot better with Harpoons, Fire, and Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is going to sound so horrible, but I don't know any other way to put it.
[SPEAKER_13]: The sad thing is my list, I don't have a problem giving my gamer tag out because it's on the forums.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's green sky, but it's S-K-I-E, all one word.
[SPEAKER_13]: But here's the problem is that my friends list is completely full.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Microsoft does not address the issue about letting us expand our friends list yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I try to when new OLR listeners want to be added.
[SPEAKER_13]: I go in my list and I look for people who haven't signed on in like a week and I'll delete them.
[SPEAKER_13]: but the problem is I'm trying to balance I don't want to delete anybody I know offline but I also don't want to make any OLR listeners sad so I'm having to play this really delicate balancing game with the friend list so you can send me a friend request I guess I could delete someone who hasn't signed on in a week but it's tough please don't be hurt if I defriend you or refuse your friend request I'm just full and I'm not even on Xbox that often I'm still waiting on my request
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you... Didn't I accept it?
[SPEAKER_13]: It bounced back saying it was full.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you gotta like call me or text me and say I'm gonna try to add you and then I'll dump somebody who hasn't signed on in a week and then add you.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about after the show maybe?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll do it after the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: On the same subject, my WeConnect24 is now working.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you wanna add me... And it's all on the forum because you don't know your friend code I would imagine.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: PC Games
[SPEAKER_13]: See, FearTheClaw in chat says, Aw, how sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sky has too many friends.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cry face.
[SPEAKER_13]: I feel like I sound like a stuck-up ass when I say that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You are a whore, darling.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just, you know, I... Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Emails, please.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to quickly go through some of these and paraphrase them.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68, who introduces himself in English, Spanish, and Japanese.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to know what happened to the guy who said that geeks and otaku were the only ones who wanted more storage space and said that it's sad that a representative of Nintendo would have to hold to a level of professionalism and didn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, you haven't heard from him lately, so that's hopefully a good sign.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thumbs up, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: And wants us to come to Final Mate 2009, which will be a likely.
[SPEAKER_13]: Most likely, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Outlook good on the Magic 8-Ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: And says, this email was brought to you by Sizzler, home of the Endless Salads.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, California Extremes in two weeks, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going!
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we want to trek out there?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going!
[SPEAKER_13]: You have room in your car for one more?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're only going for the one day, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: You're not going to stay overnight or anything?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't think we're going to stay overnight, but we might go back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I might just go for one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we're going to do the Saturday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I think I'd only be able to stay in the one day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I think we'll both go on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll come with if you don't mind extra room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright!
[SPEAKER_13]: OLR car trip!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, short email from Saltech.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, OLR, I was learning if anyone, including chat, knows anything about whether Diablo 3 will be pay-to-play like World of Warcraft or buy the game like Diablo 1 and Diablo 2 anyway, love the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad to hear you like the email address.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's actually supposed to be 666% pure evil, but you can't use the percent character in email addresses.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it ended up with being what it is now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, periods help.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far as I know, and this comes as a Blizzard fan, it's going to be pay once and play.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just standard Battle.net model.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Diablo 2 is the same way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, if Blizzard were to change it now, they'd just be getting greedy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't think that's going to be the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: So I made my parents take me there with a friend and we were all like, where is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: But just when we were about to give up, my mom was all like, hey, is that it?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm like, yes, it is!
[SPEAKER_06]: So we take a look inside and my parents are all confused because they aren't otaku and it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was called Planet Zero and I was so happy I almost cried because they had imported games such as Poppin' Music!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only thing that really, really sucked was the arcade was small, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, thank you for taking the time to read this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry it's long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lol.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your friend, Isabel.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's signed as Ro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last email.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a long one.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Long email is long.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this one is special because of their ISP, which I think is funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, we can't say?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, it's... I'm pretty sure that the name is pronounced Nige just as a nickname.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I always think about this one song that has the name of this supermarket chain in the title.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Read the email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fine!
[SPEAKER_06]: Dear OLR...
[SPEAKER_06]: I finally had my first sustained encounter with a PSP last week after years of getting my gaming fix on a Nintendo system, and I was very surprised at how much I liked it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The public perception of Sony's computer entertainment strategy at the moment generally seems to be one of a company suffering a midterm malaise, much like Nintendo went through after the year of the 16-bit era until the Wii slash DS combo.
[SPEAKER_06]: as you always rightly say it's all about the games and although there were a handful of interesting titles in the PSP it never really grabbed my attention until Crisis Core arrived in Europe as my girlfriend has a PSP I decided to buy the game and give it a go the game itself is very good I have to disagree with Loki's comments a couple episodes back I find it very entertaining
[SPEAKER_06]: Part of the reason for this, personally, I feel, is because I've been out of the Final Fantasy universe for so long.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Final Fantasy Tactics on GBA, the Credit Crystal Chronicles spin-offs, and the boring Revenant Wings game on the DS, along with some of the mundane remakes, but not any of the console games since Final Fantasy IX.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really like the art style and the more fluid battle mechanics that appears to have replaced the original turn-based system.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also think that the mission structure fits the portability of the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can pick up the game, play a mission for five minutes whilst in a shop or sitting on the toilet and then can put it down again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I told you I keep a Neo Geo Pocket Color in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I'm ready to spend time with the story, then I can get bogged down in wasting an hour or two, but when I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that's not my main point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Accessing the PSP has been like opening a shiny door in my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: What a wonderful product.
[SPEAKER_06]: With all that functionality, it really is a media center in your pocket.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it could be argued that Sony's insistence on turning their game machines into home computers may have been something of a flaw in their strategy, but then this is also the first week that I have been listening to the OLR podcast out in the sunshine on a PSP before catching up on other RSS feeds that I regularly check out on my desktop PC, which I couldn't do on my DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: And thank you for making us your first priority this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are pros and cons to any product in a competitive marketplace.
[SPEAKER_06]: The opportunity cost of the next best alternative will always be subjective.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, with Nintendo's seemingly lackluster provision of mature, and by that design I don't necessarily mean M-rated, just intelligent grown-up design versus the likes of Imagine Babies titles, and the lack of desire to provide choice, goodbye freeloader and region-free gaming, the historic...
[SPEAKER_06]: the historic poor strategic vision in PAL territories and of course the fact that we are seen to be geeks and otaku I'm starting to feel marginalized by Nintendo who I once championed so much it seems ironic that in the moment of their greatest commercial success I find myself completely disinterested by what they have to offer it may have something to do with my age I'm not going to say
[SPEAKER_06]: and my gaming habits but I am or rather have been a loyal customer and I do agree with you and I'm not much older than you.
[SPEAKER_06]: My girlfriend, the PSP owner, who fits the historic profile of a traditional European gamer, having been raised on PC and home computer gaming scene in the late 80s and early 90s, rather than foreign consoles, asked Kropotkin for more info, summed it up neatly for me recently.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were once their target market, but not anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it really is that simple.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the Nintendo marketing executive said with their vision really is, and I'm fine with that, they're opening up gaming to a broader audience and making it socially acceptable lifestyle activity.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just have to look at all those unrealistically happy generations of families in their TV commercials to get a sense of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who would have thought Granny would ever get so enthused by virtual puppies and Sudoku puzzles whilst bonding with their grandchildren on an expensive nuclear family vacation to an unspecified exotic location?
[SPEAKER_06]: So why am I bothering to say anything at all?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want Nintendo to know that thanks largely to the production of the must-want titles by their competitors and tepid treatment of their customer base, a personal tipping point has finally been reached.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm in the market for a PSP Slim and a PS3 now.
[SPEAKER_06]: My Wii is gathering dust, my DS gets the occasional play, and I think I'm not alone.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very interesting quote in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Something about, you were the target audience, but not anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: It kind of hurts to hear, but I think your girlfriend's on to something with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or no, was that his quote, or the girlfriend?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: But whoever said that is definitely on to something.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think something the hardcore gaming fans forget once in a while, like, OMG, Nintendo, how could you screw us over like this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it was so much better when it was 8-bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it's not 8-bit anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we're not 13 anymore, you know?
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of something to think about.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the last one I'm reading.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sorry for everybody else that I skipped over.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I had a shit ton of emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there's always next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com Yeah, I'm leaving the ones I haven't read as unread.
[SPEAKER_13]: And maybe we'll post some on the forums and respond to them there.
[SPEAKER_13]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, mailbag at orange.com if you'd like to contribute to DarkSakura's massive emails.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, back to some gaming news, eh, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: XBOX 360 Pro Model
[SPEAKER_12]: A rumor, wink wink nudge nudge, and who knows if it's true, but yeah, I guess we'll just have to wait until E3 to see if it's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: But boy, wouldn't E3 be a really good time to announce something like this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that would be a very good time to announce something like this.
[SPEAKER_13]: E3, Quandary
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, that's really sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: But we're sure that that wouldn't happen, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: That would never happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: But you know, hey, these Microsoft rumors, they're never true.
[SPEAKER_12]: HALO HALO
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: It could be Peter Jackson's game, but the interesting thing about it, it will not have the Master Chief in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So could the Halo franchise survive without Master Chief?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I forgot to mention, too, as part of that story, the 20 gig model is rumored to be phased out with this price drop.
[SPEAKER_12]: You may remember last year, I believe, when the 80 gig came out, they dropped the price of the 60 gig also for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Same type of thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we would have no idea if that is actually happening.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, we would have absolutely no idea that something like that would actually be happening.
[SPEAKER_13]: A question for our guests in the studio since we haven't heard from you in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Could Halo work without Master Chief?
[SPEAKER_12]: Ask someone who fucking cares.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they have Halo Wars and I'm pretty sure Master Chief's not in that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_12]: Tell a game about Cortana.
[SPEAKER_13]: A game centered around Cortana?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Getting warmer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma, any thoughts?
[SPEAKER_14]: I could give two shits about Halo, really.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what would be awesome?
[SPEAKER_12]: Red vs. Blue, the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: That'll work.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rabble, rabble.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would play Sister.
[SPEAKER_13]: They could do a Halo game without Master Chief, but that's like a Halloween movie without Jamie Lee Curtis.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just destined to not be as good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_14]: That broke me.
[SPEAKER_13]: That broke you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Syntax error.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it would be with the Arbiter.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_13]: E3, we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't believe that Halo would be a franchise Microsoft would just like, go away into the sunset.
[SPEAKER_13]: It'll be back one way or another.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this makes me plenty happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: A new zombie smacking minigame game is coming out called The House of the Dead EX.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's zombie love, zombie rock, zombie bowling, zombie whacking, zombie shooting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Zombie whacking?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep, some zombie love.
[SPEAKER_06]: but it's actually I do believe it has a lot to use the guns or this sort of pedal that's on it like in Time Crisis but it's an arcade machine and it's also a really cutesy kind of bizarro cel-shaded anime style it's the cel-shaded sort of like how House of the Dead 3 was but it's just cute
[SPEAKER_06]: House of the Dead 3 House of the Dead EX
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think zombies and cute should ever be in the same sentence.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless you have a not in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then will Uwe Boll be basing a new movie based on that too?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm thinking no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Uwe Boll will be a zombie in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't go there.
[SPEAKER_14]: For the love of God, don't go there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think he should be a boss.
[SPEAKER_13]: Zombies got talent, says Vandalist in chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now they're just doing all these zombie things in chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: is that each episode will be free or be a free download and remain a free download for a 24 hour period.
[SPEAKER_12]: After that, each episode will go into GameTap's archives and be available to download individual for a yet to be determined price.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where the fuck is Alice, by the way?
[SPEAKER_02]: We need an American League game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need Alice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that not on GameTap yet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have not seen Alice on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's probably coming.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can bet that if this game... They're probably waiting until like a month before or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: So these will all... I guess the first one is going to debut on July 31st and it's going to be called A Boy Learns What Fear Is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds a little scary.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, changing gears here and moving on to something completely different.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know when this music plays, the news is not going to be good, folks.
[SPEAKER_13]: You heard that when the Sony PlayStation 3 launched, you heard all sorts of crazy shit happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: People were getting shot up in line.
[SPEAKER_13]: People were getting the Sony PlayStation 3 stolen from them right out of their hands.
[SPEAKER_13]: But now, kids, we have reached the lowest of the low.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it didn't even happen in the US.
[SPEAKER_13]: It happened in Australia.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought everyone got along in Australia, but no, this is how horrible it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Zach Tuili, I apologize if I mispronounce that, but Zach Tuili, unfortunately, he has a form of muscular dystrophy, and he is confined in a wheelchair for most of his life.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was able to get something from the Make-A-Wish Foundation.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Zack opted to get a PlayStation 3 from the Make-A-Wish Foundation, which, by the way, is a great charity.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've helped raise money for them before.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were a wonderful, wonderful charity.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: The charity got him the PlayStation 3, got him the games, and this week thieves broke into his home and stole everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jewelry, appliances, PlayStation 3, and all the games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuckers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe his wish was to be mugged.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think this is one of those things where I would say this country's going to hell, but unfortunately it didn't happen here.
[SPEAKER_13]: This world's going to hell.
[SPEAKER_13]: Congratulations, everybody.
[SPEAKER_14]: But then again, it's Australia.
[SPEAKER_14]: We didn't see that coming.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a lot of nice people living in the land of upside-downness.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, you don't want to go there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you don't go there, girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, obviously, that's about 99 different ways of fucked up, and we will count them out for you right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or at least give you our FUs of the week.
Oh, this is bad.
Here is justice.
Here is punishment.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here is... This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to the 580s.
[SPEAKER_06]: and, um, FU to the asshole.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, FU to getting pulled over.
[SPEAKER_13]: Snapped.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got pulled over at the Sacramento airport.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, I was dead tired, exhausted after having driven most of the day and wandering all over the city, well, all over Chippewa County, and Berkeley, and all this.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we stopped at AM, PM there, and I had to circle back around so I could actually get back there to get some coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I ended up pulling out and going to the Garden Highway and some to the exit on the 5, going, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm trying to find my way out and I got pulled over and my tags need renewing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they wanted to search the trunk and do all this stuff and it turned out it turned out that they were looking for someone.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were asking all of our IDs and checking everything but they left me off with a warning.
[SPEAKER_13]: Were they looking for someone that looks like you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Of all things?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was my evil twin Skippy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like how you have an evil twin named Skippy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Skippy Sakura, Dark Skippy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Light Sakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was Light Sakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um, but, uh... Well, you know one of the nicknames for evil Sakura is Hiyakeshita Sakura, which is December.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does Skippy have a mustache like evil Spock?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: No!
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything else, Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't give me a ticket.
[SPEAKER_06]: I got to go.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we heard a sort of yelling fight at the Chevron station, which was stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said, man, people, if you're going to argue with somebody and talk shit, no one else cares to hear your fucking nonsense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Go keep it to yourselves, or talk somewhere like civil human beings.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said, that bitch!
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, be civil.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be mature.
[SPEAKER_13]: GameGuru corrected me.
[SPEAKER_13]: EvilSpock had a beard, not a mustache.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, NerdTrekky.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm so rude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, one last thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: A semi-F you to the ending of Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_06]: The season ending of Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it was sort of a cop-out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was, as a fangirl, I did have my fangasm, and I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to look as good as Liz Sladen when I am 60 years old.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because that woman is gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um, but it was, it was, it was a bit of happy at the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a little copy out-y.
[SPEAKER_06]: A little copy out-y.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm wondering, there's two people who are, no, I don't want to spoil it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to spoil it, I'm not gonna just, ahhh!
[SPEAKER_06]: Next!
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would have said FD to programming, but I don't have reason to do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I'm going to say FD to my car being in the shop still.
[SPEAKER_12]: Unfortunately, the thermostat housing is busted and leaking coolant, so I took it in on the 4th of July, and unfortunately, the dealership was closed, and they were unable to fix it, so now I have to wait for my car to...
[SPEAKER_12]: until Monday when the dealership is open because that's the only place that has the park.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even though I could have driven my car, you know, leaking coolant as I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Might not have been fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was alright, but, you know, I just want to get it fixed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's keep the FUs moving.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to make mine quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: FU to drama.
[SPEAKER_13]: FU to unnecessary drama.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Makes me pain in places I didn't know I had.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rama!
[SPEAKER_13]: Which rhymes with drama.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma Drama.
[SPEAKER_13]: That should be a podcast you should do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma does not rhyme with drama.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, I'm just, in my real ghetto, don't know how to speak thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Drama Llama Rama.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to let that one slide.
[SPEAKER_13]: You should have a podcast where you just talk about drama in the cosplay world.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet it's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I do slip some in there from time to time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, FU's of the Week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I need to stop.
[SPEAKER_13]: FU's of the Week.
[SPEAKER_14]: First, F you to people who have made my vacation a living hell that started it off.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't need to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Leave me alone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Second, F you to Continental Airlines.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, my friend will help me out, but still, I don't want to be stuck in Texas for nine hours, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: George Bush, and your luggage went to New Orleans, which sounds so much like Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_06]: But your luggage did come back from its early Mardi Gras, like Sauce said.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but the thing is, when I opened up the bag, there was no tequila, no alcohol, no nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's an evil bag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or boobs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not even beads.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_12]: All there was was, you know, parts of Hurricane Katrina and...
[SPEAKER_13]: Boo, too soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, dude, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck this heat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, fuck the heat.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am dying too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: You gotta give a nice, loud, hearty, fuck the heat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, yeah, fuck this heat.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: A little better.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll second the fuck you to the heat.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll second the fuck you to drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you to Ubisoft for not making sure that a game works before they push it out the door.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of, of course, Ghost Recon Assault Warfighter 2, which decides to crash as soon as I load a level.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're not being able to drive yet, not being able to learn to drive yet, because of this heat...
[SPEAKER_02]: Here is driving me crazy
[SPEAKER_13]: Death, death, blood, shit, and puke.
[SPEAKER_13]: And cornflakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, in actual news, I really have to give it to the male population of Canada because there is a study that has come out, a survey actually that Microsoft put out wondering how many, well out of a thousand gamers in Canada, how many of them play naked?
[SPEAKER_13]: And this is something we really needed to know.
[SPEAKER_13]: This was scientifically sensitive.
[SPEAKER_13]: We need to know this information.
[SPEAKER_06]: 17% of men game naked.
[SPEAKER_06]: And 9% of women game naked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_13]: Like all the time, or just have once in a while?
[SPEAKER_13]: Or like have before?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, but get plastic wrap for your controller, please.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_13]: They say this about Canadian gamers, but I'm wondering if it's true about American gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm wondering something here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if the people who took the survey counted, say, taking a handheld into the bathroom as gaming naked.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a valid question.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a valid question.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, outside of the handheld in the bathroom, who has ever gamed naked?
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, have you ever gamed naked?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you remember what game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, first of all, I was running a fever of 103.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It probably wasn't DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was actually Super Mario 3, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was before that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it was Top Gun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, have you ever gamed naked?
[SPEAKER_12]: I always game naked under my clothes.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, really?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so we're 50% so far.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma, ever game naked?
[SPEAKER_14]: Normally my lawyer would tell me not to answer, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it was Dance Dance Revolution.
Magic image.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_14]: When I was done, there was a bunch of fangirls outside wanting my autograph with the other pen.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't do it in a public setting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to try it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was in my own house.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't know the window.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wasn't... Close the shades!
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why didn't I defend what they want?
[SPEAKER_13]: Drew?
[SPEAKER_13]: To make them want it more.
[SPEAKER_13]: Drew Bowles.
[SPEAKER_13]: Drew, have you ever gamed nude?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say with all confidence, I have not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't plan to.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never... See, I've even... I don't plan to.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've lied naked in the bed playing PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you ever read a book in the bathroom?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever read a book?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they trying to do Naked Fun Games?
[SPEAKER_13]: GameGuru asked, is Jess wearing underwear, Kat?
[SPEAKER_12]: I vote for more Naked Fun Games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm all for Naked Twister.
[SPEAKER_12]: Naked is naked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Naked is just naked.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just naked.
[SPEAKER_13]: People are too bent up.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually one of the things we talked about in my massage school about working on people's gluteal muscles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't be afraid.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a butt.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've got one too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if they fart, they fart.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've had people fart on the table, Rob, and one of those people is in this room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not naming names.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go to while the comedy is still going here on Orange Lounge Radio, let's go to one of our favorite segments here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's right, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's time for the OLR Match Game!
[SPEAKER_13]: and in order to play the match game tonight we need contestants so folks in chat if you want to play match game tonight say me once and only once if you say it more than once you're disqualified you just say me period or no period nothing else besides that if you would like to play uh
[SPEAKER_13]: Match Game in our chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just say me.
[SPEAKER_13]: While I introduce tonight's celebrities playing tonight's Match Game.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you've never heard the Match Game before, it's just like the old school game show, which is coming back, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which I heard in the news recently.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's hardcore.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: It already did.
[SPEAKER_14]: It starts in a few weeks on Comedy Central.
[SPEAKER_13]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, joining us tonight for OLR Match Game, we have the one and only...
[SPEAKER_13]: Van right here from New York City.
[SPEAKER_14]: Say hello to DJ Ranma S. Hi, I'm DJ Ranma S. This is my first day of being sober.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, sorry, this is not AA.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Say hello as well to... Get a rope.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dark Tetsuya is here, the man that actually updates orangelaunchradio.com once in a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, there he is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hard working as ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: And also joining us tonight, intern Drew.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yo, what's up?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki is here as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura and me.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's six opportunities to match tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is a huge celebrity panel, so everybody's got something they can write with or think their answers in their head.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Ranma, since you're our out-of-town visitor, pick a number between one and fifteen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 Rapid Slasher is going to be our chatter tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I didn't count that exactly, too bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm going to say, are you there?
[SPEAKER_13]: Make sure he can send me a private message, otherwise he's DQ'd.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, so we have Rapid Slasher playing in chat tonight if he responds to my message.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's get somebody on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's got to play against somebody on the telephone.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: So now I have to type to Rapid Slasher.
[SPEAKER_13]: Stand by to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: Happy face.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Skype line is open.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR if you want to challenge Rapid Slasher in tonight's OLR match game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: GS68, are you ready to play the match game against Rapid Slasher?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, you gonna kick his ass?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I don't know how long he's been listening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, three questions tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here is the first question.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: This past Tuesday was Canada Day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Happy Canada Day to all our Canadian listeners.
[SPEAKER_13]: To celebrate Canada Day, Rob decided that he would play all his games in the nude for that day.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first game he played was blank.
[SPEAKER_13]: Celebrity panel was thinking about their answers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dangerous68 says ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did everybody ding?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm thinking of my answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have my answer, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: So did everybody ding here in studio?
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyone still thinking?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're waiting on Rapid Slasher.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's got to send me an answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Send me an answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: And if you want to help our players out, you can always answer in the chat room, chat.orangefansradio.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if Rapid Slasher hasn't thought of anything, you should take one of the chat room answers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me turn on the music there.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a little loud there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Still waiting on Rapid Slasher.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you can hear me, sir, please hurry up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did he leave?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is he still there?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, there we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got an answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: GS68.
[SPEAKER_13]: This past Tuesday was Canada Day.
[SPEAKER_13]: To celebrate Canada Day, Rob decided that he would play all his games in the nude for that day.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first game he played was... The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Guardian Legend, says GS68.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, and Rapid Slasher said...
[SPEAKER_13]: The first game he played was Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see if we've matched anyone on the panel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma S, what did you say?
[SPEAKER_13]: Or is it just Ranma now?
[SPEAKER_13]: Just Ranma.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma, no S. The first game he played was?
[SPEAKER_13]: I said Rez.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rez.
[SPEAKER_13]: Transfibrators, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, hell yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I get a hell yeah?
[SPEAKER_13]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, there it is, Rez.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dark Tetsuya, the first game he played was?
[SPEAKER_13]: I also said Rez.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rez!
[SPEAKER_13]: Two people saying Rez in the studio.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first game he played was?
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine Babies.
[SPEAKER_13]: Imagine...
[SPEAKER_13]: That's just wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's very wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: So 0-0 so far.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, GS68.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see if we get a match on Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, the first game he played was?
[SPEAKER_12]: I said MapleStory because, you know, it's Canada Day, so Maple.
[SPEAKER_13]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where's that Price is Right losing noise?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, just kidding, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: You didn't say video game.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I didn't say video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I said whack-a-mole.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whack-a-mole!
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: All hail DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_13]: You haven't heard my answer yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: So my answer this past Tuesday was Canada Day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did I say Guitar Hero or Rez?
[SPEAKER_13]: Not Rez.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guitar Hero or Guardian Legend.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: To celebrate Canada Day, Rob decided he would play all his games in the nude for that day.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first game he played was Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my second choice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_13]: Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_13]: 2DX.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right side pride, yo.
[SPEAKER_13]: That explains the firm handshake.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, GS68, I'm sorry it's still 0-0.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you ready to match on this next one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, GS68 says yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Next question.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki recently confessed to a big crime.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was the one that hacked PlayStation.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: When the police asked him to confess, he confessed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I did it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hacked PlayStation.com because the website didn't have enough blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki hacked PlayStation.com and said, yes, I did it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hacked PlayStation.com because the website didn't have enough blank.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm still thinking.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that doesn't mean I have an answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, I'm going for that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sounds like everybody's dinged.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I didn't copy-paste the question to Rapid Slasher.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shit, he's probably still thinking.
[SPEAKER_13]: Badhost, no cookie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Please hurry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I'm slow that time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, back with the music.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Rapid Slasher, thanks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki recently confessed to a big crime.
[SPEAKER_13]: He was the one that hacked Playstation.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: When the police asked him to confess, he confessed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I did it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hacked Playstation.com because the website didn't have enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, we got an answer from Rapid Slasher.
[SPEAKER_13]: So GS68, the website didn't have enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pylons.
[SPEAKER_13]: Old standby answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, there we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we have pylons and tits.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma, the website did not have enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Prawn.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not a match with tits.
[SPEAKER_13]: Prawn is not tits.
[SPEAKER_13]: Prawn is wannabe tits.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, DarkTetsuya, the website didn't have enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Iraqi suicide baby.
[SPEAKER_13]: Iraqi suicide baby, says DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't get the joke, what's the joke?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a Starcraft joke
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: The guy that made the over 9,000.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well shit, that's a match.
[SPEAKER_13]: Congratulations, GS68 is on the board with a point.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a match for pylons.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, Loki, the website did not have enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cleavage.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cleavage!
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that a match with tits, judges?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because cleavage is the... It's a match!
[SPEAKER_13]: I will say a half point.
[SPEAKER_13]: A half point for Rapid Slasher.
[SPEAKER_13]: A half point for rapid slasher.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, as I am the only person in this room that possesses said substance.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, he didn't have enough?
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_13]: PlayStation.com didn't have enough fuck?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Needs meat making.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, and my answer, the website didn't have enough Iraqi suicide babies.
[SPEAKER_13]: I also went with the old stand-by OLR joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, could have gotten you two points, but there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, one more question, a chance for Rapid Slasher to take over the lead.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you worried, GS68?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that was a no, it was very quiet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, here we go, question number three, and it's the last one, so your last chance to make a lot of points.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ding!
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm waiting for Rapid Slash's answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everybody in the studio, good to go?
[SPEAKER_13]: Good?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, everybody in the studio looks good.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're just waiting on our chatter.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chatter, if you need help, there's tons of answers in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like some of these answers.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, some of the answers we have for the previous one, on the website, website didn't have enough Eye of Judgment, Worthwhile Content, Porn, Hentai, Super Bacon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Website didn't have enough, that's a good one, that would have been a good one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, and then the other one, the first game I was going to play naked, Captain Commando.
[SPEAKER_13]: Boom Blocks, Texas Hold'em Dick Woman
[SPEAKER_13]: I said Guinness Woman Guinness Woman
[SPEAKER_13]: Very well done.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dark Tetsuya, her name would be?
[SPEAKER_11]: A bit cliche, but Bionic Woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bionic Woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Her name is Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Drew, the name would be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ferret Woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ferret Woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_13]: A match.
[SPEAKER_13]: And with that, Rapid Slasher takes the lead to one and a half versus one.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, the evil robot's name would be?
[SPEAKER_12]: Bitch, get back in the kitchen and make me dinner, woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, that's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you hear that on Justin.TV?
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, her name would be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: She doesn't need anything else.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be pretty evil.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got the finger.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: If I said Dick Woman, then GS68 wins.
[SPEAKER_13]: My answer, if I made an evil robot, her name would be Sniper Woman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sniper Woman, which unfortunately is not a match, which means Rapid Slasher wins in a narrow victory of one and a half to one.
[SPEAKER_13]: GS68, I'm sorry you're the loser tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: So is there any final words you have?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am already... Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: You get hung up on because you lost.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, that's what the losers get.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pwned.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: GS68's been on the show a million times.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nothing there.
[SPEAKER_13]: He knows the rules.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rapid Slasher, if you have anything you want to plug, send me a private message and I will plug it.
[SPEAKER_13]: As the winner, you get to plug whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: Meanwhile, Loki's going to get to the next story while I assess the damage of the party foul.
[SPEAKER_12]: There is another rumor of a game coming out now for, I believe, the PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this would make sense since, well, they've had other similar collections on the PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is the Star Soldier collection.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's supposed to contain four different Star Soldier games, including Star Soldier.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see, Final Soldier and Soldier Blade.
[SPEAKER_12]: And one other one, oh, Superstar Soldier, I guess, as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I'm sorry, and I got this all wrong here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Superstar Soldier, Final Soldier, Soldier Blade, and Star Parodier.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Parodia!
[SPEAKER_12]: and it would retail, I guess, in Japan for 2,940 yen, which is less than $30 US.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do want this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Parodia is like the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Haven't I done Star Parodia on a classic game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you did one form of Parodius or another.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if it was that specific one.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not Parodius.
[SPEAKER_06]: It has nothing to do with Parodius.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Star Parodia is a parody of Star Soldier.
[SPEAKER_13]: That I don't think you've done.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm all about Star Soldier myself, so do want.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's funny, though, because on the little screenshot that they have, or box shot or whatever it is, they have a bunch of the Bombermen guys running around.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I never saw Rapid Slasher send something he wanted to plug in private message, so I guess that's that.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe after this story.
[SPEAKER_13]: Burnout Paradise.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is one of those games I played for a couple days, and I was like, eh, I'm over it, which is sad because Burnout was such a fun series.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know...
[SPEAKER_13]: hats off to the folks at Criterion because they keep trying to invent new ways to make the game more fun granted they had a patch of theirs get pushed back a little bit but guess what's coming for the next patch this is very interesting Criterion is considering after this whole Cagney update is done they're going to put planes in Burnout Paradise yes planes
[SPEAKER_13]: Like pilot wings, planes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see an airborne takedown.
[SPEAKER_13]: That could be very interesting, but I worry about all the fan videos on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want free running to be in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want people just running and then running into other people, and that's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're going to explode and crash.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will say, though, referring to an earlier story in the evening, it would be pretty awesome to fly the plane in Burnout Paradise with a custom soundtrack playing Danger Zone.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Hells yeah, I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the, I'd have to say, best RPG series ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me untangle myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not called Let Me Untangle Myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be a pretty fun RPG.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're doing a Phantasy Star Portable.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a demo that is actually out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, on the official website, I do believe, at fantasystar.sega.jp slash PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got new characters and some downloadable content, and the demo is going to be out on July 14th, and the game will be out on the 31st, but that is Japan only.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it will be 301 megabytes in size.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: The demo, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Could be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to be, as they say, an extensive demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: you can access story mode and multi-mode and you can bring your saved data from the demo to the final game
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, I got the plugs from Rapid Slasher before we get to tonight's Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR Username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio Rapid Slasher would like to plug his YouTube channel available at youtube.com slash user slash Rapid Slasher And I'm looking at it right now, it looks like he has a two girls one cup reaction video Oh, those are always fun It looks like a friend is watching it on a cell phone there or something So there you have it And a video called Chewbacca, which I can only imagine what that is Stop it
[SPEAKER_13]: Rabbit Slasher would also like to say, Indiana represent, and go see Radiohead this summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Radiohead.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't know Radiohead was going out on tour.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have an album out.
[SPEAKER_06]: We might have to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rainbow's album.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, we might have to go do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Radiohead.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm thinking that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except Tom York is nuts.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look, before we get to the Skype line tonight, we have a very special late-breaking report, like live stuff going on right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to our OLR correspondent who's on the line.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you there?
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Tyrant What did you use our name to get into this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to Anime Expo, which actually just ended today, and I just got home about an hour ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I got to play some games that aren't out yet, got to check out some stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, first question I've got to ask.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anime Expo gets a little bit of a bad rap out there in the community.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've never been, so this is not a personal... That's okay, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: But all I've ever heard is it sucks, anime sucks, suckspo, anime, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does it still suck, or do you think people might need to pay at another visit?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think people might need to pay it another visit because they've restructured a lot of the upper people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did it suck as bad as last year?
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems a lot more organized now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did it suck as bad as last year, asked DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was much improved over last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I heard that nothing could suck as badly as last year has ever sucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last year was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: In order to come up, you've got to hit rock bottom first.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there you go, rock bottom.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many rabid Odon Host Club fangirls did you have to push your way through to get to the games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Too many.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's talk about games.
[SPEAKER_13]: What type of video game stuff did you see at Anime Expo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lots and lots of fighting games, because that seems to be pretty much 90% of any anime video game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Were they lots of fighting games based on animes, like any particular ones that jump out in your mind?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, the typical Naruto games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Namco had their PS3 Naruto game, and that looked really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: The graphics were really nice on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And D3 had their Wii Naruto fighting game, and so that's probably not going to be that great because it's on the Wii, and Wii fighting games generally are not that great.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_12]: I was going to say, which, by the way, if you want to play the demo for the PS3 one, you can download the second episode of Core, and they have an exclusive demo in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you subscribed to Core?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, but I read it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I ain't buying demos.
[SPEAKER_12]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, Jimmy.
[SPEAKER_13]: What else was there?
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to actually Arc System Works panel, which does Guilty Gear, and they showed off a couple trailers for some games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Castle Shikigami 3, which is a Wii title, it's another one of those shumps.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks really beautiful, and it looks a lot like Hikaruga.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Were there any non-fighting games there, or was that like all you saw?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was all that was pretty much playable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Soul Calibur 4 was playable.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looked really, really beautiful.
[SPEAKER_13]: Street Fighter 4?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: Capcom was not there, so Street Fighter 4 was not there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, tell us more about Soul Calibur 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you get some hands-on play with Soul Calibur 4?
[SPEAKER_13]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I didn't, but it looked pretty much like a standard Soul Calibur game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, there were only three playable characters, none of the exclusives.
[SPEAKER_08]: No Darth Vader or Yoda or Kratos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Another one from Arc Systems' work was Battle Fantasia, which I got to spend some time with.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's another fighting game, but it's exclusive for the 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll have Xbox Live Play coming out, I think, September 16th, they said.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a PS3 version.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very similar to Third Strike in that there's...
[SPEAKER_08]: A parry system in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You hit the R1 shoulder button and the next attack is parried.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you do it and there's no attack, there's kind of a cooldown from when you can attack again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I know there is a PS3 version of that because I'm actually trying to get a friend right now who's over in Japan to import it for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I'm surprised they're not localizing that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Probably a paid exclusive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that came up a lot during their panel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everyone was like, are you bringing it over for a PS3?
[SPEAKER_08]: And they haven't made any announcements yet for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They also showed a trailer for the Phoenix Wright style game, Jack Hunter.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was kind of funny to see that because it looks almost exactly like Phoenix Wright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see Blue Blaze Calamity Trigger?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I saw the game and the line was huge for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks very similar to the Guilty Gear XX series.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has the same style of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: and there's a blocking system in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to check it out and on that top bar, if you've played Street Fighter Alpha 3, there's a guard meter where you can only guard so much and it's separate in that game but in this game, both people share it so I can see some strategies playing out because of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm a little surprised that you didn't see more RPGs, MMOs from little companies and all that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw a ton of the little MMOs, MapleStory.
[SPEAKER_08]: They got me to sign up for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they gave me $10 in free...
[SPEAKER_08]: Nickel and Diamond DLC or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was it worth selling your soul?
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't sell my soul yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Keyword.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jimmy, before we let you go, we gotta know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for giving us the fill on what we missed on Anime Expo, but I gotta know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Best cosplay and worst cosplay?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: My favorite cosplay was probably a Captain Falcon that looked pretty darn good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_08]: Worst cosplay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any of the females that really didn't need to be in skimpy outfits?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you have that at every con, though, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just not appealing.
[SPEAKER_08]: David Hader's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: I assume that no cosplayer's got shot being in L.A.?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm shocked.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why everyone assumes that.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, well, DJ Tyrant, I'll see you at BlizzCon.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're in a nicer area.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be a blast.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care, Jimmy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for being on the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, we like hearing from Jimmy, and I'm glad he has a place to come on and talk, sadly, because STFU is no more.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there is, uh, STFU is kind of combined now, you know, you got half of, uh, STFU, you got DMN, and you got, uh, Travis Donovan, they do a show together, here on, uh, All Games Radio, it's Under Station Live, it airs Saturday nights, and it was the show I started on years ago, and DarkSakura was a guest like 50 million times.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, if you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR, and it's already ringing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, this is the other New Yorker, SSJ100Matt.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yo, what's up Matt?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Chrono Trigger
[SPEAKER_13]: Chrono... No, you're right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not according to me, but I still think it's pretty darn good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not even as good as some of the Final Fantasy games I've played, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Even I will probably get the Chrono Trigger remake on DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was this collective explosion of fangasm on the internet this week when that was announced.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: My LiveJournal friends list exploded, and I'm sure people's Twitters blew themselves up as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um...
[SPEAKER_13]: What would you, as a Chrono Trigger fan, really want to see in this new DS version, Matt?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I assume it's going to be based on the SNES version, but I think just keep everything the way it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think they said they were going to add more dungeons and online play.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's fine with me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I beat the game 10,000 times since it's come out, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: What would you have thought, Matt, if it had turned out that this game was a 3D remake in the same vein as Final Fantasy 3 and Final Fantasy 4?
[SPEAKER_13]: Would you have been a little scared or what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I probably would have been a little scared.
[SPEAKER_01]: I probably still would have bought it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Still would have bought it, just to support Chrono Trigger, but a little bit apprehensively.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, maybe if we each buy 50 copies, they'll make Radical Dreamers or some sort of sequel.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dream on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dream on with that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you never know.
[SPEAKER_13]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Stranger things have happened, so there you have it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I have my fingers crossed that Chrono Trigger will do the fans justice.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have not played the game in so long.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't played Chrono Trigger since I was a kid, so it'll be fun to revisit that series.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's good because a lot of the younger generation who were born in the 90s, they'll actually get a chance to play this because I'm sure there's plenty of people in the chat room who have never played it before.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am kind of curious, though, how the whole two-screen thing is going to work.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm very curious to see what they do with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we'll be waiting for some more screenshots and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they make it 3D, they better do it justice.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Sprite.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's old-school Sprite.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Matt, thank you so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any other last words you want to say real quick?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, two things.
[SPEAKER_01]: When are you guys coming out to New York again?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey Joe, hey Joe, hey Joe, hey Joe, hey Joe What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait a minute, where have I heard that before?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds familiar.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later, Matt.
[SPEAKER_13]: For that, you get hung up on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have got room for about, how long are we running this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, shit, we're almost to an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe like one more call on the Skype line at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sack Anime, a little closer to home, last week of August.
[SPEAKER_02]: Be there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, it's Penny Arcade Expo, same weekend.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can't do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine, I'll go.
[SPEAKER_13]: They do like five SAC animes a year.
[SPEAKER_13]: They do two.
[SPEAKER_13]: It seems like there's a con at the Sonic Center every month.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have two SAC animes a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, two SAC animes a year and four SAC animes a month.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_02]: And four smaller SAC comic cons a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for the local news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love Sunrise Mall.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll stop with the local chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk to somebody on the skyline.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: I spaced out there for a sec.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is Gold Banjo.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: The heat is making us spacey too, but it's starting to cool off a little bit, thank God.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, it's not as bad over here in New England and New Hampshire, but I feel bad for you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys have to deal with humidity.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least we don't have that.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, well, actually, I'm one of those Chrono Trigger people, and, well, once again, I know you might not be as crazy about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't actually even know much about the game, and I know that I have to play it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, that just goes to show you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that's almost an adage.
[SPEAKER_13]: How old are you, if you don't mind me asking?
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: And to the new generation, do it, or I'll come over the internet and kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: The new generation.
[SPEAKER_13]: So old.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gold Banjo, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I just wanted to call in and say that real quick.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Have a good night, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: You too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have fun with Chrono Trigger DS whenever it comes out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I'm definitely looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Call back and let us know what you think, young whippersnapper.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's hot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hot Garage is very hot, but thankfully it's cooling.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's getting a little more bearable in here now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, any last-minute stories from you tonight?
[SPEAKER_12]: I've only been looking at stories, unfortunately, because I've been too busy working on stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: and apparently they had an elf loader on there that they were able to run a Genesis emulator.
[SPEAKER_12]: On what now?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a program called Swap Magic.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was one of those things to run on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Run, I guess, burn games and stuff like that or region-free stuff on the PlayStation 2, but they ran it on the PlayStation 3 and were able to play Genesis Simulator on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sure, you could run Linux or something like that on your other operating system on that and easily run games that way, but
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not as fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was one thing that was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, the Wrath of the Lich King beta signups are open.
Shh!
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't tell people because I want the key.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, speaking of things we missed, if you were an Uru Live fan, a Missed Online fan, on GameTap, they are pulling that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The publishers are taking it back and apparently going to revive the community.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, good for them.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you're all three people that enjoyed that, come on back.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, we've got some other things here real quick.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bomberman's coming to the iPhone with Bomberman Touch, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also, I guess Game, the UK retailer, is going to start publishing some independent games.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's interesting to have a retailer doing that at the front like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exclusives.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can you say exclusives?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Sony, I guess, is putting out another game that's going to be, I guess, coming out in September called Aqua.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's a sequel to Aquanauts Holiday, which is sort of like Endless Ocean on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: So think of Africa, but under the sea.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it looks pretty cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, there's a rumor that Golf Tee It Up is supposedly coming to Xbox Live Arcade next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever the hell that's supposed to be, but apparently it has its Xbox.com page now, so that's on there, as well as, I guess, Pirates vs. Ninja Dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_12]: About time.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then there's also a Guitar Hero homebrew game that's supposed to be coming out towards the end of August, August 20th.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's called Video Game Hero.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two of the tracks that they have on there, Eye of the Tiger and Inspector Gadget.
[SPEAKER_12]: Inspector Gadget.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the Inspector Gadget theme, which both of them sound kind of like...
[SPEAKER_12]: Very MIDI sounding.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the game, you use the touch screen or the directional buttons.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of like Oda Jam almost.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which, that'd be something else good to bring to the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dark Tetsuya, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: That little keychain thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Cyberman.
[SPEAKER_05]: You were wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: Google Maps on my phone with GPS has been making me uber geek this entire weekend geek, nerd damn proud of it my final thought is hot DarkSakura exterminate the heap Loki hot chair is hot
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks so much for tuning in to us.
[SPEAKER_13]: And remember, hey, we brave the heat.
[SPEAKER_13]: We do this every week for you guys, the listeners, for free.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't get anything from doing this, contrary to popular belief.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't get paid by all games or none of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's all completely free for you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: All we ask, guys, if you enjoy our show, tell somebody.
[SPEAKER_13]: Spread the word.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell two friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Post a nice review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Put something in your signature or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: that's all we ask and a lot of you have done that so thank you guys so much for that and thanks to that independent internet radio will continue to live on we suffer for your entertainment do it for another 286 episodes we hope unless we pass out first so until next week
[SPEAKER_13]: Pray for a rainstorm or some windstorms and we'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week