[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight, July 6th, 2008, a 16-bit RPG classic is being redone for the DS, Rock Band 2 leaks hit the internet, and could a popular racing game soon take on airplanes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Joining me as always, say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I gotta make sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are we hearing Inter and Drew tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are we hearing Inter and Drew?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I think we are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Barely, although that's very quiet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do I have the sensitive mic tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do I have the sensitive mic?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Live radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're doing sound checks live on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sound check one, two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, when I talk, it makes little lines up here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the magic of radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You haven't figured that out after six years?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, say hello tonight to our website master, Dark Tetsuya is here in studio, amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know, I made it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You live in town and yet you never seem to make it over here, but here you are tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Drew said he was going to come and get me yesterday, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
Here I am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well Dark Tetsuya is here, we'll get him a little louder, we'll give him some mic lessons a little later.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really bad tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We may have to take a heat break in the middle of Part A. I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't laugh at me, Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll have to get the Gatorade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, it's pretty bad in here tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want Jamie to die live on air.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be horrific.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't want to die on air either.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we might take a heat break in the middle of Part A. I want to die on bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, say hello as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The good news is, since we broadcast at 6 o'clock, you know, the heat reaches its peak around 5 o'clock, so it should be cooling off, thankfully, throughout the night.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, say hello as well to, um, well, wait, I guess we're not in order of importance anymore, because she'd be on the bottom of the list.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess!
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, aren't I on the bottom anyway?
[SPEAKER_05]: Aren't I the last person?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just messing with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut your face, Rob!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you, Miss Princess?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mad at you now.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you love me.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have a very full house tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just lots and lots of people to comment on the news tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, you in our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got lots of people in chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Stickax282 who says, I'm kind of new here to this whole live thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boy, did you pick a shitty show to have as your first show because it's going to be chaotic tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But welcome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shadow Charlie says, Holy crap, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: Holy crap, indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Zappy says, somebody dying live on air sounds exciting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I think it's one of those things that's better when you're at home watching, but if you're like live in studio and considering the fact it's Jamie and it would kind of, like, I don't want Jamie to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, Jamie said some things that have made me angry before, but I don't want her to die.
[SPEAKER_02]: Heart.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess Jamie has died and the ferret has taken over tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie is alive and very well and wants to talk to you all about her gaming week.
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's imbalanced, but I managed to replay on my first ball.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the only time I've ever done well on that game in my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: No Fear, and World Cup Soccer in the house and everything else that's outside.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dan's working on our friend's Indiana Jones machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I was going to say, when I was there, I saw an Indiana Jones machine that was being worked on.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we used it for cookies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I actually ate a cookie off the Indiana Jones machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was very delicious.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were mint cookies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it was very delicious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Foodio.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else that you played with your week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Any de-essin'?
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Traffic a lot, and I played Getting Lost to San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_02]: You played in Traffic?
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Driving.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people tell me to go play in Traffic, but I've never actually played in Traffic.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Initial D for real.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it was on the freeways.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was more like Wan Gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, let's go around the studio and see what everybody else has been playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will start with the guests tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Loki and I will go last.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who has the mic for you kids over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess, since you were on the bottom last time, why don't you start off?
[SPEAKER_02]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Non-existent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, you're boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, Ranma, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was tolerable.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played Mario Kart DS on the plane ride coming in and throughout the week on the subway, I was playing Custom Robo Arena, which has really become one of my favorite games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell us a little bit about Custom Robo Arena.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I've ever heard of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, Custom Robo Arena is like a Pokemon-ish type game where...
[SPEAKER_09]: You get like this little cube as a robot and you customize it with different parts and you battle with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the fun part of the stylus is like cleaning up your robot because throughout the game, if you're running around with a dirty robo, nobody wants to fight with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a Tamagotchi where it'll poop randomly and you have to clean it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds very awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not bad for $9.99, so hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we'll put it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to apologize for the audio quality you've been hearing in the first little bits of the show, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the mics got switched, and the guests got the mic with a very low gain, and I got the one with a very high gain.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was very loud, and they were very quiet, but we've switched some things over here on the board.
[SPEAKER_02]: I ninja'd over to the board and switched some things while they were talking about their gaming week, so hopefully it's getting a little better.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you as we move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DarkTetsuya, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, just a lot of Need for Speed Carbon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually beat it, but I went back and did some of the challenges to unlock some more stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, don't you have a Justin.TV channel or something where people can actually watch you play games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I stream random emulators and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: What kind of games can people see if they check you out on Justin.TV?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm working on Zelda right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm waiting to do Death Mountain.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I was actually on Justin.TV very randomly one night, and you might not know what Dark Tits are, but I was watching you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing about Justin.TV is you can actually watch people and they never know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You were playing La Mulana, and that was actually the first time I'd ever seen it, so it was cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually got to check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does look very retro.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can see why people are really into that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you do not host your own podcast right now, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not at the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not at the moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Drew.
[SPEAKER_02]: Intern Drew, do you host a podcast, for heaven's sake?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not yet, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You got plans for one, don't you?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any asshole with a mic can do a podcast in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how to describe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a platformer action game with RPG elements.
[SPEAKER_07]: That, I've been playing some Fire Emblem 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: Trying to actually beat it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is brutal, even on the first try.
[SPEAKER_07]: And aside from that, I haven't been playing much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weren't you Captain Excitement?
[SPEAKER_07]: I picked up Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter 2 at Used Bookstore the other day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't get it to run.
[SPEAKER_07]: It crashes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Best ten bucks I ever spent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now make your games work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that's going to... He's putting his mic down somewhat angrily.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you play?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to figure out which mic I'm supposed to be having here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you're that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play too much this week because I've been busy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I did play...
[SPEAKER_08]: Grand Theft Auto 4 Defender Castle
[SPEAKER_08]: and Mario Kart Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had to download a ton more Miis.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, we got one that's got a crab on the person's face, which is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: It pinches its claws.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crab people!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, crab people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then one with Mickey Mouse.
[SPEAKER_08]: We just downloaded a bunch of Miis and played the levels with the Miis in the background.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I just tried the...
[SPEAKER_08]: Homebrew, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: game that someone had made or worked on.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I guess it's very early because it's not very good right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, it's not... Needs work?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not even close to being started, let alone done.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was it for your week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had a pretty slow gaming week, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you got other projects going on, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm busy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then my car was in the shop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun, fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've had an exciting week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan really loves Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_02]: So then it's worth it to Dan.
[SPEAKER_01]: But we didn't buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Me, Guitar Hero Journey, I would have dropped the $60.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would have paid $100 for Guitar Hero Journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not Guitar Hero Journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Guitar Hero Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it did motivate me to go back and actually play some Guitar Hero 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I still cannot beat that freaking Slipknot song on hard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you download the free song?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Top Gun song is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish it was Danger Zone, but... Still, what a great patriotic tune.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the last thing we need is homoerotic volleyball scenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, that's the part I'm having trouble kind of getting over because I want to strum everything and it's hard to tell when the notes are coming that fast which ones you have to strum and which ones you don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does Guitar Hero people in chat know what I'm talking about, please?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or do I just sound crazy?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because everybody in the studio is looking at me like, huh?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, like the hammer-ons and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the tutorial does not explain it that well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The tutorial explains a little bit about the, how you can, like, I'm not even going to try to explain it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The tutorial doesn't explain it very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of something I had to learn on my own.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Before we begin, I have presents.
[SPEAKER_02]: Presence?
[SPEAKER_02]: What a good way to start tonight's housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love housekeeping to begin with presents.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, before the show, I was showing the people on JustinTV this, but Loki got me some new floor mats with Hello Kitty on them, which is hilarious because I already had ones with penguins on them, so I'm going to figure out how to use them both.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to lie on a shirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys didn't plan that, did you?
[SPEAKER_07]: You have no choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you so much for the shirts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, that's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll change into one right now, but not live on cam, because that's kind of gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do heart NY.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait to go back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, hey, I'm wearing my shirt that says Ice Skull Pirates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, she is!
[SPEAKER_08]: No comment!
[SPEAKER_08]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really have anything for the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have no interviews coming up, which is kind of sad, but I will say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: We always have our LiveJournal community and the MySpace communities.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook, we are the OLRMY, O-L-R-M-Y, if you want to look us up.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to join us on LiveJournal, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: No radio, just Orange Lounge is us on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_02]: And on MySpace, we are Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Three different names for three different sites, if we could be any more confusing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good job, Standards Department.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't confuse us with the group Orange Range.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or the group Orange Lounge, for that matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although, has Tomosuke made an Orange Lounge song in the past three years?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think he has.
[SPEAKER_02]: Has he?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we own it now, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think there's some rule now that we own Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, let's get to tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Loki's going to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so more details about Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is going to be completely 8-bit looking, including the very limited color palette as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be also really fucking hard, just like most Mega Man games.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, there was some hands-on stuff from Joystick and some other...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to mention about my gaming week I've been playing Mega Man Anniversary Collection and I'm starting with Mega Man 1 I'm about to pull my fucking hair out on the Iceman level with those fucking blocks Whoever invented the block puzzles needs to burn in hell
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, once you get past the blocks, once you get past the blocks... Then it only gets worse in Mega Man 2 and the Heat Man stage, unless you have Item 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless you have Item 2, which you ought to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But seriously, until about the fifth game, the fifth NES game, I never thought Mega Man series was really that hard.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob, if you want to make everything easy on the first Mega Man, start with Cut Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have killed Cut Man, Elect Man, Guts Man, Bomb Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just... I got to get Ice Man now so I can get Fire Man.
[SPEAKER_09]: GameGuru says Nintendo games should be Nintendo hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: They're okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I like the Nintendo Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this old school thing made you squee in many places, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good to hear.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they should just continue with making Mega Man games just like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just make them all a bit from now on and if you want to do the 16-bit or the little higher graphics games, just do the Mega Man X series.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have really too many series going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have that ZX series now and then they also have Star Force and just...
[SPEAKER_08]: Bring back Legends.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bring back the original 8-bit Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they are.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're getting half of what you want.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, but they need to continue.
[SPEAKER_08]: One game is not bringing it back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to read some comments as well from JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have more people on JustinTV than I've ever seen before.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Illustrator says, Real fucking hard keeps the ignorant noobs away.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Mega Man 9 is not really a multiplayer game, so who cares about noobs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let a noob noob themselves in a...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be fucking hard, and then you keep playing it until you can pass it, and then you become better.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't just go, oh, I suck, move on to the next game.
[SPEAKER_07]: As it was said before about leading noobs to water, most of what you get are wet noobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now you're leading noobs to Splash Woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think she's going to be a bit wet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you're disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe that's a little tagline on the poster.
[SPEAKER_02]: This September, Splash Woman gets wet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are we explicit yet?
[SPEAKER_07]: We always are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck!
[SPEAKER_07]: Now we are.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have to say it a few more times because I watched... Fuck, fuck, fuckity, fucker, fucker, fuck, fuck, fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I watched Hancock over the weekend and they did have fuck in there once, but it's still PG-13.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's got cock in the title!
[SPEAKER_08]: Every movie should have cock in the title.
[SPEAKER_08]: His name's John Hancock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the fuck show already?
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Cockio.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's the cock show!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Mega Man 9's been dated for September as well, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that's what I already said.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, I missed it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was sleeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking about Splash Woman's cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: because you know she probably had one at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dr. Wily has his leftover parts.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow!
[SPEAKER_07]: What is it with Wily and making every single one of his robots male?
[SPEAKER_07]: You think he's got a little secret?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now he's branching out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it sexist, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, he's bi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it sexist?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, because see, Dr. Wily likes little boys, but that's okay because so does Dr. Light, and Dr. Light also likes little girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell is wrong with this show?
[SPEAKER_02]: For real, I'm clicking unsubscribe right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Click.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was disgusting.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you're saying Dr. Wally's a member of the Catholic Church?
[SPEAKER_02]: God, Chris Hansen's gonna be here any minute.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take a seat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, shit, you already took a seat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I don't think there's any altar girls.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he's probably Presbyterian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to a much cleaner, safer, kid-friendly game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_02]: There has been a teaser in the latest official Nintendo magazine over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you look at the magazine scan that's floating around the internet, or if you're actually on the magazine, it says, it's been a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's time to revisit an old friend.
[SPEAKER_02]: How's your village doing these days?
[SPEAKER_02]: That is... It just has a little picture from Animal Crossing and has that quote.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could that be a hint that we get Animal Crossing 83?
[SPEAKER_01]: I bet, I bet, I bet, I bet.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I have a thought.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to make everyone use their GameCube versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Wii one's going to make everyone use their GameCube versions?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's going to make you load your GameCube Village.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, maybe that's why the quote saying, how's your village doing all these days?
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, you better go pull some fucking weeds or you're in for it when the new game comes out.
[SPEAKER_01]: It means I better go get my memory card back from my friend who was taking care of my village for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't me, was it?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what would be funny is the reason they're saying that they're all, yeah, you should really go back and check how your village is doing because you're not getting a new game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You better go back and play the old one.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be the joke.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got the Japanese one, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got a new memory card.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lost my old village.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have a new memory card, so I'm thinking about making, like, OLR Town and maybe playing it on Justin.TV and letting the chatters... You should do that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, let the chatters name stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: For real.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because we have to have... Who was the lesbian?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: She lives in my village.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a lesbian that lived in the village.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: Her whole house was a gym.
[SPEAKER_01]: And she was our resident lesbian, so we put a nice little rainbow sign up in front of her house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we put a gay pride flag in front of her house.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then she moved.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we started putting the pattern up in every town we visited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't we have her saying, like, I like boobs as a little thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Animal Crossing is so awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course, we also had someone running around going, cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says the question is if Rob and Irene will quit WoW to play Animal Crossing Wii Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: RicePrincess says she already has Are you getting a head start in a new village?
[SPEAKER_02]: Only if they'll batten you all It is a 12 step recovery program Alright, it is a 12 step recovery program We'll see, E3 is coming very soon I have my fingers and toes and other parts crossed that Animal Crossing will be an announcement at E3, so we'll see
[SPEAKER_02]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on with other news here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, actually, I'll read quick chat comments here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sharon says, Animal Crossing was only somewhat kid-friendly.
[SPEAKER_02]: It taught you to not take loans from anyone.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you do, you'll have to do bitch work for your neighbors and take all the furniture they throw away for the rest of your life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: More news.
[SPEAKER_00]: Gotta.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotta.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Chicken butt.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's... Guess why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Chicken Thigh, In Your Eye.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is totally one of those shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Having people in studio, like a live audience practically, ruins this show.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Rob, for my story, you need to do something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what do I have to do for your story?
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to pull up the said site that this refers to from Squeenix and play the sound effect and see if anyone in the chatroom gets it first.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a feeling everybody in chat already knows what's coming.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I want the sound effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is fucked up in front of a live audience.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a demanding woman tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, I've got to get there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're going to have to start reading the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a particular game that I'm sure a lot of people have been wanting for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_01]: And by the way, it's the link that says Japanese website, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are they bringing back to some sort of system their Super Metroid?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're bringing back an RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is speculated to be a port, hopefully remaining in 2D, on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it in Fury or Super Metroid?
[SPEAKER_01]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But do the viewers, do the listeners... I'm going to throw something at you, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Please do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you go to ScreenX's site, the address is square-nx.co.jp slash ctds.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as Rob is pulling it up now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of slow because we're broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're going to hear the effect.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even know if they're going to hear it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got so much shit running in studio tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: at any rate, well if you go to that site you will see the clock and you will hear the ticking and you will know that it's Chrono Trigger because no other game freaking has that clock making that same ticking noise at the very start of it
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, my computer is not enjoying broadcasting an internet radio show and doing the Chrono Trigger website at the same time.
[SPEAKER_01]: We will let you do that for yourself so that you can have a truly interactive experience, those of you listening to the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alpha Cananogram says in chat, DarkSakura, now it's chronotrigger.jp as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Rad.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't make it 3D, Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't fuck it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shaoran says Chrono Trigger, it's over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, guys, there are other RPGs that have better storylines and better character development.
[SPEAKER_01]: No!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_01]: You did not, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think he did.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they haven't translated the ones that do surpass it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing, I heard that the Chrono Trigger... What, Loki, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to say about Chrono Trigger, it's not 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't we already know it's going to be the same old sprites?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That we can tell, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bonus dungeon, Wi-Fi play.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe add some bonus dungeons.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard co-op, but how can you play co-op in that game?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you have three people.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be like Secret of Mana.
[SPEAKER_02]: Secret of Mana
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got a multitap, so that was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the other speculation, and actually I hope that this will be included, is that the animated scenes that they did for the PlayStation version are rumored to be making it to the DS version, especially if they're spending less of the processing power on the way the game runs and putting more of it into having the cinemas, because that'll make it sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: More endings!
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Mad asks, co-op gato battle.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ooh, sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I want to know, everyone who's in this room that's played Chrono Trigger, how many endings have you gotten?
[SPEAKER_02]: Two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell, if I remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably four.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have no time on your hands, sir.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you have too much time.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was the secret one where you go watch the...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I've done that one.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the one where you get the developers ending where you actually have representations of the developers and you go into the last room and it's Toriyama wearing his gas mask and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the credits go by really, really fast because they want you to skip past it again.
[SPEAKER_02]: All this freaking reminiscing here in studio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki looks like he's about to explode wanting to talk about Elebits.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play really much of Chrono Trigger and I don't feel bad for not having played Chrono Trigger either, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: If I wanna play Chrono Trigger, I'll hook up my Super Nintendo and grab my cartridge.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the DS one might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't play Final Fantasy 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seeing as getting a Chrono Trigger Super Nintendo cartridge at this time, if you didn't hang on to one, it's going to cost you a lot of money to get one now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hear this game is going to have this super secret final ending where you take the game back to GameStop and trade it in for store credit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't pay for my copy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Someone gave it to me and he moved.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I have it in the box.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nice, inherited.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't plan on paying for my copy either.
[SPEAKER_01]: What a coincidence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: More stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Less exciting news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Elebits 2 has been confirmed, and it's not the same Elebits you may have remembered.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now it's some sort of top-down, sprite-based game, and there's lots of Elebits running around.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's almost like a cartoony version of Pikmin or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Elebits, The Adventures of Kai and Zero is coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think maybe they're just like, you know, the Wii one just didn't work like we wanted it to, so let's just jump ship and go to the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: They probably tried to do a 3D version on the DS and were like, wow, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then they're just like, okay, let's see what we can do with the touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no way they could have done a 3D version on the DS anyways, because there's no depth in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not a lot of depth in a lot of DS games, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Pokemon sells billions and billions of copies, so it probably is not a bad idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming to the Wii, however, even if Elebits 2 may not be coming to the Wii, apparently Cooking Mama...
[SPEAKER_02]: there's going to be another Cooking Mama game on the Wii it's Cooking Mama World Kitchen and it's coming to you from Majesco and it's a follow up to the game Cooking Mama Cook Off which was kind of crap because they tried to port a DS game to the Wii and it just didn't work very well sadly
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm betting on the second.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really hope not because Cookie Mama's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, Jamie, I know you love Cookie Mama very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about a rhythm-based Cookie Mama game on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll reserve judgment until I actually try it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, and I feel the same way, but your heart doesn't like, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm completely apathetic towards it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm interested.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'm not going to make my judgment until I actually see it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, honestly, I've had games where I've made a harsh judgment about them to start.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's turned out that they've been pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm not going to... Like Imagine Babies?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_01]: That game sucks!
[SPEAKER_01]: That game is like the bugs that live in shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where did we have in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, Rob, crack, crack, crack the egg into the bowl.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Frisbee says, Cooking Mama, Hell's Kitchen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that might be a little bit fun if somebody screams at Cooking Mama and makes her cry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Except if they based it off of a show, it should be based off of a good show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Hell's Kitchen is already getting a DS game and it's actually coming out before Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that's going to be any good though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll see about that Cooking Mommy game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I have to admit it makes me a little bit nervous, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: We shall.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, for more happy wee news, this might make some people very pleased, but there is a...
[SPEAKER_01]: A little bit more coming out for WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was actually released on Friday.
[SPEAKER_01]: First is Pokemon Ranch, where, to quote, it's a place where Pokemon and people love living together.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need Pokemon Bunny Ranch.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or Pokemon Sniper.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's Jigglypimp's Whore Lounge from Kalec in the House.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slut Bunny Slut Bunny
[SPEAKER_02]: Shaoran in chat wants to know if you can brand them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemon Snap 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: This time you have a gun.
[SPEAKER_02]: A whole new kind of rail shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pokemon Snap their necks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cheeseburger says Imagine Sniper.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would play Imagine Sniper.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'd be like Silent Scope, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's going to be 1,000 Wii points.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the other one is a game that you pop bubbles on.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bubble popping game is finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a clever title.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just pop bubbles.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it like Buster Brothers?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think it's supposed to be more like... It's a bubble wraps game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played with that the other day!
[SPEAKER_01]: It was called Bubble Wrap!
[SPEAKER_02]: It was called Going to Seize Candy and the best part is the bubble wrap.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was called I Bought a Teapot and Played the Bubble Wrap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you feed a Pokemon an Alka-Seltzer, will it explode?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Only the avian ones will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's some of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's birds.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pikachu giblets everywhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rice Princess has this horrified look on her face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would you play Pokemon Ranch?
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it sound like a fun game to you?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: But Rob... Why?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's 700 Wii Points.
[SPEAKER_08]: To pop bubbles.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is awesome, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo and WiiWare, they're really doing some different things.
[SPEAKER_08]: People want a new Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles game.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get Crystal Chronicles, My Life as the King.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not really a Crystal Chronicles game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's more of like other people are having fun outside of your city and you're just staying home watching TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whereas Pokemon Ranch...
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel an OLR game somewhere in here called, like, Goddamn I'm So Bored.
[SPEAKER_07]: We play it every Sunday.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's like the Me Parade.
[SPEAKER_02]: In God Damn I'm So Bored, you start a podcast with your two friends, and then you just sit there and pop bubble wrap the whole time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a game to be made here somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to think about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You also have to include turning on your Wii for the first time and trying to watch Me March with only one me on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's goddamn, I'm so lonely.
[SPEAKER_08]: Magnetica Magnetica
[SPEAKER_08]: Magnetica, and then they have Toki Tori, which is just lame, and the bubble popping game, which, I don't know, it's all kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Something else that hopefully is not lame.
[SPEAKER_08]: Castlevania Judgment.
[SPEAKER_08]: The kind of, not really a Castlevania game, but now it's Soul Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Soul Calibur, but Castlevania characters and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will have Wii DS connectivity.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll be able to plug in your new Order of Es... What was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_08]: Ecclesia, the new DS platformer game coming out to unlock bonus gameplay content.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also so Konami can say, we sold you one of each.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sucker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me guess, let me guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking a character that you only see in the DS game is going to be playable in the Wii game if you connect them.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably paid to unlock content because you're paying for the DS game to unlock the content on the disc that was already there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't surprise me at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: But here's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get a friend that has this game for the DS and you just have him come over and done.
[SPEAKER_08]: No purchase necessary.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Loki was talking about this a little bit earlier during his gaming week, but if you haven't heard yet, there is a homebrew Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rumble that's available on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's by a homebrew programmer that goes by the name of Fuzzy.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you touch him, do you get dizzy?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad joke there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, apparently, though, the game only has three levels in it right now, and just one character is playable in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Mario.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I have not actually played the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's YouTube-age of it, but Loki, since you've actually played the game, tell us a little more about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very simplified.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's sprite-based characters, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it Smash Bros., or is it like Mario?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's supposed to be like Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, the only playable character is Mario right now, and...
[SPEAKER_08]: The computer player doesn't really do anything, just kind of runs around trying to avoid you, and you can't really smash him off the edge, defeating the purpose of the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: Personally, I think they should just port over Mugen, but that's just... It's asking a bit much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't know if it would be able to run it either.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, if you are homebrew enabled on your DS, which I'm actually kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to ask the chat room a question.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many people are actually homebrew enabled on their DS?
[SPEAKER_02]: We have how many people in chat right now?
[SPEAKER_02]: Almost 50 people in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to know how many of you are homebrew enabled in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say something while we go over some release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll start with the UK.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, coming out in the UK, we have a number of things all on the 11th.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have Beijing 2008, the official game of the Olympic Games.
[SPEAKER_01]: The official video game, sorry, of the Olympic Games.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Devil May Cry 4 on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Doodle Hex on DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Secret Agent Clank on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sports Party on Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: Summer Athletics on PS2, PC and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: And The Incredible Hulk on PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like a busy week.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the US, it's not that busy of a week, but there's still some stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Civilization Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm excited, yay!
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also this week, Unreal Tournament 3 for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of people looking forward to that one on 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy Fables, Chocobo Dungeon on the Wii, which I guess it's not quite a port of the DS game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Carnival Games on the DS, and Wonder World Amusement Park on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, is the Carnival Games on the DS the other way around, where they ported a Wii game to the DS?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beijing Olympics 2008 on the PS3 and Xbox 360 Devil May Cry 4 on the PC PurrPals for the Wii Code Lyoko Quest for Infinity on the PSP and let's see and I believe that's pretty much it for the week
[SPEAKER_02]: Stickax282 says Civ Rev for the fucking win I agree, that's the game I'm definitely looking forward to because I actually really like the demo and I don't think it's going to crap on my childhood memories of the original Civilization which I was a little worried about at first so I'm pretty excited about that GameGuru agrees, Civ Rev for the win and Rob with 2B says Carnival Games is a different game
[SPEAKER_02]: N, I don't Me, I don't even have a DS If I knew how to do it I am Sky, I am homebrew enabled Raise his hand, can play homebrew Nope, I am homebrew enabled Yep
[SPEAKER_02]: DS, what's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have not turned on my DS in like a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not, but my friends is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, no homebrew on my DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am homebrew enabled for DS, Wii, PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even have a DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: And lastly, my GBA, DS, PSP, and iPod are all running homebrew apps.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually a larger percentage than I would have thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't run homebrew on my DS because I just don't know how to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: and Loki's like, hey, you want a hit?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, once you get the device to do it, it's really simple.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's just drag drop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not like, you know, a Wii where some installation is required and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go over to Japan and look at some release dates coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Xbox...
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Xbox 360, some games are getting a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Viva Pinata on the Xbox 360 is getting cut in price, as well as Forza Motorsport 2 and Test Drive Unlimited, as well as the Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all move into the Platinum Collection in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: again a couple games go into the best series but here's what a lot of people are looking forward to Persona 4 comes out in Japan on July 10th and if you're a hardcore RPG fan and you can read Japanese and understand it you are probably importing this game I would imagine just call it a hunch
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Nintendo DS, Custom Beat Battle, Draglade 2, Cosmetic Paradise, Maki no Kiseki, Pet Shop, Monogatari DS, Taito
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the Sony PSP, I doubt there's a lot this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Taking a look.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God of War, Chains of Olympus.
[SPEAKER_02]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: God of War, Chains of Olympus gets its Japanese version this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought I read that last week on the show, so I must have been looking in advance or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, a vehicle battle game comes out on the PSP from Irem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ponkotsu Roman Daika Sugeki Bumpy Trot.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, what the hell do they call it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Steambot Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that other name, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bumpy Trot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bumpy Trot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Random question from chat that has nothing to do with anything we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: FearTheClaw asks, well, sort of, because we mentioned it during release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: FearTheClaw asks, I've never played Viva Pinata.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it really that bad?
[SPEAKER_02]: Gosh, where do we begin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Viva Pinata was Xbox 360's kind of foray to try and rip off Pokemon, in a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not necessarily rip off, but... They went in at full bore.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually did a TV show.
[SPEAKER_02]: TV show, everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know...
[SPEAKER_02]: The problem was, the game was too complicated for seven-year-olds to understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the teenagers and adults that wanted to play it, it was a little bit too much of a kid game.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the original's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a bad game by any means, especially considering how cheap you can find it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the sequel, Viva Piata Party Animals, that's bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that wasn't even the same type of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Vivo Pinata, Trouble in Paradise Vivo Pinata, Trouble in Paradise
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, in other news, and this actually specifically goes for folks in Chandler, Arizona, at the McCullough Price House, there's a, I don't know if this is still going on, but it was going on as of the first, but an exhibit that's ancient history of video games, specifically on 70s consoles, and they are all set up to where, first of all, for games that didn't require electricity, like Lincoln Logs.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not a game!
[SPEAKER_01]: Just to, it actually, as it started there, it actually moved on through towards more modern era systems, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just, I guess, to show how video gaming has evolved.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they were having a lot of people bring in their private collections to loan some of their systems in for the project.
[SPEAKER_01]: And basically, sort of like how our Classic Gaming Expo was, if you remember that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to say, it sounds like the museum at Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's exactly what I think it was like, but it even had a full 80s era arcade that had a bunch of games and exhibits set up.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were all on free play.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: If it's still going on, though, if anyone lives in or near Chandler, Arizona, we would definitely appreciate if you would actually go get us some pictures from this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: We like pictures.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd appreciate it if you stole something for me.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember, remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we didn't tell you to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Remember, if you value your soul, don't bother playing the Fairchild Channel F. It sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: So noted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Duly noted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Music Monsters is a new music game developed by publisher Joe Wood.
[SPEAKER_08]: It combines Owen Dunn with Jam Sessions and Band Brothers.
[SPEAKER_08]: and it's kind of neat you have like that could be neat it's it's basically the gameplay is just like owned on there's little circles that you see that appear you have to tap with your stylus but as stuff goes along it's kind of walking you through playing like music on like uh they have like a harpsichord and then it goes to like this weird tripped out guitar thing and as you're playing the game um it will it's kind of like beatmania a little bit almost too where you like you'll play the you know guitar part then you play a keyboard part etc but they have like stuff in there there is um
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe there was a Depeche Mode song in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: The ones I saw in there, also, other than that, Final Countdown, and there was the, was it Pneuma Pneuma or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that the song that the fat kid dances to in that YouTube video?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those were, yeah, in there as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, no word on when that's coming out, though, yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe the, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: Halloween Time, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, also a quote from Teasdale.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've also secured what I can easily say is the best set list I've ever seen in a music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really, sir?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, some of that best set list apparently leaked out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, YG4 TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, gotta love them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except not.
[SPEAKER_02]: In their show X-Play, they were showing a little clip of Rock Band 2 the day it was announced.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you know how to pause your screen at just the right moment, guess what?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see part of the song list.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it includes, let's see, Dream Theater, System of a Down, Red Hot Chili Peppers, Foo Fighters, Kim Wilde, Kids in America.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a DDR song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Motorhead, Cheap Trick, Journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much, Wynn.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Who, Pinball Wizard Sweet!
[SPEAKER_07]: Everlong Fuck yes
[SPEAKER_02]: Rage Against the Machine, The Guess Who, Lenny Kravitz.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be either one because American Woman is the song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Billy Idol, White Wedding.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is badass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alanis Morissette, You Ought to Know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never thought I'd see that in a music game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never thought I'd see her in a video game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jethro Tull.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aqualung.
[SPEAKER_00]: Aqualung.
[SPEAKER_02]: either the Thin Lizzy or Joan Jett version of Bad Reputation Alice in Chains get this, even gets better this is where I start to go, this is too good Soundgarden with Spoonman and get this Jamie, this is the best ever Radiohead?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not quite because you can use your Radiohead download content at least The Go-Go's, we got the beat I think I'm going to take the Alice in Chains with a big grain of salt because the song featured is Man in a Box I don't know how they would censor that
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they censored in the regular game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Journey is there.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's an automatic win.
[SPEAKER_02]: Automatic win!
[SPEAKER_02]: Say no more.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had me at Journey.
[SPEAKER_07]: Proof that flutes do belong in a rock band.
[SPEAKER_01]: Jethro Tull for the win.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_02]: and HitStunInChat says, actually, yeah, I'd play that Alanis Morissette guitar part.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was like her most rockin' song.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be great for a rock band.
[SPEAKER_02]: And DreadlockLord says, are these rock bands?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, some greats in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just can't believe that she wrote that song about Dave Coulier.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Matt says, Rob, what about Like a Prayer?
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I hope not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've never in my life gotten over that Did you see the other one?
[SPEAKER_02]: The other rumored track list or whatever So we've gone from little grain of salt to medium sized grain of salt to now big grain of salt
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this is big grain assault.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was some leaked track lists.
[SPEAKER_08]: First one, I guess, is from some guy named Demp, a commenter on 8-Bit Fix.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he says he's got, I guess, someone that saw it via an email source or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, it's like a fourth-hand hearsay, they said.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's some of the tracks that...
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, Beastie Boys.
[SPEAKER_08]: ACDC, Let There Be Rock, AFI, Alanis Morissette, which you ought to know on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's just read the important ones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beastie Boys, Beck, Blondie, Devo, The Donnas, Duran Duran, Fleetwood Mac.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is too good to be true.
[SPEAKER_02]: If that is the real list...
[SPEAKER_02]: Game Set Match Survivor, Eye of the Tiger
[SPEAKER_08]: Presidents of the USA with Lump.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bon Jovi.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, this is a fanboy list.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's a real one, I am so sold.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I bet you it's only a few more weeks away, E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to announce some stuff about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was also some rumors that there's going to be some additional hardware, optional hardware stuff for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if like effector pedals or something like that that's going to be involved, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Tell Me Baby, Snow, Heyo, Rush
[SPEAKER_02]: Closer to the Heart, and Working Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, The Who.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were going to try to get the entire album, Who's Next, but unfortunately the master recordings weren't all available, so you get something even better.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a best of The Who, and it's a ton of freaking songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing Journey, Baba O'Reilly, Behind Blue Eyes, Eminence Front, Going Mobile, Leaving Here, Real Good Lookin' Boy, Sea and Sand, Who Are You, and live versions of My Generation, Summertime Blues, and Young Man Blues.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for Who fans, you're ready to go with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta ask, where are you from?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, you have more Rock Band news, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: That I do, Mr. Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: As in, we played a bunch of it at my house.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's actually a number of bands that are in talks to do different music games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Frontline Music Label, of course, has Aerosmith.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the other groups in talks are Guns N' Roses and Van Halen, who are wanting to put out music games.
[SPEAKER_01]: and there's also the Eagles and Steely Dan have agreements in the works so we might be seeing quite a number of other really big names but there's actually one group that's never going to do it and that's Led Zeppelin because they don't want anyone to touch the master recordings I think they're just being bitches about it How about you?
[SPEAKER_08]: They're bitches.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_08]: In other news, completely unrelated to Rock Band, Firmware 2.40 for the PlayStation 3 was released last week and immediately pulled back down because there were some issues with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But 2.4, of course, as you may remember, was the one introducing the brand new trophy system, as well as in-game cross-media bar and, you know, custom soundtracks and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, there's obviously a problem, and they're working on fixing it, and hopefully it'll be up again soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: There was some other stuff I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they have some updates already for some of the older games that have come out to add trophies to them, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think right now these trophies don't really mean much to me until I think Home comes out, and then you can actually display them.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, oh, hey guys, we fucked it up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's try again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I saw Scott Rubin was having some issues with 2.4.
[SPEAKER_02]: and we got in chat Rob with 2B says thank god I waited to download it and Zappy says it's fine I've used it since Wednesday so it sounds like the problem is sporadic or what if it's a certain model of PS3s that's having the issues because you know they've had different types they've had you know the ones that can play PS2 games the ones that can play so alright so did you check out the firmware yourself Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry I skipped out for a minute nope not having it?
[SPEAKER_08]: nope
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't really care because I haven't played a game on my PS3 for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think my PS3's been on in like three weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I use it for movies.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the next game that we're getting is the initial D game anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, the trophies that are going to be the big part of 2.4 whenever they get the working version out...
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, there was an earlier statement that every game would actually have trophies in it, but that probably only meant the actual first-party games, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The third-party publishers, some of them say they're not going to go back and put trophies in the games because they've moved on to bigger and better things.
[SPEAKER_02]: For instance, Insomniac, one of the bigger developers, they are focusing on Resistance 2, which I guess that would actually be a first-party, because Insomniac developed the game for Sony, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are focusing on Resistance 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are not going to be putting trophies in Resistance or Ratchet & Clank Future.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is not their biggest priority right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt says, the trophies are a lie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And by the way, also adding to the list, Call of Duty 4, Civilization Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not right now for trophies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless they're yanking our chain, which is possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: But I somehow doubt it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Out of curiosity, you guys here in studio, what do you think about trophies?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it something needed or is it just like whatever or what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of neat, but I haven't even really figured out what all that means.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know there's different trophies you can get.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are different bronze, silver, gold, and platinum.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know what any of it means yet because I haven't played a game that uses them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_00]: Upload since they're shiny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe when Home comes out, who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Resistance 2 I'm definitely going to buy, but... Xenocore has a good point in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ratchet and Clank has its own trophy system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't need the ones on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru says, trophies like achievements are meh.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Tigerclaw says, geez, just when we have to deal with achievement whores, now we've got to deal with trophy whores.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait until those houses open up in Home.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's when you're going to see the trophy whores.
[SPEAKER_07]: My Billy has gotten all these trophies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but you've still got no life, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: 50 points.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Ristar, which is a platform game that was done by Sonic Team.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you play it, you will notice quite a number of similarities to the Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Quite a number of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it is... It's this little star who runs around, and he can move across bars and things, like monkey bar-type hanging bars.
[SPEAKER_01]: and jump over things and shoot things well land on things really to kill them they're in a way but you go through different planets trying to to see you know trying to get through to I guess rescue the star goddess and I apologize guys for some reason we don't have the music tonight I don't know what is causing I may have to close Justin TV to do that but we don't have music tonight and I don't know why
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: This was an unlock in one of the Sonic collections?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was in the Sonic Mega Collection Plus on PC.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: And had a Game Gear release, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's available on the Sega Genesis Collection for PS2 and PSP, and also available on the Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_01]: But as you go through the game, your health is actually registered in...
[SPEAKER_01]: Starz, and each hit is one star.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is that good?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's the little theme song, because sadly, Rystar wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you also, as you gain momentum in running, you get sparks of stars that go behind you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Shooting Star.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so you can fly in different directions.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's a pretty neat little game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It had some differences from the Japanese and English versions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Planets had different names in the English version.
[SPEAKER_01]: The English one, in the Japanese one, he ran around with a very happy face the whole time except during a boss battle.
[SPEAKER_01]: And in the American one, they gave him the angry face the entire time that he had during the boss battles.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was also a skiing sequence that was added to level 5 in the US one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ito Mori was a giant cat in the Japanese version with a change for an ice monster.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's anti-gravity shoes in round 6.
[SPEAKER_01]: Different treasure names.
[SPEAKER_01]: The European version of Ristar actually took advantage of larger resolutions that were available on PAL systems.
[SPEAKER_01]: And actually the third game on the Game Gear version is if you play the Japanese version on an American Game Gear, the third stage is missing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just vanished.
[SPEAKER_02]: Went away.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, if you play Burning Street that was on Genesis, if you put your Japanese cartridge into a US system, either by a converter or whatever, it changes the street to Rage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was put out by Acclaim.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: It got a 9.5 by GameSpot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rystar is your classic game of the week, and you can check that out on just about any Sonic Mega Collection that's out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sonic Team!
[SPEAKER_02]: GameGuru is clarifying Rystar was available on all the Sonic Mega Collections, GameCube, PlayStation 2, and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's out there, waiting for you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a Sonic Team game, it may as well be Sonic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sadly, it's the only way you're going to hear the music, thanks to our failure this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go on and find it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to mention there was another game that they had gameplay footage of come out this week and that would be Wario Land Shake It.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what's funny is that game looks very much like Sonic.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, that's going to do it here for Part A of Orange Lounge Radio, but we will be back with plenty more, and we've got some fun stuff planned for Part B. We're going to play the match game tonight with all these people in the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know that's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: One chatter and one caller will get to go head-to-head in the OLR match game, and plenty more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: We haven't even touched barely the Xbox 360 and some other stuff, but we'll get to all that when we come back after this break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio