If there's one downside to an unexpected and massive spike in success, it's that
when things go back to normal it can look worse by comparison.
That quote this week applies to Nintendo whose 2021 looks quote unquote worse year over year
because Animal Crossing, the third biggest selling game last year has no equal for Nintendo
so far this year.
A completely obvious quote and yet rarely considered when it matters.
It's time for your hosts Rob Roberts, Jamie Sommers and Loki to bring you everything
but the numbers and a few of the numbers in the rest of the week's gaming news.
Starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet welcome back you should fake the audio down
there before I start that hello again my friends out there on the internet and welcome back
to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice it is Orange Lounge Radio and
we are live once again with episode number 879 of our show for this August the 8th of
2021 my name is Rob Roberts and I am joined remotely by my co-hosts say hello first and
foremost to Dark Sakura or Jamie Sommers oh hi hi how are you doing I am doing okay I
am I just found a bunch of interesting usernames that I had saved and my new favorite one is
Elliott phone home oh and this is all like dead by daylight stuff right yeah I have like
a thing in my discord that's all like the best dbd usernames just because some people
are really funny yeah there was a really jerk face Ash last night who went by Jolene and
I started singing the song on stream while I was hunting him and I thought it was pretty
funny my username and dbd right now is very very clever it's witty dbd name is my name
so very very witty very clever is that very is that worthy of your archive um once I get
a screenshot of it sure okay sounds good one day we'll go up again just post it yourself
you're in my discord true true all right uh also say hello welcome back this week to techmaster
Loki hello hi Loki how are you doing I'm doing good good good um I hope you had a good week
off it was one of the kids birthdays right yeah as my son Josh's birthday so we went
out to a Brazilian barbecue with him oh that would be fun the bed now wait a minute was that
a present for him or a present for you it's a little column a little column b yeah I see I see
all right uh well he wanted to go to lazy dog instead I was like this is much better but he
had a good time all right good good all right um so uh I'm glad he's 11 now right he is yeah we did
his actual like uh birthday party with his friends yesterday so oh my gosh time flies that's that's
crazy but he's he's he's kind of grown up to be a little gamer just like you right he plays a lot of
like Minecraft and all that stuff I mean you talk about that a little bit on the show he's doing all
the prickly roadblocks roblox all roadblocks yeah does he create in roblox because I know he was
going to um those coding classes um pre-covid he went he went well he he did actually go to
a summer camp not that long ago like I think sometime in July um to learn how to make levels
and uh worlds and roblox I don't think he does anything with it he just basically plays I don't
they play a lot of this thing called Brookhaven which is kind of like a roleplay game mm-hmm but
not like a traditional roleplay game it's like I'm gonna pretend to be a high school student you
know type of thing or um I don't know my son just my my younger son keeps talking about it all the
time he watches this guy um omg I guess who's on youtube that there's like lore in the game
about this agency or something I don't know so they they kind of go between that and there's
this other ninja game that they play it's kind of like a it's not a clicker game per se but it's
it's like that set up you know where you grind something and then you can you kind of prestige
or whatever and you get more you know bonuses towards earning in-game money and stuff like that
see I remember Becky's son was into this pirate 101 mmo for kids I that and that's different than
puzzle pirates which I think we all played at one point or another I actually didn't play puzzle
pirates oh you didn't I thought you did at one point nope okay I thought about it and never did
like I am with many a game it's it's interesting though to hear how like 11 year olds are are you
know exploring through things like um you know the pirate 101 or uh roblox or minecraft or whatever
because here comes uncle roberts back in my day I don't know about you guys but we had neo pets
and Gaia online we didn't even have that shit I'm talking about when like I was 11 and 12 we didn't
have any of that shit on Commodore 64 you know we had we had pen and paper and so we would draw
our little dungeons on the pen and paper complete with like the item store that you could shop at
beforehand and we would draw I know some of you kids did this too that like you draw out the thing
and like your little like here's where you start here's the final boss here's the pit of something
and whatever and then it's it's basically dnd without dice and like your own house rules it's
basically that that's that's what we did without roblox has we used to use the study lab though
this is when I was a senior in high school my friend Ashley and I would make up our own rpg
and then we would just spend an hour role playing um now I will say uh when I was around 13 in
junior high and I guess I would be like 12 we did play scorched earth on lunch break in the science
lab like the science teacher loved it he let us come in there and take over the computers like as
long as like he he would kind of like walk around and just make sure we weren't like looking at porn
or something or you know whatever but like when he saw that we were just nerds shooting each other
with tanks he was like all right these kids are fine these kids are gonna be okay and look at me
now look at you little did he know I'd actually love to see how that guy's doing he was he was
Mr Abe if you're out there give me a holler you never know you know what's funny is that after
I graduated high school I actually in the phone book looked up my french teacher to wish her a
pleasant Bastille day you know my my one of my favorite teachers ever was one of my math teachers
in junior high school and my mom ran into her at the mall right before it's probably about a year
before my mom passed she ran into her at the the mall out in Roseville and I guess they had like
they she recognized the teacher and they had a pleasant conversation and I remember right when
I graduated high school she had had a baby and my mom was like she had a teenage daughter with her
and I was like that baby grew up well I stayed in contact with my favorite teacher after I
graduated and we were friends on Facebook and chatted for a while and she sadly passed away
a couple of years ago yeah that's hard to hear yeah but she was almost another mother to me
yeah and I bawled when I found out but she was an absolute angel of a human being
and was one of those teachers that truly cared about her students on a different level you know
what I mean mm-hmm I hear you like she invested well it was also the gifted classes but you know
so she didn't have like a whole lot of us at a time but she really invested a lot of effort into
us and and so hats off to the teachers out there in the OLR crowd hats off to you those of you that
are out there making a difference thank thank you for what you do unless you're mean to the kids
but I don't think any of you are I really don't unless you're my sixth grade algebra teacher where
you're kind of cool dude but you're also kind of a dick or my high school biology teacher who is
who is not a pleasant person but you know what we're not gonna let one bad egg ruin the entire
you know whatever whatever analogy I was going for though we don't let one ruin it for the the
99 of the great ones the coach Milne was really cool he was my chemistry teacher and I'm friends
with his son love that well someone's also um like a year behind me in school and now he's living in
Hawaii and has been on like a few tv shows all right I gotta say I gotta say hello to the chat
hi guys because we do yeah them we do tape live of course every Sunday night at six o'clock pacific
nine o'clock eastern right after the bobby blockwolf show at vog network or the voice of
geeks network twitch.tv slash vog network you know I noticed um earlier in chat we had a few people
um yyr was saying I really want to play ridge racer six now and mike deft is saying I just
noticed the game on loki's background love me some ridge racer so of course for those on the podcast
you don't see the backgrounds on the the little maka's discord call we have here going on but uh
loki what made you pick ridge racer tonight so I could say it's ridge racer ridge racer yeah
no I I really liked ridge racer six and I'm still waiting for them to put out another one
yeah I know there was ridge racer seven it was basically ridge racer six just on playstation
three um and we don't we don't think we don't ever think about or even acknowledge ridge racer
on the vita um the ridge racer god I don't remember which team did that one but there was
that um the one that wasn't ridge racer but it was done by I think the um I can't remember I have it
there was the ridge racer 3ds too unleashed or something like that yeah well the 3ds one was
pretty good too um so there's an I think unleashed or something like that which was supposed to be
pretty cool like a track editor and stuff like that nothing is our for that that's like it's
it's all right um but yeah we need a new ridge racer game like a ridge racer game on playstation
five or like the xbox series xbox looks so amazing like come on like do it namco do it I agree where
where the hell is ridge racer been like it's I I know it got memed a little bit but people love
that series it's like years ago how long ago was it it's like that's 15 years ago from this point
like come on heck yeah all right and uh yeah shout out we have a lot of people in chat tonight it
seems like I guess the olympics end and people show back up again no I love like great to see
you guys again and uh I I'll acknowledge no one special 77 is saying they're good news out of the
physical rehab facility sometimes this week that is great news congratulations so glad to hear that
all right um let's get into our kickoff topic tonight and uh talk a little bit about a big huge
monumental event in gaming news and you know this is a topic that I must have picked because I want
to talk about ariana grande that's right here of course you do here on this podcast about the
video games about our favorite video games things like dead by daylight final fantasy minecraft you
name it I want to talk about who ariana grande come on y'all we love to see it she is even if
I don't like all of her music she is pretty awesome I love the dark soccer she's like
bitch you don't need an excuse let's go right no
all right why why am I sippy sippy in her honor why am I bringing up ariana grande
on the show tonight y'all because you have no tears left to cry that's that's right
I'm taking the positions that this is now an ariana grande podcast
all right um and literally nobody in chat is trying to jump in with an answer there
although sia tabiri says the girl who played penny in hairspray live yes that is true
uh sia tabiri also says the other one from rain on me yes good answer thank you it's flea ding ding
ding gold star you get a gold star for the correct answer because of fortnight yes okay so there's an
ariana grande cross fortnight thing going on so you can actually yeah we talked about it on the
show we did we did we talked about the skin on the show last week yes and how it's unfortunate
that she doesn't say yeah every time that the pickaxe is used but there was an upcoming concert
that was scheduled in fortnight right that is the news this week i wanted to talk about that concert
in fortnight um i did not go in the actual game but thanks to the magic of everybody streaming
everything on twitch now and youtube and things like that i was able to consume the content that
way and i'm gonna tell you guys it was not what i expected whatsoever has anybody ever gone to a
concert in a video game like i know fantasy star online has done them a couple times um i feel
like other mmos like maybe uh like uh warcraft even did them but i feel like i went to a tour
and chieftain thing in warcraft back in the day i'm talking back in ragnarok we used to harass like
a a bard or the dancers yeah yeah oh yeah the mock concerts like in uh that that happened in
ever quest that you're ragnarok every game that had bar now it's huge in final fantasy 14 yes
and usually that involves a bunch of characters up on a stage and like everybody is kind of down
below just kind of role-playing right in fact i was um i was actually playing 14 with um shane
last night and i was telling him about this and how i thought it was very interesting and he was
kind of like have you ever gone to the thing in fantasy star online because it's just they're up
on a stage and you're down below it's not that interesting and i think that's what many people
thought this was going to be in fortnite and i'm here to tell the other concerts that they've had
there have been like that i'm here to tell you something changed here i don't know if it's
because of of the power that ariana grande has the impact the uh the numbers the cultural iconery
of ariana grande or what it is but it was not that in fact i found the concert experience to
be kind of an artistic experience and it's something very interesting for video games
and that's why i wanted to bring it up so what happened the concert was only about 12 minutes
um obviously i can't show it to you here because some of the audio would get into dmca issues and
i don't even know the visuals might but so just and plus we're a podcast anyway i don't want the
folks listening on the podcast feed to feel left out so i would encourage you go look up you know
a video of what was going on with this thing and basically what happened there was a whole like um
it was like kind of like an experience type of thing your car so it's all run in the fortnite
engine but your characters get teleported to these scenes that kind of go with some of the
different songs that are playing like before ariana comes out there's one where you're kind of
like bouncing around on some different flowers you know in the scene or whatever and then there's
another one where you go into a mini game where you're like shooting planes and stuff like that
and you're like on the plane and then everybody kind of like crashes i don't know and you have
to like revive people and that's when ariana comes out and she she also is like kind of like revived
and she starts singing um yeah players are strapped into planes and then there was a whole sequence
where there was a what they're calling mc escher kind of like stairs and pillars where um she's
kind of slowly walking up the stairs and she has this big hammer and she's singing one of her
songs she's actually singing the duet she did with um mac miller who passed away um a few years ago
and obviously that was very you know tragic for for her um and a lot of people saw that as a
tribute to him like she was climbing up a stairway to like heaven or something to like i don't know
knock on the door or however you want to interpret that the point is this was a very she just went
from zeppelin to dylan this it was a very artistic thing and you know if we're going to continue this
conversation about video games or art i'm here to say i'm just as shocked as anyone else honestly
that fortnite and ariana grande brought us this very artistic kind of really neat thing this past
week i need to find this on youtube or something you really should it and it and again i stress
it has yes the ariana grande skin is in fortnite and you can go play fortnite with that this thing
was none of that this this had nothing to do with fortnite except for the fact that it was
running in the same engine and therefore we had a lot of the same emotes a lot of the same ways to
move around and things like that but it was not a you know one versus 100 type of thing so um
it's really interesting i i i'm curious did anybody in chat actually check this out or see it
and did you kind of take away the same impression i did that like this could be this this is a
really interesting direction for fortnite because i know we've heard in the past like within the
past couple months right like fortnite and i think a lot of this might have come with the epic and
apple thing or whatever whatever whatever we've heard a lot from epic the past few months but i
feel like epic has talked a lot about how they don't see themselves as a game as much as they
see themselves as like a pop culture or a pop and we we were all kind of sitting here going what
it's it's a fucking game it's fortnite like don't like you're not taking yourself like
just accept what you are fortnite and now that i've seen this i'm kind of like oh
i see where they might be trying to go with this like fortnite is the canvas upon which this event
was sort of drawn honestly so um let's see sg100 matt says i didn't and i kind of want to watch the
video for it now yeah check it out it was only like honestly when all said and done it was only
like 14 minutes start to finish like it's not a long concert in the traditional sense it really
felt more like an interactive music video quite honestly because i don't think she was performing
it live or anything like that it really just sounded like it was the studio recordings to
be honest um tiger claw on chat says fortnite is more like a game that's a service i think
yeah that's probably a big part of it as well um let's see uh tryna see uh up in chat as well
interesting sg100 matt says fortnite is more mtv than mtv this is like kind of revolutionary in
terms of music video type of sphere that's what i'm saying that's why this thing kind of took me
by surprise i wasn't expecting it i was expecting ariana grande up on the stage doing some twirls
singing you know maybe either a new recording or something of some of her greatest hits
and then you know but spend twenty dollars on my dlc thank you bye thank you next you know that's
that's it but it wasn't that at all um yeah let's see uh and yyr of course is bringing up the music
game related news here yes ariana grande is also related to the music games and ddr uh ariana
grande was in ddr except break free was cut from ddr last month after being in the game for five
years whoops the licensing ran out that's no fun now that uh now that the game is mandatory to be
online um bobby blackwolf in chat says i've seen some of these music video experiences in the past
but none have been as big as this the chain smokers did a psvr experience for one of their
new singles yeah i saw a psvr thing for i think it was utada hikaru uh they did something for
uh kingdom hearts it was like a live studio show where they were singing um one of the kingdom
heart songs and you could look at it in vr um and i've also seen the literal vr music videos like
i think it was bjork did a vr music video or it was like a youtube 360 like really close type of
thing so it's yeah there have been those experiences but still there was this this felt different than
any of that um is that it really just felt like it was an entire it kind of you know what it it
actually reminds me of i'm gonna throw it way back do you remember on the old school computers
especially the commodore 64 but i'm sure this was done a little bit on apple 2e's and stuff too but
especially the commodore 64 because of the sound chip and the particular unique sound and music
that that did do you remember the demo scene and the demos that would come out bobby i know you're
gonna light up with this i know that was that was your scene when you were younger that's what this
ariana thing reminded me of is that and those those um demo things would be like a like a song
might play and you would see like a it would like push the graphic chips to do something on the
screen and then like maybe a different part of the song it switches a little bit go look up like an
old school like happy holidays commodore 64 compilation or something to see like what
you know it's so show different scenes of the holidays what would play different like um
christmas carols and things like that uh bobby says really it was about the amiga for the demo
scene that's right the amiga really stepped that up even more and bobby points out of course the
pc demos yes that was still a thing even in the 90s and um i think that name is showing up black
on black yes it's jason hi it's our voiceover man jason saying demo scene is still very much alive
as niche as it ever was honest and i i hope nobody hates me for this comment because it's actually
meant to be a compliment the ariana grande concert felt like a mainstream demo scene project
honestly it's honestly what it felt like to me so um jason it might be the way things are set up
on my computer your name is black and it's just i'm on night mode over here so it's coming up on
a black background i wouldn't worry too much about it um let's see zen monkey 11 in chat says i go to
concerts in alt space vr they have holograms in there so you see the real artist in vr in
front of you not on a screen zara larson did a roblox mini concert the metaverse is real and
it's here i'm all for it saw the ariana concert inside of fortnite i try to experience them all
it's cool yeah now that i've seen this one like if another artist does one that i that i like or even
like kind of like like like for i i'm kind of into little nos x right now because i think i
i love how he's pushing people's buttons right now and the music videos and stuff you know it's like
fortnite is more playstation home than playstation home is you know because it could be like this is
like kind of you know you have this world that exists that you put stuff into it like these
different media pieces and stuff whereas if sony were smart they would bring that playstation home
but since they haven't um you have these types of venues now where artists can you can have
different crossovers with artists and properties and all sorts of licensing i didn't even think
about that but you're you're you're you're right on that um cia tabirian chat says i mean i know
there were some stand-up comedians who were doing comedy shows and animal crossing well yeah i mean
especially especially because of the nature of the pandemic and animal crossing really hitting at the
right time i mean the kk concerts are a staple of animal crossing now you know obviously i still
miss him though doing his thing in the um you know in the coffee shop because we need the coffee shop
back yes we do you put that side by side with the ariana thing and it looks a little sad but
i mean it's it's it's still it is what it is for that game and it was kind of like
it warped you out of the traditional world and had that credit sequence you know as basic as
it is it was still something kind of interesting and different um jason our voiceover guy is uh
continuing with a comment about way back in the day beastie boys did a live internet concert back
in the 90s i'm talking like real video era quality and it was just a single camera angle with audio
of course yeah yeah that's that's like a streamed concert type of thing and honestly again i think
that's what a lot of us expected from this but it really was different um you have low-key
playstations missing out from not rebooting home but at the same time playstations really trying
to push itself is like the place you want to be playing fortnite even though fortnite is available
literally everywhere else except you know that that little spat epic has going on right now but
we're gonna we're gonna overlook that it's available a variety of different places than
just in most places most places yes so um st100 matt says i don't think playstation home had
concerts but i feel like there was a watch a long or listen along communities i kind of remember
there was watch longs in the olr house in home but then sony updated the game where no media
could be played at home yeah there was a lot of potential in home that really went unrealized
like i feel like just when home was kind of like finding its rhythm and where it could belong and
really blossom somebody just pulled the plug and like on on like the development front it was like
no we're not spending another dime on trying to make this better or trying to establish some of
the copyright issues or things like that like i really think they just they really yanked that and
now fortnite even though fortnite doesn't really feel like home to me but i i i get that comparison
i get why you're saying that um zeba in chat says synth riders oh yeah that vr game you brought up
in the email has three experience songs that you are inside a vr version of the music video of the
artist much like in the background of ddr oh that sounds neat that sounds kind of interesting it's
different way to do it uh and bonds 006 says i would go back into home i i would absolutely
give home a second chance i'm really surprised they didn't bring it back with the vr i thought
for sure that was something they were gonna do was try to take on the vr chat second life type
of angle but for whatever reason they didn't so um interesting yeah as jonah matt says ps home was
both the butt end of jokes at its time and also way ahead of its time there's things like that
in gaming um that just one versus 100 on xbox i'll say that i'll say that until you pull the plug on
this show that thing was way ahead of its time hell even the things that preceded it and the
berkeley uh games online like acrophobia and stuff like that that was you know that was huge
anyway so we'll see what had any any artists that you would want to see in fortnite with an
interactive visual experience you know i have to ask this what artist do you want to see in
fortnite with an interactive visual experience i feel like i don't listen to a lot of like modern
music so i i i'm going back to what i said earlier like a little nos x because he's really pushing
the buttons with things right now i'd like to see somebody who's kind of known for reinventions
like maybe madonna i'd be very curious um and uh if it's in fortnite she wouldn't need her walker
just kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding come on all right anyway
uh oh gaga of course who who wouldn't who wouldn't go to a gaga concert even this even the straight
people would want to see a gaga concert in fortnite because she's a heck of a performer
that would be really great uh any any oh oh i like that answer sg100 matt says daft punk
but they're broken up and i feel like they did one over already well hell if they ever reunited
that would be a heck of a thing to do that's for sure any any thoughts on on a fortnite experience
dark soccer or loki yeah i have two widely different things okay go for it oh well good
okay go would be interesting because they do like their uh seamless videos and stuff it's pretty
interesting makes it a completely separate side of the spectrum death lock
all right i i'm all for a guar concert in fortnite let's see that happen
dark dark soccer how about you i want a gorillas one gorillas of course oh god the bands that are
kind of technically inclined to begin with that makes a lot of exactly that are animated to begin
with yeah yeah absolutely why i kind of you know why i say tech inclined because there's a lot of
tech that goes into the concerts and stuff like that that's a great answer um Hatsune Miku why not
also that i think has been done you're right i think that has been done uh bobby bobby blackwolf
says the tupac hologram in fortnite which was similar i think that could be dangerous
um orange right says a weirdo concert fuck yes oh you know weirdo would do it hell yes i love it
all right win-win all right let's move on since my co-host did not attend the concert in fortnite
but to be fair neither did i i watched it uh i watched a wrap-up summary just because i was
curious and everybody on social media was saying it was great and i was like i have to see what
was so great about it and then i watched it i was like oh this is not what i was expecting at all
so um we were playing video games and too busy not to go to virtual concerts so what kind of
video games have you been playing this week we'll start with dark sakura how was your gaming week
i played dead by daylight of course you did you played you were playing i beat
phantasian you were playing at one in the morning this morning dead by day well because my um
my stream time for uh i actually go live at midnight now after such this early sunday and uh
i mean i just play until like maybe 2 33 in the morning um i had some good people in last night
actually got a raid like right before i was about to sign off i don't know why happens it
i'm on my last game and people raid me and it's all good it's always happens to me too
so i played another round that i didn't do as great in but i made rank 13 last night which
for me is a big deal because i always feel like i completely suck at the game but i'm pretty okay
with pig so i like pig i think you it is you i was just gonna say you called it out on your stream
when i was watching it's it's it's the fact that you have to kind of use a trackball i think kind
of like you're not able to be as fluid as some in some motions or at least you're working up to that
still and i think once that kind of gets a little more and i think you're only your pig game i
watched last night games actually were way improved from what i'd seen back in the when
you first started so i mean i was whipping stuff but i was also super super tired when i was
playing but um i figured out my way of countering you know the upfront 360 and i don't know if you
noticed that i was doing this but i would chase get close and stop because at the point that i
know that 360 is about to happen they will just turn and run right into me because i stopped
that's like a nurse that teleports like they start their teleport and then as soon as the
survivor runs around they teleport into the ground so that they don't actually move forward
it's kind of a similar thing yeah i i did actually get the idea from watching lc
and our uh our everyone's favorite you know nurse one trick but uh i got the idea watching and then
i was thinking i can't turn that quickly with the trackball but why don't i just stop i've never
seen anyone do that except playing nurse so i was like why don't i just stop i think that's
clever i think the more you find those workarounds that are unexpected the more you're going to see
the rewards that come from that yeah no one expects you to stop like i actually got a
compliment on it from a jake player the other day um it was one of my uh offline games and
he was he was like you're the first killer i've ever seen just stop and let me run into you
and i was like well i have to use a thumb trackball because i have bad wrists we were
just chatting about it and he's like also are you a microsoft star like no i'm on stadia because i
play on a mac and so we got into a little discussion about it and like in that match
like he was like rake four and we started talking about it and he just flat out said hey i'm gonna
i'm gonna borrow this idea for my killer games there you go i was like cool i'm glad i'm glad
to be of service but um and i've actually started talking through like some of my thought processes
while i play and why i do the things that i do and talking it out and getting advice from people in
my chat really i think helped me do better and i've also had my builds look at looked at by
a few players that i trust so i've gotten some really good advice and i want to actually give
a thank you to to lc to hydro to nick and prince uh a few people out there who's given uh laurie
bird gave me really good advice on my builds nice and i'm also playing wordscapes because i'm a word
nerd a word nerd all right loki how was your gaming week or weeks as it is uh well it was
all minecraft um so it was i don't know it was a lot of just like kind of grinding to get stuff
done and um i was doing a lot of i was cutting some videos together so like i did a tutorial
video i think last week maybe it was this week i don't know everything's starting to blend together
um so i did tutorial video to try to drive some more views to my channel so i put that out and
and that was pretty successful because there was um it was all about timing because there was an
episode that bdubs had done on hermitcraft where he did a two in one like stone generator and i'm
like i bet i can make that three in one stone generator because um it should be pretty easy
to add uh basalt to it so i did i i put out a design that's based sort of like on his not
exactly the way he did it but like a similar looking design and added that in there so i was
trying to help you know promote myself that way so that it's it's got okay views i mean so it
you know it's working there and then i'm working on my latest episode um pretty soon so in that one
i built this because we have issues on our servers still with mob spawns it's an issue with the
software server runs it's not vanilla minecraft it's like paper which is like a sort of modded
server um it fixes some bugs it also introduces new bugs and so because of that there's a bug
with uh mobs spawning correctly so if i'm on the server by myself or i'm on the server with
somebody else and they're in another dimension for me there's no mobs spawning whatsoever in my
farm so it makes it really hard to run shops on our server and so i had to create a a cash for
gold store to get people to sell me gold so i can use it in my gold farm um and so that was
a fun build i made it look like a rundown you know strip mall store so um so that'll be my new video
and then um yeah so it's been just a lot of that a lot of this week just kind of um
i don't know i don't even know what i've been working on i think a lot of it's just been afk
in in the server oh and then also working on other projects for people on the server as well so
there's some other things um tied with that but i'm trying to get more on track to put out stuff
in a regular basis i mean i have been putting up videos about once a week but it's not my normal
smp let's play stuff it's been kind of you know here and there so still trying to get that down
faster but making progress all right well best of luck on the youtube front make sure make sure
y'all are following loki on youtube at loki olr on youtube yep all right uh my gaming week honestly
i've been playing mostly a lot of the same stuff i've been talking about in previous weeks on the
show uh myself i'm still you know uh moving along in dead by daylight i did a random stream on my
own channel on friday that was that was fun except uh jamie you've expressed this too like when when
the camera's on i have all bad games and then when the camera's off is when i have my good games
although i did i had my one trick bill game um because i had a daily that i had to like get an
item and escape as bill well bill was like level one so i ran i ran i was like screw it let's do
i ran a game with uh bill with one talent uh borrowed time and oh billiam i did it i i i
opened the exit door and escaped that was not the item and escape it was the exit door to scare i
opened the exit door and escaped so uh yeah and it was funny because when that happened it was
pod culture somebody started spamming that icon from your channel with the the bill with the slash
through it i'm like hey you mean the one that i'm doing right now yes in chat so yeah there's that
um i was playing some fun fast c14 last night uh yakuza like a dragon i kind of hit a wall
uh those of you that played the game i hit that three million yen wall you all know what i'm
talking about um and uh so it's it slowed me down a little bit but i am gonna try to uh pick that
up because i'm too close to finishing it and too invested in the story to not finish it um
i also just some random new stuff was showing up on game pass i was like oh i want to play that
again so for example luminous is on game pass now i love luminous i know it's so good it's the
remastered version of the original so it has shine in which is like you know the best one of the best
songs i've ever had in that game you mean the best song what well there was a holla back girl
and luminous too let's not get crazy all right here's the thing that pissed me off though you
know how you have to get to level 100 to um basically beat the normal i got to level 94
it took me an hour to get there and then i choked i was so mad but i'll just have to play it again
um katamari damashi reroll is also on game pass i downloaded it but i haven't played that yet so
that's all i can really say about that right now but here's the new thing i want to talk about that
i actually tried this week um that is kind of interesting so i out of the blue got a message
on my xbox inbox that said you're invited to test out the xcloud service at xbox.com slash play
so uh i did and i'm giving you that url because it's uh it's pretty one easy one to remember and
maybe you have it you don't know it so check it out um and so i went to um check it out and it's
based it is their cloud-based service it's basically their stadia okay but it's it's in
the xbox environment um and if you have game pass then you can just fire up any of the game pass
games on there otherwise you can fire up um things that i i think i think it might only be
game pass games but i can't remember if it's things that you own in the cloud but it's only
certain games that have the permission which i think mostly overlaps with um uh uh game pass
uh mike defton chat says uh welcome to the xcloud gang rob i barely use it i had to try it out i
wanted to see so the first game i played of course was no man's sky because i feel like that is a
good benchmark game for me a i've played a fucking lot of it b i've played it on pretty much every
platform no i i i'm not i've played it playstation 4 playstation vr xbox 360 xbox one xbox series i'm
sorry not the 360 what am i saying the xbox one the xbox series x uh steam i've played that game
a lot of different places um i played that on the invidious thing too so i played it on xcloud a
little bit um and it was i would say it was um it was fine but i think stadia might be a little more
responsive i think the technology might be a little bit crisper on stadia i don't know if
it's just that they've had more time to perfect it or whatever the case is um but um i it wasn't
bad by any means it's just i would notice the artifacting a little more and especially when i
was turning in these heavily graphical areas like my game save was on the um the anomaly which is a
pretty graphically intensive area i could notice like it did seem to lag a little bit so um but but
it wasn't like it didn't make the game unplayable by any means but i i think for that particular
game i would just continue to play my xbox series x version why wouldn't i but the other game i
played i played doom the 2016 reboot um and again i did notice some of the stuff with the artifacting
and maybe some of the colors weren't quite as vibrant but i did definitely notice it was
streaming 60 frames a second and it was smooth and especially a game like that doom which is
very fast pace like it actually went a little bit through the first level to kind of get a feel for
it and i was kind of like this does play really well for like a cloud-based thing so although i
would say in my evaluation this the stadia technology was a little bit ahead of where
xbox was at i still think it's really exciting it's not bad by any means and i think where this
is really going to shine is being able to test games before you spend like 80 gigs downloading
them because you know that doom reboot is like a 40 gig downloader maybe 50 i don't even more
well why not stream a little bit and sure streaming is going to take up bandwidth too
but streaming for 15 30 minutes is only going to be it's not going to be a like even a gig
you know to test the game a little bit out and see what you think about it and then make a decision
from there and i think it's also great for these things where it's like uh sometimes in the xbox
rewards it's like you need to get an achievement in one of these 10 games and i'm like i don't want
to download one of those 10 games now i could just do it through the cloud gaming so i'm really
excited too to see what happens when the cloud gaming hits the actual xbox series x i think
that will be very very interesting um as 100 matt says i also got that invite as well i look forward
to trying it out at some point yeah why not try it out you got it um especially if you have game
pass you just are going to have all those games already ready to try out so why not um i have not
tried it on my phone yet it is supposed to work in safari or um uh google chrome or whatever
depending on what what you got uh it but i just haven't tried it on my phone yet um let's see
uh jason and chad says 80 gigs ha call of duty has already eclipsed 200 call of duty was not
one of the games um grant that no i don't think grant that on five was in the cloud
no uh i don't i don't think so i thought i saw streaming yeah um paitlin hanumea says i got two
platinums in no man's sky one for playstation 4 and when i installed it on playstation 5 it gave
me a second yeah a lot of people are having that interesting over that flight simulator on there
no which surprise or at least i don't remember seeing it i don't want to definitively say that
i didn't notice it um i mean that would be worth it because that downloads probably yes it's a huge
download but i also think see flight simulator is one of those where i'm like i think it's better
if you download it because the 4k visuals are stunning and until they can uh get the cloud
gaming at 4k uh i think i think it's it's worth the download but that's me um yyr in chat says
omg rob you are a genius i've been downloading extra games just to finish those damn weekly class
quests launching them via xcloud is so much smarter thank you ego inflate thank you ego
plus plus you inflated rob's ego it's super effective thanks why we are good luck uh and
bobby says i think exactly um bobby blackwolf says i think flight simulator is coming later
because they're still upgrading x cloud xbox series x right now it's all on xbox one oh that's
a i forgot about that thank you oh i'm very curious to see what happens get the old fight
simulator then like the emulate that old ass one from like the pcs in 1988 we'll do flight
simulator one how about that i think that can that can work right i think i saw a skin in the store
where you could do or maybe that's just for the little computer on the plane i don't remember but
a flight sim and run flight sim in flight sims yeah that sounds fun why not i think the the
crazy thing about flight simulator the some of the shit in the store is why would i ever buy this
there's things where it's like download the improved uh airport in whatever city in germany
for fifteen dollars what i'm gonna say fifteen dollars on fucking airport dlc like i have to be
super serious about my flight sim to spend that kind of money i'm sure there's someone out there
that drops it hey you spent your money on whatever you want but for me i was like what the fuck that
is way too much money for something like that s2100 matt says zaku would get that dlc i don't
even i i need the man to speak for himself i don't even know zaku would get that dlc that's
like some of the planes for a couple extra bucks i get that an airport for that much money no
anyway that was my experience with xcloud i'm looking forward to seeing how it continues
can't wait to stream from my own xbox because apparently that will be a thing that's coming
in the future very exciting um and uh i i will say dead by daylight was a game i almost tested
um but i was kind of like if i'm gonna play dead by daylight on my pc why wouldn't i just play the
steam steam version that i already have on here but it is there all right well you know why i'm
playing on what i am because the steam one yeah yeah but um yeah yeah if they ever i really hope
they get that cross play working across more platforms that would be lovely we'll see all
right we're gonna get back into some more news and uh we'll start it off with oh i guess i should do
some quick housekeeping um right now as actually no i'm i'm confident saying this so there will
not be a show in one two three four weeks uh labor day weekend there will not be a show i will not be
here um right now my agenda has me going to dragon con i'm hearing rumors and rumblings that could be
uh maybe not a thing even if they do not end up having dragon con i'm still taking a vacation
um i've been working way too hard over the past year and a half i deserve a vacation i'm taking
a vacation uh i don't really want to live in the space of negativity so i'm not gonna list out my
different options of what i'm going to do if there isn't a con but i'm thinking about it and there's
lots of ideas right now so we will see but there will not be an olr that week because i'm not going
to be here uh one way or the other so that's that um all right otherwise let's move on we have so
but if there if there is a dragon con and you feel up to coming i i get it's a weird year let
me know if you're gonna be there i have a lot of panels be great to see you all right let's move
on we got a lot of news uh in fact we have this story um again this week but some important
developments on the activision blizzard front loki start us off yeah so blizzard president
j alan brack is stepping down um good no basically uh you know he was one of the two people that were
mentioned by name in the um allegations in the first place so it makes sense that he would do
that since you know there's probably going to be some uh stuff coming out about that so he is
stepping down he's being replaced by um jen o'neill and mike gabara and then also apparently along
with you know all of this kind of all these statements from the company that we're hearing
about how you know oh yeah we're addressing the you know the issues and stuff like that but
coming from the actual employees themselves and not leadership we're hearing that it's actually
not really happening the way that leadership is saying basically saying that um you know
there's no no no comment on paid transparency you ignore our calls to end mandatory arbitration you
didn't commit to adopting inclusive recruitment and hiring practices um so all these solutions
basically that you proposed you're not really addressing any of them or any of the solutions
that they propose so it doesn't sound like change is going to be coming anytime soon
um so we'll just have to see how this all plays out well for what it's worth and i i i want to
just start off by saying i completely agree and support that the employee demands need to be
listened to and they need to be responded to and that needs to happen however i think the first
thing that had to happen for any of this to happen is j alan brock had to go so the first the this
this was the first step it's a step but it's not the finish this not the finish of the last
of the story um we all know he had to go he knew he had to go i guess i don't they don't really
say if he opted into it or they they uh it doesn't really fucking matter honestly he's gone um and
that was the important first step um i think the selections of this the i guess successor temporary
successors is interesting uh mostly because uh mike was with xbox and i know we got a lot of
pr stuff from him out of xbox a lot of quotes because i i always would joke because mike deft
has a very very similar name and so i would always laugh like you know oh act deft at the time you're
in the news again you know talking about xbox um so it's i i the we know that he has a familiarity
certainly with the um pr stuff uh jen she come i think that is very interesting because she comes
from vicarious visions who blizzard just acquired not that long ago so that is very much a sign of
we're willing to take this culture in a different direction because she hasn't been a part of
blizzard's culture as long but i again i think that's a good thing um and obviously vicarious
visions have been doing a lot of things right um so i think i think it's interesting um i don't
i don't know if ultimately it will be one of them or maybe another outside party ends up coming in
to lead a ceo or what but i think it's an interesting um partnership so that's that's for
sure um sj100 matt chat says the svp of hr also left this week which also needed to happen yes
i'd heard about that as well uh yes considering hr all of this happened under hr's watch
absolutely that individual had to go as well so see you later um who's next uh what what
was her name we brought up last week fran town said i'm hoping i got that name oh she needs to
go she's i heard she resigned from that council so like i i don't know that's not resigning from
the company which i think is what we would like to see but we're seeing movement we're seeing
movement yeah oh thank you quest buster thank you francis towns and also stepped down from the abk
women's network but she's still in her executive position for now so we'll see what happens um in
the coming coming days she just needs to absolutely go i didn't know that either sj100 matt says she
deactivated her twitter too well she made some good less garbage on twitter ah so yeah um i i'm
really glad though we are talking about you know we're still kind of putting and i think for those
that um want to support what's happening and i think it's it's very interesting that i think
a lot of people have realized that like a boycott isn't really the path maybe for i mean at the end
of the day you need to do what's comfortable for you and if a boycott's what's comfortable for you
that's fine but i think there's a lot of people that realize there's a lot of great people at
abk that want to continue to support the you know those people the majority of the people who are
really great people um and uh i think the best thing we can all do is continue to uplift these
voices our retweets our reminders that hey just because j alan brack took the fall for a lot of
this stuff doesn't mean that it's over because this poison was uh in a lot of places in the
culture and so a lot of these other things have to change so that this doesn't happen again we
have to continue to uplift that message need to pump their stomach and get rid of all the bile
yes absolutely so uh yeah um i suppose we'll see what happens in the coming weeks i
again don't think this is the last we're going to hear this this is three weeks in a row now
and i i think this is a story we're going to hear about honestly every week until at least
the end of the year so we'll see where this continues to go um anything else on that loki
did we get everything well i was gonna say you know it's good that we're talking about it with
you know activision and stuff but i would hope that we'd also not forget that ubisoft is also
covering up for these types of people as well so i need to put the pressure on everybody
and hey in the ea just because we're not talking about you right now don't think that you're out
of this either because i i'm willing to bet this culture is everywhere we have not forgotten 100
fair call out this culture is everywhere within the tech industry and i know i've said this before
on the show and i'll say it again every company should be evaluating these sorts of things right
now especially in the tech industry you know this this should be the wake-up call every company
needs to find this poison within its culture and as dark sakura said initiate emergency procedures
to get rid of the bile pump the stomach pump the stomach so yeah mike deft is saying riot
so many companies in our chat over twitch.tv slash vog network absolutely so um yeah and a great
call out loki this is ubisoft is not off the hook just because the spotlight's on abk right now
and i think with a lot of these call outs and things you know especially if you if if we don't
see the management really deliver on these promises i think it's going to get us closer
and closer to where we all have thought the employees of the industry have needed to be
for a long time now which is a union or at least and like i said in last week's show
a legal support group is kind of like the first step in that capacity so all right anyhow let's
yeah sj100 matt says yeah i'm still surprised eve's at uh ease come on ubisoft still has a job
yeah me too i'll quite honestly so and bonds 006 says music industry film industry media all of
them absolutely but you know what the music industry and the film industry have at least
unions yeah there's that so anyway since loki brought up ea let's talk about ea but it's
completely different type of topic we're going to talk about boring financial reports but um
kind of something interesting because a lot of companies have been reporting financial results
this week and ea is certainly one of them as well um so obviously what we just talked about has not
been in the news for ea so hopefully internally they are looking at it um it certainly did not
come up on their earnings call at least to my knowledge uh if they said a quick sentence or
two about it it did not cross my radar but what they did talk about i know of was uh their
financial year and and and how things are holding up there so ceo andrew wilson of ea and the report
said it was a strong start to the fiscal year with our incredible teams delivering experiences
that continue to bring hundreds of millions of players together uh our expanding ea sports
portfolio uh apex legends battlefield 2042 and our leading live services were set to deliver
more great games and contents to players this year um what i think is interesting is when the cfo
blake yorgensen uh started to talk a little bit about f1 2021 which was codemasters first release
under ea because you know ea bought codemasters not that long ago so we had kind of the first
release it's and this is a quote from the cfo it's to the testament of an exceptional game
development team that was able to produce the right assets to produce the right marketing
materials to help us drive this business and the team's working together and you know what i think
we don't get enough credit for that ea is a bunch of people who really can work well together and
we do a great job of working with other parts of our company and when we bring in acquisitions we
work well with them i think the poster child is respawn and you look at what's happened with apex
legends this is a team effort and respawn has obviously driven the amazing development of apex
but they've partnered with us extremely well to drive what is now it's coming up to almost
2 billion in business over two years that's unheard of in our industry and i'm not sure
we get enough credit for it well ea there's a reason why you don't often get credit for
acquisitions if i may pandemic visceral games maxis software westwood studios black box games
play fish mythic entertainment bullfrog what do all those studios have in common
ea bought and closed them so that is why ea you don't get a lot of credit when it comes to the
acquisitions and things like that in fact people are kind of wary of you when it comes to that
that is going to be a trust that's going to take you a long time to earn back congratulations on
the success of apex though respawn really did do a great job yes yeah clap hello let's celebrate
that yes apex is a great game what did ea do to do for that okay i guess they they put money to
advertise it a little bit more and maybe you know invest in a little bit fine you get you get you
get a gold piece of um glitter that is that's that's the new award here when you did something
so minuscule fine we'll acknowledge it congrats ea you get the gold piece of glitter for your success
you you did the bare minimum huzzah
thank you for doing what was expected of you but you know who gets the gold star
respawn studios sure you can have a gold star too dark but but respawn really gets the credit there
because again you know look at the stuff that ea still owns and i you know even if i want to be
you know i would say a smart ass but i'm really just speaking the truth when it comes to those
closed studios i would even say look at ea's partnership with clump companies like bioware
um i don't think that's been a great partnership no it hasn't massive Andromeda thinks that has
not been a great partnership in my opinion anyway it's it's been it's been how very uh bonds 006 and
chat says when i hear or cea i expect loot boxes yeah but i mean i guess that's part of where some
of their but essentially they didn't name star wars and any of that stuff in their financials
but i guess that's because it's only related to the news you know in the past few months
and what's really done well for them which of course you would expect you know with the
f1 2021 and so forth uh apex of course is ongoing sure they're gonna um have some announcements of
the things to say there but i just thought that uh that whole thing about you know we should be
celebrated more for what we're doing with acquisitions it's kind of like why don't you
why don't you pull over a little bit here on some of that those comments you know why don't you why
don't you give some of these studios the space they need such as bioware to really make uh
good games when they go on sale day one bug-free experiences then we'll say you're being a good
partner oh also it's not my job to pat you on the back for doing a job you know what i'm giving you
no credit for anything the only credit i'm giving you for is all the terrible things in this
industry that's what you can get credited for ea interesting because one of the worst companies in
the industry bobby blackwolf and chat says and that's where perception is everything ea games
for the past few years haven't had loot boxes yet nobody cares i thought fever still had them
because oh no no no no they they still do they still totally do they have the whole ultimate
team stuff which is loot boxes so yeah they they have had them they just haven't had them in some
games like uh like star wars and um trying to think some of the other ones that they had but
yeah they know the the thing is they make so much money from fifa ultimate team that they don't need
to put like loot boxes and everything they still have it in madden um and there's lots of things
that they kind of fifa just kind of pay for the rest of the company like pretty much at this
point like it's just really like if it wasn't profitable for the company i mean you wouldn't
have people farming this stuff in giant server warehouse you know with all these playstation
fours and stuff like that we just had that last week or the week before i remember that yeah
people thought it was bitcoin so like i mean obviously it's incredibly profitable for them
so like i'm sorry no you're not a little indie studio we're not going to pat you on the back
because you did a good job and like honestly like this last formula one game was probably developed
before he even acquired codemasters so you get no credit for that i'm sorry like just you get
nothing you lose good day sir uh stirlock in chat says fifa ultimate team is so bad there's a
literal black market no i'm not joking yeah the uh the playstation farm we just alluded to a
little bit ago uh as shown under matt says you get a participation award ea to pin on your fridge
now take your jukebox it goes even farther back to that remember when they your account got hacked
because of uh and got stolen and people bought you know fifa ultimate team stuff do i it it's
been it's been years yes i understand that but like this thing has been going on for a long
time like and these these are the guys that wanted you know online passes and stuff like that for
used games like ea is just an evil company i'm sorry i'm not going to ever forgive you for any
of this stuff you're an evil company and you're always going to be an evil company period you
know what though i'd rather these type of evils than the other evils that have been in the news
hate to say it but obviously in a perfect world you know what it's just different shades of the
rainbow okay of evil that's the rainbow of evil all right let's move on i had an x that i would
call the rainbow of evil but we won't go there all right let's move on and the rainbow of evil
dark soccer it's who i think it is you know which of course you know which which x it is
yeah all right moving on that was a choice i don't want to talk about it moving on
uh next story dark saga well something that probably comes as a surprise to nobody and has
less to do with uh companies actually being terrible is uh the intellivision amico the
the console that a lot of people have been like super excited mitigated about
well it's been delayed again um it was originally supposed to come out in october 2020
and then it got pushed back to april 2021 and then fall 2021 and now uh this email went out
to those who pre-ordered and it said that it was delayed further with the pre-orders due to arrive
at the end of 2021 um i got that email yeah because you had yours pre-ordered i sure do
yeah it says uh and i'll just read a little bit of the content the team at intellivision has been
working tirelessly to bring amico our family focused entertainment system to eager households
around the world we've grown to a strong and stable company of more than 60 passionate team
members spanning three continents representing some of the industry's best talent all of us
are extremely excited to share amico with you and going on uh in spite of all these hurdles
hampering our ability to fill to fill all orders we are focused and determined to deliver pre-ordered
units by the end of the year this will all also allow us more time to optimize our operating
system for future game development i'm i'm not mad about it so it's it is what it is it is what
it is and i'm gonna tell you why i'm not mad about it and i'm not and i because it's not a problem
unique to intellivision as a friendly reminder can you walk into target and buy a playstation 5
no no it's been almost a fucking year and you still can't walk into target and get playstation
5 you can't get an xbox series x either or an s you can't walk into target and buy the fucking
console um which is really unheard of in video game history almost a year out so i think that
shows you there's issues there's problems in the supply chain going on nobody can get a fucking
graphics card nobody can get a graphics card without pirating it right now so i'm sorry not
pirating getting really lucky yeah or yeah congrats like honestly buy a lotto ticket if
you got a new graphics card because you've got some real luck right now so like you can't look
at this and say like oh this is an intellivision problem no it's an industry problem did intellivision
maybe set some of their goals a little bit loftier than they should have perhaps but at the
same time nobody could have predicted what was going to happen in 2020 and is still you know
happening as of now so again as much as we we could all dunk on tommy talarico for you know
sometimes the way his ego comes off and all that stuff i just don't think this is the appropriate
place to do that this this is just a symptom of a larger industry problem and that's that's what
it is period um uh bobby blackwolf says look at a new car lot same chip shortage is affecting them
i didn't even think about that but you're right all the chips that go in uh new cars i'm sure
that's pretty uh crazy uh digirama s says rob mid-tier graphic cards are available but they're
double retail prices in stores a 1660 super should not cost 379 4 59 retail um quest buster says
unless amico has the magic ability to build their own fab plants and supply chains they have the
same problems as everyone else yep dr tsuya says exactly everyone loves to kick tommy while he's
down but in this instance i don't think they're entirely at fault here no there's other places if
you want to dunk on tommy you can do it um i just i think there's other things in this industry that
are needing to be dunked on and i think the fact that tommy talarico hypes up his games look we
always have those kinds of people in the industry peter molanu was no different than this is no
different than this and there's other people hello remember uh no man's sky before and look y'all i
fucking stan no man's sky i love that game but was it the game that was hyped up when it came out
we all know the answer to that okay so there are carnival barkers in this industry fine
and i and i've said this on the show before and this is you know what i respect tommy talarico
i think he's a good guy i am very i met my spouse at video games live for the first time in person
there's a lot i'm personally thankful to tommy talarico for putting together and making happen
i still i can say that and still say but the best business advice i would give them give him is that
he should have more visible faces that represent the intellivision amico than just him there needs
to be more visible pr faces than just him um and i've said that on the show before and i'm saying
it again um because not everybody is buying what tommy's selling and ultimately that's going to be
what kicks the system in the butt if they're not careful um yyr says there are some real issues
with amico that go way beyond covet or manufacturing problems if you look at their
recent videos internet posts you see all kinds of red flags in progress videos of games that should
have been done ages ago a rocket's office filled with wastes of backers money and of course tommy
attacking anyone who dares to criticize them hence why i said there needs to be other pr people that
do some of this speaking as far as the other stuff goes well that the time to pay the piper is going
to be coming so yeah we'll see all right moving on let's talk about something else that's getting
a lot of hate mail in the industry this week we touched on this towards the end of last week's
show but we didn't really dig into it and this story kind of got bigger this week um and so
loki why don't you tell us about this yeah so this is it seems like we were also talking about this
like at the beginning of the pandemic as well or like somewhat into the pandemic but you know
niantic had removed some of the pokemon go safety measures um despite the fact that we're having
different variants of covet 19 popping up now so you know there is still the risk of transmission
of these new uh variants as well and so uh back in june apparently they had you know started to
roll back some of the double distance tweaks and um some of the other enhancements you know being
added to the game despite the fact that you know some people might not want to leave and also other
parts of the world are having resurgences um in their area um and because of that you know fans
of the game have been kind of you know trying to let them know hey we don't think this is a good
idea and i've even started like a change.org petition that's gotten over 130 000 signatures
and basically saying that the ink should extend this um these enhancements that they had in place
right now especially also you know there's you know disabled players as well that these
additional enhancements that they had allowed them to actually be able to enjoy the game more
um so yeah and then of course with that of course they uh fans were actually saying that
they're going to start boycotting the game um because of some of these issues and they're
boycott a free game well i mean yeah you you can do that i mean but like if they make money off
of people playing the game and buying the in-game purchases so if you boycott the game it does hurt
them in the wallet so that's all you can really do um but basically yeah so now you can announce
some more legendaries from sword and shield that are going to be coming to port uh pokemon go and
uh with those they're going to be part of this ultra unlock thing they have to do these challenges
to unlock it between august 20th and september 1st but apparently um they were saying that you know
because of you know some of these issues and stuff folks are just going to be kind of boycotting
the game um unless they you know come back to you know extending these features that they had so they
were trying to trend uh boycott niantic to show their displeasure with the game and i don't know
i haven't played pokemon go in a long time pack your bags because you're not going to like the
resolution they come up with so the question is going to be how important or shinies to you
i i'm i'm trying to be mean or rude but i do think there is a large percentage of people that
are signing these petitions and things like that and the number one reason why they're mad and they
want things reverted back is that they can no longer hump the pokey stop that was just outside
a range of their house anymore for gear all day long or that is absolutely not fair to the
disabled community that is but i did not say everybody i said most now the disabled but as
far as the disabled community go i i agree that there are issues there and things that that need
to be looked at but these are things that have kind of existed for the first four years of the
game as well i think they did a horrible job in communicating i said this last week as well is
that for them to say oh these changes are because of covid and then they say at the time but we're
going to keep them for the foreseeable future which implies there's no end date and then to
revoke them when they did and by saying oh well you know now that covid is even though they kind
of didn't phrase it that way but they kind of insinuated because covid is winding down we're
gonna you know go put back all these changes that we made and i said this last week and i do agree
for with this part niantic did stupid with that like they shouldn't have done that but my honest
and i've said this a lot they're gonna put that 80 kilometer or that 80 kilometer that 80 feet
thing back you're not gonna like what they're gonna do because i'm i'm telling you right here
i know how this ends they're gonna put that in there but they're gonna put a cool down on pokey
stops like more than five minutes they're gonna do something similar to ingress where maybe you
can spin it four times and then that's it no more gear for like six hours or 12 hours um because
that's the thing that niantic is trying to stop are the people is that that i really truly believe
to be the majority of people signing this petition who are just upset that they can't
spend their desk portal and and so forth as far as and again i want to stress as far as the
disability issues yes i understand those concerns that's legitimate that's a different issue that
niantic has to look into that's an issue that's needed to be looked into for the last four years
it's nothing new now um let's see uh bonds 006 in chat says i am split on the radius debate of
the pokey stops um and that's it's other folks still uh pod culture says who me abuse a pokey
stop never look and i'm not saying like those players are doing anything wrong or bad or what
have you i'm just it is playing the game yeah they're just i get like and i'm not trying to be
mean again i promise i'm just giving you the reality check right um go ahead i was going to
say i've kind of looked at it the same way as the people who complain about no ed and dead by
daylight it's in the game it's a function if people use it it's okay it's a function of the
game so i don't get mad about it and niantic did botch the messaging on this they absolutely botch
the messaging on this and their reply to this community thing which i thought was very impressive
that all the community sites got together and demanded they give a response i thought niantic's
response to it was very like yikes but again i just don't think you're gonna like where they end
up on at the end of this um but i was gonna say i don't fault the people that were you know like
pod culture saying i was spinning a stop and all this stuff sure i benefited from it too are you
kidding when i would walk around and you know use my bluetooth of course i could hit stops that were
even further away but um nobody likes to be given something and then have it taken away
nobody likes that that's what this really boils down to um and as far as the whole the other
weird thing to me is this whole well number one the fact that they're introducing zassian and
zamzata and all this stuff and the the freaking gen 8 pokemon before they've even finished gen 6
have done nothing with gen 7 i mean it's just weird like i i can understand that they could
you know you sometimes have regions in pokemon that are a mix of other regions is it like this
new um uh uh pokemon legends our arceus game that's coming out is kind of like that where
it's like a mix or snap or things like that like but it's like it hasn't been in the pokemon go
lore until now so it feels a little weird but i don't i do not think this is some resp like them
putting gen 8 in the game suddenly the the some of the gaming media is trying to frame it like oh
this is a response to the protest and everything going on is niantic's now trying to sweeten the
pot y'all it takes a lot longer to prep the artwork the data and all this like this has
been in in the works well before they were making any of these changes so that no i don't no no no
i don't buy that and that that part kind of makes me roll my eyes when i see those headlines because
i'm like y'all don't understand clearly nobody out there is playing this game that's writing
about it so anyway um so yeah i mean that's that's my take on it take her to leave it um am i gonna
stop playing the game probably not but i mean i just use it as something to kind of like
incentivize my walking i don't necessarily need to spend a ton of money on the game i don't think
niantic is really convincing me to spend money on the game outside of you know some of their events
are pretty cool um but that's you know that's it um the remote passes i guess are kind of neat too
but i'm able to get enough coins for that by doing the gym thing um sg100 matt says they emphasize
that the game is about exploring and walking they use this as justification of the 40 meter spin
radius thing which i get but doesn't the fact that remote rate passes kind of go against that
exploration of walking they're calling for no because it makes money and i i think that's a
fair call out is that again why their response was not great and having played niantic games
for a very long time and understanding that john hanky comes from a google maps background and that
is very much about like being out there and exploring especially with street view and things
like that like i get and especially when you look at that they're very if you look at niantic's very
first app what was niantic's very first app it was not ingress gotcha a lot of people say oh
yeah angry nope it was no it wasn't ingress but i don't remember what it was field tripper
was their first down and that was i don't think they supported anymore but that was that was
where the very very very original uh ingress uh portals came from was this game about kind of
you know starting that idea of these landmarks in your city to go exploring and all of that stuff
that's where that came from so like i get that that is niantic's mission and honestly for me
it's been very successful i've seen a lot of places i would never have gone to if it wasn't
for things like ingress i'm gonna specifically call out ingress pokemon go just kind of piggybacks
on my ingress experience to be quite honest um no that's absolutely accurate yeah so that part of it
i get um but i also at the same time can recognize what has to show in her mat is saying you can see
that obvious conflict there and i think that's what a lot of the community is starting to call
out is that but if you pay for it you can have this experience and i think you know again there's
talk about like poke you stop power ups and stuff like that that maybe could uh yeah um
pod culture and chat says field tripper a bunch of bored kids on a bus with tired adults
no no no not that kind of thing uh as joe and her mat says wasn't that where the memes of being
let off a cliff came from well i think also i've seen those memes about um the the pissed off
pokemon go player base and it's that meme of the the guys just happening with map quest back in
the day well it's the meme of those guys on the pirate ship and they're about to die or something
like that and the one says like uh i'm an angry pokemon go player and then it says ingress player
first time that whole thing uh because ingress has had its own share of issues over the years for
sure but i've never seen the player base quite well we had that transition to prime that a lot
of people straight up didn't like and a lot of people left the game as a result of it and i'm of
a minority opinion of sorts i think sometimes prime has made ingress better it took i don't
know i stopped playing ingress a while ago it didn't help it took a long time to get there
but it now it's made ingress better that first year i don't i can see why people were pissed
off absolutely but now ingress prime has made the game better but it just took like what three years
to get there so all right anyway let's move on uh oh let's talk about a different nintendo story
i mean technically pokemon go isn't really nintendo it's more of like a license type of thing
but let's talk about nintendo sales and nintendo financials so nintendo has published money their
most recent quarterly report and uh they have uh made a little less money this year uh in the three
months leading up to june 30th they had a operating profit of 119 billion yen that's
about 1.1 billion dollars that's a lot of fucking money um however it's not as much fucking money
as last year when they made 1.3 billion that's a 17.3 percent drop but i think we all was still
animal crossing the other year though exactly exactly i was like we can all see what the what
what what was happening last year that isn't happening as much nearly this year lockdowns
and animal crossing it was the perfect storm combination last year that worked out very well
for nintendo we don't like to look at companies profiting off the pandemic um but nintendo didn't
that was not nintendo's plan we're profiting off people having to be home it's less of the
pandemic you know and they didn't even know that there was going to be a shutdown the same month
they released animal crossing yes and as i was trying to get to that was not nintendo's plan
like nintendo didn't play it was just the perfect storm that happened that allowed allowed things
to get there um but yes they have not had an animal crossings this year quite frankly
i don't think they've really had a big game yet this year now i mean some may argue that oh
sure mario tennis and all that stuff yeah no um but when you look at later this year we've got
wario ware get it together zelda skyward sword will show up in the next um uh right because that
was a july release uh metroid dread is coming mario party superstars pokemon brilliant diamond
shining pearl so i mean there's a lot of good stuff to look forward to from nintendo and i
think the financials will be different um but at the same time if you're upset about 1.1 billion
dollars um stop that i'm upset about the 1.1 million dollars that no one's giving me right
i would take 1.1 dollars right now every little bit i could use a few more dollars than that
um yyr in chat says i thought the drop would be way more not because they're doing poorly now but
because they did so well last year yeah like i mean honestly the fact that they only fell 17
actually seems pretty good uh sia tabiri in chat says and animal crossing updates yes the game
could still use some of those as well i'm surprised they didn't do dlc i think they're
done with that though they did and they did one recently i covered it last week yeah that was that
was a tiny tiny little bump though we we need something major major uh like that mario thing
was pretty cool or something like that would be you know nice or the fucking cafe like you said
some more buildings from the other um iterations it was data mine that we were supposed to have
brewster yeah man if they announced that i would be immediately back into playing um the gyroids
i'm surprised was never a thing this is yeah they're kind of morbid though if you actually
know where they came from yeah but we don't have to talk about it um stirlock in chat says
i really need to get back into animal crossing i think there's a lot of people saying that
but animal crossing at the same time should give us something to come back to
right yeah yeah all right let's move on dark sakura well um here's the nintendo franchise
that i think uh we can agree is fairly epic and that's going into metroid so they released a
trailer um for metroid dread that brings up the chozo um it's it's a pretty short little
little trailer it's like you know 34 seconds but it brings up the chozo it you know shows their
their sort of hieroglyphics looking uh wall art i don't know what to call it like
it's very very egyptian like in nature um and so uh of course in the previous metroid games we
always had like a statue or a ghost or something written by one or the chozo
uh robot you know that did something on you go to the abandoned ship in super metroid
um what people aren't realizing is that there is a whole lot more lore already existing about
the chozo and if you look into samus uh into her uh history she was raised by the chozo
and actually had some of their dna bonded to her so that she could live on their planet
and so i'm actually hoping that we get a lot more throwback to uh her time with chozo you know
a lot more of her history with growing up among the chozo and where they all went and what happened
to them because you know they also made the metroids and where did that get them i'm really
looking forward to it i've always had fascination with the chozo in that series and you know me when
i get into a game i really get into the lore so i'm really excited about it and of course um
it'll be out october 8th for switch and we'll find out our answers there i reckon
yeah i mean samus is a pretty unique character you might say she's the chozo one
are you looking at how i'm staring at you right now no i'm not you should be i will be
episode from the archive so that pun dies tonight this is me staring at you in judgment
just carrying on the tradition of the 23rd maggots that's all all right you are a dad i guess
somebody has to bring the dad jokes to this show all right check out they call them dad jokes
because they don't want to call them bad jokes hi i did one too now that actually was pretty funny
all right moving on come on dad what's the next story yeah dad well uh let's talk about
duke nukem again um so apparently uh the embracer group has bought seven different studios including
3d realms so they had purchased um basically some of the publishers uh like uh gearbox
thq nordic and deep silver uh but now they've bought three realms ghost ship games um what else
uh forcefield easy trigger uh dixie uh dixie art and crazy labs so a lot of those i don't recognize
but i mean i definitely recognize 3d realms so don't know what that means necessarily in
the terms of new games i guess we'll have to wait and see i would like to see a keep well making if
they keep making duke nukem games at the um regular rate we'll find out in about 2030
yes well there was like um there was a a new 3d like fps game that was done in the
build engine so you know definitely the same technology as uh duke nukem 3d but you know
pretty awesome polished game they had a lot of stuff with that that retro throwback game yeah
yeah yeah yeah so they have some of those i like to see more of those coming along i mean duke nukem
he's a hard character to kind of bring into this modern age of 2021 i mean just not necessarily
a character i could see a lot of folks liking nowadays um but i don't know more games like that
that would be fine i guess like actually now that i think of it you know there's some games
that came from the build era that are still kind of doing well so maybe who knows what was that
game forever was not good what was that retro that game now it's gonna bug me it it uh it had a like
a disagreement with a metal band it was very similar to um some metal band there was that one
but there's been there's been actually a few other ones oh i don't remember that was the one i was
thinking of yeah i know which one you're i don't remember the name but yeah i it's there was a
couple other ones that were also using the build engine that looked pretty awesome there's one i
just saw recently it's using the doom engine like the original doom engine but it's like it doesn't
look like it's running doom anymore i mean they've done so many tweaks to it but there's a lot of
these games i like that where they kind of take this old technology and really enhance it to with
the modern visuals but it's still you know the old school engines which is kind of cool
or just a mod just a really good mod which you know is a really good mod the the um you know
xbox and playstation and all those versions of the game like officially support mods now
thank you dark tetsuya gold star for you iron maiden but they changed the name to ion fury
yeah i knew it was some metal iron maiden yeah exactly iron maiden had an issue with it and
yeah so now it's ion fury yes thank you dark tetsuya gold star for you all right you get more
than just the glitter for doing that research for me all right let's move on let's talk about a game
that for some people gets a gold star for some people not so much it's pokemon unite which
i actually i played a little bit more of that this week but um i don't know i like playing the game
by myself isn't as fun like if i can hop on there with friends and stuff it's a little more fun
because we have something to talk about but playing with randos gets kind of old to me but
i i still as far as mopas go it still is probably one of my favorite ones i'll check it out when
it's on mobile phones as well i want to see how it plays on the phone um comparatively but pokemon
unite just got a big update so um there is a new update that really went in there and uh changed
some balance and maybe that's why i'm pissed because eldegoss kind of got hit with the nerf
bat and she can't heal as much as she did before um although i guess her uh special attack move
uh can do more so i don't know i guess there's a trade-off there but um like pretty much all the
other pokemon got some type of changes i i'd list them all off but it was just about everybody
uh so that here earlier this week and i believe it's also bringing a spectate mode to the game
although they did not enable that at first um i can't remember if that's in there now or if that's
still coming um but uh next month there is plans for the mobile release and there will be cross
platform play between of course the switch and smartphones um and if you log into your nintendo
account or your ptc that's pokemon trainer club account you can cross save data in progress which
would probably be a good idea i'm just curious how moving around is going to work on the mobile
phones but i guess if you just tapped on the screen where you want to go it might work out
um so interesting mike defton chat says i'm playing it right now well i hope you're i hope
you're doing well i hope you're winning who's your main mike deft that's what i want to know
because i was i will say the one thing i did do this week i i'm like an eldegoss main right i
played like 98 of my matches with eldegoss i bought snorlax and try to match with snorlax
because i i like snorlax as a pokemon and uh i thought the moves would be fun oh boy did i get
beat oh boy did i get beat i guess i need more practice okay nine tails i was looking at i was
looking at that's because it's a lowland nine tails slash volpix right i was looking at that
one because i like the whole like freeze mechanics and stuff um maybe i'll check that one out next
all right anyhow it's uh time for our next segment here at orange launch
radio which uh i would say needs no introduction but we actually have a special introduction
and now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where i'll dive into the vault and pull
out a classic and tell you about it it's time for the classic game of the week
but as we know in a 2021 twist once a month we get a flag that means fucking weird arcade game
and i believe that's what dark soccer has picked for us tonight right oh believe me we get the flag
so basically the game that i chose and on its own it doesn't necessarily seem like it should
be a flag until you actually see it played the game is final furlong which i have brought up
many many a time as the horsey humpin game it is a horse racing game developed by namco it came out
in arcades in 1997 um it is one of the only two games that run the namco system 22.5 gorgon
hardware which is a early revision of the namco system 23 hardware so basically in this game you
have three checks to choose from six and a half furlongs a one mile and a one and a half a mile
you have different horse classifications you have like a leader a front runner a mid runner
a strong finisher and two quote almighty runners who like to keep their position
you sit on a saddle as it were and you have this
i this thing it doesn't really look like a horse it's got like well it kind of kind of does but um
i've seen the ones where they don't exactly like look exactly it's just so weird they're just weird
okay they kind of look like horses but you have this bar you hold on to and the thing is is that
if you fit on it then you're supposed to ride it like it's a horse and you know move with it
and everything but i've seen people who are way too tall for this thing who just stand up and
push at it and people look like they're humping the horse just just what it's just it's fucked up
um we had one i don't know if they still have it because i haven't been there in ages but
roseville golf land had one no they had one i remember they had one at uh country club lanes
for a while um but that's gone unfortunately roseville golf land had one that's tucked over
like along the same wall as the entrance that's where i remembered it being and then they replaced
it with derby's owner club long gone yeah it's been a while it's been a while years um and uh
uh basically though it did get a rating as one of the best games overall with the quote from
gerald lynch for tech radar saying the machine was brutal popping you a straight a giant plastic
horse you'd propel yourself forward by getting up your steed rocking maniacally forward and
backwards to speed the beast up best played with two players the marathon like events would last
so long you wouldn't be able to walk for a week um yeah that's what they say about humping sometimes
too just saying um at any rate there actually was a sequel to final for long um and that was
final for long too aptly named one we had actually yeah i'm pretty sure that that was it um and it
had like some more options it came out in 1999 um and it also was uh i want to say it also ran on
no it ran on system 23 it ran on system 23 so it did use the upgraded system um both of these
though i do believe could link up to four players playing so it was kind of neat it was just i mean
the thing that that again classifies this as swag for me is just how how it looks when you play it
yeah they look like less of them riding it more of them choking the horse violently yeah yeah
they're they're they're doing the hump with the horse but
they're they're getting their fictitious catherine the great on
but yeah that's that's the game final furlong all right there it is let me give my earbuds back in
there classic flag of the month final furlong and um i'm sorry i ran to the restroom so you
guys probably brought this up but we had that one locally at a country club right yes i also
brought out the one that they had at rvgl as well i don't remember i don't remember that one
and i had one for a hot minute fun all right yeah and honestly uh derby owners club was a much
better horsey game i'll be honest it was but but but not quite as much fun to watch as this one
i've injured myself on final furlong i wonder where all those derby owners club games have gone
i think the one from what i understand the one at rvgl is still there but i also haven't been
there in like two years no it's not i i'm pretty i want one the last time i was there which was
back in 2020 i'm pretty sure it was not there anymore i i usually walk around because if it
was there i would totally be playing it so i'm gonna kick dan's mustang out of the garage and
get a derby derby owners club kidding that's worthy really nice um i swear the last time i
was at a dave and busters i think the one of the great mall they still had this set up for it but
granted that was a few years ago at this point so i haven't checked on it lately that's a dnb
that has gone kind of downhill ever since they got rid of the uh battle tech thing oh yeah i
forgot that was battle tech in the day too now it made me nauseous as all hell but the battle tech
pods were really fun well yeah those are the ones that bobby's talked a lot about those on his show
because they still they still bring them to dragon con every year i used to play that back in was
that they had it was i never was called now in the downtown plaza in sacramento it was like a
bunch of uh bars fuck that's america live america live that is a throwback locally here that place
that is that is now an arena well yeah yeah
pod culture brings up the star wars pod it's kind of not the same thing though because you're not as
immersed yeah this is like um it's very you know the battle tech had a very complicated system
yeah but it was cool uh yyr says uh pretty sure all the dave and busters got rid of derby owners
club by now well that's unfortunate but at the same time it probably wasn't bringing in the money
and they probably wanted to put in you know i don't know whatever stupid machines make money
i just remember the names we would name our our horses oh yeah all the silly names who come up
because i still have a bunch of my cards um i haven't um been to a dave and busters a long
time ever since round one was a thing i don't think i've been to a dave and busters since
round one kind of started being a thing i went to dave and busters about a it had to have been like
in january or so because i met up uh last year because i met up with jd and we went to the one
that's like way out closer to daily city oh yeah yeah way out there okay the ceremony yeah yeah
yeah because that's where it was already at and so that's where alan lived when we first
started dating was that area this was quite a quite a commute yeah yeah um uh i was gonna say
that round one here locally in roseville still not open as far as i know unless it just happened in
the past couple weeks but i don't think so and uh that's it's weird because round ones have been
open i've been to the one in concord since the pandemic i was there just recently a few weeks
ago before the the delta variant kicked up and all that stuff but still it's still like i'd
they're not shutting businesses down again they're saying get vaccinated and wear a mask
and you know most businesses are staying open um so uh um i've been around one recently so
it's weird that the one in roseville still isn't open but i guess maybe they really just want to
wait out the the quote-unquote worst of the pandemic behind they're just behind on getting
it done because there's also the movie theater that's supposed to go above it or blow it yeah
another industry that got hurt through all this pretty yeah it was like a
cinema or something like that so it's
yeah i i i look every time i'm at the mall and it's it's never open i'm like oh i wonder if some
of these movie theaters are waiting for that um was it a warner brothers deal or that whole like
hbo max thing they'd only promised that through 2021 so i wonder if some of these are waiting for
that to be done before they open theaters new theaters again you know because i guess the whole
like a simulcast deal has been hurting some of the box office intake ask ask garland johanson
what she thinks of that and that whole thing so yeah yeah all right anyhow uh let's go ahead and
travel around and check out some rapid fire news and quickly check out some other things going on
in the industry we'll start with loki so curveball space program has officially announced that they're
ceasing um development on the first game which i guess makes sense because they're putting out
curveball space program too so it would have had to have stopped at some point but keep in mind
though they've been developing the game for 10 years so a long time you know i i think that
they're allowed to do that the last update uh was just released on august 3rd um and that was
the one point 112.2 update which fixed over 90 bugs in the game so yeah i guess it's fine that
they've stopped development on that since they got to move on at some point um and apparently
pac-man 99 has been doing well uh despite the fact that it's not you know the the mario game
and that has surpassed four million downloads on the nintendo switch um i attribute that to
the lack of things that they're putting out as part of that nintendo online since we're not
getting a lot of new games but you know hey people like their battle royale games and that's kind of
cool um is this going to be a temporary game as well because like i don't know they haven't really
said i don't know i don't think they undated it i don't think i just want still around right tetris
one's still around and uh it was just that mario one for whatever reason they put an expiration
date on it that's so stupid i don't get it it's just dumb um all right uh is dark soccer there
as she turned off her cam so she might yeah she might have gone afk for a second so um i'll do
a quick aside before we get to her story since she brought up pac-man um uh alan was just at costco
like just now today like before the show and he said you're laughing because you know where this
is going right were you know where this is going no i haven't been in costco but i already there's
only one possible outcome because i could just be so he sent me this picture on our chat app that we
use um oftentimes um that he saw at costco for i'm sorry i'm looking at the price here 369
he found this i'm holding up my phone like you guys can see it he found this arcade one up machine
that is super pac-man now i gotta say i love the fact that it's branded super pac-man because a
lot of times these things are reskinned as oh hey alan funny you should walk in here this
i'm talking about what you saw at costco here do you want to do you want to are you camera
safe do you want to talk about no he showed he didn't want to come on and talk about it
but he sent me a picture of it and he was like you know kind of not word for word but was kind
of like you know you want it type of thing basically and i here here was my response my
response says the minute we put the money down to buy that cabinet that's when the
tron pre-orders are going to go up and we're going to be pissed so i i actually said no
you saw that they finally announced the stupid simpsons arcade game right yes i did see they
finally announced the stupid simpsons arcade game i don't know why they waited so long but like i
don't either yeah um so the here's the thing and then we'll get back i see dark soccer's back so
we'll get to her rapid fire stories as soon as i wrap up the story um the on the arcade one-up
machine uh with the super pac-man i did again i love that it's super pac-man branding which maybe
jamie wants to hear this i don't know uh sure at costco a 369 super pac-man branded arcade one-up
with super pac-man pac-man pac-mania galaga galaxian dig dug and pac-land so it's seven games
and those are like honestly i love me some super pac-man i like pac-mania i like pac-land i love
dig dug so that's a pretty solid cabinet the only problem is if i i there's another cabinet they put
out not recently that's not excuse me a little bit recently that's not at costco and it's the namco
legacy machine and that machine has all of the same games but it's 4 49 it's it's almost like
80 more than costco but it's pac-man pac-land pac-man plus super pac-man pac and pal pac-mania
galaxian galaga dig dug dig dug two mapi which is huge and rompers are in that machine so yeah i'm
like oh the dig dug two even though that wasn't quite as good as the original uh because it's
very different and um the uh mapi really make that cabinet but i love the fact that this one is is
branded super pac-man now to answer the question in chat where somebody said why not somebody
said why not both uh w04 said porque no los dos um the tron cabinet and the super pac-man eventually
um some things are in the works that i haven't talked about yet um but i will very soon i promise
and we'll be able to have a little more um space around where we live to have some more cabinets
because we're making some changes um but right now i could i could squeeze in one more
but you know again like i said the minute i buy the super pac-man cabinet that tron cabinet's
gonna come out and then i'll be pissed because i won't have any space for the tron cabinet
so bobby blackwolf in chat says wait for tron that's the plan because here's my thought tron
could end up being a limited thing like maybe the burger time thing was and i don't know if
i'll be able to get it forever pac-man you're gonna be able to get pac-man forever and it's
not even so much pac-man as it is super pac-man for me but those games are always going to go
hand in hand if there's a pac-man cabinet it's gonna have pac-man ms pac-man pack of
pac-land it's gonna have the various pac-man games in it for sure so i will wait all right
anyhow i won't wait any more to get some more rapid fire news dark sakura now that song is in
my head i can't wait my new shoes oh i thought you were gonna the dawson's creek song no
um first of all no second of all i hate that song and third of all no and number four i hate that
show so getting into some actually interesting stuff um there uh there's another mario game
that has come out and sold for a shitload of money there is an unopened copy of super mario
brothers again that um sold for 2 million um that topped the 1.56 million uh for a super mario 64
this particular one by the wata scale is a 9.8 a plus rating which means it is in exceptional
condition and cool i just i just don't understand what you know i i get that this is a very specific
pressing of the game so even if you have like a super mario brothers cartridge lying around
chances are this is not the two unless you again are extremely lucky and have you know lottery luck
it's not the one that's going for 2 million in fact these things going for 2 million have the
box instructions unopened but it's that very specific like sears tab top to the box it was
sold for a very limited time only at sears so silly all right and then um now space invader's
invincible collection is going to be on switch but it's gonna cost 60 bucks on august 17th
too much uh huh i said too much money yeah that's pretty much what i'm going with um
tito announced the collection um it is available for pre-order um but that that's quite a bit um
it has 11 different versions of space invaders from the original 1978 uh to uh 2018 space
invaders giga max 4se and has a free download of the 2017 mobile release arcanoid versus space
invaders um but i mean it is kind of niche you know yeah i'm with sterlock who says that's one
expensive tab the good news is these types of games tend to go on sale pretty quick so wait
for like you know around the black friday time of year and i bet you this comes way down in prize
yeah but i mean i i won't be spending it for that i mean if i was gonna get getting a physical copy
maybe yeah but no i think this is interesting the stuff that yyr is talking about is still talking
about that mario sale but i think this is interesting why we are in regards to the mario
cartridge sale says this is basically just one company trying to drive up the prices i wouldn't
be shocked if they sold it to themselves nothing about these last few weeks record-breaking mario
game sales is legit it did seem to come out of nowhere didn't it when i've always been led to
believe that stadium events is supposed to be like that must have nes game where did this freaking
like super mario brothers original box like 2 million cover i think stadium events was what
like maybe 700 000 last time we talked it's just it's just we it is weird that this is all all of
a sudden in it all right maybe i'm getting too much conspiracy theory but i think i think it
just the timing is strange somebody else has suggested it's like pandemic driven
collectible mania or something but i don't it's just weird all right what's not weird some new
video games to play this week let's travel around the world and check out some releases
of what's coming to a store near you first in the us loki yes we have a brand new game i am dead
on playstation 4 playstation 5 xbox one xbox series x sadly not sequel to i am bread uh age
of empires 2 the definitive edition dawn of the dukes on pc we have black book on pc nintendo
switch playstation 4 and xbox one um ever forward on nintendo switch playstation 4 playstation 5 xbox
one xbox series x uh godfall finally coming to playstation 4 shadowverse champions battle on
nintendo switch 4 closed on uh pc nintendo switch playstation 4 playstation 5 xbox one xbox series
x and stadia that sounds exciting um hades is going to be coming out on playstation 4 playstation
5 xbox one and xbox series x and is that it for this week yes it is yeah if you have game pass
and haven't played hades yet highly recommend when that hits game pass this week highly recommend
all right looking at japan it's a little smaller this week on the nintendo switch we have a yugioh
game yugioh rush duel psyche battle royale is out this week and that is on april the 12th on
the nintendo switch um as far as the playstation 5 nothing this week on the playstation 5 and going
to the playstation 4 um gosh it's also pretty barren a pretty non-weak i get a yugioh dominates
confirmed this week in japan there's also some like peripherals if you're into charging stands
and new there's some new stuff coming out but yugioh that's it dark sakura how about the uk
for the uk what we have is uh let's see on the 10th we have uh power rangers battle for the grid
super edition we have uh foreclosed on the 12th on the 13th we have hades also paw patrol adventure
city cause uh shadowverse champions battle tormented souls and that looks like it's it for
the week i hate to keep going back to this but you y'all are falling down the rabbit hole in
chat and i love it um sha100 matt again about the collectible thing says there is a backlog with
collectible appraisals services where you ship your collectible for it to be graded due to the
pandemic because of that prices have shot up on things and see i would never really thought of
that but i didn't even realize that was the thing you could do but who would make who would mail in
a two million two million dollar video game but i guess i guess it's possible but i can't i get
but i also understand like that is like something that's driving everything up even if not this
particular piece of merchandise went through that process so um fascinating i guess i need to watch
more antiques road show because i have no idea how all this works when it comes to collectibles
so who knows what i have a lot of shit in my house and who knows if any of it's worth anything
maybe that's why i hang on to it all right let's move on a few more stories for you guys before we
get to the listener round table you may or may not have heard we are taking calls again so
we'll check in on the green green room a little closer to the um listener round table in a little
bit uh for now uh loki yeah so apparently we're hearing some more rumors about that
new playstation vr2 and this is coming from a leak from a sony developer conference and
apparently the leaker has been known to um have some reliable information so we'll go with that
and um you know some of the things we've kind of already heard about before you know with
you know the different uh you know field of view so like you know it's supposed to have
110 degree field of view uh 10 it says up from 10 degrees from what it was before
uh the resolution of 2000 by 2040 pixels per eye and apparently it's a little bit
that is a little bit better than say the oculus quest 2 and then um you know of course there's
going to be you know a oled display on there and um you know of course better lighting you know
color with that i want to hear more about the actual controllers but i don't think there's
anything in there about that um but yeah so lots more um a little bit more information
kind of piggybacking on some of the earlier rumors that we heard before but there's this
whole video out now uh by this uh p psvr without parole um a youtuber that has uh some of the
details about that so i don't know sounds interesting i'm excited they when they finally
announce all the information and kind of how that's gonna work with especially backwards
compatibility and stuff like that and whether there's a new you know uh until dawn rush from
blood or rush of blood game because that's really gonna sell it for me um but yeah next year i guess
we'll just have to wait until all those leaks come out hopefully you can walk into target and
get a fucking playstation 5 oh yeah yeah gonna have to have a playstation 5 to run that on too
i guess that's kind of important so um they can't figure out those chip shortages this vr is going
to meet the same fate so this is true yes but um yeah and i'm sure i'll use it so much more than my
current vr headset which has been in the box for a year or two i don't so i don't know well it just
depends it just depends if the games are there that's the most important thing so yeah all right
well one game i don't think we'll end up on psvr too because i think this is more of a microsoft
thing is pubg but did you guys hear the name of pubg has officially changed this week the new
acronym is pubgbg because the new game the new name of the game is pubg battlegrounds
now atm machine yes it is like atm machine okay because think about let's let's think about what
pubg meant player unknown battlegrounds so the name of the game is player unknown battlegrounds
battlegrounds that is yeah it's a game where that's like saying fight against each other
and and it's that's like saying atm machine yes exactly i just said that
i missed it so yes uh pubg battlegrounds here's why they're doing it so they want to expand the
pubg brand through new experiences set in the universe so calling pubg battlegrounds that is
going to be representative of the battleground game but there is a new game coming out called
pubg new state it's a mobile title with a futuristic setting uh it is uh um i guess the
creators of dead space made a game called the callisto protocol which is connected to this
oh yeah i remember seeing the trailer for that at one of the just call it the player unknown
universe or something like that like i mean pubg
i don't know the only way that they can really do this now is really lean into that like we need to
get you know you need to get someone saying yo dog i hear you like battlegrounds so we put
battlegrounds in your battlegrounds so you can battlegrounds why your battlegrounds you know
they need to really lean into that now uh bobby blackwolf also points out part of it is that
player unknown has left the industry so they don't really want to use his name anymore so
pubg has just kind of become a i guess you know perhaps you should have renamed your game a long
time ago well wait i have okay i have a great idea here because i was going to say here's
some even more exciting now if you want actually something to actually be excited about when it
comes to pubg bg here it is there's an official collaboration coming between pubg battlegrounds
and blackpink the korean pop band cool so yes uh you could it's a black there's a blackpink
collaboration bundle there's like a new parachute and there's some other stuff as well so in my
opinion why don't we just make this game blackpink battlegrounds because now there there's an
unproblematic fave that we can all be excited about uh owning the franchise so that's my bp
bp bg bp bg bg the future of gaming although is it you know what when it comes to the whole like
we want to create a universe and other experiences you know think back to the start of the show
and you know we all remember a day when it was pubg versus fortnight uh and you know look at
what we just we spent i can't believe we talked for 15 minutes at the top of the show if not more
about fortnight but we sure did because it deserved it it did something that kind of
necessitated the discussion um and you know what if pubg is going to be mixing it up with
different types of events and stuff i mean i don't think blackpink is doing a concert
i think this is just some some branded you know costumes and stuff for the store but
i for i for one welcome our bpg bg bg game um yyr in chat says blackpink versus ariana grande
we can only hope that is the only way we can solve the fortnite pink worked with cardi b
that's and a few other american artists yes and you know what let's let's not pit the
women against each other let's let's let's just let's let's be fans of all the games
how about that all right how about women uplifting women right that's right that's right
all right uh w u w bg bg all right let's move on dark sakura
so um oh i lost my place for a moment anyway uh our type final three has been announced
and it's a free update to our type final two like are they just like do they call them final the way
that graphic designers call their projects final or share it's never final or final
we all know that shara's had so much surgery she's practically immortal
um either that or she's just gonna have uh um chad michaels fill in for her for the rest of
her shows why not but anyway um granzella the developer is uh putting out the the update um
there's on the kickstarters page for uh uh our type final two um they're saying that there's
going to get be more dlc more ships um and over the rest of the summer there's going to be some
improvements to the pc version and finally by the end of the year our type final three
it'll be a free upgrade for those who already own our type final two and uh that it's only japanese
only but there will be english subtitles later on so uh yeah at least they can count to three
valve uh orange right in chat says i played through our type final two good game
well now you'll have final three to play through as well exciting i love our type
but nothing is ever the first level music for the first our type um the hits keep coming in chat in
regards to the pub gb g story uh yyr in chat says you're listening to olr radio okay let's have a
chat do not refer to this show ever as olr radio um i don't want to speak for dark sakura but i
have a pretty good feeling that if you do call this show olr radio if you look in the mirror
and say olr radio three times dark sakura will reach out to the email and slap you silly so
don't do that am i right it will happen
um and then bobby blackwolf says rob roberts hey watch it so i hate to bring things down
but but i just found out that an actress i really like died oh the marquee post story yeah i love
night court okay no night court was great that is sad i had no idea she was um in in bad health but
i guess she had been battling cancer for a little bit because um yeah she was still acting for quite
some time she was uh the mom and something about mary yeah yeah so and she didn't she'd done other
stuff here and there so yeah i actually saw john larroquette's post about it i don't mean to bring
things down but oh my goodness no it's fine well it's also sad that like like we've lost several
people from night court just in the past few years it feels like harry anderson died in 2018
and charlie robinson died uh this year as well yeah yeah i i was like i thought we just lost
somebody else from that show not that long ago so anyway that's all right sometimes sometimes i
have a night court marathon sometimes the news breaks during the show i mean even though that
technically was overnight but that's right sometimes we don't find out about them until
we just hit that right tweet yeah all right um loki i feel like we alluded to this already in
the show but uh why don't you make it official yeah so apparently grand theft auto 5 is leaving
xbox game pass um you know it's not been on there for very long uh but yes there's gonna be some
other um games coming as well though um so like this at least the early part of this month we've
got a you know katamari democracy reroll as you mentioned uh skate and skate 3 were put on there
as well uh this week art of rally and of course hades and then the stuff leaving um aside from
grand theft auto we have uh dark siders genesis final fantasy 7 and uh don't starve and train
sim world 2020 so yeah a lot of games leaving but there's been they've gotten a lot of like
i just said like luminous and uh katamari were added recently so let's be honest if
you haven't played grand theft auto 5 in the 10 years it's been out i mean like true
true okay it's not even i played a little bit of five finally it hasn't been out for 10 years
but it's been out close almost it's a long time it's almost eligible for classic game of the week
it is almost eligible for classic game of the week and we don't even have grand theft auto 6
yet so what is going on all right sorry games well um a game that absolutely should be and by
the way if you want to call into olr we're almost to that point of the show so um headed to the
green room if you want to call into olr i see somebody in the public chat but i'm not sure if
that is just left over because that was the same person that called in a bobby show so i'm not sure
if that's where they just kind of ended up after the show but head over to the green room if you
want to be in be in tonight's olr um while i get while we wait for that uh heading to this story
which now this is a classic game i'm almost positive this had to have been the classic
game of the week at some point if not dark cycle we need to remedy that at some point but um this
game is absolutely something that's worthy of a classic and one that i wish would come back and
i'm talking about marvel versus capcom 2 uh is a game that a lot of fans this week have just like
it seems like it's a very viral thing on twitter oh it has been now uh episode 789 according to
our wiki whenever that was wow i'm not gonna say it's because of our show but i mean i did have it
as my background video a couple weeks ago so i just you know want to take full credit for that
and and everybody look at tonight's look gonna take you for a ride look at tonight's episode
number 879 and dark soccer just said this was the classic game on 789 is that a coincidence
there are no coincidences anyway marvel versus capcom was 388 well for some reason the credit
for this particular uh recent charge to get this game re-released is a content creator maximilian
dude um i i don't know the name myself but they must be more popular than us um they began a
hashtag campaign called free mbc2 which apparently got a lot more steam than president kat did
but um sorry one sec guys i just had an earpiece fall out
okay that was extremely graceful all right um so this style he's grace
he'll drop his earbuds in your face again and i'm just sitting here lamenting how are there
all these people more popular than us while i'm a big klutz we'll have on air all right
uh there's a free mbc2 hashtag to try to get support among folks who want to see this crossover
head out now this these types of uh uh campaigns happen once in a while what makes this notable
a similar thing to what made the president cat thing notable back in the day and that is the
developer responded remember that remember when the developer responded to us during the president
cat thing and i'm sure they were like what the fuck but that's not what they said i'm not a
famous capcom responding so that's fine yes uh so in this case the studio head of digital eclipse
mike mika actually said on twitter we made what i think was the last mbc2 release on console when
we were known as backbone um let's see uh 16 by 9 and so forth i love the outpouring we'd swap
in ggpo and do documentary and museum work we'd need to talk to disney and capcom to make it real
we're game if they are hashtag free mbc2 and oh yeah disney is a player now because disney owns
marvel so that would be very interesting um so yeah um and of course folks note that digital
eclipse has worked a lot with this type of stuff they did the street fighter 30th anniversary
collection they also did they also have worked with disney the disney afternoon collection
and so forth um there was a playstation 3 and xbox 360 port of marvel vs capcom 2
and that was pulled from online stores in 2013 because of the license that expired for the
comic book characters so um yeah it'll be interesting to see if this can actually happen
though i would love that i could i can stand behind this that's for sure but some folks are
saying you know again we don't you know if you could re-release it we don't have to shell out
a hundred dollars for a copy you know that was on the dreamcast or whatever or pirate it which
is what a lot of people are doing i think at this point so interesting uh dr tsuya says ggpo is the
online thing i believe some of capcom's older re-releases use it like i think dnd did yeah
they're probably talking about updating some of that online stuff so yeah i would i would love
that uh and quest buster filling me in because i'm very uncool and i don't know all the content
creators telling me that maximillian dude is a massive fighting game aficionado and he breaks
down info to make it appealing to people that may have never played a fighting game before all right
well prop props to him he this this crossed our desk so um and you know obviously we don't catch
everything so um congrats that's great uh dj rama s says i prefer capcom versus snk 2 over marvel
versus capcom 2 to which i say why not both everyone's entitled to a wrong opinion why not
both let's have both in one release i think that would be great all right anyway i just i you know
i don't even get you know talk about talking on fighting games to a level of people that don't
usually get into fighting games i don't get into fighting games a lot but that is one that i love
and i would instantly buy if it was re-released and you know not buggy or things like that so
that's that's for sure uh some folks in chat uh bobby blackwell says tatsunoko versus capcom
well that'd be pretty cool um and dj rama s says rival schools hell yeah to that now we need
shooting to justice die got going as in the college years all right we're gonna go to the
listener round table and we're gonna take some calls here on orange lounge radio uh we just
recently brought this feature back and so it's still a little bit of an experiment in progress
but if you want to give us a call head on over to the green room keep in mind i could pull you
in here at any time so just be ready for that that's the one thing uh i've lost from before
is the ability for people to hear when i've picked up the line and then acknowledge them they can't
hear that anymore they're just boop they're on air so we'll see how that goes and we're gonna take
this call right now and see how it goes um hello you are on orange launch radio who's this
hey there's that hey act f it is great to see you how are you
i'm doing pretty good um i just like some some of the things uh we're probably gonna talk about
but yeah i'm thinking what's on your mind tonight um well basically i do want to talk about uh the
niantic and pokemon go pull out all right have a great week we'll see you next time no i'm just
kidding what what is your you you love pokemon go you play it a lot what's your take on this
whole thing uh yeah basically as you'll probably know i i do like a lot of what is pokemon and
especially pokemon go i talk about it oh probably probably for every week uh if you see me on
twitter i post a lot about it uh either getting chinese getting like perfect id
pokemon playing go battle league me ugly begging you to join a remote raid
sometimes yeah or open gifts stuff like that but yeah uh but basically i just want to
add a little bit to at least a little bit little bit more of context to what's happening right now
yeah well yeah and obviously you all take all talked about uh the covid bonuses and all that
uh and especially the distance thing which it is it actually it is actually really useful
and like dark sakura mentioned uh too it's it helps a lot of disabled people
uh i i personally know some of the uh in the community that actually benefited but because
of that because they are disabled or they don't they don't have like easy access to some of the
polka stops so it actually helps them and at the end of the day it helps us all but aside that
aside that it's pretty much in you've already said it it's the handling of all the things it's like
yeah they responded they said they're they're they're listening or they're hearing us but at
the same time the next day when the part uh part two of the ultra unlock starts and right now you
can get a heracross from from raids it's just a regional it's a regional that it's all available
in some places of florida and most of latin america not where i live because i live to way
to up north of mexico but but still it's like okay it should be available in the wild it should
be uh for those who live in those regions it should be accessible for them and what did
diane take went and do they took out the wild spawn of heracross they took out they took it
out pretty much of out of the game and the only way you can get anywhere what is a heracross
it's only through raids you only get one one raid per day one at least one free pass
per day and you have to go to the gym uh so for anyone that oh yeah i live in central mexico i
live in south america whatever oh i can uh a lot of people were excited they're excited because
oh we're gonna we're gonna get a regional shine and niantic doing that and especially after what
they did the day before is what is driven most people like really really out of the game and
the point of all this is communication if niantic where to communicate better what their what their
plans are if they actually like consider what the community wants and likes about the game
we wouldn't have these problems it's like and and and i was one to defend niantic in the past and
and there's evidence of that too i'm not gonna i'm gonna like hide it but it got to the point
and especially this week that um that niantic is pretty much like at least they're showing us that
they don't care they don't care about us they don't care about the player base the only they
are they are only caring about getting the map you know in in my case yeah i'm gonna play the
game because like i said the game is about the community the game is about us that we made the
game basically but i'm not gonna spend any money on it like i don't no no no remote passes no
premium passes no incense nothing that is gonna come from my pocket if i get if i get like poke
coins that stuff it's gonna come from the gyms if i remember to do so you know but i was just
saying sorry but i'm glad you brought up the hair cross thing because you're right i'd forgotten
about that and part of that is probably just because i'm spoiled because i don't live in that
area where the hair across usually spawned so i forgot that this was the thing now if i remember
right niantic and again i and and let me finish my thought here because uh i i do think niantic
made a boo-boo on this but if i remember right there was a tech issue where if they had kept
niantic uh or if they kept hair across in the wild it would have that same shiny rate that
was increased for the gyms so i think they increase it to like one in 64 in the gyms ends
up being a shiny and if they did that in the wild it would put too many of the shiny hair
crosses or whatever in the wild and so i think they're going to put it back after the gyms are
done but it would be at that normal shiny rate of like one in 512 or something like that now
that all being said and i've explained the the system limitation uh there's a very common line
we've started to use on this show a lot in fact it's not maybe the golden rule of gaming where
a system is only as good as the games that are on it but maybe it's the the silver rule of gaming
culture and that is it's not the facts it's what's perceived and the fact is if the tech
system is broken niantic and the tech system is preventing you from having the thing in spawn in
raids at the same time it's in the then fix the fucking tech that's the problem because what's
being perceived by folks like mike deft and many people around is is just that you're being shit
greedy is is what's happening and so the tech side of that badly needs to be fixed quite
honestly um can i tell you a weird anecdote though and it honestly has nothing to do with
this but it was weird to me so you know that before all this covid shit started i was i was
in that part of the world right i went to miami to take a cruise to some of the caribbean which is in
that same you know uh a latitude area that like the parts of mexico where hair across spawns in
is and i caught lots of regionals i caught corsola i caught the um cactus thing that is
in that area in florida as well maractus yeah well maractus was the big one because that's
that was the one that when i brought back like all the big pokemon players were in this area were
like can i please trade you for a miraculous because that's the one you couldn't get anywhere
else um and then uh and they're all gone now that's the one pokemon like all of them went
that i caught anyway carne vine that's the one i was trying to think of that part of the world
so i got all this i didn't catch a single hair across that entire time just a weird a weird
antidote that has nothing to do with this but it so when i was hearing about this i was like well
hair across didn't fucking spawn anyway like because i was like i didn't catch them when i
was down there but apparently that is very much just like apparently they spawn everywhere and
it might just depend on the time like maybe i just was there at a weird time the only way i had a
hair across was from our pal jd because he was playing pokemon go at the time and he went to
florida on a family trip and he caught one and traded it to me so i had a hair across before
this but now i'm like well i want a pink one but yeah of course i'm not i'm not affected by the
whole um it but but another pokemon that spawns in raid right now is kangaskhan right and i'm
hearing that australia which is the new zealand which is the region or no does new zealand have
or they have just relicanth right they they i i think they have kangaskhan on new zealand too
and obviously australia it's like the oceania oceania but either way i'm hearing that they did
not pull the kangaskhan wild spawns in australia so that is just again just a weird fucking
perception too like okay but the kangaskhan are just gonna be everywhere in shiny but the hair
across can't so i i mean i get it i get why people are like dude you guys suck and and that's not
not only that there's precedent of them unlocking regional shinies before and keep it done in the
wild so it's like it's it's not necessarily that they need to boost or they they want to keep it
like fair quote-unquote for everyone it's no it's it's like there's nothing that should
uh prevent them or like stop them to to release in the wild because again there's
already a precedent we already have like taro's as you said kangaskhan barfetch and mr mine which
are regionals uh on someplace of the world and when those were really shiny though they were
still spawning on the wild i i actually remember getting a wild taurus during that event in
particular and getting the shiny because it wasn't the wild it was not only in eggs it was in the
wild and it was i think full on it's what it was for once so even like something like hair across
and i i understand what you're saying it's like understandable but at the same time
they didn't that before they didn't do that before yeah so doing this right now it's like baffling
and so many people are actually angry they're they're not putting anything in the game some
up some many have happened too well but again it yeah it's i was just to say it is it is
interesting sometimes to see where the player base will break and say you know what and i'm
talking in mass where the player brace bait breaks off and says you know what fuck this i'm out
because another game i'm thinking of that recently had this happen is world of warcraft and this is
this was happening before any of the activision blizzard stuff for the past few weeks so let's
try try to now as i'm saying this not that that is not part of that it is now for some people
certainly but at the time people were still breaking off of world of warcraft in mass and it
it seemed like it just seemed like the weirdest to from me who broke off world of warcraft eight
years ago i was like now you're leaving world of warcraft like because they did something with
sylvanas that was like i'm like the it's the story of the last few expansions has been pretty mad
this is just weird that like now you're leaving okay but um now it's like with pokemon go it's
like hair across that's the thing that sets you off okay interesting but i'm just i'm i don't i
don't mean that in a negative or condescending way it's just it's interesting to me what sets
off the player base in mass sometimes i think uh not only the hair across thing but it's like
the snowball getting bigger and bigger and again coming this coming after niantics like
like like really really bad response i i don't want to go way further into my words but it was
a really bad response and even i and when when they put out the response they posted it i was
at least they responded they did something better than nothing but after seeing the hair across thing
is like yeah i cannot justify them anymore it's like i'm done with them but again it's like
and and i was talking earlier this on my own um gff cast uh that i do not feel the like the
tinesing fallacy or whatever it's called because i have so many good memories of the game and
i have met so many awesome people through pokemon go it's like i have i have found so many communities
even like in on twitch it's like there's so many good stuff i have from the game that i have
uh gotten from it it doesn't necessarily in the game so yeah i was i'll still play pokemon go
i'll do like again go battle league i'll do raids whenever i can when when i do have like free
passes all that stuff but again i'm i'm not like really in the mood to put any money into it like
like uh sj 100 mad saying like uh the the community days the one dollar thing it's like
yeah i'm not gonna buy that i always buy it even if it sucks but now it's like i'm not gonna buy it
at all yeah so yeah it's like um and it's so it's like it's like it's a really easy fix it's not
they're not necessarily talking about the game it's like gigantic just communicating to us like
being a little bit more transparent if they're like expect and again that's returning to the
heracross thing if they had said oh heracross is only gonna appear in raids at least we would know
it's like okay we we understand okay it's whatever we'll wait if if we want if we are in the region
and all that stuff but like being so secretive for something like that it's like no no this
that's not how we play let me ask this question before we wrap it all up because um we're gonna
play the hypothetical world where um and i love this hypothetical world because the hypothetical
world where rob is right so let's play in this hypothetical world where rob is right that uh
what i said ends up happening the the 80 meters comes back but you're gonna burn out pokey stops
after four spins for a four hour period i don't know something like that so let's say they kind
of do like a halfway type of uh thing is that gonna bring you back into the fold or have we
gone past the point of no return at this point
it's like even if they actually do a radius thing like like even like if you say it's like it's
going to be done like oh a burnout after first things like they do in english it's like it's
the same on english if they do that the same as ingress it's like okay it's a compromise
but we i still need to see more from them it's like we still have so many problems in the game
uh and and like again go battle league the lag the the bugs all that stuff it's like still present
in the game yeah uh so many many stuff in terms of uh of cash grabbing like the raids like the eggs
there's so many things that need to be addressed at least that until they do that i will i will
invest in the game of fair but until then yeah that's that's like no go even if they do that
it's like no we have to at least keep a little bit of pressure into address at least them addressing
all that you know what's really interesting and i i totally forgot to bring this up during my gaming
week but i'll bring it up now on wednesday night i actually went to an ingress meetup and it was
an official ingress meetup because you know there's a whole kind of separate team and group
that's working on that and maybe you've even heard of this uh deafness some of it's probably you know
crosses over and some stuff like oh well look what they're doing over on this side they have
that whole van tour or the xm detection van which is the whole thing of the ingress lore so they
have this van traveling around right now it was just in portland yesterday and i think it's in
boise on tuesday and it was just here in sac on uh wednesday so i actually went downtown and it
was there was about 75 people there because you know ingress doesn't have quite the fan base that
pokemon go does but it has its own loyal fan base right and um you know they they did their welcome
and everything it was and part of i think why they're doing this is they're actually kind of
introducing like their new community manager for like ingress at niantic who's done um a good job
so far i would say she had a really nice write-up about the event and she was really like engaging
with people and you know so forth i thought she did a very good job with the event overall
but i thought what was interesting is that when she was being introduced by the other guy
he was like you know and uh you know let her know all your feedback that you have on ingress and
you know all the other niantic stuff too if you have feedback on pokemon go or harry and you could
just see her eyes kind of went like like shut up shut up don't no no i don't want to talk about
the game because that was well it was she was at least uh but she uh i quit on friday yeah but
the community matter for pokemon go actually quit yeah i heard that not the same person just to be
clear but yes i heard that whole thing as well it's very interesting but i just a funny anecdote
your story kind of or your your comment reminded me to tell about the whole like taking feedback
like she's still kind of like you know smiling like sure i'll hear what you have to say because
luckily it's only 75 people and most of them care primarily about ingress right but there's
there's a hell of a lot of overlap there were plenty of people wearing pokemon go shirts
and i certainly have my little pokeball because we do what i call dual wielding we're playing
ingress on our phone and we're bluetooth catching on the pokeball we're dual wielding the games so
there's a lot of us that do play both so it's just uh i thought that i thought that was interesting
how she she kind of was like i i've opened because that was the same day as that letter
i think so i think she was very much like i want to talk about it i want to talk about it
i'm not i don't have my bullet points they probably knew if it was wednesday and the on the
letter thing was thursday they oh they probably knew because the letter was made by influencers
who worked with niantic on pokemon go anyway it was brewing it was brewing it was definitely like
you knew like people were pissed so anyway uh mike deft uh the rebranded act f mike deaf thank
you thank you so much for uh calling in tonight i do want to see if we can get to some other calls
but um thank you so much uh if you speak spanish you really owe it to yourself to check out the
gfm cast if you don't speak spanish um you still support them in other ways uh but uh
mike deft it's always a pleasure to have you here i'm glad we can have you back on the show
thank you for having me all right you take care of my friend
yes all right bye-bye all right i think we have another call so we're gonna oops
i tried to drag deft out of the chat and i ended up dragging the studio out of the chat
oh whoops for the record rob we don't have any emails oh yes i was gonna acknowledge there are
no emails tonight um because you mentioned that before the show participate at orange
launch radio.com if you'd like to send us an email please let's uh let's have some of those
new future week all right that's okay we're still working the bugs out here as we're getting back
into taking phone calls here on olr but we do have another person on the line i'd like to get to it
hi you're on orange launch radio who's this it's sterlock hey sterlock it is good to hear from you
so i have a funny feeling because i know you called into bobby's show tonight i have a feeling
we might hear a similar topic but that's that's okay yes that's okay this is this is a good thing
for people to know about so tell us uh what's what what would you like to talk about tonight
so uh it all started with some reddit thread um
a couple weeks ago i posted a thread on reddit uh asking if uh you know hearthstone could be
modded to be accessible and i got just quite a bit of sorry i don't mean to cut you off but i
want to make sure our listeners who don't already know know because you've called into the show
before but admittedly in this covet age we haven't been taking a lot of phone calls for a bit so um i
just want to make sure those that don't know know that you are a blind gamer and you've often called
into the show kind of talking about um games that have like awesome accessibility things like the
last of us part two and um you know so forth and games are not so great accessibility because i
think these are good things for us to sort of keep in mind is that hey there's lots of people
out there that would like to play games but sometimes can't and so this is with you and
hearthstone so sorry i just want to make sure people have that background yeah yeah yep no
problem um and you know the the thread got quite a bit of traction and a lot of people are like oh
that would actually be really cool and then you know there were some people that were interested
and and you know thoughtful and but there are a lot of people were just like i don't know how this
could be done and some people were even like well this might be against blizzard tos you know to add
keyboard support um i can tell you that that's not going to be a concern um for reasons i'll get into
later but um so that you know i that thread goes on for like a day day and a half and kind of
fizzles out because you know reddit um and i didn't really you know think anything of it
it's like yeah you know it would have been cool if something came of it um but then i got a couple
that someone a couple people added me on reddit like look at this and uh turns out somebody had
already been working behind the scenes in secret for i guess months like completely independent of
my thread to make hearthstone uh accessible to blind people nice and uh it's you know it's pretty
you know it's pretty basic right now i mean it's it works very very well like battling works
flawlessly um what is lacking currently is uh selecting other modes and deck editing
and things like that but uh he wants to keep working on it and
yeah so basically what this does is it interfaces with your screen reader and you have a lot of
keyboard shortcuts to get to various parts of the field
and uh sorry i think i interrupted you no you're fine you're fine i want to make sure you you get
your piece out because i think it's important for people to know like you know kind of like
how this makes the experience um accessible for you um yeah but one thing i want to kind of with
the with the terms of service and the tos that whole thing i think the last thing blizzard needs
right now is a case on their hands where they shut down a mod that is making a game more accessible
um that is not the pr story blizzard needs right now so like um this this this will be in the clear
yeah no absolutely yeah well plus plus um there is a known blizzard uh developer oh named nikki
crenshaw uh who frequents a friend of mine uh super blind man uh he's a blind streamer
uh he streamed this on on friday when it came out and she happened to tune in and uh saw this and
she was just over the moon and apparently she showed it around to the the office and people
are just oh my gosh this is insane so that that those are those now that's good because
especially if she was you know one person is one person but if she was showing other people in the
office now that's a conversation and that might lead to the whole well how did this guy do it
maybe we should do this and blizzard does have a track record and from having covered world
warcraft for years and years blizzard at least the old blizzard but i don't see why you know
there's a lot of great people at blizzard still there's still yeah really good people at blizzard
even if some of the execs are crappy people exactly um and that's why that's why i don't
feel bad about playing this and and supporting because there's also rumors that diablo 2 is
going to be accessible so you can absolutely do both but i was going to say yeah wow wow did have
that track record of if a mod was really popular they like deadly boss mods was like almost like
a must-have mod for raid boss encounters they ended up yeah they ended up like incorporating
some of that into the main game so they they do look at the mods out there and the stuff that's
really popular they do have a tendency to kind of so that could bode very well for this um but let
me we're hoping we're hoping we uh we're hoping that like they decide i don't know if they're
going to but it would be awesome if uh you know blizzard you know gets a hold of them like hey
let's uh let's talk let's talk about how this works um let me ask you this though before uh
you know because uh we do have to wrap things up here pretty soon but i want to make sure uh i get
your opinion you know accessibility issues aside now that you've had the chance to play hearthstone
how do you like hearthstone as a game so good it's so good i just unlocked uh all the classes
and uh still working on getting the initial levels you know up to 10 to get the core the core cards
and uh i actually played a couple online matches even though so you can't i'm not gonna get into
specifics but there's a way with your screen reader even though it's not supported in the mod
itself to get there accessibly there's a way to do it where you can get to um online matches so
i've actually played a few uh online matches and so i'm kind of working on clawing my way out of
apprentice which is the basically like the newbie ranks yeah um and you get more cards by by
completing that so you know if nothing else i hope blizzard doesn't just hear about that i'm
so happy it's accessible but i hope blizzard hears that enthusiasm when you said it's so good
i hope that is what's heard where it's like hey by implementing something like this officially
you can make a lot of people say what you just said about hearthstone and i think that that
should be the most exciting getting it is getting like it's spread around now like a lot of the
blind community is playing it and is super excited about it so um yeah i i'm looking
forward i'm looking forward to deck building and uh packet opening because those are things that
are not currently uh accessible yet but uh hopefully soon all right well sterlock i'm
gonna let you go so we can wrap up the show but thank you i appreciate the update and uh what's
going on there i think that's good stuff for people to know about and uh keep us posted on
future um efforts for more games um to get those sorts of features i'd love to hear your take on
it definitely all right take care of my friend yeah you too all right bye-bye all right and
with that i think we are uh going to oh if i can find the right shot there there we go uh we're
going to get into a few more segments here and then we're going to wrap up here uh let me get to
last minute stories loki i don't know if you have anything tonight but do you have any last minute
stories i did have one thing so there was a deal that happened this week between uh trade parker
and matt stone with viacom cvs regarding south park so they're gonna be bringing like 14 movies
um several seasons and a video game um in the works apparently so we're getting another south
park video game at some point so that's pretty awesome i'm not surprised those games have done
pretty well but i've it is interesting how is it that these animated series are on forever like
south simpsons has been on forever uh south park uh forever family guy feels like it's been on
forever uh futurama has got to be getting good is is that show still on i think that's getting
canceled oh has it oh i feel like i'm still seeing it all the time so okay all right but still i feel
like like wow there's a lot of animated shows that go on for a very long time but you know why this
one's interesting because when i first read it and you know insert whatever joke you want about
south park being relevant all this stuff look it's just i i just want to talk about the deal itself
the the whole fact that they they've commissioned 14 movies you know that whole thing is just a
workaround right because hbo max through comedy central has the right to south park or no no
because comedy central is part of viacom but hbo max or somehow has the deal for one way or another
this is paramount plus or viacom leveraging their arm to get content for paramount plus
so the shows are going to be on hbo max at least for a couple more years and now paramount plus
is getting its own original content as well that's the part i think is fascinating about the deal
how they kind of strong-armed their own content for paramount plus because yo drag race all-stars
season six is going to be over in a few more weeks whenever they finish their game within a game so
it's time for new original content i guess huh i guess yeah yeah for sure that's cool
yeah for sure um all right uh one other thing and yes thank you i'm glad you brought this up
uh as joe and her to matt because i saw your uh post in our discord about it over at vog network
dot com slash discord if you want to join our discord and chat with us throughout the week
um as joe and her matt says thoughts on the cookie clicker i said cookie clitter i almost did
cookie clicker remaster and yes that is they are remastering cookie clicker
and bringing it back i don't know how to feel about it i would rather see a clicker heroes
remaster because the sequel wasn't that good the sequel wasn't as good as the first one
so that's uh that's what it is pixel pakas just put rob in all caps i can't help it
rob rob rob rob rob rob rob rob rob rob all right i can bring that back you know what's that
i could bring that back you could you could um let's see uh there was a car or there was a
question from no one special 77 earlier before we started in the phone calls here we go uh and i
thought this was worth addressing real quick here in the spirit of the flag this week i'll ask this
what's the weirdest game you personally have played and he didn't specify arcade so we've
been talking about the weird arcade games through dark soccer segment maybe the weird
console games that you've played what are some what's the weirdest console game you've played
well the weirdest game i've played in the arcade isn't all that weird but uh probably prop cycle
i love prop cycle i love it it's not it's not it's just an unusual game it's not like terrible
not bad it's just fun i'll go one step further and say the prop cycle adams family that's what
i was gonna say i was gonna say what the yeah the prop cycle adams family stop stealing a potential
idea well you said it first you stole it from me so they have a prop cycle ab family game like you
power you you have to run the prop cycle to power the machine isn't it like that oh that okay i
thought it was like an actual prop cycle game where you like fly around through like the adams
family house or something like that i was like that sounds really cool why haven't i seen that
but no that's that's different okay i'll talk about something not in the arcade you know what
was a weird game nintendo dogs that game was a little weird i mean it was cute i'm not saying
i'm not saying it wasn't cute i'm just saying it was happy petting sim and they didn't they didn't
really take it as far as they should have in my opinion i'm surprised we never really got a true
i know there was the nintendo dogs plus cats for the 3ds but i'm surprised we never got like a
proper switch sequel and we just had all the knockoff stuff instead you know what else was
connect the moles you know what are you not impressed by connect the moles here's another
weird game the cooking mama game that mined bitcoin that's a weird game although that wasn't
true but in in my brain my head canon is it was true cooking mama things like scribble knots
oh that's a good one scribble knots is good there's a lot of scribble knots games man there's
a all very strange oh magic pen gel that game yeah that legend at the apartment that loki and
i used to live in absolutely time to penis all right i mean and let's not even start about uh
nobi nobi boy which i played a lot of ribbon so no nobi nobi boy man i rock those shirts i have
two nobi nobi boy shirts and i wear rock those every day i agree with sturlock tulip was an
interesting game yeah it was also that dream simulator game that came out that i played very
briefly it was called like lsd or something oh yeah sort of remember yeah what was that infamous
turbo graphics 16 game with the muscle men a choaniki that's it yeah yeah good times
all right it's everything on the awful block all right uh we gotta gotta wrap things up here um
i want to thank you guys for tuning in to orange launch radio and supporting us again this week
thank you so much for downloading our show or listening to us live however you participated
with the show uh all we ask please tell a friend about the show help us spread the word because we
are the show where every gamer has a voice but we need more voices here to get out on the air
especially now that we're getting more of you to call out uh on the phone call segments before like
that last call we heard about um the the additional accessibility through a mod for hearthstone that
we only hear about things like that thanks to our community so please tell a friend and help us
spread the word about our show um oh rob yes w aforementioned c man and i agree oh that's a good
one um if uh what's gonna say oh uh our discord over at vog network.com discord please join it
chat with us throughout the week appreciate that um we would also uh if you you don't have to but
if you feel so inclined to give a little coin uh vog network.com slash shop you know loki was
just talking about picking up two nobi nobi boy shirts i just bought two shirts on the shop this
week uh because uh with dragon khan on the horizon i wanted him for that or if if you know i'll just
have them to have them if nothing else i bought uh two dark soccer made shirts i bought the vog
network uh spray painty logo looking thing and i bought that sega e orange launch radio thing so
i have two shirts for those i have a baseball jersey of each so um i'm glad that you enjoyed
them yes uh well i haven't gotten them yet but i wear i'll wear one on the next show once they
get here i don't think they've shipped yet either which is weird but i'm trying not to read too much
into that so um yeah uh vog network.com shop if you want to do that and uh yeah uh auto host on
twitch uh hosting of the channel for vog network goes an awful long way uh also we really appreciate
the support on our personal endeavors uh loki has his youtube channel over at loki underscore olr
i'm sorry no loki olr sorry um dark sakura has her twitch channel which is dark sakura
underscore underscore or okay that's where i get mixed up underscore olr which you can follow on
twitch i am also here on twitch at rob roberts um we appreciate that so um i think that's it we're
gonna get to final thoughts and i will start dark sakura i should start with you
um i would love if people hang out with me tonight and let me know if you like any of
the designs that i've made on the orange lounge shop i plan on making more excellent uh all right
and um loki we'll go to your your final thought um hopefully gonna be putting out some more videos
soon can't wait to see them yeah all right and then my final thought is um the the last bandage
came off of my neck today from the surgery a couple weeks ago and i'm happy to say and
i'm turning around for the camera here on twitch i'm happy to say it looks pretty fucking normal
back there there's just a very thin red light you probably can't even see it on the camera at this
point there's just a very thin red line and probably what's going to be a pretty bitching
scar but it's really not much going on back there so that's pretty exciting
and three in three more days i can get into pool again and submersion water so there's that all
right that's it that's going to do it for another episode of orange launch radio have a fantastic
week everybody and we'll see you in seven days to do it all over again happy gaming be nice to
people online be nice people in general have a good good week everybody bye you've been listening
to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr studios to join us for a live
show tune into fog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m eastern the views and opinions
expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio
or bog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you