Gamescom's presentation has come and gone and I keep seeing comments about a resounding
meh, which I think is awfully ironic but maybe this is just my Aunt or Grandpa Simpson coming
out yet again. Meanwhile, I'll be over here waiting to play another horror game involving
a camera so I can ramp up my personal paranoia all over again. Horror games done right.
This is one of many headlines you expected to hear and now it's time for your hosts Rob
Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to go into detail about this and the rest of the week's
gaming news. Starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet. Welcome back to another week of the show where
every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio and we are live once again with episode
number 882 of our show for this August the 29th of 2021. My name is Rob Roberts and let's
talk about video games. We're going to talk about some video games with my co-hosts. Say
hello first off to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers. Hi.
Hi. You're looking great. I love your new hair that you have.
Oh yeah, let me. Hold on, hold on. I have to do it.
While you do it. Which folks can see if they... Yes, she's shaking out her hair. Sorry. Which
folks can see if they watch live over at Twitch TV slash VOG Network or VOG Network.
Sunday nights at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Black Wolf show.
But we know it's a podcast. We try not to rely too much on the visuals, but I had to
comment on DarkSakura's red lovely hair she's got going on there. So kudos.
It's a gradient. Kudos to your barber, whoever they may be.
Well, thank you. My, my, my friend Hillary is awesome. She does great work. She is worth
every penny I pay. But this was a long time coming. Cause you remember when I went black?
I do. Of course. Yeah. Well, we let it grow and we let it grow and
we let it grow just for the sake of being able to do a red to black gradient.
Oh, clever. Some advanced planning. I like that. We do.
There are pictures of me blonde and y'all will never see them.
We do have our live chat room that gives us some comments here. Pod Culture mentions Sassy
do. So, uh, yeah, I think, uh, I think, uh, this is a very clearly you could be in a shampoo
commercial if you wanted, but anyway, well, it's just expensive styling products.
All right. Also say hello to tech master Loki with the short, short hair that, uh, isn't
gradient or styled, but that's okay. Hi lucky. It doesn't have to be too short. That's okay.
You don't have to hide yours under a hat. Like I do. Cause mine's, mine's a little out
of control right now. Cause, uh, it's about time to shave the hide yours either. I don't.
And actually I've done a few shows here at OLR without a hat, but here's the thing, uh,
with dragon con coming up this week, I'm actually waiting until like the last minute to give
myself a fresh buzz and then I'll go out to, uh, dragon con.
Le Bald. So, uh, uh, those that, those that I will see there this year, you have that
to look forward to so under the hat, but I will still have plenty of hats at dragon con.
Uh, Loki, what is the game playing behind you tonight on Twitch? You usually run a little
video game behind you there on the green screen. It's a shadow run on the SNES. Oh, it sure
is. It took me a minute to recognize it. And the minute you said it, I'm like, it sure
is shadow because my head's in the way. So you can't really see it. Yeah. Yeah. But I
can see enough now that I make out the character and there was a screen just before that. I
gotcha. That's a classic. That's a good one. Um, I was playing games today too. We will
get into our gaming weeks here after we do the kickoff topic, but I have to quickly mention
I ran into the studio not long before showtime. So I was a little better than I was expecting,
but I went to an ingress event this morning in San Francisco. So, uh, my buddy is that
who sometimes listens to the show who also plays the game. Uh, we got in a car here at
nine AM, drove out to San Francisco. We actually got there. Traffic, the traffic gods were
very good today. We parked at about 10 45, which is kind of unheard of for a trip to
San Francisco to only really actually be an hour and a half. And then, uh, we, we did
what's called a mission day, did a bunch of missions around there and they did this
thing called a van event where you like hack the van basically. Uh, and then we got in
the car and came back and, uh, the traffic gods were a little meaner on the way home,
but I still made pretty good time home. So, uh, hacking a van, isn't that like hot wiring?
I, I, something like that. It's hacking the planet. No, I, I, is it one of those free
candy vans that I've heard about? Yes. Except it ties into the lore of ingress, but I don't
play video games for lore. Well, that's not true. Sometimes I really get into the lore.
Like a lot of the final fantasy games, there's many video games where I'm just like, I don't
care about the lore. I just want to play the game. And ingress is one of them. So the,
the van is something about detecting XM. I don't know, it plays with the story somehow.
So being able to, because it travels or it's a moving portal. So let me, let me, cause
I know hardly anyone plays ingress. So let me, um, let me give the analogy to Pokemon
go. Imagine if a Poke stop moved from city to city. That's, that's basically what the
van kind of is. Uh, which I guess actually the van has shown up as a temporary, uh, pokey
stop sometimes. Cause there are people will post it to Reddit going, what the hell is
this as a pokey stops. It's kind of funny. It's the government spying on you. It's fine.
That's right. Take this Pikachu in return. Here's all your, where you take all your privacy,
which is, which is honestly true. Uh, all right. We're just going to Pikachu at your
network package. How would you like to buy all of these Pokemon products now? Let's get
into the gaming news of the week. We're going to start off with our kickoff topic tonight
that has to do a games com because there was a quite a bit of information that came out
of, came out of games com about what to expect at this coming year, uh, including X-Box did
their own event. And then we had the opening light, opening light, opening night live event
from Jeff Keeley, you know, who does the game awards and has done, you know, uh, did
that E3 summer game Fest. So I feel like he does three or four of these types of big to
do press conference. I keep calling press conferences, but they're really like media
events, media spectacles, um, every year. And I I'm going to get just right into it
Loki cause I need the details because I saw the tweets. So opening night live, we talked
about this last week on OLR. We knew there was going to be a saints row reboot, uh, that
was going to be announced at this. It was, it was like way past rumor status to where
they were tweeting like teaser images and stuff. So they actually showed us a little
glimpse of what the next saints row game looks like. And saints row, I know is one of your
very favorite series, Loki, although you kind of, you kind of like the saints row two era
of the game.
Well, I still liked, I liked saints row. Okay. So like saints row as a game, let's just,
let's imagine. So they did announce the saints row reboot, which is just being so tell us
your thoughts, Loki on this reboot.
I'm good. I'm getting there. Okay. So they have the reboot that they announced it's coming
out February 25th, um, next year and it takes place in this new city called Santo Aliso,
which is kind of like, think of like a Vegas type of thing. And so it's a little bit more
of like that kind of, uh, type of environment or maybe like, um, Arizona, new Mexico, that
type of thing. Um, and so they, they showed it off like, and here's, here's a good indicator
of how I thought it was. So I saw the trailer and to myself before I even knew it was saints
row, I'm like, I really hope this isn't saints row. I really hope this isn't saints row.
And then I saw, you know, I forget to call it. Um, I saw the purple, I saw the symbols
and like, Oh God, it's, it is saints row. Isn't it? So here's the problem. So saints
row had a really great cast of characters that really kind of drove this series. Like
I always talk about like Johnny Gat in the game, like very awesome character. Um, and
you know, even just like Julius and like all really characters, you know, given to life
by like really big name stars, these characters were as generic as possibly it could be like,
and this is granted, this is not a gameplay trailer they showed. This is like a cinematic
trailer, I guess. But even, but even like with cinematic trailers, like in the past
with like saints row three and stuff, it had been really awesome. Like just really like
nailing home. This is the vibe of the game. Like this is going to be really cool. All
this, the only vibe I got from this is like, this is the most generic game I've ever seen.
Can I jump to the punchline here, Loki though? And that you're going to buy it anyway though,
right? I we'll see, but here's the thing. Okay. We'll see. So like probably I will buy
it, but like, here's the, here's the problem. And like, and don't get me wrong. Like I'm
sure the game is a good game, but what they showed does not convey anything about the
series. So for example, like one of the things that the, the voice actress or the actress
that was in the, the presentation basically said, I'm the new boss in this game. Not exactly.
Okay. Cause they do still have the character customization. She's basically playing the
female voice actress for the role. They, they usually have a male role as well, but it wasn't
conveyed at all. So right there, like people thought immediately, Oh, so there's no customization
anymore. And just, you know, what's up with that. And then, you know, it wasn't conveyed
also with the co-op the like co-op in the game. So there's a whole lot of details that
they didn't really talk about in gameplay that they showed was just so minimal and yeah,
the game looks like saints row when you play it, but also they talking about like, Oh,
let's bring it back a little bit less ridiculous and more realistic. Oh, but there's going
to be flying motorcycles and VTOLs and stuff like that. That's just Saints Row 3 again,
they're making Saints Row 3 again, but except this time they've taken out all of the good
characters in the game and they have these like knockoffs. It's like, it's like if Epic
games were copying Saints Row for Fortnite and these are the characters that they came
out with. Like we have Kevin now who is like the new Johnny Gat basically kind of taking
on that role like this crazy, you know, Daredevil type of guy. You've got the, the Pierce stand
in with Dion. I think I don't remember his name, but who cares? It's like, it's basically
like the hot new game is coming from Nintendo. It's super Mark O brothers and it's coming
out and they're like, Oh, and then this person, they're the driver. It's like, but you're
playing the game as your care is the boss and you're driving the car. Like, why do I
need a driver? I don't need a driver. I'm like, who cares? Like it's just, I don't know.
It just really didn't sell me on it. Like if you want to sell me on it, like in you
bringing it back, like rebooting the franchise, here's my expectation was like, okay, reboot
the franchise, but like with the same cast of characters in there and just do something
different with it. Like for example, if I'm going to reboot Tomb Raider as they did, and
I didn't put Laura Croft in there, people would be throwing a fit about it. You know,
this game, this is, uh, this is Tomb Raider with Mary craft is actually, uh, the star
of this, uh, new Tomb Raider game. Or if it were, if it were, if I reboot, like, you know,
street fighter and I took out all of the characters that you liked in it, but it's still street
fighter. You're still actually, actually data East did that and called it fighting street.
That's a very famous court case. That is street. There's another thing about that because
that was actually a release of street fighter for turbo graphics, I think. Oh, right. But
wasn't that the whole, wasn't that the whole, is somebody completely ripped them out of
fighting? No. Yeah. That's art of fighting. No fighting street was the data East thing.
Anyway, allow me to history. Okay. That was it. Here's where I start to get concerned
and, and I'm going to, I have to find the quotes because the quote, okay, here's where
I get concerned. So chief creative officer, Jim Boone was interviewed talking about saints
row and their, their inspiration for the game. Now, remember saints row was a game that was
basically gangsters. There was drug dealing. There was Robbie and convenience stores. There
was pimping. There was drug running. There was gun running, stealing cars, all the fun
things you look forward to video games. So here, here's the new saints row. It is broadly
a contemporary millennial power fantasy. These disinfected millennials turn to crime, for
instance, put food on their table, feel part of the community and pay off their student
loans. That is not saints row. I don't know. I don't know about you guys, but I've had
a few millennial power fantasies in my day.
I don't know. I would, I would have turned to, to crime to pay off my student loans.
They were pretty expensive.
It is not saints for growth. Like this is just ridiculous. And the characters that they
show, I swear to God, it's like, it's like clout chasing, Tik TOK fantasy game. I mean,
that's what it is. It's just, it's stupid. And I get it that it's supposed to be like
a saints row game, but it really is not. It's like, you're trying to reboot. You're trying
to create another game and you're throwing the saints row label on it. Like you killed
the franchise. You basically killed the franchise rebooting. It's not going to help at this
point, like best of luck to you. And here's the thing. The game could be pretty good and
there may be are very engaging characters in it. I did not get that from the trailer.
I certainly didn't give that from their comments by the current, the creative leads, which
has been concerned. So the messaging could be bad. The messaging is terrible. It's, it's
you can't do worse than that. Like, and this is a company that had, um, uncle Busey, you
know, promoting saints, which was fantastic. Gary Busey promoting saints real too hilarious.
But like, I just, he is, he's crazy. And that, that was the whole point. It was like, he's
talking about weapons and stuff and it was great. And that's, you can do stuff, you can
dial it back in a way. Like if you want to make it like, I get it, like maybe pimping in a game
that comes out in 2021 is not PC enough for the mainstream audience nowadays. That's fine. Take
that out. Okay. Whatever. You know, but like going back to even saints row, the third, they didn't
have drug dealing in it. It was dealing your merch, which was stupid to begin with. But like, I
get the point, like they were just trying to do the same mini game, but like, Oh, we're making it
even more rated G or something for everybody. They're covering their asses. Well, whatever.
It's a, it's a mature rated game. They don't have to like it. They don't do that in grand theft auto,
like take the chances, take the risk. Well, but if that was the case, hot coffee would have still
been in the game in grand theft auto days. There are certain things that they don't want to cross
because they don't want to end up on the NBC nightly news. But that's just, it just wasn't
the time. Here's the problem. It is a very American thing. This country has a bigger
problem with sex than it does with violence. Just saying. Yeah. And I get the, I get the idea. They
have to dial it back because like, where do you go from ripping off the matrix and the, you know,
the head of the saints is the president and you know, you've gone into space and stuff of like,
that doesn't make any sense anymore. Like what game is that? Even like it may be a fun game,
but it sounds, it is, it's a parody of a parody. Um, and I get it. You have to dial it back. I
think, like I said, you know, I'm a big fan of Saints Row 2. I thought that that kind of took
what Saints Row had originally established and took it to the next level. Like there was
ridiculous stuff in there that doesn't make any sense whatsoever. Like there was a mini game where
you set yourself on fire and drove around on an ATV. Cool. That's that's ridiculous. That's a
little bit extreme. You could rip out and you can rip out signposts and fire hydrants and stuff like
that in like fight people with that. Like that's ridiculous. I did that yesterday, but that's also
a little bit more grounded in reality. Like I, I, I hear them saying that, Oh yes, we're going to
make this game, you know, we're going to dial it back and stuff. And it's like, but once again,
they have the same, almost the same factions that they did is Saints Row the third. It's like the
remaking Saints Row the third. We've got, we've got this one faction that, you know, Oh, they're
kind of cyber technology. Okay. Well that's like in Saints Row the third. Oh, we have this other
faction, you know, they're more of like muscle and stuff like that. Okay. Like the luchadors.
Um, and then, Oh yeah. And then we've got this, you know, kind of security company. Oh, you mean
like in Saints Row the third, they're literally remaking Saints Row the third again for the fourth
time. Like, all right. I got, I got to get some comments in our chat over at twitch.tv slash
vog network. Uh, we had a comment about the gameplay. I wanted to read here. She Hulk 10
in our chat says the actual gameplay part looked last gen Xbox three 60 era graphics. That's why
they chopped it up with video cut scenes. They only showed like four seconds of gameplay, right?
They did only show like a few seconds of gameplay. They've also done early. They know they also had,
they showed some more like in another, they've been doing these clips where like they had some,
I literally thought like I saw videos coming out and I thought that it was going to be an
apology video for such a terrible like trailer that they did, but no, instead it was just more
than doubling down on that. And they did show a little bit more gameplay footage than that, but
it looks like Saints Row. I mean, that's what it is. It looks like Saints Row, but the problem is
like, like the, yeah, the gameplay could be solid, but the care you need characters and like, yeah,
I get it. Maybe Kevin is a really cool character. I didn't get that from it. It just felt ridiculous.
It felt, it felt stupid. He does, the characters lacked charisma. Like,
whereas in the first game, like this nerve and talent, you, you really like, you know,
kind of like really get attached to these characters and like just their storylines.
They have depth to them, but like these characters meant nothing to me. And if it's like, Oh, these,
they're, they're college students and they have student loans and stuff like that. Like,
I'm sorry that like, what is this? Like, it's like, it's a millennial power fantasy.
It's like, it's so stupid. It's like, is this what they really think gangsters are nowadays?
It's just like people like, well, we're going to go. And even that trailer was stupid. It's
just like, Oh yeah, we're starting a criminal enterprise. Like, it's just like, it's stupid.
All right, grandpa, let's get you to bed. No, I get it. I get, I get, I understand the concerns.
A lot of the community, a lot of the community, here's the only reason I will, I will take a
chance on this game is because idle Ninja, who we'll get to about later, said that, listen,
like he had contributed to like, you know, feedback and stuff for it and said that the
game that they're making looks really positive and looks like a pretty solid game. So I will
give it a chance based on that. But so far, the marketing has been absolutely terrible.
And if this is the direction that they're going, it's just going to not be good.
There's been a lot of games where the marketing wasn't very good, but the game ended up being a
little bit better than that. I mean, honestly, like my brain, the first place my brain goes
is the entire Sony PlayStation 3 unveiling concert unveiling event, right? I mean, all this talk
about Ridge Racer and giant enemy crabs. I mean, all that stuff. I mean, I don't think that
particular game was notable, but all that stuff ended up out, out shadowing all the games
themselves. It's more, that's more of an awkward and out of touch versus like, this is just in,
this has been the contention for a while now. Like people have been asking for certain things
like Saints Row the Third. Once again, they made, I don't know if they don't, if Volition knows how
to craft a good story is I think the problem because like in Saints Row the Third, they're
like, yeah, we're going to, we're going to kill off one of the fan's favorite characters because
Ooh, you didn't see that twist coming. Like that was the reasoning for behind it. Like,
Oh, it will have some emotional impact. Yeah. People getting mad at you for doing that.
Like, and then they, then they like try to retcon it in the next game. They're all this kidding. He,
he got abducted by aliens. He didn't really die. It's like, come on. Like it is, it's just really
stupid. And I think that they don't know how to craft a story and I get it there. There is
a, you know, I don't want to dog on the developers here, but like, dude, look at the stuff that you're
putting out. Like, look at how like the people you're talking heads are putting out this kind
of stuff. Like what am I supposed to think at this point? Like, I get it. I don't have to buy
your game, but I don't know. I I'm very skeptical that this is going to be good at this point. It'll
be solid gameplay, but. DJ Rama S in chat says, I think we need to wait until more info on the
game comes out. Well, I mean, perhaps there's somewhat negative reception. I mean, of course,
we're just, I mean, in, in this bubble, we're just hearing from Loki, but I do feel like on the
wider, like social media and stuff, I don't feel like that trailer landed as big as people hoped
it would. And I think maybe I know Loki, you weren't as into the over the top comedy, but I
think that being completely missing was kind of damaging. I, and I think he goes, yeah, what's
what's considered over the top, like the, the space alien thing. And like, I'll read this
comment bonds. Double 06 says Epic game store gave away saints row, third remaster. That is true.
And the first question my girlfriend asked after seeing the trailer, do we still get the
penetrator? So that, that is, I think what people are talking about. Yeah. You won't get that
because that is too offensive nowadays. I know many millennials that have a giant purple dildo
bad as their power fantasy. So they sold it. I mean, people have that. It's just like,
yeah, that unfortunately nowadays people are going to take offense to it. And so they're not going to
put it in their game. Like I am fine with that. Who cares? The weapon was stupid. It was just like,
he, he looked at what we did. Like, you know, there's other things that they could do that
the saints row games have a really like, they really like to dive into this crazy BDSM
scene that they have in, in a lot of them. So there's a lot of like these weird
missions revolving around that kind of stuff. So I, are they going to still do that? Who knows?
I, I, I'm not even getting into like the details with that stuff. Like I don't care about weapons
and stuff right now. I'm more considering like, who are the characters? Who's the story about here?
And so far, I'm not liking what I'm seeing. All right. They're not interesting. All right.
Enough saints row. We've gone 20 minutes about saints row. Let's talk about some of the other
stuff at games com. So Loki, what were some of the other things we saw I guess in the opening
night or the Xbox or wherever you want to start? Yeah, sure. So starting off with like the Xbox
stuff more games, you know, we saw a new trailer for dying light two, which looks pretty awesome.
And that's supposed to be coming out here pretty soon. 7th of December. We've also got some more
footage of Microsoft flight simulator, which looks pretty cool. There is going to be, I guess,
some deal to bring a lot of the humble games to Xbox game pass on day one. So if you don't
remember humble is now also a publisher of games. So some of those indie games will be coming as
well. Let's see more stuff about games past ultimate and cloud gaming on Xbox consoles is
holiday. So that's pretty awesome that you've been able to do that. We had some DLC announced
for wasteland three, the holy detonation. It's more sea of thieves stuff. The mayhem ship they
had. So those are kind of cool stated decay to homecoming straight blade, lots of different stuff.
But yeah, I think I didn't get to see this, but I know that they ended with Forza horizon five,
which looks amazing. So definitely want to check that out eventually. So yeah. Yeah. Sadly,
I couldn't watch either one of these. I really just had to see the highlight reel just because
the timing was right in the middle of the workday, which, you know, it's it games com is a Europe
centered event. So yes, the time zones work out that it's a little earlier in the day for us.
But yeah, sadly, I kind of had to hear about this stuff after the fact, but I need to go back and
watch that Forza horizon five extra footage because apparently it shows the intro of the game,
which Forza horizon four had such a good one. Yeah, it's just it'll be interesting to see how
they top it. Yeah. And then let's see. So with the games com live, they're opening night stuff.
So aside from Saints Row, they showed off a trailer for Midnight Sons, which apparently
is that new strategy RPG from the folks that make Xcom. So that. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I have some
people very excited about that. I've checked that out, too. Yeah. So that looked interesting. They
showed a trailer for Call of Duty Vanguard, the single player campaign for that. And that's coming
out November 5th. Looked like Call of Duty looked pretty cinematic. So pretty awesome.
Show off some new trailer for Halo Infinite. They had one for like the multiplayer as well.
We had this cool indie game called Cult of the Lamb that's coming from Devolver Digital.
Super Monkey Ball Banana Mania. Yay. That's got a bunch of like characters, including Morgana.
And what else? They showed off a trailer for Lego Star Wars, the Skywalker Saga, which has now
been pushed back even more. So I think that's coming out next year now. The Outlast Trials,
in case you haven't played enough of the Outlast series. What else we get?
In case you didn't poop your pants enough playing the first two Outlast games. Here you go. Here's
a new one. Yeah, they have another trailer for Far Cry 6, which is coming out in this October.
Trailer for New World, which is coming out at the end of September. Age of Empires 4,
Valheim Hearth and Home, which I'm not sure if that's oh, that's an update that they're doing
with some balancing changes. Sifu, which is that kind of stylized martial arts game.
Death Stranding Director's Cut, which looks weird. What was all that weird side stuff they had in it?
They had a Mario Kart game type of thing in it. It's shenanigans.
We're just going to put all of the game into the game.
It is, but I'm not going to lie. I'm kind of into it. And I do want to get it whenever I get a
PlayStation 5. But I think I'll kind of wait for the newness to wear off a little bit so that it
maybe goes on sale a bit. But yeah, I have to admit all this extra stuff in Death Stranding,
some of it is so absurd. I kind of have to see it just because the game itself was so
such a unique mood. I don't want to use any negative terms because I actually really enjoyed
the game, but it was very unique for a video game. And so the fact that they're adding kind
of these silly tropes into it is fascinating to me. Then they have this other game called Dokke V,
which is almost like a, not necessarily like a Pokemon game, but it's a monster catching game.
Where you catch like a Dokke V, they say, where you exist with these monsters. But it's like,
kind of looks better than like Pokemon. Pokemon the hardcore.
It's like Pokemon, but it looks pretty awesome. Like, I don't know.
Yeah, I'm curious to hear more about it. So they have that. And I think that was pretty
much everything. Yeah. I mean, there was a lot. I mean, that opening night live was like a two
hour long thing. It was a long presentation, but you know, lots of good updates in there,
especially considering the bulk of what is coming out the rest of the year. We know about at this
point, you know, there's not going to be really any more holiday surprises. There may be a little
thing here or there, but there's not going to be any big surprises at this point. Well, they
can always, I mean, Nintendo does their own thing whenever they want to. But even then I wouldn't
set the bar too high for a Nintendo surprise. Oh gosh. My, my bar with Nintendo is incredibly low.
I would say like a Nintendo surprise would be Tetris 99 type of thing, you know, and I'm not
saying literally that, but you know, something in that caliber, like Pac-Man 99 kind of ended
up being so, or whatever it's called. There I'm not, well, maybe there will be another 99 game,
who knows, but I would think something in that kind of vein is where to, you know,
aim appropriately when it comes to big surprise for the holiday. Orange Ride in Chat says,
I'm sure people will still believe Nintendo is going to bring the great pumpkin.
Possibly. Yeah. A lot of people on Twitter and social media set the bar too high when it comes
to Nintendo. So probably. Oh, comment from Tiger Claw, who I know watches all things Ninja Turtles
very carefully. Is a big week for Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles as April was announced in Shredder's
Revenge. Yes. That, I did see a little bit on that, you know, it's, it's basically a throwback
to the old Ninja Turtles arcade game, right? Though the Ninja Turtles game, everybody loved,
right? And now they're, you know, kind of the, the Shredder's Revenge is very much that,
but, you know, for, for 2021 and now April is actually playable in it, which is kind of neat.
The fact that she kind of beats people with their microphones kind of fun. I've wanted to do the
same thing several times. So pretty fun. All right. Yeah. Let's talk about some things we
have been playing this week, not just the stuff we're looking forward to. Let's get into a segment
called how was your gaming week and what are the types of games you've been playing this week?
Dr. Sakura, we'll start with you. I did finally get my start back on Final Fantasy 14.
They put me right back on the same server my other two characters were on,
even though I tried something different. So whatever. And of course I played Dead
by Daylight. Apparently, and now this was actually a build that was suggested to me
and we did some modifications to it. Apparently my resident Pigou build is loved.
I was watching when you had Nick and Prince play your build on his stream. That was fun. Yeah.
Isn't it evil? It is just the whole concept of, yeah. Anyway, I don't want to,
we talk about too much Dead by Daylight on the show. I'm not going to get it.
Bourbon played it today. Oh, okay. And we switched out a corrupt intervention for Lethal Pursuer.
And it was pretty vicious. So I'm going to have to take that and incorporate it into the official
resident Pigou. All right. So anyway, and if anyone who's playing wants to know what resident
Pigou is, let me know. But it's called that because it relies on playing the Raccoon Police
Department, AKA RuPaul's Drag Station. Or just watch Dark Soccer's stream on Twitch.
I've been trying to get a number two rule set and have it or a tamper timer. No luck.
So I'm going back to leveling Pyramid Daddy with his nerfed butt.
Does he have any less power now that his butt's flatter? No, it's a graphical thing.
Freddy. Yeah, Freddy's power got nerfed in it, but it's not that bad. It's not that bad. It's not
that bad. No, a lot of people just start playing him randomly and I'm like, okay, more Freddy for
me. I'm still playing. I'm still playing it exactly the same way. I was playing pre-nerf,
so it's no big, you know. It's gonna be really awkward if they ever add Five Nights at Freddy's
characters with Freddy. It's just gonna be confusing. Well, we're technically going to have
two pee pee heads because there's Pinhead coming in now. Yeah. But he's cool. Oh my God. I can't
wait for it to go live and to see if they fix the problems that there were during PTB. Yeah,
I will say I hope Pinhead is in the game around the time I get back from Dragon Con. I don't know
how much longer it's going to take to- You opened the box and I came.
Yeah, that's the first, well, I guess Trickster had it, but that's the first killer that has,
you know, such menacing sentences. Trickster's vocals are very like, you know, ha ha ha ha ha.
They got a Korean voice actor for him. Yeah, he has little things, but-
Keep in mind, Adiris had lines. Oh, that's right.
They weren't in English. That's right. No, you're right.
But she spoke, it wasn't actually Babylonian. It's like one of the other derivative languages
though of that timeframe. I want to say it was like, I'll look it up later, but it was,
it was a derivative. Yeah, anyway, they did research into her, which I thought was really
cool. But from that too, I was also playing word skates because I love my word games and
I actually got Gardic on stream for me to try to incorporate later. So we'll see if that happens.
It's so much fun though. I love it. So I have to, you know, get my tablet stuff together.
All right. Well, that's it for your gaming week. My gaming week. Oh, yeah.
We did a pinball trade, so we now have a Rick and Morty as a temporary. Dan traded Metallica
temporarily for us to have the Rick and Morty in our garage. So you want to come play it.
I kind of do, because I don't know the Rick and Morty table at all. So I was going to play it the
other day, but you know, I've been getting over this Sinus infection. I'm mostly over it now.
Yeah. So my gaming week, I've also been playing a little bit of Dead by Daylight. I did a stream
one night this week randomly, and that was a lot of fun. And I've also been playing like,
just a lot of the like stuff I've talked about on the show before, you know, Final Fantasy 14,
but then I also kind of dipped into some other stuff. I randomly started playing No Man's Sky
and I got an achievement that I hadn't unlocked yet. I was trying to basically get back to the
center of the galaxy again, or no, I was trying to finish the Atlas storyline, which I thought
would trigger the center of the galaxy story again, because I thought you also kind of did
the same thing, but it didn't play out the way I thought it would. You kind of just get an item
that instantly like shows you where tons of black holes are. So that's kind of fun. I mean, spoiler
alert, but not really. No Man's Sky is a five-year-old game at this point. I think part
of me is also just anticipating that new patch. And I think I do want a platinum No Man's Sky,
but I'm playing on Xbox. It's not really platinum, but you know what I mean? The hardest achievement
is going to be that permadeath one because permadeath mode isn't just, you know, permadeath,
but it's like a higher, like the resources cost more, things drain faster. Like it's going to be
a rough grind to get that one, but I kind of want to try it. So we'll see, but I'm really awaiting
whatever the, you know, there's been, we talked about on a previous episode, there's been teases
of another, you know, big content patch for that game. And I'm hoping another seasonal event will
come with that sort of like the Mass Effect thing, but it doesn't have to be a tie in with
anything else. Like I enjoyed the first event for what it was. So I'm hoping there's another
one that comes in pretty soon in that game. That would be fun. And then I played Katamari Damacy
Reroll because that is on Game Pass now. So if you have Xbox, Microsoft, whatever you can play
Katamari Damacy Reroll and that game is still, that's the game is still a joy all these years
later. Cause if you think about it, that's based off the original Katamari game, which was out
around the time this show started a long time ago. So it's, it's a delight to play again and
just experience that that's for sure. So that was pretty much my gaming week. So let's move on.
I will mention quickly before we get into the rest of the news from this week,
just some quick housekeeping things. There will not be a live show or a podcast next week,
which is very, you know, if you've been listening to the show for a while,
it's kind of been that way over Labor Day weekend because I'm going to be out of town.
I'm going to be at Dragon Con. I hope I get to meet a lot of people at Dragon Con,
but at the same time, it's going to be a very different kind of year where I'm really focusing
on panels and not so much parties, just because obviously with all the stuff going on out there,
I want to take things a little bit cautiously, although I was very,
very happy to hear in the past week, week and a half, Dragon Con kind of made the same move
that PAX ended up making. And that is they will be mandating. You have to have either the vaccine
or a negative test in the last 72 hours, whatever. So that's on top of the mask mandate. So that's
makes me feel a lot better, but I'm going to, I'm going to really enjoy the panels. I am on
six different panels this year. I gave an overview of those last week, so I'm not going to detail all
six of them again tonight. I'll just point you over at my Twitter, twitter.com slash Mr. Rob
Roberts, that's MR Rob Roberts. And all of my panels are listed there in the pin post. I made
it my pin post for now. I will point out three of those panels are online. So if you are doing
virtual Dragon Con this year, which many people are, you can check out those three, three of those
six panels I'm going to be doing are going to be streamed online. So I hope to see some of you guys
there. Two of them are on Friday. I have, it's, I have like eight hours of panels on Friday.
Which is, I mean, no, no, I overstated that, but it's, it's a lot. It's an hour and a half,
no, an hour panel and then a half hour break. So it's six hours of panels because it's four
back to back to back, but it'll be fine. I love doing panels. It's my favorite part of the show.
So I'm very excited to do that and hopefully meet some people at Dragon Con this year,
either virtually or in person. Okay. That's it for that. We will see you in two weeks
live. So we will not be here next week. I imagine Dark Sakura will be here on Sunday
streaming probably, but I don't know. I don't want to, maybe she'll go out and enjoy. I don't know.
Maybe you'll go out and enjoy the night. I don't know. Maybe I'll do a marathon. Yeah,
there you go. Bobby won't be here either that night for obvious reasons. He does the same
thing that I'm doing. So Sunday night is going to be open. So there you go.
Also, although I don't think any of our regulars are in the area, I do just want to acknowledge
that, that hurricane that's happening in Louisiana right now and the surrounding area. I just, you
know, want to say, I hope everybody is safe and got out of the path of that storm and was able
to evacuate and definitely sending my thoughts to those that are affected by that. Cause that does
not sound like a lot of fun right now. So, um, yeah, just, uh, wanted to acknowledge that and
hope that all of our listener fam is, uh, in a drier place right now. Okay. Uh, let's get into
some other gaming news. Loki. We'll start with you. Starting that news with what I played this
week. Uh, did I skip you completely? I sure did. I'm sorry, Loki. What did you play? It's just,
it's just Minecraft. I know I was gonna say, what did you play anything besides Minecraft?
Uh, you have your own Christian Minecraft server now. I don't have my own Christian
Minecraft server. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to skip you, Logan. Oh, that's all good. Um,
no, I was mainly Minecraft. So like I meant to put out a video this week and then I realized
that we have our road contest thing, which is technically it was due like yesterday, but
you know, the people there are judging it. They're on vacation, so it's fine. So I've been like
working in that for a long time. So yeah, still feeling the pressure to put out a video and I
have a lot of content for that. Just had priorities. So, um, anyways, so one thing I
definitely would have seen going to be playing this week is the fan made Metroid prime 2d project.
And, um, you know, it was this awesome work by a team, uh, SCU that released the demo for prime
2d. It was a side scrolling remake of Metroid prime that they've been working on it for 15
years. You already know the punchline to this. It's a Nintendo game. So of course,
Nintendo was going to put an end to that and they did. They, um, cease and desisted it and it's
buh-bye. Um, so yeah, so they put out a, um, a post in Reddit saying, hello, dedicated fans.
It's an announcement that you've been dreading. We have been asked by certain games related company
to discontinue our work on prime 2d in its current form. We have removed the demo download and
soundtrack MP3 download. We are currently in dialogue with that company in terms of
they're not going to undo it. I mean, come on. Um, so yeah, this is what happens when you talk
about your game before your games. I just have to make it. And I know you're really excited about it.
You really want to share, you know, the work you got to understand they're going to C and D that
so fast that it's just, I mean, come on, you've been working out for 15 years now or planning,
I'm sorry, planning for 15 years on it. You kind of knew what was going to happen.
I mean, they've only done it to everything. You, you have to do what they call in the music
industry, a Beyonce, if you might remember Beyonce just dropped an album with no warning,
no lead up, no hype, no nothing. Um, she was really, I don't know. She was the first artist
ever to do it. She's certainly the first that I think of. And, you know, certainly the digital
era, I think kind of changed a lot of the rules. Um, you know, you just, just put it out there
and it's done. And so I think, uh, that's what a lot of these fan projects that are in questionable
territory have to do if they want to actually see a release is they just have to Beyonce it,
uh, and just drop it. Um, not, and again, I get that it's a legal gray area and especially with
a Metroid game coming out next month, Nintendo is going to protect their trademarks and they,
they do this aggressively. This should not be a surprise to anybody. Does it suck? Yes. But at
the same time, should it surprise you? Absolutely not. Um, we can only hope for at this point that
they will be able to redo some of the sprites and some of the things to make it, uh, you know,
matroid supper matroid. And you want to contrast this with what like Sega is doing. Sega just had
a fan game festival for Sonic. So they were showing off a ton of fan games that were made
with that. Just different companies, different, you know, philosophies about it, but like
Kano wish Nintendo would just take the Sega philosophy, you know,
Sega does what intend don't. And that's not finally allowing fan games to exist. Yeah.
All right. Um, let's move on. This is, this next story has had a lot of people talking this week,
especially on social media. Um, you know, and just a couple of weeks on ago on the show,
we were talking about the Ariana Grande concert in Fortnite and how, um, it was very unique and it
really had people thinking about Fortnite as an artistic platform and as, you know, oh, maybe for,
you know, and, and if you've looked in some of the things that, you know, Epic and they've all
said about Fortnite in the past is that they want Fortnite to be this, you know, not just
their battle royale game, but they want it to be basically a pop culture, you know, puddle. Um,
so that makes this, this interest, this latest development from this week, very fascinating.
Um, and that is that time magazine helped craft an interactive exhibit called March through time.
It is a, uh, uh, interactive experience all about Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Uh, and, uh, I have not,
I don't have Fortnite even installed on my computer, so I haven't been able to experience
it myself. Um, but I am told that you will, uh, transport to DC 1963, which is a re-imagined
version of the nation's Capitol that allows you to visit, um, exhibits that are kind of like a
virtual museum. Uh, they actually kind of explain what Dr. King's speech is all about, uh, talks
about the, the March on Washington for jobs and freedom. Uh, and I believe you can actually, um,
uh, hear the entire I have a dream speech in there. Um, and you earn a special spray that you
can use in your Fortnite matches from going through the experience, perhaps to entice people
to go to it. Um, and this has gotten a lot of feedback because there's been a lot of things
from like what to, hey, Fortnite's trying to do a good thing and, and bring education to the
children, to these very interesting pictures of, let's say the Xenomorph from Alien, who is a
playable character in Fortnite walking around Washington, DC, 1963 with Rick from Rick and
Morty. Um, and this experience has already had some issues too, is that they had to disable emotes,
uh, from outside, I guess the experience brings eight unique emotes. Um, so you can use those
unique ones in the experience, but you can't bring the outside ones in anymore because people
were doing things that were inappropriate. And it's a lot of the, um, optics that are causing
some people to take issue with, like, for example, the loading screen will give you a tip for how to
play Fortnite Battle Royale, which might involve like how to properly use the gun, which is a
little bit tasteless when you consider the end of the story of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. It's
pretty tasteless. So some of those optics don't play out too well. Um, I don't know. I, I don't
know. I, I feel like I want to experience it for myself before I really form an opinion, but I do
kind of feel like it's extremely well-intentioned. It's, and I saw a very, I saw a very interesting
comment that I thought is worth repeating, and I'm very sorry. I don't know who said the comment.
It's one of those things I picked up on Twitch, or I'm sorry, not Twitch, Twitter, the other TW,
um, on, and somebody had said, you know what? If they're gonna not teach critical race theory
in schools and people have to learn about critical, you know, that type of stuff through Fortnite,
that's wild, but I'm glad they're doing it type of thing. And it did kind of stop and give me pause.
I was like, cause you know, I'd seen a lot of the negative blowback on the experience,
but when I saw that comment, I was like, fuck, this person has a point. When you consider what
Fortnite's target audience really is, which is kids around Loki's age. I don't know if it's
really a bad thing that they get to- I hope kids are not my age.
Sorry, sorry. You know what I mean? The kids that are Loki's kids age.
Hey, fellow kids. Um, I actually, I kind of like, you know what? I, I think it's pretty well
intact. I think, I think there's a lot of like optic issues and like learning curve types of
things that maybe this isn't where I would have started and maybe learned about some of those
things by maybe, but at the same time, again, it's, it's hard to be upset about it, but I do
think there's a lot of feedback that Epic and the Fortnite team could certainly hear about it.
I don't know. What do you guys think? I don't know. Has anybody played it at all or what do
you think? Well, I don't play Fortnite. No. But I think honestly, though, well-intentioned is a very
apt description for something like this. And I think it could be positive, especially given,
again, that we've got these states that are rolling back education about such an important
part of American history. But I think that, that it's not enough, that it's just one focus.
Um, I, it, it will, it will be, I think, helpful and bring some attention, but I think that we
need broader education out there and accurate representation. Um, not black and white photos,
but photos that were taken in color in the sixties, because it wasn't that long ago.
Um, Bobby Black Wolf in chat says apparently kids have reactive really positively towards this and
they have actually shocked their gamer parents. And that is a good point. I think is that it can
start a conversation that I think is a good conversation to have. Um, and I don't know what
else to say. I think, I think, I think there are, again, there's, there's many good things about
this. I just think that the putting it in Fortnite and it's almost like you're, you're,
you're kind of like jumping like five steps ahead to this thing that it's like, this is,
this is very good. This is very important and we're glad it's here now, but maybe there would
have been some learning steps along the way before we got here, but it's, it's hard to look at this
and go. It's terrible. I think it's, it's just, I think so many of us were unprepared for Fortnite
to bring this. So it's interesting. Um, let's see, uh, other comments in chat. I wanted to say
here, um, DJ Rama S in chat says, got to educate these youngins one way or another.
Uh, Mike Deft in chat says, it's like, it's a nice gesture, but this ain't it chief. Um, yeah. Uh,
and then, uh, move, moves on to a reply to Bobby saying, if the end of all of this is positive,
then I'm all for it. Even if I don't agree with how it's done entirely. Um, Quest Buster brings
up an interesting kind of like, um, analogy, I guess, uh, is, uh, with Ubisoft's, uh, relatively
recent Assassin's Creed titles have tried to do with their history walkthroughs of ancient Egypt
and Greece, that they can use games to at least spark a sense of discovery instead of simply being
games. Excuse me. You know, I thought of that too, actually. And I thought about also a game like
civilization and how much I learned from really loving that game when I was in high school.
And even though that wasn't an edutainment game, it wasn't the Oregon trail. It wasn't
Carmen San Diego. I certainly learned a lot about some of the natural wonders of the world or the,
you know, manmade ones as well. Some of the wonders of the world, if you will,
through that game, you learn about leaders of the world and their different styles,
except they kind of messed up Gandhi. And if you know civilization, you, you get the joke there.
If you don't look it up, uh, Gandhi was, he was problematic. Yes. Um, but anyway, there was,
there was, um, anyway, there's a lot I learned from playing civilization, um, that, uh, I,
I wouldn't have gotten if not the fact that I really enjoyed the game. So it's, I don't know.
I, uh, I, I was tempted to download Fortnite just to check this out. It's just one of those things
where I don't have the bandwidth to download a 60 gig game right now. Um, but I, I really should
have sat down and watched at least a YouTube or somebody playing through it on Twitch. I'd like
to sort of see it for myself, um, to get more out of it. Um, but I, again, I think it's a very,
I think it's going to start a bigger conversation. Um, and I think this whole idea of educating
people through video games is generally a great direction for the industry. And I think we just
have to figure out what's the magic formula to really make that work so that we don't have,
you know, offensive emotes coming from the, the xenomorph and the aliens, you know,
trying to look through the exhibit or what have you. So. I don't think it's necessarily that it
was like offensive in the sense that the emotes were offensive. I think it's more of like,
you know, maybe we shouldn't be like doing the Carlton while Martin Luther King's giving his
speech. I think it was more of that, like, this is not the time for that. Right. Um,
our man with the voiceovers VX chase next V in chat says learning through concepts is one thing
learning through interactive concepts is another. And yes, I agree with that. I think, and again,
you know, kind of going back to what Bobby is saying is that this is, this is starting
conversations. I th I think this is a good thing. We just have to figure out how do, how do we
make sure it's right and that we don't have people doing the Carlton, you know, when people,
you know, and, and those sorts of things. Cause unfortunately on the internet, things are going
to, maybe this should have been something that was like explored as a single player or in a party
with friends only type of thing. Um, I don't know. I, I'm not, I'm not saying definitively that
should have been it. I'm just saying maybe there's some other things we have to kind of figure out
about how to get all that to work. So anyway, I'm sure we will hear more on this and other
similar things as Fortnite dips into the, um, the edge, the education for the children as well.
I'm also curious, Loki, if your kid, maybe your kids are a little bit too young, but well, I don't
know. I don't know, but I'd be curious to see if they end up in this and what they get out of it.
I'd be very curious about that. Oh, they don't play Fortnite. So I thought they did. Oh, it's
Roblox. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Unless, unless they're, they're doing a Martin Luther King thing and
wacky wizards or in, uh, Brookhaven, I don't think it's going to happen. Well, it'll be
interesting to see what the industry kind of looks at this and does. And I honestly, I mean,
let's be real. Fortnite has ripped off from everything else. Let's just, let's just spill
the tea. Everything in Fortnite was ripped off of someone else. And honestly what Questbuster was
explaining about that Assassin's Creed. Hmm. Where do you think, where do you think they may have
gotten the inspiration? I'm allegedly, supposedly, maybe hypothesis planning is completely
historically accurate nowadays, you know, with its Pegasus and Norths gods and all that stuff.
Well, but they, they do have those educational modes that, you know, bring a little more to it,
not the actual game part anyway. All right. Does it talk about the, uh, the harboring of sex
abusers and Ubisoft as well? Is that part of the education I'm also going to be getting from this?
You know, I think they omitted that part. Uh, that's, that's something they got to rely on the,
the community to remind people of is that there are still many problems with the industry. Uh,
but I think we come to some of those a little later in the show. So I will, uh, get to that
later. Uh, in the meantime, how about a nice, how about a nice story that takes Orange Lounge Radio
back to its roots? Let's go to Dark Sakura for its next story. These roots are kind of grown out,
aren't they? A little bit. These roots give me a heart attack these days, but I think it's neat.
Oh, Rob. Um, so, well, long gone are the days of Mr. Spanky and Betty. Um, there is a new
dance dance revolution, uh, PC coming out. Um, and I'm actually looking at the tweet here,
uh, that came out with this one and hold on, let me, let me see if I can take a better look
at the tweet. Uh, notice of the version of dance dance revolution, second open alpha test
for a limited time will be holding the it's it's translated as Konaste,
um, version of dance, dance revolution, second open alpha test. Please take this opportunity
to try it. Um, from what I can at least tell from what the tweet says it is in Japanese and I'm
kind of half reading it. Um, Oh, good. They translated it. Uh, anyway. Um, so Konami has
ended the alpha test for, uh, DDR V five, I guess it is an HTML five browser version of DDR and
renewed the game with a second open alpha test. Uh, so DDR, uh, dancers revolution PC for the
Konami amusement game station. So that's Konaste. That's where that came from. Also known as EA
cloud or maybe alpha, I guess. Um, but it's going to run from August 24th, 2021 through September
six, 2021. Um, it is very similar to the arcade version, DDR a 20 plus, and I was surprised
because I didn't even realize there was a plus version of that game. Yep. There is. It only has
a few songs in it and, um, no safe feature. Um, but the dance pad is up on Konami style and
dance pad look nice. I gotta say they look very different now, but in true Konami style fashion,
though, you, they have to get a thousand pre-orders in order to actually make it.
As I was saying, I may have already, uh, told the husband I'm pre-ordering one. Oh, good for you.
Um, the price of it right now is 17,380 yen. So roughly about 170 bucks really isn't that
bad considering, um, is it a hard pad or is it, I mean, it looked like one of those like
cheapy soft pads. I mean, I don't know. It looked like it might be the foamy kind.
That's kind of, hold on a second. I was to say it might be the price might make more sense if it's
one of the foamy type of things. Like, uh, you remember towards, I want to say the end of when
we were all playing DDR, but it was around that time they had, I think red octane or one of those
companies put out foam, uh, some comments to chat, uh, Jason in chat says EA cloud is EMU's cloud.
Orange, right. It says the pad is way overpriced. If it's a regular soft mat. I agree.
Darted says it has a free mode, but it locks you to pre DDR stuff. Maybe they don't want you to
play all the arcade stuff for free. Um, you know, and that's also in like, this coming out also
doesn't surprise me when we've had a B-Mania 2DX we've had a, you know, we've had other
Bimani games that Konami has looked at putting on PC anyway. Sorry. So I have, I have more USB
connection, Bluetooth, low energy compatible, no compatible service at this time, body weight
approx a size 983 millimeters by 840 millimeters body weight, 1.4 kilogram USB cable, not included
corresponding service PC version, connoisse, dance dance revolution, uh, has a music pack comes with
it. Uh, purchase benefits will be reserved to their Konami ID. So there's a lot to your Konami
ID. Um, bonus songs will look like also be going through Konami ID, um, number of units,
a thousand units order acceptance period, August 24th through September 6th. Just reading the,
I just ran it through, um, a translator. Nice. I'll, I'll wait, you know, until they crack it
to allow me to play whatever songs I want and it will happen immediately. So true. I can't wait.
Um, so as far as other, uh, things to go with this system requirements are, um, uh, Windows 10 64
bit, um, at least 2.8 gigahertz processor recommended Intel core I five or higher AMD
eight at 3.5 gigahertz or higher, uh, 40 gigabytes of hard drive space of recommended
Ram eight gigabytes, uh, video Ram one gigabyte or higher. I mean, that makes sense if it's going
to be playing music and graphics, I mean, you'll, you'll need it. So, um, direct X nine, uh, C or
higher stereo on board sound recommended resolution 1280 by seven 20 at 60 kilohertz.
The arcade hardware. I mean, that's basically kind of what they're talking about there,
because that's, I think what the arcade machines run and they run on PCs anyway.
Are you saying they just repurpose the arcade software for a home version? You've got,
well, I finished the story. All right. All right. Okay. Um, so the songs that are included right
now is make it better. Keep on moving, drop the bomb higher, broken my heart. Oh,
Polteri comes back exotic ethnic destiny. Xenon Astra gazer, uh, digital love Helios level up
hyper bomb in the past splash gold. And one more thing, hold on. Cause I have to translate it.
I don't read that much kanji. Um, one way ticket to space.
So looking at the product page, it is a soft mat and it's wireless Bluetooth though as well,
but for a soft mat, no, no, no, no, no $100. Even if it's wireless, I don't care if it's
like there's toys, they're wireless. Like it doesn't cost $100 to put a Bluetooth module
into their thing that that is vastly overpriced. Um, although like I do show them folding it up,
like you can fold it down, but like maybe there's maybe technology has advanced further than the
soft pads of lore. Um, but I, I don't know. Like it just, it looks cheap. Definitely not
something I'd buy for a hundred dollars. All right. But I definitely want to check
out the game at some point. That's for sure. Yeah. All right. Check out the game.
Yeah. Anything else on to report on DDR PC Darsagra? Apparently not.
All right. Let's move on to our next story. Loki.
Yeah. So halo infinite was something that they also were talking about during, um,
games com the opening night live. So they talked, well, first the release date for halo infinite
leaked out and then it was confirmed to be true. So it is going to be coming out December 8th.
And, uh, along with that, they're going to be having some brand new, uh, um, limited edition
consoles and whatnot. So they're going to have a, an Xbox series X that's going to launch, um,
on November 15th. And then, um, looks like we also have the elite series two controller,
which launches November 15th. Maybe I was wrong on that date. I think that was, was it November
15th for the game actually? Yeah. November 15th for the game as well. Um, I'm saying why I think
December 8th, that's weird. Um, anyways, so those are going to be coming. I like the controller,
the leak controller, not buying it for $200, but it looks nice. I mean, and that, uh, the series
X looks nice. Um, I, I like the con I like the controller with that console. I would buy that
separately. Um, but I already have an Xbox series X, so scan it, I guess. I don't know. Um,
oh yeah, no, I'm sorry. So yeah, the console's coming out November 15th game is coming out
December 8th. I knew I didn't forget that. Um, the limited edition Xbox series X,
550 bucks. And then the elite series controller, $200 vastly overpriced if you ask me, but
I mean, it's, it's, it's a controller. It looks the master chief.
And this, the system is so, so good looking. I really want one.
Yeah, the system looks nice. Um, yeah. And then they didn't really show too much. They
have like a cinematic trailer for like, um, I guess the multiplayer. I don't really know
what exactly was, that was all about. It kind of didn't make any sense to me, but,
you know, glad to know that there's that it's coming soon, the release of that.
And they were able to get their act together pretty fast, but yeah, we'll have to wait and
see. I'm sure we'll hear more about it as soon as we get closer to that date.
E3 VL in chat says, uh, over twitch.tv slash vog network says I heard launch content for the game.
Isn't that great? Yeah. It seems like they're going to really be kind of adding a lot to it
as it goes. The co-op is not going to be there at launch, which is kind of weird.
Which would usually be very obnoxious. Um, and I think the folks that are paying the
full $60 price tag may have some reservations with that, but we also have to remember Microsoft
is really all in on game pass at this point. And I think, you know, if they can still get a lot of
people to check the game out on game pass in a way that's still a win for them. And I think there will
be a lot of people that will check out, even if it's just kind of like partial halo, I'll be one
of them. I enjoy halo enough to check out on game pass. Um, whatever, whatever parts of the game are
there, uh, the day that it launches. So it's just interesting to kind of think about. Yeah,
the whole game's not really there, but when you think about Microsoft's overall strategy,
is it that surprising? I mean, I think we all know the development of the game plays that we have
right now. Yeah. Cause like every game nowadays has a roadmap for it. I mean, it's becoming more
acceptable, unfortunately. Um, but I mean, I kind of, I trust that Microsoft will put out a decent
game. I mean, they, they kind of know what they're doing three for three knows what they're doing
with, um, these games. So we'll have to wait and see. All right. I'm not getting a day one anyways.
So, I mean, I guess I can play it on games pass. So in a sense that we'll be getting a day one,
but yeah. All right. Well, moving on to our next story. So, um, on a prior episode of the show,
dark soccer and I were bantering a little bit about the, um, stranger things content being
removed from dead by daylight, uh, in November. And, uh, certainly a lot of speculation as to
the reasons why it was going away led to the fact that, Oh, Netflix is doing, we know that Netflix
is planning their own, uh, gaming service and stranger things probably ties into that. And then
there was even more fuel on the fire. Uh, when I had noticed that on games pass, uh, the stranger
things three RPG was set to leave the service on September 1st. And as it turns out, there is
something going on with stranger things and Netflix gaming. Um, and a lot of it went down
in Poland, uh, believe it or not because that is Netflix is basically their testing region for
this. So what happened in Poland? Um, well, starting this week, uh, Netflix members in Poland
are able to try Netflix mobile gaming. Um, it's only on Android, uh, for their test for whatever
reason. Um, and there's two games for it. Stranger things, 1984 and stranger things three, uh,
stranger things three, of course, is that RPG. I think if I remember right, stranger things,
1984 is a not great puzzle game. Um, but it's, it's, uh, it's part of the stranger things,
you know, licenses or whatever. So these are the two games that are a part of the test.
So if you're a Netflix member in Poland, you can check these out on your Android device as part of
the membership. Uh, Netflix did say, uh, it's still very, very early days and we will be working
hard to deliver the best possible experience in the months ahead with our no ads, no in-app
purchases approach to gaming. Interesting that they also emphasize those points. Um,
just as the infrastructure to do that. So, you know, well, we'll brag about it as a positive
justice and FYI, you do not stream these games through the cloud. That's not what this does.
And this probably is may explain why it isn't currently testing on the Apple side of things.
I would guess I don't, I don't, I can only really speculate there. It's not through cloud gaming.
What you do when you installed now, uh, you go to the Google play store cause it's Android and
you download the game on the device. Uh, you can also download the game directly from the play
store, but you have to use your Netflix login as your credentials. So you can then play the games
through the Netflix app or their own dedicated app. Hmm. Now they, now Netflix does say an iOS
test is coming. So that is, you know, they're not leaving it out. Uh, and then, um, yeah. So,
but then we don't know exactly how that will work. Uh, yet if it downloads to the app store,
what we'll find out more when the test gets there. Um, but Netflix is using stranger things as part
of their gaming service test. So not, um, a terrible, terrible, big surprise when we talk
about some of the content shifting around. I still don't think they needed to do it. Um,
like you kind of said earlier, Sonic shows up in all these fan things and,
you know, it's Mario and Sonic at the Olympics. And I don't think it hurts
sales or brand identity that move or that movie still did very, very well when it came out.
So, um, I'm not sure I see the logic as to why they need to remove stranger things from dead
by daylight, other than. They just don't want to, it's not worth it to them or whatever. It's,
it's a little weird, but I guess they're within their rights.
Well, they're, they're also not really that like sought out of, you know, to,
I'm not like seeking it out to play. And they're also available. Like I think
some of that's already on like the steam storefront or Epic games and stuff like that.
So it's, it's other places like, I'm not gonna be like, Oh my God, it's gone from games path.
I better go check this out in Netflix. No one's thinking that at all. So whatever,
not these games, but it'll be interesting if Netflix comes up with originals and who knows,
maybe they have their own dead by daylight clone kind of game. We'll say, uh, uh, we'll say, um,
lopsided four V one kind of game that maybe we'll use the, then it'll make more sense to me why they
wanted to pull back from dead by daylight. Even though, again, if you bought those characters,
you keep those care, you're going to still see those characters in dead by daylight.
I wonder if they'll be like for the record, it's just stranger things stuff.
What's that Jamie? For the record. I think that the DLC cosmetics are the vector cosmetics
are going off sale before like a few days before the whole thing actually is gone.
Yep. Um, as to show 100, Matt, why you can. SSU 100, Matt, with a good perspective here saying
Netflix survived by taking a chance on streaming and making their own content. That is true.
Um, you know, Netflix really started the ball with making their own stuff. Like when
orange is the new black, I think was one of the first shows that I can remember being a Netflix
original. And there was a huge fucking deal when that came out that, and, uh, the one that
unfortunately had Kevin Spacey and that whole mess tank, that whole show, that was another early
Netflix original camera. What the fuck the show was called. Somebody in shadow will remember,
I'm sure, but those were like some early, early Netflix originals and the quality of those shows
was so good. At least the early seasons of orange is new black was pretty good. I don't know about
the later ones, but you know, it drew people into the streaming service house of cards. Thank you.
That was the other one I was trying to think of with the Kevin Spacey. All right. Um, and then,
then they like wrote them out of the very last season or something like that. I remember that
was a, a whole thing. So, um, yeah. And then, uh, as 200, Matt says just to test venture with one
of their own IPS. So it's nothing to lose. I think it'll go beyond their own IPS eventually. Um,
but we'll, we'll stay tuned for that. So, and pod culture says orange is the new black had
capable group from Voyager. Yes. That was a reason reason why I watched it actually is that I love
Kate Mulgrew and she plays a very different type of character in that show. So, uh, yeah.
And then I, I grew to like a lot of the other characters, except the main character hated her,
but everybody else was great, but I hated the main character in that show.
I don't even remember her name, but I hated her. All right. Well, she's not great in,
um, the Handmaid's Tale either, but you know, she in that show too. Well, I don't have a
problem with the actor. So I just had a problem with the character. Yeah. All right. All right.
My depth and chat says we all did Rob Robert. Okay. They, I'm glad to know I wasn't alone. All
right. Anyway, let's move on. Uh, dark Sakura. Uh, what do we have next? Um, a move that's
honestly, I think just a gesture, but, um, for people who enjoy Overwatch,
there is a change coming by renaming the character McCree, who is named after, uh, the,
one of the developers who was let go from the company with all of the sexual harassment claims
going on. Um, it's a nice gesture, but that's all it is, is a gesture. It doesn't address.
I mean, yeah. Remove them. I say remove all references. That's great. That that's good.
But yeah, but they, uh, we're also planning on doing, um, a new narrative, uh, in Overwatch
in September, but because that character was involved in it, they're delaying it for later
in the year. And in the interim are doing a new FFA map, but I'm going to read the direct quote
from the development team. Sure. Um, we built the Overwatch universe around the idea of inclusivity
equity and the hope, uh, and hope are the building blocks of a better future. We continue to discuss
how we best live up to our values and to demonstrate our commitment to creating a game
world that reflects them. We believe it's necessary to change the name of the hero currently
known as McCree to something that better represents what Overwatch stands for.
And if fortunately the name that they chose was Cosby, the cowboy, and it's just not working out,
top it, delete your account. Stop it. They need to call him. Uh, I look like Wolverine, but not
really. I think I saw some name that was the Yee-Haw McGraw or something like that. Like just
give them a real over the top name. All right. Um, Mike Defton chat says, yeah, another nice
gesture, but at the same time, it's like, how does this fix things? And I definitely,
um, see that side of it. Um, because I just want to remind everybody it has been one month
now since the employees made demands of the leadership at Activision Blizzard King,
sometimes known as ABK. And those demands have still gone unheard from by the way,
Francis Townsend still employed at ABK for some reason, not sure what that reason is,
but that is, uh, something that should be noted has been one month and that those, uh, demands
have not been responded to. So they're pulling it. They're pulling a new Orleans. What do you
mean by that? Little bitty patches on those, uh, levees, but the storm hits and they break.
That may not be the best time to reference with what's going on. No, actually I did it on purpose
because I know those situations very well. I grew up in that general area and I'm very
pissed at new Orleans for not still having done the proper repairs on it. So I stand by my
statement. All right. Um, that's 200 Matt and chat says kind of like, Hey, I know we've been
shitty lately, but here is a semi warm cookie. It may or may not have chocolate chips might be
oatmeal. Oh, it might be raisins. I hate that. We are getting rid of the chocolate chips that,
uh, you know, the folks who are allergic to chocolate, uh, unfortunately we're replacing
them with raisins. Oh boy. All right. Uh, anyway, um, let's go in right into the next story because
it kind of ties into all of this. Right. Loki. Yeah, unfortunately. Um, so as we know, the,
um, California has been, you know, investigating Activision Blizzard for their, um, terrible work
place environment. And unfortunately there's also some more to that now. Um, so now we're
getting allegations that, um, Activision Blizzard is shredding documents that were requested by,
um, the DFEH though. I don't know. That's, that's not good that we're hearing about that.
Um, yeah, basically that Activision Blizzard hasn't been cooperative, um, that they have
cited their, um, non-disclosure agreements and the requirements that employees must speak with
the company before contacting the state department. Um, there, um, of course, uh,
Wilmar Hale, who is, you know, busting unions and, um, other, uh, examples of lack of cooperation,
but yeah, the shredding documents tooth is also our shredding abuse evidence.
And, you know, basically, you know, it's not a good look for them, but of course,
Activision comes out and they're saying that, listen, we've done a lot. You know, we've,
we've, we've made several high-level personnel changes. We're revamping hiring and recruiting
practices and requiring diverse interview panels, greater transparency on pay equality
and clear boundaries on workspace behavior with a zero tolerance approach to harassment of their
actions that diminish or marginalized. So in other words, they may be saying
words, but it's not like an oral fart. That is exactly what I was going to say
is that their lips are moving, but all we hear is great minds think like us.
So, yeah, I don't know. I mean, this it's typical corporate, you know,
it sounds like that they're being as accountable about this as Ubisoft is.
So, um, meanwhile, SSJ 100 Matt is continuing the cookie company story going now it's like,
while you enjoy that cookie, pay no attention to the man shredding documents behind the curtains.
Pay no attention to the guy replacing your chocolate chips with raisins.
Evil fucking things. And I mean, both. I don't, I don't hate raisins,
but they ain't craisins, which are far superior. So I just want to make that clear.
I have a lot of love for craisins. Rob, what, what the cookie of choice is peanut butter,
which is fine. No, dark chocolate chip craisin oatmeal cookies.
Why would you put all of those things in a cookie together?
Because they're amazing. Okay, I don't know. See, I like I guess I guess chocolate and
craisin would go together. Okay. But at the same time, when you say the best cookie is,
I'm just going to say, Oh, peanut butter, like all those things.
They're Samoas. Oh yeah, Samoas are really good too. And snickerdoodles.
One last thing, one last thing on the cookie tangent.
Okay. One last cookie tangent. When I make black sesame cookies,
you have to have one. They're like little goth peanut butter cookies.
You gave them to me once. They're really good. I did?
Yeah. You brought them over. It was back when OLR. We were still doing it here and you,
brought them over one night. They're great. Yeah. My little goth cookies.
Yes. That turn my tongue black. Yeah. Those are awesome. I'll make them again.
All right. Awesome. Okay. Let's move on completely different topic. Although it does tie into some
activism things going on online. You might remember last week on the show, we talked
a little bit about the day off of Twitch. That's going to be happening on September 1st.
So a little reminder for folks that that is happening on September 1st. And many of your
favorite streamers will be participating, but at the same time, there are other streamers that
maybe cannot take the day off, whether it's due to their finances or the fact that they have a
contractual agreement with some company to play the game on that day. So I think everybody needs
to make their own decision and let other people make the decisions that are best for them.
Um, however, it is. So what's that? I said agreed. Oh yes. Um, however,
with that, um, you know, when we were talking about all that, I talked about how there really
isn't going to be pressure on Twitch until there is a competitor to Twitch. Now I'm not about to
talk about a competitor to Twitch directly, but this is fucking fascinating to me. So here it is
Streamlabs, who a lot of streamers use to, interestingly enough, do things that Twitch
can't do, right? So Streamlabs kind of adds things to the stream that Twitch doesn't natively do.
Well Streamlabs is also going to now be allowing streamers a way to make money, um, that is monthly
tipping. So it's a subscription, if you will, through Streamlabs. So yeah, I got an email
about that cause I already have, um, the direct ship, uh, tip jar. Yeah. Yeah. So now it's a way
for streamers to set up a subscription service and creators get 100% after PayPal takes their fees.
So it's going to be a lot different than the 50 50, um, down for this now, but here, here's the
thing. Uh, so, so the Streamlabs creator subscription, that's going to probably be more
appealing to people than Twitch's built-in service, but you should be aware. Remember
when you do the Twitch subs, you lose the ads and all that stuff. Streamlabs can't interface with
that. So if you're selling subs through this, Twitch is not going to treat these people like
Twitch subscribers because they're not Twitch subscribers. So any of those benefits that come
with a Twitch subscription, such as ad-free viewing or extra emotes or emotes at all,
um, that's not going to be available through this. So there is going to be a trade-off there. So I
just, I need to make that clear because I feel like that's an easy misconception when people
are reading about this and going, Oh, Streamlabs is competing with Twitch. Well, they're competing
on that amount of the money you get front, but they can't compete on that technical front because
Streamlabs isn't directly a Twitch competitor yet. That's me inserting that word. I have nothing
further to go off of, but I can't help but wonder. If Slots was worth actually freaking using,
then maybe. I can't help but wonder. Nah, I don't think so. They don't have the infrastructure for
it, but, um, it is cool that they're doing that. It sounds to me, it's almost like an
alternative to Patreon versus like, say, um, you know, what you would get with Twitch.
It's still something though that like they could basically try to, you know, say, Hey, you want to,
you know, contribute instead of like Patreon or something like that, you can do that through this
Streamlabs thing. And then it'll be all integrated within Twitch or something like that. Um, which is
kind of cool, I guess. Now, Tigerclaw brings up, um, in chat, there are many places to stream to
other than Twitch. Using a service like Restream, it gives you tons of places you can stream to
other than Twitch. True. There are two problems with that. Number one, when you are a Twitch
affiliate and you do decide to make money off Twitch, you're actually violating the terms with
Twitch to automatically Restream your content because you do, uh, say in that fine print that
and I, I a hundred percent realize people are not playing by the rules. They're doing that at their
own risk of peril. Okay. But like, for example, we don't simulcast to YouTube because it's part
of the agreement that we're on Twitch for a 24 hour period. And then we can, you know, if we
wanted to put a clip of the show on YouTube or whatever, we could do that. Um, I was also,
some of us are eventually trying to make partner. Yeah. So we absolutely don't want to ruin that.
I was also reminded when I talked about that there are no competitors to Twitch on last week's show,
I was reminded offline that Facebook gaming exists and I'm going to stand by what I
originally said on last week's show. There are no competitors to Twitch. Facebook gaming,
as far as I'm concerned is a non-factor and watch, I may have to eat my words in five years,
but if you allow Facebook to take over the gaming space, you people are fucking fools.
I said it, I said it, you know what? I know you're not supposed to say it,
but I cannot stand Facebook getting into this gaming space and all of these other things.
They can't keep misinformation and bullshit off their platform. I do not want that in the gaming
space. Period. So Facebook gaming, as far as I'm concerned is an illegitimate competitor.
It is not going to get a seat at the big kids table in my eyes.
If you disagree with me, that's fine. And I'm sorry to those that work very hard to
establish their Facebook gaming channels. I personally think you made a poor business decision.
So video games, they're lovely, aren't they? Yeah. I have a few.
Anyway. Let's see. Bobby Black Wolf in chat says the people who got lured in by Facebook
gaming in the beginning served the length of their contract and went right back to Twitch.
Mike Deff says Facebook gaming is big in other countries though. Well, you know what? Friendster
was big in other countries for a very long time. And that's no, look, that's no disrespect. I'm not
trying to disrespect that, but I'm just saying, you know, people will gravitate towards one space
and my thoughts when it comes to Facebook gaming is still the same. I don't care what country
you're in. Facebook has no business getting in that space. Yeah. Mike Deff says so many
people in Mexico don't know what Twitch is and that, but that's on Twitch to some extent there.
Yeah. Bobby Black Wolf points out live journal is still big in Russia. I have a huge spot in my
heart for live journal. I met my husband on live journal. I met Dark Soccer and Loki pretty much
on live. Even if we didn't meet, I may not have met them on live journal, but our friendship was
strengthened by live journal, I think is a nice way to put it. You know, in the community that
was there. Do I give a shit about live journal in its current form? Absolutely not. Although,
oh no, they didn't. It's fun to look at once in a great while. They got some good gifts.
So that's it, you know? Yeah. And Bobby Black Wolf brings up that story about there's apparently
a new young adult novel about a kid trying to find out who her mom is by finding her dad's
live journal. Wow. And usually, usually I read these tips after the show, but I have to
acknowledge She-Hulk 10 donating 100 biddies. Thank you very much. But it's the comment for me
where it says Pornhub gaming would be fun. Honestly, She-Hulk honestly, honestly,
I'm very surprised they haven't tried to enter the space.
Hmm. Maybe not directly, but Pornhub's got its subsidiaries and Loki, you just said, you know,
the stream labs can't get into the space because they don't have the infrastructure for it. Well,
Streamlabs, meet Pornhub. Pornhub, meet Streamlabs. Now kiss.
Yeah, I can see that.
Streamhub. Perfect. Thank you, Orange Right. Streamhub, Pornlabs. Probably not. I think
Orange Right might have the better name there, PodCulture, for what they're trying to put on
this space. But yeah. Anyway. Bobby Black Wolf points out there's already a triple X game
streaming site, or at least there was. Yeah, again, a lot. And I'm well aware there are
other competitors out there too, and I don't mean to shit on any of them, except for one that I've
already named. But some of these other ones that are like the up and comers, that's just,
they're up and comers. And I stress this on last week's show, I don't want to repeat myself too
much, but just the whole fact that they don't have that path to make money easily laid out the way
that Amazon backed Twitch has right now, which is why people are still, when people just say,
we'll go to a different platform. People are like, no, this is our platform. This is where
we've established our community. This is where I'm going to fight to make work, which is what
Dark Soccer is also referencing there. In spite of all this, I'm going to make partner on this
website, and we're going to work with what we've got. Yeah, VG Realness in chat says,
Pornhub has the infrastructure to take out YouTube and Twitch, and they're sleeping on it.
I 100% agree, VG Realness, and I'm wondering what it's going to take for them to get into that world.
Probably the whole content management stuff, because right now they don't have good
relationships, I think, with their payment processors because the whole issue with the
stolen content and all that stuff. So if they can't manage that in just the platforms that
they have now, then why add to that? Plus they own several, they own so many streaming sites
outside of just the Pornhub stuff. They pretty much own the whole thing,
like all of the streaming services. It's ridiculous. Like RedTube, is that them too?
There's one that's shutting down at the end of the month or next month that is very similar,
but it must not be part of Pornhub if it's closing. It's XXX something.
They've got the RedTube, Tube8, Thumbzilla, they have so many.
I'm sorry, did you say Tube8?
Yeah, Tube8.
Okay. All right.
It's like six different sites, so it's just ridiculous.
Interesting. All right. Enough talk about Pornhub, but I couldn't help but talk about
that with the streamers. So anyway, I didn't get to this, but I will say Streamlabs,
also keep in mind the tipping can be integrated into OBS, and OBS allows you to go to YouTube,
if you want, Facebook, TikTok. I didn't even know you could stream to TikTok.
Yeah, there's actually a guy I watch who does Minecraft. He does live streaming from TikTok
and Twitch simultaneously.
Well, maybe TikTok is I in this space too. I don't know. Anyway, Streamlabs lets creators
decide what they're basically selling with their subscription and set the price point on that.
There's also going to be leaderboards, badges, and all that fun stuff there. But again,
I can't stress this enough. It is outside of Twitch, so it's not going to disable some of
those things that Twitch does with their subscriptions. So keep that in mind when
you're weighing all these different options.
Well, I mean, they were talking about putting ads on people that subscribe to the channels too,
haven't they? So who knows what's outside of Twitch at this point?
Well, they better not until they fix some of the bullshit that Dark Sakura can speak to firsthand,
because I know you had to deal with that bullshit in this past week.
So until they fix that shit, that's like still actively happening. I really would not do things
to make people further teeter on the edge of leaving this site. So, all right.
Anyhow, let's go back to a simpler time when we didn't stream games in our next segment.
Now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a
classic and tell you about it. It's time for the classic game of the week.
I picked Picross DS. It is a puzzle game that was developed by Jupiter and published by
Nintendo for the Nintendo DS. It is the second Picross game to be released. The first one
was Mario's Picross, but it failed outside of Japan. There were a bunch more Picross games
in Japan, but this one apparently did a bit better. So basically you have different
nonogram logic puzzles. With this is that you have to mark each square as full or empty,
and it eventually reveals what the picture is. You can also create your own puzzles,
send them to other people, download some classic puzzles, speed competitions using the Nintendo
Wi-Fi connection. Or you also have a daily and online challenge mode where you receive a hint
that reveals one randomly selected row and column. It doesn't affect your player time,
and three different kinds of background music can be selected except in classic puzzle mode
and the unlockable extra 11 extra puzzles. Or you can turn the music off.
So you do have different modes. And by the way, the only one I could find without someone talking
over it was a speedrun. But anyway, in normal mode, you get told to mark a square that should
be unmarked. If your first mistake happens, you get a penalty of two minutes. The second,
four, and each of the following mistake, eight minutes. You can choose from an easy mode that's
five by five or 10 by 10 puzzles. It can go up to 25 by 20. So you have all kinds of just different
things that you do. So you have different timed mini games. You can also unlock one called catch
where one by one squares float around the grid and you have to tap them to clear the mode or sketch
where the top screen displays a picture and you have to copy it on the bottom screen.
And then there's also hit where you hit squares and make them disappeared once you have a certain
number tap mode is cleared. Your music choices are jazz, reggae, and bossa nova. You also have
free mode. If you're not told when you make a mistake, they just get harder and harder to
complete. You also have the mini games, but they're more difficult in free mode.
And then in free mode, you get rock house and ambient for your music choices.
So the game actually, with this one, it got a reading of 9.4 out of 10 by one reviewer. And it
was basically ranked fairly high for a P-Cross game to be released since Mario's P-Cross.
Mario's P-Cross, it did get some pretty favorable reviews, but this one topped it.
And so, I just picked a little game. It's something that maybe not a lot of people
have a lot of experience in that maybe it's something unique and different.
What's that game that Bobby had talked about before, Murder by Numbers or something?
But that's kind of like this too. It's a P-Cross game.
And me personally, I'm not the biggest fan of P-Cross,
but it is a fun little time sink from time to time. Much better than a Minesweeper.
There you go. Now, one thing I will say about the P-Cross,
because you mentioned it kind of in the beginning and you just brought it up again as Mario P-Cross,
that is one of the games that's on the Nintendo Switch library. They added it a little later.
It wasn't in the initial set. So people might not realize it's there, but if you want to sample a
P-Cross game, that's a great place to start. Because obviously the DS games are a little
harder to play now just because they don't really sell them for the Switch or anything.
I mean, you can find a used copy at your local Game Flop or whatever, but
I still think Mario P-Cross is worth a look. It's still quite good.
Well, at any rate, there were other versions. Of course, Mario's P-Cross came out before that.
Afterwards, Nintendo and HAL Laboratory did P-Cross 3D. There's also Essential Sudoku DS,
which has, I guess, a P-Cross mode and P-Cross E, which is Jupiter's other follow-up for Nintendo
3DS. But basically, P-Cross is based off of the concept of nonograms, which are logic puzzles
that require you fill in the right things based on numbers. Yep. So you can actually find nonograms
in those penny press puzzle magazines and things like that. Yeah. So there you go. There it is,
your classic game of the week, P-Cross DS on the Nintendo DS. Great, great shout out.
Bobby Blackall pointing out, I got into it, meaning P-Cross, with the Pokemon P-Cross
free-to-play game on 3DS. Yeah. Yeah. I think that might've been the first one I played too.
There was a Zelda one as well, I remember, that was really good. So check that out. I don't know
if that one was free. I can't remember. Bobby Blackall also points out there's a billion
nonogram apps out there. Absolutely. They're not called P-Cross, but they might be called
Picture-Cross or something like that. So there's other ones. So very cool. All right. Great pick.
I got to talk about this. So ready for a food tangent, everybody?
So I had no idea that these were things that existed, but you know that grandpa Matt or
captain Matt, depending on if you listen to Hoard House or Starboard Power Coupling when
those shows were around, for those of you that know him, he likes to send me all the pumpkin
shit in the entire world. I was wondering if that happened yet. Well, okay. So here's what happened.
I ordered some more masks for Dragon Con because I wanted to refresh my collection a little bit.
So I ordered some more mass at Amazon. A certain package got here first and I opened it and I was,
what the hell is this? And it was a bag of pumpkin pie Kit Kats is what showed up. And it is part of
grandpa Matt's pumpkin thing he does. The pumpkin spice lattes are back and they are fabulous as
always. However, with as much shit as I get for liking pumpkin and being called basic and all
that stuff, I want to point out, they also rolled out an apple drink, that apple macchiato. I told
you this was coming out. It's pretty fucking good. That's what I hear, except I hate caramel. Is the
caramel flavor strong? Just order it without it. Cause I think it's the drizzle they put on top.
Yeah. Like I was told to try the apple syrup in a chai. Yes. And I think they do a frat with it
as well. And I haven't, I haven't tried either that, but yeah, the apple is a standalone syrup.
So I'm probably going to be giving that a go tomorrow. Well, I normally do my pink drink
cause it's one of the things that doesn't make me sick. Oh yeah. I like the pink drinks too,
but I, I really want to try the apple in a, in a chai. So Renee Yasiner chat, hi,
it's so good to see you. Uh, says, uh, pumpkin pie and then I'm a slut for their apple drinks.
I mean, same TBH, like with as much shit as I get for the pumpkin thing, I will do a lot for
an apple drink as well. They are quite tasty. So say that. I am not finding a pumpkin spice, uh,
Reese's on a, you probably need to give it a few more weeks. It is still early in the pumpkin
season. I am used to the pumpkin spice latte coming out the day I leave for dragon con. So
I feel like it was a whole week early this year than usual, but yeah. So anyway, I'm going to
enjoy one of these pumpkin pie kit cats, which are quite tasty. You know what they taste like
pumpkin pie. Um, and it's good cause the, the wafer kind of kit cats. I love had those before.
They're good. Japanese ones are better. Pod culture says there's an apple mountain
dew coming out. That sounds like it might be pretty tasty. Anyway. Yeah. I've had the,
I've had the pumpkin pie ones before and I honestly truly believe that the Japanese,
a couple of Joe ones were a lot better. There's some great flavors in Japan. I'm excited that
we're finally getting some of that shit in the U S and it only took like 50 flavors of Oreos
for other companies to catch on that like, Hey, people like wacky zany flavors. So there was
another flavor that's out that I think that you would like Rob banana caramel. I love banana.
Heck yeah. They do have a banana like us when they're doing in the U S but one of the current
Japanese flavors is banana caramel. And if I find it, I'll get you some. Yeah. A pod culture says
there was a key lime kit cat. That was awesome. Yeah. The key that that was something that was
around. Those are pretty good. There's a mint one. There was, um, some other flavor. I kind
of dig the duos. Yeah. The mint and the mocha ones. Yeah. Anyway. All right. Enough food. Yeah. I
know back to video games, but Hey, you know what? I snack on a lot of Kit Kat bars. Well, I mean,
well not, not too many, but enough. Oh, I'm playing video games. So let's travel around
the world and quickly talk about some other things going on in the gaming world. Uh, Loki,
we'll start with you. Loki. I think you're muted, which will explain why I heard you say
not a thing about Kit Kats, which is unfortunate, but that's all right. I don't really like Kit Kat.
They're okay. Yes. Yeah. So, um, we talked a little bit about April and Neil coming to
the new Ninja turtles game. Um, but she's also going to be coming to another game,
Nickelodeon all-star brawl. So we have April Neil coming to that game as well as a fighting game
character and then cat dog also coming to that game as well. It's a really shaping up to be a
pretty awesome game. So now I'm not hearing Lori Beth Denberg, but, or moose from, you can't do
that on television. I'm not hearing these Nickelodeon things yet, but it's still time.
There's still time. Yeah. So I never really watched cat dog, but like,
it is cool to see all these other characters coming to the game. So
I mean, let's keep you coming. I want to hear about all the characters and DLC and all this
fun stuff. And then along with that, uh, the Lego star Wars Skywalker saga was something that they
were showing off during games com and it is coming out next year. Now sometime in, uh, spring
of 2022 is when they announced that they had a new trailer for that. Um, you know, it looks cool. I'm
not, I never really played the Lego star Wars games. It was more of the Lego Marvel stuff, but
I have to check it out. All right. Dark soccer. What do you have for us? Um, there is a final
fantasy four pixel remaster, uh, coming out for, uh, computers and for mobile. Um,
on it looks like September 8th, it looks pretty cool. I definitely, uh, I'm considering that one
because I love it. I love, and then I'm sorry. I love four. I hate that font in the remasters,
but I might just have to suck it up and deal with it. I did hear through the grapevine just random
that you spoonie barred is still intact in the final fantasy four, uh, pixel remaster,
which is the most important part of the game. It must be. So at any rate, um, also horizon
forbidden West has been officially delayed until 2022. Uh, the date they are listing now is
February 18th. There are starting orders for it though. So there's that. Nice. What's their,
their game then coming out this fall? Like what Sony got other than the horizon?
I don't think there is one flatulence. Uh, I, I think they're relying on third party and just
the, you know, the system did very well last year. Um, I mean, with as many of them as you
could find. Um, so I kind of think they're just trying to ride that wave until, uh,
I mean, if you want to be technical final fantasy 14 and Walker is a PlayStation five title,
and that's something that Xbox doesn't have, but of course it's on PC as we all know,
but technically that is a holiday title. So that's all I got. All right. Well,
I guess that's fine. There's no systems to be had. So, you know, why,
why bother putting out games to sell the system? All right. Uh, and some of the folks in chat are,
um, giving me tips on my font issue with final fantasy, uh, the pixel remasters,
my fifth dream says it's easily moddable and dark Tetsuya says you can swap the font for the
one in the Japanese language version. It's much better now. That's I'm, I'm interested in that.
So I'll have to look up how to do that. I think I will finally, you know, suck it up and buy at
least the first game just to see what they're like and then make a decision from there. If,
if it's going to be worth it for the really the holy Trinity of four or five and six, let's be
real. Um, two and three are okay, but they're not four or five and six. Let's be honest. All right.
Um, okay. I think that was it for rapid fire news. So let's travel around the world and check
out some release dates, things coming a little sooner than, uh, well, I guess not that much
sooner than the final fantasy four pixel remaster sooner than the final fantasy six pixel remaster.
What's coming out next week. So we got a game called lake. That's going to be on PC and Xbox
one, uh, bravely default two on PC, uh, demon gaze extra on Nintendo switch and PlayStation four.
We have a Kataria fables on PC, Nintendo switch, PlayStation four, PlayStation five,
Xbox one and Xbox series X, WRC 10 on PC, PlayStation four, PlayStation five, Xbox one,
Xbox series X, big rumble boxing, creed champions on PC, Nintendo switch,
PlayStation four and Xbox one. Uh, we have the medium coming out on PlayStation five
and that's it. I didn't realize the medium wasn't staying an Xbox exclusive. I thought that was a
exclusive. I guess I was wrong. It's not. All right. So I guess it was, or it was one of those
limited windows or something. All right. Uh, traveling to Japan, uh, checking out the Nintendo
switch this week, demon gaze extra in a regular and limited edition is out in Japan this week on
the Nintendo switch as is port Royal four, uh, and then big rubble boxing creed champions is out there
as well. Uh, and that is pretty much all the releases on the switch. However, peaking at the
PlayStation five, uh, we have that same port Royal four game is out there as well. And sadly, we
don't really start to pick up releases. I'll just read this one for September 9th. Cause this is
kind of a big deal. Tales of arise is out on the PlayStation five. And I kind of think that's the
big tent pole release, but that'll be in the week that we're off. So, um, that is something to look
forward to for sure. Uh, dark soccer. How about the UK? I'm going to do the two weeks worth.
Sure. So we have, um, on the 31st forgotten city, uh, we have rustler and we have Kiwi,
I guess that's how it's pronounced. Um, and then it's K E Y W E which it looks like they're little
Kiwi birds. So, um, then in September on the second, we have WRC 10, we have Arashi castles
of sin, the medium, Kitaria fables, Rico London, um, monster harvest. And then on the seventh,
we have bus simulator, 21 Chernobyl light on the 10th, also on the 10th.
Why are you aware? Get it together. Big rumble boxing, creed championships, family trainer,
NBA two K 22 tales of arise. And that's, uh, that's it. Um, Loki, since Jamie and I did it,
did you want to circle back to the U S and talk about, um, the week that we're off? Cause I get,
I think that tales of rise of Wario aware in that week, those are pretty big releases.
Yeah. Yeah. So, uh, for the week of the seventh, we've got, uh, Chernobyl, but,
or yeah, Chernobyl light on PlayStation four and Xbox one, uh, fist forged in shadow torch,
uh, that is on PC PlayStation born PlayStation five sonic colors, ultimate on PC,
Nintendo switch PlayStation born Xbox one, uh, the art full escape on PC,
Xbox one and Xbox series X toy soldiers, HD on PC, Nintendo switch PlayStation four and Xbox one
life is strange. True colors on PC and, uh, PlayStation four PlayStation five,
Xbox one, Xbox series X and stadia. We have a Lawson random that's on PC,
Nintendo switch PlayStation four, PlayStation five, Xbox one, Xbox series X, NBA two K 22 on PC,
Nintendo switch PlayStation four, PlayStation five, Xbox one, Xbox series X, uh, tales of
rise on PC, PlayStation four, PlayStation five, Xbox one, Xbox series X. And last but not least,
why are you aware? Get it together on Nintendo switch. All right. I'm glad we covered that
week. Cause that's a huge week. I forget the week after labor day tends to always be a big
week for some reason. So it's kind of like the kickoff of the holiday season. It's as weird as
it is to say that I really feel like that first week of September is when you really start to see
the releases start to amp up a little bit towards, um, black Friday. It's basically like between
labor day and black Friday are all your big game releases of the year. Well, not all, but a good,
probably 75%. Well, it's like the start of the fourth quarter stuff. So yeah, that too, that too.
So, all right. Uh, there you go for the world release dates. Let's get back into some other
gaming news and then we're going to get to, uh, the listener round table, which, uh, remember we
are taking calls on discord again, so you can join our green room over at vog network.com slash
discord, if you want to call into the show tonight. Um, but you also, um, can, uh, speak
up in our chat room and then we'll see if we have any emails this week over at participate
at orange launch radio.com. But first more news Loki. Yeah. So South Korea is abolishing their,
uh, gaming shutdown law. So the shutdown law banned children under the age of 16 years old
from playing video games between, uh, 12 midnight and 6.00 AM in the morning, I guess, to help them
in school or something like that. Um, and apparently companies could be fined if they allowed,
uh, players to be able to do that. They were fitting that age range. So now they are going
to be getting rid of that and says for use games are often important, leisurely activities and
communication channel. I hope that the preventative measures can respect the rights of the youth
and encourage a healthy home education. So, um, they're going to basically allow them to be
protected through a choice system, which allows parents and their legal guardians to be able to,
uh, permit and regulate the number of hours. So putting in the power or giving it to the, uh,
families to regulate that, which makes sense. I mean, if you have like, you know, kids, maybe they
stay up late on the weekends, they'll play that. I don't know if this is necessarily just during
the week or if it's just every single day, but yeah, at least it's going away. So that
makes it a lot easier for software companies as well. Yeah. I was like, I might know one adult
in here who is playing no man's sky at 1 AM on Saturday morning. I mean, I'm an adult,
I'll do what I want. Um, but I, I also, I wonder if there's maybe some pandemic stuff that plays
into that. I mean, I know these are younger kids, we're talking about like 16 and under,
but I wonder if there's something about the whole, like, you know what they're staying indoors,
playing video games, that's where we need kids to be right now. So I wonder if there's some of that
playing into it too. Possibly. Um, well, speaking of pandemic related things or things that we tried
to, uh, blame or, um, I guess pin on the pandemic, I want to go back to the Pokemon go controversy.
So we talked a couple of weeks ago on the show about the, uh, controversy around the change of,
uh, taking the stop, uh, radius spinning. So basically the radius that you have to be standing
from a stop in order to be able to spin it, you may recall they increased that to 80 meters at
the start of the pandemic. And a few weeks ago, they lowered that back to 40 meters, which
basically pissed off a lot of the fans of the game that had gotten used to the 80 meter, 80 meter
radius. Well, um, I'm going to admit this surprised me. Um, it came out this week in a tweet. Pokemon
go app said, uh, in a tweet trainers were looking forward to sharing our plans as a result of the
task force on September 1st. Remember that they're going to, uh, they, they put together
that task force of YouTubers and influencers to talk about all this stuff. Uh, but they continue
in the tweet, but one thing does not have to wait from now on 80 meters will be the base interaction
radius for pokey stops and gyms globally. So they did take that radius back to 80 meters. Uh, and I
I'm assuming the crowd rejoiced, uh, on that end of things. Um, I'm sort of waiting for the other
shoe to drop because they're still waiting. Like they're still saying we're going to announce the
rest of the task force on September 1st. So I'm sort of waiting for that. And the radius is back
to 80 meters, but we still got to make money off this game. You have to buy an 80 meter pass in
order to know, cause they've already implemented it back in the game. So there's no 80 meter pass
or anything like that, but I'm, I'm still waiting for the, but if you spin it more than five times
in an hour, congrats, all you're going to get are purple potions. Please enjoy them purple potions
and, um, the banana thing. That's Nanab berries. That was a useless one. Yeah. That's all you're
going to get from those stops. Um, still waiting to see what that is. Uh, going to our chat because
I know two of our big Pokemon pals are in chat. S200. Matt says, I still don't believe this will
be forever. Niantic really wanted to keep the 40 meter thing. I apparently they got talked into it.
I actually feel like this 80 meter is going to stick, but there might be, I still think there's
another side to the coin, but we'll see. Uh, Mike Defton chat says, yay for the radius increase,
but we definitely need to say, see what they say on September 1st. Yes. Let's wait for the other.
Let's keep the confetti cannons. Just store it away. You can ready them, but don't pull the
trigger on the confetti cannons until we hear what else is changing about the game. Because we are,
it already was data mined that we're going to do this stuff with like powering up pokey stops and
things like that. I'm just, what is, what is, what is the other half of this? I'm waiting to see.
We'll see. We'll see. All right. But I knew our Pokemon Go fans in the house would appreciate
that. By the way, how many of you have been rating the new, uh, uh, Zacian and Zamzenta,
the Galar region, the Pokemon sword and shield legendaries is so weird to see in Pokemon Go
already. But, uh, I picked up one Zacian. I wish I'd done more. I didn't do enough of
those raids because hello, you could transfer them to your sword and shield game through
Pokemon home. Like the easiest way to get those legendaries. Gosh. So yeah. Um, I have a couple
Zamzatas for now though, or if I'm even saying that right, I'm probably not, I'm probably missing
an N or something, but anyway, uh, it's just weird. Uh, Mike Defton chat says, uh, I did my
Pokedex registry and that's it. Uh, bonds 006 says Zamazenta. I got two of each. So there you
go. Pod culture says I need one. So yeah, it's, uh, try to look for those raids in your area.
See if there's a, here's, I guess where I'll recommend Facebook. See if you have a local
Pokemon Go Facebook group in your area. You probably do. And there's probably a discord
server for it too. And there's a lot of people that do raid organizing in those places. So it's
probably the best way to find. And even if not, you can probably find like,
even though Sacramento as a whole, you know, there's like a million people in the region.
Sacramento as a whole uses discord with Pokemon Go community, but like the locals here like to
use group me for some weird, it's like the worst of the messaging apps. I don't know why they like
it, but they do. So, uh, that's where the locals are to look for raids. But I use, um, there's
actually a network of Ingress players that also play Pokemon that use telegram to coordinate the
remote raids. And that's what I use. That's how I got all those, uh, things that I have is, uh,
using telegram looking for raids. So, uh, as Joe and her map points out pokey Raider. That's right.
They've built all separate apps and websites for the remote raid stuff too. I always forget about
that. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Moving on dark soccer. Let's get to this story, which I think is
kind of neat. So, um, EA has, um, patented accessibility options that are free for all
developers and publishers to use in their game, um, in their games. Um, so these various patents,
um, as they've been shared are contextually aware communication systems and video games,
um, which includes apex legends, uh, ping system, uh, systems and methods for automated
image processing with images with similar luminosities. So those are for color vision
deficiencies, uh, constant ratio detection and rendering system that allows, um, the system to
automatically detect and update subpart contrast regions again for visibility and personalized
real-time audio generation based on user physiological response. So basically, um, this
wasn't developed by EA yet. It's just been patented. Um, but it would, uh, basically give,
uh, clues based on how a player would hear. So they're, uh, really wanting to improve, uh,
the ability of disabled people. I reckon to be able to play games and enjoy them as much
as an abled person. Well, I think, you know, and I agree with our Tetsuya in our chat room.
I know EA has done some scummy stuff in the past, but I can appreciate this. Yes, this is,
you know, these types. Why patent it though, if they're not going to, I don't understand.
They're making it available for other people. They may have it in development,
but they want to have the patent down first. I guess they may have been worried. That's normal.
Yeah. They may have worried someone else would patent it too, when they do want to include it
in their own games. And they're trying to do that good guy, EA thing, especially. I mean,
I don't want to think this is the case, but I worry it may be, especially when their biggest
peers in the industry right now, EA, I'm sorry, Activision Blizzard and Ubisoft, like EA has kind
of not been in that conversation. And I think that's where they prefer to be. Um,
so I think these sort of public interests, doing a good thing, sorts of things are very good for
EA right now. And they know it. Um, so again, I want to believe it's not tied to that and it
is completely separate and independent and just, you know, good guy, EA. Um, I, I don't know that
I a hundred percent put faith that there isn't some interesting timing going on with all this.
Yeah. Yeah. But it's, it's, it's, it's a might suss yo. Yeah. Sus, I think is a good way to put
it. Um, regardless, let's try to focus on the end result, which is good thing. So, you know,
sus or not the end result is a good thing. So, all right. Um, let's move on. Loki,
let's go back to saints row, but, um, for good reason, uh, this is, I know this is very upsetting
for many people in the community. Yes. So unfortunately, like right after we got the
announcement of the super lackluster or scenes for a reboot trailer, um, we also got the
announcement of one of the champions of saints row two, and it's basically a community developer
that's been working on saints row two for the longest time with gentlemen of the row. He,
he went by the name idle ninja. Well, his real name was Mike Watson. And while he was champions
saints row and everything, he, um, a while back actually announced that he was battling stage
four cancer. And unfortunately he succumbed to that cancer around the same time as the
announcement of the saints row reboot. Uh, he was actually solely working on saints row two and
trying to, um, bring that game back to a playable state. Cause you may, I don't know if you knew,
but the PC version of saints row two was horribly rushed and broken, like completely broken.
Pretty sure you've bitched about it on this show. Yeah. So apparently, you know, he, he was able to,
uh, work on that game and actually was able to recover the source code for the game to be able
to actually, you know, do a lot of things for it. And so now there's lots of different mods for it
and lots of patches, you know, the gentleman of the row was something that he had put out
and, uh, worked on for a long time that made the game actually playable. And unfortunately now,
you know, it's like kind of one of the last, you know, people that was really kind of behind the
whole saints row series and kind of leading in the right direction. But, you know, it's unfortunate
they had to pass away. Yeah. Well, I'm sorry to hear that for, um, his family and, you know,
all the community that, uh, appreciated his contributions, um, to the game. So, um, yeah,
that's, uh, it's unfortunate. So, all right. Yeah. Well, to try to end things on a bit of a lighter
positive note tonight, um, I thought we could take this on as our last, um, uh, slight slated story
tonight, and that is a good old fashioned, make you feel old story. And you can probably read it
right there on the sidebar. Oh, but if in the podcast, no, you can't read it. So let me tell
you and inform you and give you your, your old moment. You ready? How old were you when the super
Nintendo came out? Because add 30 to it and it's your age. Now the super Nintendo turned 30 years
old this week. Uh, the super Nintendo, of course, uh, launched back in 1991,
if you can believe it. And I don't think it launched with a lot of games at the start. I know,
um, uh, Oh, by the way, and I should point out the super Famicom came out in November, 1990,
the U S launch was, uh, uh, in the last weekend of August, right before all the kids go back to
school, uh, in 1991. And I believe the launch games were pilot wings, F zero and Mario world.
And that was it, even though, even though some of the early trailers and some of the, you know,
like, um, I didn't realize this, did you know, Paul Rudd, the ageless man behind Ant-Man and,
uh, clueless the movie, you know, from, from very different decades, did you know Paul Rudd was in
that super early super Nintendo trailer? I didn't know that until I forgot it, I guess until this
week. But in that first super Nintendo, you know, they show a little bit of pilot wings. They show
a bit of Mario world, but they also show early footage from Zelda and some football game. I
think, uh, um, not, not the big football game, uh, super high impact. I think it did. Maybe it was,
I don't know. But anyway, um, they, they actually say in the trailer, these games are not out yet,
but the other ones, you know, work as pilot wings was a launch game. Um, I will say one of my
earliest memories of, of the super Nintendo. Um, I played it at a friend's house and I remember
playing pilot wings and I was just blown away by the use of 3d. Cause remember guys, it was the
early nineties. We didn't have like mode seven and what that gave us, which all mode seven is,
is basically the 3d manipulation of a sprite. If you look at a pilot wing stage, it's a bunch of
sprites strung together, but the way they rotate it and make it look, they make it look like a
fucking like actual, like that was the most like real life thing you'd seen at that point. That
was incredible experiencing that for the first time. And, uh, in case you forgot many people
remember, um, the, uh, airplane stuff and pilot wings in the skydiving, but don't forget pilot
wings in the later stages had that fun as hell rocket pack thing. You remember that there was
something they had the rocket pack. That was so awesome to play. Uh, and it wasn't really any of
the previous. So I think, I think that was it. I think it was the plane, the skydiving, the rocket
pack. And I think there was one other thing that showed up in some of the levels, but yeah. Uh,
and then quest Buster says I was playing F zero F zero was also an incredible use of mode seven.
If you think about it, those stages, all they are, are just a bunch of sprites together,
like lie down in a 3d form and it was incredible. So, um, yeah. Uh, those were really impressive
launch games and y'all know I stand F zero and I really wish they would release another F zero
game. Although I feel like Mario karts all we're going to get. Um, but, uh, those were some strong
launch games that did the Nintendo thing very well at showing off what the system could do.
And then Mario world of course, was just a rock fucking solid Mario game that showed off a lot
of cool stuff. It didn't show it off to the extent that pilot wings and F zero did. But, you know,
I think many people still remember that very first stage where the bullet that's like eight
times the size of Mario starts flying at you. And of course, Yoshi, right? Is that so, um,
and honestly that Mario game was so fucking good. Many people consider that the best Mario game.
Um, usually it's a tight race between Mario three, Mario world and Mario 64. And I think
a lot of it depends on your age and what Mario game you have memories with, but I digress. Um,
yes. Tiger class says another thing about pilot wings. When you make it far enough,
there was a level where you fly a helicopter, I think, and you were bombing some targets.
Yes. That was like a surprise twist, like way late in the game. Like you have to get all the
way to like stage seven or eight. You're right. You're right. Oh, Bobby Blackwell says no love
for Gradius three or SIM city where though that's right. SIM city was a launch title.
No, I have a lot of love for SIM city. Gradius three was good too. I didn't really honestly play
that one a lot when it launched, but that's right. SIM city was Nintendo's take on a rock
solid PC title. And that was where they had Dr. Right. Right. Based off will right. And you could
get the Bowser stat. No, it was Bowser instead of Godzilla. It was a Mario statue. It was a very,
it's it's honestly, I think it's the best port of SIM city, uh, next to the CD rom with SIM
city action news, which we've parodied on this show before. Uh, it's probably the second best
SIM city game. That's true. Uh, quest buster and chat says great music and Gradius three,
uh, sacred Jade says I still have SIM city for the SNES. I I'll stand it. Uh, and that's,
you know what it is. That version of the game has things no other versions of SIM city have.
So based on that Nintendo touch, so that is something to consider.
Um, yeah, ultra man on the SNES points out tiger claws, right? So there's,
it's just 30 years of memories on the super Nintendo. It was a good time. And honestly,
I don't know about you guys. I really think super Nintendo was just the best system they
ever put out. I th I still think the super Nintendo holds up stronger than even like the
PlayStation four or the X-Box. I just think the super Nintendo was it. And maybe that's my age
talking. I don't know. And maybe the turbo graphics in Japan, not in the U S so I don't
know. Or maybe it's just because my love for super, super Metroid is that deep, but y'all
that are going to respond with chrono trigger. Guess what? That was super Nintendo too.
So how many consoles can say they have both chrono trigger and super Metroid? I mean,
the galaxy is at peace when you consider both of those things were on the super Nintendo.
Um, let's see. Ooh. All right. Uh, let's see. Yeah. I still have that little bit of a cough.
Sorry. That's okay. Um, Bobby Blackwell, the chat says the chess master was the first SNES game
release, not on launch day. Really? I didn't realize that. Um, let's see. Uh, and Bobby
Blackwell says super Nintendo is my favorite console and I won't read his other comment.
He can go post that on Facebook gaming, uh, w four. He just sees dog in super Metroid.
Uh, w four says blockbuster with a bucket of popcorn specials. Oh yeah. Talking about renting
super Nintendo games. Hell yeah. When you go rent the super Nintendo games of blockbuster or
Hollywood video or whatever, and then yeah, you can get your bucket of popcorn and you know,
$4 candy. Absolutely. Ooh, quest buster with another great early title. Act raiser is another
great game that I'm a huge fan of. I stayed up all night playing that one. And you know what?
I can't think of a lot of things like Actraiser in gaming, maybe I guess, but see, I can think
of things that are like the SIM part of Actraiser, but the way that Actraiser really blended those
things together, I can't think of anything like that. Um, I know I've talked about it on the show
before, but, um, the game that I got, so I didn't get my super Nintendo on launch day. I think I
ended up getting it that holiday or maybe the next year, but my parents had no idea what game to get
me. So it came with super Mario world. And they said that the person at the counter at Montgomery
ward, where they got the super Nintendo, I think that was it or some of that recommended
that they get Draken, which was a PC game that they had ported to super Nintendo.
Um, it was okay. It did the, it did the 3d thing in an RPG environment, but I will say this,
the sequel dragons view is great. That was one of those blockbuster games. I read it because I was
like, eh, the first game was okay. I didn't love it. I did beat it eventually, but dragons view
two is fucking great because it does more like side scroll or action stuff. It kind of does the
act, act, razor thing a little bit actually. So there is that. All right. Uh, let's get to the
listener round table. So if you guys want to give us a call, you can head on over to the green room
over at vog network.com slash discord. Um, or we can do some emails, although I'm not sure we have
any tonight, but I'll ask over at, um, uh, participate at orange lounge, radio.com. Do we
have any emails tonight? Dark soccer. No, no. Just some spam. All right. Well, I don't want
spam. Send, send the spam back. Um, if you would like to send us an email in a future week,
participate at orange laundry.com is the place to do it. Uh, I didn't see anyone in the green room
either. Let me check in. Well, actually I will also open it up, uh, for folks in chat. Uh,
folks in chat are still talking about super Nintendo memories. Let me ask you guys,
I mentioned that like Mario world and Dracken were kind of like my first
super Nintendo games. What about you guys? What were like some of the first early super
Nintendo memories? Although dark soccer, you were, were you a Genesis household? I can't remember
how this went. I was a super Nintendo house. Okay. Dan had the Genesis. What were, Oh,
you were, you are the lucky kid on the block. Uh, I mean, after he and I got together long past
when I was a child. Oh, okay. Okay. Well, what were your, what were your early super Nintendo
memories? Um, playing home alone with my brothers, uh, kicking them out of actually
putting the super Nintendo in my bedroom and kicking them out so I can play legend of Zelda.
Um, lots of turn taking in super Mario world and trying to figure out blastress with the super
scope. We had a super scope. That's awesome. Yeah. Loki, what about you?
Um, I mean, I don't know. I had, there was privilege with my ex.
I had roadrunners death Valley rally. Cause that was the game I picked for some reason.
I think probably cause that was the only game that the store had with, cause I had sold my,
uh, Coleco vision and Nintendo to get a super Nintendo. And so I got, I think roadrunners
death Valley rally. And then I don't remember any other games I got, but I had a lot of friends.
I borrowed games from, so that's fine. Um, but yeah, probably that game. And then like,
you know, uh, link to the past and final fantasy six, you know, three, I guess. Um,
but yeah, those are probably the games I remember. Oh God, when final fantasy two came out, you know,
here in the U S uh, number four was number two in the U S um, uh, when that game came out, I,
I remember asking for that for Christmas and I got it and I know it was not a cheap game. Um,
and, uh, I played that so many hours I lost in that game. That game was incredible.
And then of course, when three came out, I lost a lot of hours in that one too. That's for sure.
But then I think like, God, the super Nintendo was the system that brought us street fighter.
Remember they released street fighter on the super Nintendo. And it really was
like for us at the time, it really was arcade perfect. Even though of course you go back
through another lens now and you kind of look at it and you go, eh, it did have its issues. Like
it wasn't quite as, as crisp as the arcade, but it was, it was, it was damn good. Yeah,
it was damn good. Um, we got it. What passed as arcade perfect back in the day, you know,
with like, you know, some of the stuff that was on earlier systems, I think that it was
acceptable, um, for that. And especially that in like moral combat or something.
I was just about to bring up mortal combat, which came out on good old mortal Monday,
because video games didn't seem to have a regular release day back in the day.
Mortal combat was also on the super Nintendo. Now I, I think a lot of people notice it did
move a little slug sluggish more, but the graphics were very good. Like it looked a
lot like the arcade version, except, Oh yeah, that whole issue with the sweat versus the blood.
And that was a huge deal back in the day was that, wow, this is arcade perfect. Except for one thing,
the thing that most of us associate mortal combat with, but that was, you know, that was the big
thing going on. Yeah, that's true. Then tiger claw points out when the original Mortal combat
came out on the super Nintendo, the first one wasn't perfect, but when they released mortal
combat two on the super Nintendo, this was the first time they had blood showing on the super
Nintendo. That's right. I keep forgetting mortal combat two came out on the super Nintendo, but
yeah, that was a really good, uh, translation of that game too. And yeah, I had the vote because
at that point, now you had the ratings were established. The ESRB was established.
So Nintendo was willing to put out those games now because they had those warning labels on them
and kind of that general system that was in the U S so yeah, mortal combat two had all that blood.
So, um, that was a pretty big deal. Mortal combat three then moved on to PlayStation. Um, I don't
think that ever came out on super Nintendo. Cause I think they kind of upped the, uh,
although I don't think the graphics were that much better than two, but I guess, I guess maybe the
stages when you like, cause moral combat three was when you could like knock somebody down under the
ground or up through the ceiling or whatever, things like that. So it kind of, um, did stuff
there. Oh, did it. Okay. Sorry. Sacred Jade said mortal combat three did come out for super Nintendo.
I guess I only remember it on PlayStation. So, all right. I see. I forgot about that one.
Interesting. But then mortal combat four went 3d. I know that one was a super Nintendo,
uh, Bobby Blackwolf and chap pointed out that a Frogger was the last release on the super Nintendo
and my brain went, Oh, they must've because that PlayStation Frogger was very popular
when it came out, they must've done a port for that for super Nintendo. Actually. No,
it turns out I, it was just a different type of Frogger game actually. So interesting.
All right. Um, let's go to any last minute stories that Loki might have tonight.
I don't have any. Oh, all right. We covered everything. Huh? All right. Let me see. Uh,
I'm going to go to our discord over at vog network.com slash discord. And I just want to
check in real quick because you guys post a lot of good stories throughout the week in the orange
lounge radio channel. So, Oh God, I saw this earlier today and this cracked me up. And maybe
you'd like this to Loki, uh, dungeon Buster posted in our discord, the no Skyrim mod.
And it does just what the name suggests. It stops you from playing Skyrim. When you
boot it up to start a new game, it simply won't let you know what a stupid idea, but I love it.
Okay. That's the mod for dark Sakura. No Skyrim. It's a, it's a mod called no Skyrim.
And that's exactly what the mod does is exactly that. When you try to start a new game of Skyrim,
it won't let you. Okay. How about I've never actually played through a whole game of Skyrim.
You should, you should try this one. Nobody has true. It's a very long game. Um,
time do I have for that? I've got, um, yeah. All right.
Um, let's see some other, uh, of stories that have been posted. Oh, I thought this was interesting.
Um, 13 X forever, um, posted a tweet, uh, that, uh, good old games updated five old
ask Konami titles on PC. But this also is a reminder. Some of these games reported to PC
and you may have forgot, including the Castlevania and Contra collection. I used to play that on
game tap just to not age myself too much, but maybe a little bit, uh, metal gear solid and
metal gear solid two silent hill for the room. I forgot that got a PC port, but it did.
And the original metal gear. I forgot that is based off the MSX version, not the Nintendo.
They actually translated the MSX version. So I didn't even realize that was something I could
buy. So I might get that. So yeah, they patched all those titles this week. Why? Because they
wanted to support modern controllers. So all of these games now support like PlayStation
controllers and Xbox one game pads and stuff. And the key bindings are a little different and
things like that. I thought that was really, uh, neat, uh, that those games, it was a good
reminder, like, Hey, if you want to play like the actual original metal gear, even though we
associate the NES version, a lot of times with that, uh, you can check that out on, um, uh,
that version of the game, which will now work with your current controller.
Um, awesome. Awesome. I think that I'll leave it at that for now. A lot of these other things you
guys posted, we did cover on the show at some point, but I thank you guys for bringing those
to our attention in discord anyway. And I think with that, we are towards the end of the show.
Um, so I'll go around and get final thoughts in just a moment, but first,
as always, I want to thank you guys for downloading orange lounge radio and participating
with the show, whether you did that live, you were downloading the video live as we were doing it,
or if you, uh, listen to us on the podcast feed later in the week, I really want to thank you for,
um, making orange launch radio part of your week. Um, I said at the top of the show,
I'll just remind everybody again, we will not be here next week over the labor day weekend. Um,
since I will be out of town and I think a lot of people have their own plans going on anyway. Um,
dark soccer will be streaming though. If you want to, if you want to still hang with, um,
somebody it's, it's the night for Debbie delight. All right. And, uh, I, I hope to, uh, come back
in a couple of weeks and talk a lot about some of the awesome things I heard at dragon con and
some of the panels hope to meet a lot of great people there. Um, if you enjoyed what you heard
here at orange launch radio, please help us spread the word, tell a friend or two about the show,
because we are the show where every gamer has a voice, but if the voices aren't here to put
out on air, what can we do? Um, so please help us spread the word. I'm an auto host for VOG network
here at Twitch goes a very long way. So thank you for everybody that does that. Um, you don't have
to, but if you want to, you can check out our shop, vog at network.com slash shop, and you can
pick up some, uh, good looking clothes for yourself to wear to conventions or wherever you like the
grocery shopping, wherever you want to take it, uh, such as, and I'm, I'm surprised nobody pointed
this out yet, but I will point out, I am wearing the Vaught. Well, dark soccer and Loki haven't
pointed it out because they can't actually see me unless they're watching the Twitch feedback.
Um, we have, okay. So I am wearing that new VOG network logo logo design. That's a little
bit like jet set radio or eighties ask, uh, the dark soccer put together a couple of months ago.
So I am wearing that new and you can check that out over at vog network.com slash shop. If you
want to, uh, after the show, I have to put this right back in the wash. So I have it ready for
Wednesday when I leave, uh, cause I want to wear this. I actually have like four VOG shirts for
the five days of dragon con, I guess Monday, I'm going to just wear normal clothes, I guess. So,
uh, yeah, there it is over at vog network.com slash shop. If you want to, uh, check out this
shirt that I'm wearing on the Twitch feed or for the podcast folks, you want to see what I'm
talking about. It's over there on the shop. Let's check that out. Yeah. There's all different styles
of the shirt. I like the baseball Jersey, even though the long sleeves aren't always awesome
for California. I will say it will be late in a couple of months when we're finally past the
summer. And I went to San Francisco today and this shirt was perfect because it's still easy breezy
in San Francisco. So there's that for sure. All right. Um, now we can get final thoughts
and dark soccer. I know you're going to head off to start, uh, the murder party. So, uh, what,
uh, is your final thought for us tonight? Um, don't be a dick.
Good call. I appreciate that. All right. Have a good one. Bye. Uh, let's see. My final thought
for tonight is, um, I just, I'm really looking forward to getting out of the house for the first
time since March and going on a trip. So, um, you know, obviously, uh, you know,
with the Delta variant and everything, I can't say I'm not a hundred percent nerve free,
but I appreciate that there are lots of people, including the convention taking precautions.
Um, and, um, I think that everything's going to be just fine. Um, but if you haven't been vaccinated
yet, uh, please do that. Uh, as you probably heard the Pfizer vaccine got the full FDA approval.
So if you were holding out on that, um, there, it went that there's your excuse. Uh, I still,
I still, it blows my mind how people are like, I don't want to take an experimental vaccine,
but I'll inject myself with animal drugs that haven't been proven to be used. I do not
understand that logic whatsoever on the animals. I understand I'm going to have political
differences with people. Um, but I would think those political differences would come down to
like, should the governor be recalled? And in my opinion, no, he shouldn't. And don't forget to
vote, but that's my opinion. And people are going to disagree with me there. At least I can
understand that disagreement a little more than I understand how the governor ticked people off
that one. I get a little more than I'm not going to take a vaccine. I'm going to inject myself
with a cow drug that I just, I don't get. So I don't, I don't know. I don't know when that
shit became political or why. Well, I, I do, but it should never have gotten that way. All right.
Anyway. Um, Loki, let's go to you last but not least in your final thought.
I played laser tag today. I'm surprised that the place isn't closed down yet. And they,
they actually, within the two years time that they had to fix all this stuff, they, um, did hardly
anything. So what are you going to do? What are you going to do? Uh, and Bobby does point out,
you did leave the house, Ida. Yeah. We missed a show. Cause I went out to Idaho one point. Yeah.
For me, that felt a lot different though. Cause I was going to like my friend's house. It's just my
friend's house was 10 hours away. I wasn't hanging out in like a big, big crowd of people, but I get
it fair point for a point. Uh, that's why. And somebody did get COVID after that trip.
So it might not be, it wasn't me, but it might not be the best comparison. Uh, entire call in
the chat says, uh, and don't forget to take a shower before going to the con. I take a shower
every morning, even during a convention. Thank you very much. I feel gross and sweaty if I don't
take a fricking shower in the morning. So I just, I can't, I can't live my con life like that.
Also. Uh, you all know by now that, uh, we, we, we splurge on a suite at dragon con. We,
we spend the extra money. It's don't worry. It's not the money we spend our own money,
Bobby black Wolf and myself on getting a suite at dragon con. And the reason why we do it is
so that it's like, we're not cramped in a room with four or five people. I've done that. I
know many of you still do that, but it's nice to just have space and just be like, I'm going to
just, you know, there's, there's not six people I'm trying to fight for the shower with. I can
do that. You know, it's, it's, it's very easy. Uh, and so we like doing the cons that way,
but if you didn't know, we were actually grandfathered into that suite by, uh, the
incredible Travis Donovan, formerly of understation live, um, who was a legacy
room holder at the Hyatt. And basically he kind of ended up transferring that cause he stopped
going to dragon con for a couple of years. He kind of transferred that to me. And that's where
the VOG network suite, uh, comes from. Yes. And Bobby Blackwell says your subs and bits do not
pay for the suite. Yes. I want to make that very clear. That is not what it is. Uh, legal fees and
the legal thing to run this network. Yes. Um, appearances and promotion at other conventions.
Yes, but not that we, I don't want people to get that idea. So, um, cause that's, that would be
very, very bad optics. And we know that, um, yeah. As 200 Matt says, yeah, I'm too old for the
cramming 10 people into a two queen room for con thing. Just want to bed in my own space. Look,
I don't begrudge anyone who does do that. Cause I know plenty of people that still do that.
That's fine. That's a great life for you. It's just not a great life for me. Anyway,
that's it. That's enough. Uh, we're going to see you guys in two weeks.
Have a wonderful night, everybody. We'll see you next time on orange lounge radio,
happy gaming, happy, whatever you do over the next two weeks,
enjoy Wario aware and all the games coming out. Have a good couple of weeks, everybody. We'll
see you next time. Bye. You've been listening to orange lounge radio. Orange lounge radio is
a production of OLR studios to join us for a live show. Tune into fog network.com Sunday nights at
6 PM Pacific 9 PM Eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily
reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio or fog network, but you know, they were all still
true. See you next week.