[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob so loud and proud, you hear it, it's Christmas time and we got the spirit, Jack was chillin', the hawk is out, and that's what Christmas is all about, the time is now, the place is here, and the whole wide world is filled with cheer, my name's DMC with the mic in my hand, and I'm chillin' and coolin' just like a snowman, so open your eyes, let us in, we wanna say Merry Christmas and Happy New
[SPEAKER_09]: Down in the workshop, all the elves were making toys For the good Gentile girls, and the good Gentile boys When the boss busted in, nearly scared him half to death
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Well the workshop is gone now, he decided to vomit Everywhere you'll find pieces of Cupid and Comet And he tied up his helpers, and he held the elves hostage And he ground up poor Rudolph into reindeer sausage He got Dancer and Brasser with an old German Luger
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, Virginia, now Santa's doing time In a federal prison for his infamous crime Hey, little friend, now, don't you cry no more tears He'll be out with good behavior in 700 years
[SPEAKER_09]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Tonight on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 167.
[SPEAKER_18]: Merry fucking Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: Happy fucking Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Super duper fucking Kwanzaa.
[SPEAKER_18]: Solstice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Whatever the fuck tickles your fancy.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's the Orange Lounge Radio Christmas Fest here tonight on the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_18]: And we might actually get cancelled mid-show tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: It may happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: Lio365 might finally pull the plug on us mid-show tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: And we'll talk about why that would happen all after this lovely introduction featuring that same introduction you've heard all year long, which we desperately need to change.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you know you love it.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll be back with more Orange Lounge right after this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the chatroom's saying that we forgot Festivus.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck Festivus.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck it, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's stupidly late.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, hi!
[SPEAKER_18]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_18]: And this is episode number 167 for this December the 18th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I'm sorry, but it's not a holiday unless they have a greeting card for it.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I don't remember seeing a...
[SPEAKER_15]: Happy Festivus cards at the end.
[SPEAKER_18]: If Hallmark can make a dollar off of it, there's probably a card out there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can I do my intro?
[SPEAKER_18]: Uninterrupted, please.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want, and this is Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_18]: Emphasis on pop culture stuff and us, our lives.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Skye.
[SPEAKER_18]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts in that corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's actually not here.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's on her way, but she wasn't in an accident, but she was like, saw one or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: We've replaced her with a ferret.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, we've replaced her with a ferret.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, she'll be here, just a little bit late.
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't know how late.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think only a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because she called in a timely manner, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: But of course, over there, the one and only Interrupting Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_18]: How are you doing, my friend?
[SPEAKER_15]: Good so far, but I just ate burgers from McDonald's, so... That could change, like the weather.
[SPEAKER_18]: That could change your mood at a moment's notice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_18]: We may have some special guests tonight, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sure Xtafer will want to do a movie review at some point tonight because we did see Jesus is Magic, an appropriate selection for the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_18]: And John's out there too watching the week-old Survivor finale.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then Bugged is out there too playing on the computer.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we'll see if we can get any of them in here during some of tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't realize Survivor's still on.
[SPEAKER_18]: Believe it or not, they're going to do another one.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's another one taping right now and they've got applications for the next one.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, my friends say I should be on Survivor.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to talk about the holidays.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to talk about some Christmas Bomani news.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, a little Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_18]: They keep giving free shit away on Ultramix 3, so I want to talk about Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_18]: And some other gaming stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to hear more about the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_18]: I heard something kind of funny happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: Today?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Had some people camped out overnight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Surprise!
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: Merry Christmas!
[SPEAKER_18]: The internet sucks!
[SPEAKER_18]: So I want to talk about that and have a few good laughs.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, I'm even, for the occasion, I'm wrapped up in a blanket here, and I've got a bottle of vodka in my hand.
[SPEAKER_18]: And today...
[SPEAKER_18]: We will be opening the gate to OLR Town, my town.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_18]: Entire show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exciting!
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, OLR Town's gonna be open.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, um, everybody that has Animal Crossing can come join.
[SPEAKER_18]: Every time I play, I open the gates, but no one ever comes in.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have to talk about Animal Crossing when we come back.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll talk about all that stuff when we come back.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have issues with Animal Crossing, I'll talk about that.
[SPEAKER_18]: So start, so you need to PM your friend Code the Loki so he can get you added.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, PM Loki with your friend code and your name and your town name so we can get you added.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, and then OLR Town will be open very soon.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll be back after this quick introduction.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, of course, since you know it is the end of December, it is mandatory Silent Hill time.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we're going to play Silent Hill and some other winter classics.
[SPEAKER_18]: So hopefully you've been a good boy or girl this year and you're going to get lots of video games for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um...
[SPEAKER_18]: And if you haven't, well, then, you know, you'll be getting a computer virus.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll be back after this with more.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm going to talk about why we're getting canceled mid-show tonight as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: Live through Suspive's fault.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's out of our hands.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll talk about it when we come back after this.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mandatory Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_18]: Merry freaking holidays to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm up here drinking and toasting, it's such a special day, tonight, nightfall, I love you, wish
Christmas is here, Christmas is here Night, nightfall, I love you
Nightfall, I love you Nightfall, I love you Nightfall, I love you
Can you hear me forever?
Do you feel the pain inside of me?
What is true?
When do we leave?
[SPEAKER_09]: Touching back No one cares
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
Please give me favor
[SPEAKER_09]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_18]: Is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_18]: Testing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Testing 1-2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't understand this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does this thing work?
[SPEAKER_04]: This thing reads like stereo instructions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this on?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Broke Down Ghetto Bomani Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: What the?
[SPEAKER_18]: and in that commercial you heard the lovely voice of DarkSakura there, who's not here yet, but she's on her way.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now I'm getting a little concerned.
[SPEAKER_18]: She probably usually would be here by now.
[SPEAKER_18]: I hope everything's going okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sure we'll get the full story as soon as she arrives, but as promised, I'm wrapped up in a blanket.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm celebrating the holidays the best, the only way I know how.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm wrapped up in a blanket, and I have a nice bottle of Guinness.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, I decided against vodka.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went for the Guinness.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I have a nice bottle of Guinness in one hand here.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm just thinking about some Yuletide greetings.
[SPEAKER_18]: which I'm sure I'll be rambling off a little later.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, how's OLR Town going over there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, our one and only guest has just left.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, how nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Glad to see things are swinging in OLR Town.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, you may have to, as you add more friend codes, and don't forget, guys, if you want to get into OLR Town, head on over to our chat room at www.orangeonestrater.com, click on chat, and send Loki a private message with your friend code.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a lot of them already.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, I have to look and see who's in here, but I have a lot of people already added.
[SPEAKER_15]: That were posting in, like, forums and stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, let's see who we got here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nah, I'll just, we'll just take your word for it.
[SPEAKER_18]: You don't have to name them all off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: If they message you and, you know, want to know if they're on the list, you can tell them if they're there or not or get them out of... Now, are you close to maxing out your list just yet?
[SPEAKER_18]: Have you maxed out the list there on Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've only got about seven people.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have Dan, I have Milty, Black Lab, Jason, Harold, you, and Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I haven't touched Animal Crossing in probably about five days now, which is kind of sad, because I was all into Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, I was so up and ready to play Animal Crossing, and I was digging all around town trying to find a copy of Animal Crossing, and I went everywhere I could, and trying to get a copy of Animal Crossing, and...
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura is here!
[SPEAKER_04]: Mother Nature can bite my abundant ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: Your abundant ass?
[SPEAKER_18]: What happened here?
[SPEAKER_18]: You want a sip, honey?
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll talk about our week and day is usually how we start off the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Since DarkSakura is getting situated, we'll go over to Loki and see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_18]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_15]: My week and day, pretty uneventful.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just still been fighting the cold.
[SPEAKER_15]: This week we actually found out though that we're going to get a lot of time off.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're giving us the Friday and Monday, you know, around Christmas and New Year's.
[SPEAKER_15]: So actually this next week I work four days and the week after I work three days.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it rocks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Must be nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: And a $250 gift card for cash.
[SPEAKER_15]: Other than that, I've just been playing a lot of Animal Crossing actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not too much in the
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you do friendly fire on Call of Duty 2?
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, well, we played Deathmatch, so I suppose you could.
[SPEAKER_18]: In the single-player mode, though, because I was watching Extifer play a demo on one of those Xbox 360 kiosks at, like, Circuit City or whatever, and I kept telling him, shoot that guy in the back of the head, shoot your friend in the back of the head, I want to see blood, I want to see blood.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, like, he said he was trying to do it, but it wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, you know, he might have just not been doing it right.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I know that it's really fun, and I like the way that they do the maps where they don't show where each player is.
[SPEAKER_15]: But when you fire your gun, a little blip goes on your screen showing you which direction the sound came in.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: But other than that, I'm actually going to try to play some more games while... Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_17]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_18]: What's actually going on is that Live 365 is doing rotating outages, and they've been doing them all weekend, and we think we've missed it for tonight, but we're not sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: So if kids, at 8 o'clock, the station goes down, we ain't coming back tonight, because Live 365 is doing rotating outages.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know what the hell they're doing.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're moving their servers to a new thing, a bigger, better, stronger, faster, harder server.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to move them to Sweden.
[SPEAKER_18]: So whatever they're doing, they're moving their servers, and if we happen to be on one of the lucky servers that's getting moved tonight, we will be off the air at 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_18]: So if the show goes down at 8 o'clock, we ain't coming back.
[SPEAKER_18]: So sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: But hey, life sucks sometimes, and Christmas sucks when you've been bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: Where are we at show-wise?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please do it with a mouthful of burrito.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_18]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Burrito.
[SPEAKER_15]: Her week and day is going to get a lot better.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been trying to get this forever.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was going to be a wedding gift.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now it's actually a Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got the last one, the actual display model, but... Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have football lacrosse.
[SPEAKER_04]: That means Dan doesn't get to play the PSP anymore.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did that actually come out?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: For real?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I want to see this thing you've been talking about.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm gonna have your present at the end of the week because I didn't go shopping last week as I had finals!
[SPEAKER_18]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, and this will be your week and your day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, finals kicked my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I got feedback on my second to last illustrated project and I made a 95 on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said that my Silent Hill cover looked really nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't got my grade on it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got full points for my Dreamweaver project, and I haven't got the results back of my World Geography final.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you link the Silent Hill thingy-bobber in chat?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because it was actually really good.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's something that I could see actually being used on a PlayStation-type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I linked it in my live journal, but I'll link it in the chat room when I'm done with my thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's not everybody in chat stalks you, LJ wise, so you should probably link that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I also am friends only.
[SPEAKER_18]: I had to fight the rain tonight because it was just really nasty I was sick before I left home, really icky and then I had to pass an accident and then I had to go to Starbucks and get a latte
[SPEAKER_04]: I picked up brownie bites for everybody.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, I wanted a brownie bite, but I had to pass because I was in mid-sentence earlier.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um... No?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they have nuts.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't know what they were.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I will have to eat one and see if they have nuts in them.
[SPEAKER_18]: These are nut-free, my friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are the nutless wonder.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just like... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: A fitting meal.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um... Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also got DJ KK last night, which is the KK Eurobeat song, while I was watching Stargate.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, actually, Loki has OLR Town open tonight for our listeners to join in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, you have the little brat lost in your town, and I have the mama in my town.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I've been trying to get, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so we'll have to fix that at some point tonight, reunite baby and mama.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to find the baby, because baby appears every now and then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, I know where mama is, so I'll go to your town and rescue the baby.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think DarkSakura put something trippy in these brownies because I'm feeling all warm and fuzzy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be the stuff at Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, no, wait, that's the Guinness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I can't have that as I'm going to be driving tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I may have jury duty tomorrow, which I hope I do so I don't have to go to work.
[SPEAKER_18]: Merry Christmas, you get jury duty.
[SPEAKER_18]: How did that happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, because I missed it the last time and I called back to reschedule and I said, yeah, but I'm in school.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, okay, well, we'll just schedule you for the week after finals.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I hope I have it because I don't want to go to work.
[SPEAKER_18]: I work for a bank!
[SPEAKER_18]: Hallelujah!
[SPEAKER_18]: Like murder?
[SPEAKER_18]: Like double murder?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a double murder, but I'd like to get on like a suicide case.
[SPEAKER_18]: How do suicide cases go to trial?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they have to prove it's a suicide for some.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_18]: But with a jury trial?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you mean to kill yourself, corpse?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just ones where they need to prove it's suicide or murder.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like those kind, but I don't like just the straight up, hack you, RR, die.
[SPEAKER_04]: RR, RR, RR.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I want to get in on a case because I, you know, I should have been a lawyer except I'm too, you know, lazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I wanted, I love studying the whole process.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like seeing it in action.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love watching court TV.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are you going to get up there and if they ask you, now DarkSakura, well, of course, that's not what they'd say.
[SPEAKER_18]: They'd say, Jamie, are you a supporter of the death penalty?
[SPEAKER_18]: And you're going to get up there and say, I am the death penalty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goods don't kill people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I support the NRA.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Inmate Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Took all them fuckers on an island.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was a movie with Ray Liotta.
[SPEAKER_18]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_18]: No Escape?
[SPEAKER_18]: And he gets off the island at the end, if I remember.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry if this is a spoiler.
[SPEAKER_18]: If I remember right, he gets off to the island at the end.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think that... I don't know if I want... I don't know if I want Kuki living next door.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that it would solve a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then the inmate where they don't get their freedom, that they get a much nicer jail cell.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they have to defend their title the next year.
[SPEAKER_15]: Someone snuck into my town and dropped fruit at my feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking about overpopulation in the jail cells and cutting down costs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a penny saver.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm frugal.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should vote for me because I would kill more people and save you more money.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I just saw a meme on Life Journal, which is the order of the presidency or something like that, where you can add your name to the list to be in line to be president.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll have to give you a link so you can add your name.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think they're on something like 5100, that if you could kill the other 5100 people, which isn't very many when you consider the population of the U.S., you, Ms.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, could be president of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because I'm not 40.
[SPEAKER_18]: Apparently they've thrown that out the door in this thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's 35, but yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a few years off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I did one other thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because my friend was DJing at Rapture on Friday and ended up going out to the club, which I probably shouldn't have done in hindsight because I was shaking by the time we got back in my car.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was so sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: The Purple Wind The Purple Wind
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't have to be beautiful Anyway And the rest of my week has been recovering from the plague And you are on the other side of the plague now
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I took my double dose of Vicodin last night so that I would sleep through the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I couldn't get to sleep with like two shots of my Vicodin syrup in me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I stayed up and finally I'm just like, shit, it's been three hours that I took it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I took another dose and then went and laid down at 4.30 and woke up at 3.00.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, I slept most of the day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_18]: My week has been very busy.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've just been kind of going out and doing a lot of things.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went to the movies.
[SPEAKER_18]: I went with Extifer and some friends to go see Sarah Silverman, Jesus is Magic, which is playing at our local art house movie, and of course Sarah Silverman's the comic that likes to say fuck a lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll let Extifer talk about it more a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: And
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_18]: from 14 years ago when I first played it is coming back to me and it's just that's all I care about right now so my village is going to be filled with weeds because it's going to have to wait until I beat Final Fantasy IV Advance and I'm making pretty good progress I'd say I'm about I don't know how far I'm into the game about five hours and how long was I game about 30 hours I'm about five hours into the game so as soon as I beat Final Fantasy IV Advance I'll be back into Animal Crossing again and then I'll join you guys in a while in our town um
[SPEAKER_04]: Your town's going to be full of weeds.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know it's going to be hella full of weeds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make sure you buy insurance.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have insurance, thankfully.
[SPEAKER_18]: I bought insurance from the dude when he came.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I have yet to have a single KK song.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've only paid off one loan on my house.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, nothing there.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was going to go to San Francisco yesterday, but the weather here has been kind of crappy here in California.
[SPEAKER_18]: When it starts raining in California, people forget how to drive, and they're not sure what to do, especially when it starts raining hard and they start doing the flood watches.
[SPEAKER_18]: People go crazy.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what's happening today.
[SPEAKER_18]: So crazy, in fact, that we might go down mid-show tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: XBOX 360 XBOX 360 XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_15]: The numbers for Best Buy leaked out to what they were going to get, and they were doing this Sunday sale that was advertised, and basically they were going to have the same allocations as they had when the thing launched.
[SPEAKER_18]: So people were camping out, and basically the sources were said, do not pre-sell any of these, these are to be sold, do not open early, these are for the advertisement.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well...
[SPEAKER_18]: No, the Best Buy, of course, they didn't listen to that.
[SPEAKER_18]: They pre-sold them some of the nights before and people camped out in the rain again for them.
[SPEAKER_18]: And a lot of people were disappointed because, oh, guess what?
[SPEAKER_15]: They sold them the night before and you waited for nothing.
[SPEAKER_15]: But here, here's a nice compact laptop computer for cheap.
[SPEAKER_15]: You want this instead?
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, it's like...
[SPEAKER_15]: So basically a nice bait and switch for a lot of the stores.
[SPEAKER_18]: So now I heard that they just plain didn't get them because we were at a Best Buy here locally and I overheard a conversation about, yeah, all these people were camping out last night and I was like, oh, ha ha, they didn't get there.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's the moment I knew, oh, ha ha, those Xbox 360s didn't show up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some kid on the internet played a practical joke on everybody, you know.
[SPEAKER_18]: So they really did get more 360s, but they just didn't play something?
[SPEAKER_15]: Supposedly they did.
[SPEAKER_15]: They got a shipment in on Friday and they were supposed to hold them until the 18th.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now the thing that was also funny though, and because this sold out so quick, and they did get them, there was rumors that they did get them, and people like, you know, waiting in line stuff, but this whole thing that they had pre-sold them, either the night before, just, you know, bad situation all over again.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, if you didn't get them on this day, never fear, they're getting another shipment on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, just before Christmas.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: You hope.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, is this coming from the same source?
[SPEAKER_15]: This is from the same source.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the source for this Best Buy stuff was an inside source.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he's been the one that's providing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think he's the guy that provides Kotaku with all their information on Best Buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's all inside stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: So pretty much, yeah, the next shipment's the 22nd, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's nice that some stores are getting them, but I notice a lot of other stores, GameStop, are not getting their shipments in on time.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just in time for Christmas, a third shipment to Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's hardly their fault.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, it's not their fault, but it's just because... Well, Microsoft's playing favorites.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, they're playing favorites with Best Buy, so... Must be nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Must be nice to be sucking the cock of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_18]: All I got to say is... Did you see Bill Gates and Melinda Gates?
[SPEAKER_18]: And Bono from YouTube?
[SPEAKER_18]: Persons of the Year for Time Magazine.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Bill Gates...
[SPEAKER_18]: Big fat mug right there on the cover of Time Magazine.
[SPEAKER_18]: And nothing against Bill Gates.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know he didn't single-handedly put out this Xbox 360 and cause a disaster.
[SPEAKER_18]: But he sure makes a good target.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but he is living proof that geeks can succeed.
[SPEAKER_15]: And let me put it this way, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: They really fucked up the whole launch of this system.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_15]: All messed up.
[SPEAKER_18]: What would you say to people though that say every launch is fucked up?
[SPEAKER_15]: There are some pretty fucked up launches out there, but I say the way they've been treating this one, it's been really bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean... At least the 360s work, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: They do.
[SPEAKER_15]: They do work.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, I mean, the whole thing of, you know, they're all defective and stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Mine's... I've had mine crash once.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it wasn't heat-related.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just a glitch in the game because of the crash.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because games were rushed.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_15]: Games will crash every now and then when you try to do weird things with them.
[SPEAKER_15]: It just crashed for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't had it crashed since then, and I've been satisfied with mine.
[SPEAKER_15]: It looks good on normal TVs and stuff, and you don't really need a high-def TV.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, you can, I mean, definitely you'll get the best picture out of it, but it's not going to suffer from having a normal TV, playing even four-player deathmatches and stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it is higher-res, it's really nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: When the screens split four ways, you can still see very well.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not like, you know...
[SPEAKER_18]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, kids, we are going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_18]: Since we already did our winter-themed break there at the start of the show, we're going to just do some random stuff here.
[SPEAKER_18]: And when we come back from this break, we'll get a check on what's going on in OLR Town.
[SPEAKER_18]: I believe that DarkSakura is on her way to reunite Mom and Baby in OLR Town.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're selling the baby?
[SPEAKER_18]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_18]: Tom Nook has offered 600 bells for the baby, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because Tom Nook would buy anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, it's Crazy Red.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because remember, we sell children on the black market.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, that's right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Crazy Red.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, so we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to get a check on what's going on in Noel Our Town.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll talk about some stuff going on in the music game world.
[SPEAKER_18]: And plenty more when we come back tonight here on Orange Lounge Radio.
Thank you for watching!
If you can't say goodbye
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Stay with your eyes in the back of your head You never know if you'll be alive or be dead That is why, always have it You tell your midnight special Never leave, but without it Always better with a midnight special In the dark, always awake You never know, who you're gonna meet Come my friend, you got a midnight special
[SPEAKER_18]: Gaming Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: So uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Welcome back boys and girls to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_18]: In that break you heard the Twilight Zone Midnight Special.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you can say goodbye.
[SPEAKER_18]: and the Rizlem remix, which people for no good reason were chatting about in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I thought I'd throw that in there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, the Rizlem remix kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know why people were talking about it, but they were.
[SPEAKER_18]: The original Rizlem is so, so much better.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, it's not that the Rizlem remix is awful, but it is.
[SPEAKER_18]: It is.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course, you can join our chat room and get in on the fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: www.orangeonstrater.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anything new going on in OLR town?
[SPEAKER_18]: Nobody?
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Everybody fucking wanted to say, or was saying to us, oh, you gotta do the Animal Crossing thing and open up your town and we'll all visit.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here we are, ghost town.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think tumbleweed is rolling by in OLR town as we speak.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, Wonder Dog Harold did leave me quite a bit of fruit at my feet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fruit is good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lots of peaches and pears, so I'm very thankful for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good deal.
[SPEAKER_15]: But yeah, I've got like what a few people added, but no one's visiting.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: 45 minutes until we get the plug pulled on this, kids.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Or at least we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, we are going to open up the Skype line in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: I understand a brand new version of Skype actually just came out.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're up to Skype 2.0.
[SPEAKER_18]: We do not have that Skype version installed over here yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess Skype 2.0 adds webcam to it or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course, we at OLR, we threw away our webcam because it sucked.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hopefully we'll have a new one eventually, but for now...
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: All right, so we are going to open up the skyline a little bit, but I do want to talk a little bit about some Bomani news, some things going on out there in the world of the DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: First things first, there is going to be a soundtrack coming out for DDR Festival and DDR Strike.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's kind of like a combined soundtrack, VWare, I don't really know what the hell they're calling it, but it's going to have a lot of the tracks from...
[SPEAKER_18]: Festival and Strike Superstar
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't think this song list is complete though.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a feeling there's going to be more to it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't think this is it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Very strange.
[SPEAKER_18]: I actually wonder at all
[SPEAKER_18]: If you're a hardcore DDR collector type person, then you'll want this soundtrack, otherwise it really doesn't do you a lot of good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because you can get the MP3s all over the internet.
[SPEAKER_18]: Illegally.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think this is kind of funny because have you visited the musicineverydirection.com website?
[SPEAKER_18]: They have a brand new flash game that you can play on the musicineverydirection.com website.
[SPEAKER_18]: And basically you go around and you collect these little icons, but you try to avoid the bad guy who's throwing, I don't know, little purple waves at you.
[SPEAKER_18]: And if you...
[SPEAKER_18]: I guess what you do is you store up these icons that you collect and then you unleash the moves or if you're in the Beatmania stage, you unleash your DJ power and it slowly converts the background from something boring into like a nightclub or a dance club or a karaoke bar or something kind of cool like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a little bit of a silly game.
[SPEAKER_18]: But what they're doing is that they're actually giving away prizes.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you get a high score, you can submit your score to the scoreboard, and they're giving away prizes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not to the top scorer, but just people who submit their scores to the scoreboard.
[SPEAKER_18]: So it's a random contest, which I think is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: But some of the people on there, oh my god, some of the scores are really high.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some of the people are playing this game into level 35 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got bored of this game after... I'm visiting the website right now, so if you hear some stuff in the background...
[SPEAKER_18]: I got kind of bored of it after like level 3, but I wanted to be able to show the folks in studio what this is like.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you want to check out this game for yourself, it's called The Ultimate Club Promoter Online Game is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's located at www.musicineverydirection.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you want to go directly to the game, go to musicineverydirection.com slash morphed.
[SPEAKER_18]: M-O-R-P-H-E-D
[SPEAKER_18]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to know what suckers they got to be the, uh, the captures for this.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's a little silly.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, you get the idea there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game looks like the ultimate in retarded.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a little silly.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, enough funk boogie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see what they're giving away here on this side.
[SPEAKER_18]: You have until January 30th, 2006.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you get first place, you get a copy of either Ultramix 3 or Extreme 2, a copy of Karaoke Revolution Party, a t-shirt and CDs, which most of us all already own, except for the t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_18]: And some of us even have the t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_18]: My t-shirt is Beatmania, though, which I don't think is one of the prizes here, so that's kind of special.
[SPEAKER_18]: MusicInEveryDirection.com MusicInEveryDirection.com
[SPEAKER_18]: I could have not told you about that and had more of a chance to win myself.
[SPEAKER_18]: But we're nice here at Orange Laundry Radio and we want to share with you guys what's going on.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also in the news, one other little thing here I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, Songpack...
[SPEAKER_18]: 14, and SongPack 26 are out on Xbox Live Ultramix 3, DDR Ultramix 3.
[SPEAKER_18]: SongPack 26 is rumored to only be out there for a limited time.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's going to disappear by the new year.
[SPEAKER_18]: So SongPack 26 is kind of like a Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's free, it's one song, it's a remix of Love Me Do, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: It really sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: The steps are kind of fun though, so it's definitely worth a download.
[SPEAKER_18]: And hey, it's free, so you can't complain too much.
[SPEAKER_18]: Free song.
[SPEAKER_18]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you hit an animal crossing, if you hit start, you can do end the party or whatever, and that'll boot everybody from the village.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, Song Pack 14.
[SPEAKER_18]: Song Pack 14 is out as well, and I'm doing this off the top of my head, but it has a new Neveraka song in it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It has, I think it's called Evolution.
[SPEAKER_18]: It has Gamelan Da Couple.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I thought it was funny because they don't credit Gamelan Da Couple to Tomosuke.
[SPEAKER_18]: They credit it to DJ Mojo or something like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: They give it a different credit, which I thought was weird.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also in there was a remix of Ghost Revival, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: and some other crappy remix I think was in there too.
[SPEAKER_18]: Really nothing to scream about.
[SPEAKER_18]: I haven't been too excited over these songpacks.
[SPEAKER_18]: But judging from the general reaction on DDR Freak, it seems to be getting an okay reception, especially when it comes to the steps.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I will give it that.
[SPEAKER_18]: The steps are something kind of new.
[SPEAKER_18]: And especially in one song that I played, I want to say it was the Ghost Revival remix.
[SPEAKER_18]: or something about Brazilian Anthem.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know if that was a previous Bomani song or if that's just coming from nowhere.
[SPEAKER_18]: They all have some kind of interesting steps, like patterns you don't usually see in DDR, which is kind of phenomenal when you consider they've done hundreds and hundreds of DDR songs at this point, and there's only the four arrows.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's only so many different types of patterns you can do.
[SPEAKER_18]: You kind of see some different stuff happening in these songs, so you have that to look forward to to download.
[SPEAKER_18]: So check that out over on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, I know you guys haven't had a chance to check out these song packs, so I wouldn't expect that you already have this up or whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, we are going to open up our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's over at www.orangehonestradio.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: Click on Interact With Us, and you can...
[SPEAKER_18]: Call us on the skyline.
[SPEAKER_18]: Also, we have a phone number.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't give out the phone number enough, but you don't even have to have the internet.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you just want to call us, you can actually do that.
[SPEAKER_18]: The phone number is area code 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_18]: But kids, please get your parents' permission before calling.
[SPEAKER_18]: Otherwise, when the phone bill comes in, you might be in big trouble.
[SPEAKER_18]: So the skyline is open.
[SPEAKER_18]: There is a new version of Skype out.
[SPEAKER_18]: However...
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't know if it's widely out there yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: A lot of you guys probably don't have it.
[SPEAKER_18]: We don't have it.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're getting a call, so let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, Skye, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_18]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I just want to say, you know, Christmas is already coming in a week, and, you know, for Christians over there, Merry Christmas to everyone.
[SPEAKER_18]: and a happy holidays to you too, my friend.
[SPEAKER_18]: Christmas, Hanukkah, Kwanzaa, Festivus, whatever the case may be for you folks out there.
[SPEAKER_18]: A politically correct winner to you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Have you ever watched the video of Love Is Dreamin' Us, you know, the beat from the Beatmania US where LED is playing?
[SPEAKER_16]: What song again?
[SPEAKER_16]: Love Is Feelin'?
[SPEAKER_18]: Love Is Dreamin' Us.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, Love Is Dreamin' Us.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, what is this about?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, Love Is Dreamin' Us is confirmed for Beatmania US.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, right on.
[SPEAKER_18]: So what's this?
[SPEAKER_18]: There's a video of him out there actually playing it on the internet?
[SPEAKER_18]: Or what's going on?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, he did play Love is Dreamin' this.
[SPEAKER_16]: He plays on the Player 2 side, and he got an A for playing it, even though it's 134k on his score.
[SPEAKER_18]: Where did this video come from?
[SPEAKER_18]: Was it him playing on an arcade machine, or was it him playing on Beatmania USA?
[SPEAKER_18]: Where was it taken?
[SPEAKER_18]: What is this going on here?
[SPEAKER_16]: I think somebody linked it on Bimani Style or VG Army where LED is playing Beatmania US with a 2DX controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: With one of the official ones?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, the KOC one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they haven't altered it or anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's exactly as the Japanese one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like video and everything?
[SPEAKER_16]: The video itself is exactly from the Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you just cut out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: We were losing you a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think you're back here.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're here for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, so it has the same video and everything, so not a lot's changed there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nothing's changed.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, so the only thing that made me disappointed was the scoring, so I think they better tune that up to the standard.
[SPEAKER_16]: Did it have the art at the end?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, the score result?
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is it an early build of the game, or are they thinking it's the final build, or what?
[SPEAKER_16]: Some semi-final build.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's the last purple interface.
[SPEAKER_18]: How are you feeling about Beatmania USA at this point?
[SPEAKER_16]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_16]: If they don't put any goalie background result videos, I mean background images of goalie arts, I don't think I'll, you know, I'll think about buying it or not.
[SPEAKER_18]: But what about those new controllers?
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, the rumor of the new controllers.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, you probably have an arcade style, so what do you care, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, KOC, not Arcade Stock Controller.
[SPEAKER_18]: But the rumor is that the Konami controller they're going to release here stateside is better than the one in Japan.
[SPEAKER_18]: I heard from Floatwalker that it's going to be spring-loaded.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: And of course, all this kind of stuff is a matter of preference as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's nothing to say that one is better than the other, because that all kind of stuff is relative, but...
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, if it doesn't stick as much and they do a different kind of thing with the keys so the buttons don't stick, they'll do that whole thing, or it has a slightly different look maybe to it or whatever, it could be a more widely popular controller.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Speaking of sticking, I just noticed on my controller...
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, I don't exactly press the center of the key, but I mostly, on the white keys I press the top, and then the black keys I press on the bottom, and then there are like scratches that causes the, you know, that causes the stickiness.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should do what I did with mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drop it off the top of the van.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's never broken.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't imagine how that worked.
[SPEAKER_18]: That would kill me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It happened at Anime Expo 2001, I think, which is when I first got my controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was unloading it from the van, and it stuck up at the very top, and it fell face down.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my controller has never stuck, except one key, and I cleaned it, and it worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like my controller is the super controller of all 2DX controllers.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm thinking the Virgin Mary lives in your controller or something because that's a miracle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I should probably, you know, take a picture of the circuit board and say, look, it's Jesus.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, you really should.
[SPEAKER_16]: Have you ever tried to bash something on DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: To do what?
[SPEAKER_16]: The Vaseline mod?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_04]: All I've done is just clean the contacts.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've been doing it every two weeks whenever I play 2DX.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it works fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually never had any problem with my... It was only one of them that stuck, and that was the one that I would always slam on with my thumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I just rotated the keys, cleaned them out, worked just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, what bothers me is playing on the shaved ones.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't like shaved keys.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's irritating.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't actually like the ones where they put the little bit of rubber or foam under the key to press the contact up.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not comfortable.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry, it's just really funny because you guys are talking about putting Vaseline on your keys and shaving it and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: You are a pervert, Mr. Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: My mind is going right to third grade.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you actually use KY for the mod as well?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure KY would work just as well as Vaseline.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to shave my controller and put KY all over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the spirit?
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to hit Bob with something.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was having it sit in for you earlier.
[SPEAKER_18]: I had it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Apparently several people in our chat room want ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: Lube up those controllers, kids, and go to town.
[SPEAKER_18]: I do have a lot of apples.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Siggy, I'm going to go ahead and let you go.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any final thoughts, my friend?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, nothing much else to say, but hopefully next year you get a Skype 2.0 so you can see what I really look like.
[SPEAKER_18]: I fear some of our listeners, I mean, not you so much, my friend, but some of our listeners might be listening to us in the nude, or God knows what.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know if I want that webcam on everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right, my friend, I'm going to let you go so we can get to another call, okay?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, and happy new year to Orange Lounge Radio in case we don't see each other.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to do something next week, but it's not going to be a live show, but we should be here in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have to talk to the crew about that when we're on a break or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: But happy new year to you as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: Have a good holiday season.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Later.
[SPEAKER_16]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right, we're going to do one more call here, and then we're going to take a break and try to get some frickin' air in here.
[SPEAKER_18]: I actually turned on the air conditioner, so the people out front are going to kill me because it's cold out front, but oh well, they can deal.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's go to another break here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what blankets and jackets are for.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not a break, a call.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, who's this?
[SPEAKER_18]: Xander from Florida.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello, Xander from Florida.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh, not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Have an interesting anecdote, if you're willing to hear it.
[SPEAKER_01]: An anecdote?
[SPEAKER_01]: We haven't heard... Okay, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a short one, so don't worry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll admit, I'm a bit... I'm a bit of a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Up to... A fanboy of Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_18]: That's really sweet.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Fanboy for what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sort of, but... I'm a bit of a Sony and Nintendo fanboy, and for a while I was kind of down on the PSP, but I never played it, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just reading stuff on the internet, it's like, oh yeah, I don't like any games on the PSP, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But since I don't really have any kiosks, I never really got a chance to play it or anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I mean, I'd seen it, but I never really got a chance to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, let's see, two days ago, I was at this Christmas party with my friend, and he's a Nintendo fanboy, and he had a DS for a long time.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it broke for a second time somehow.
[SPEAKER_01]: He must be abusing that thing if it's breaking.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know how, but he's breaking it.
[SPEAKER_18]: He's shaving it and using KY apparently on it, which you shouldn't do with a DS.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can do that with a 2DX controller, but please kids, do not shave and lube your DS.
[SPEAKER_18]: It does not like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_18]: If the animals in Animal Crossing are asking you to shave your DS, just seriously, it's time to go outdoors.
[SPEAKER_18]: It is time to go out in the real outdoors.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_18]: It broke for the second time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he gets it, and he brings it.
[SPEAKER_01]: He buys Tokobots and a few UMDs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: So he brings it, and I start playing it, and I'm like, hey, this is actually pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I mean, it doesn't necessarily have, it's not, it doesn't have all the games that are my taste, but, you know, I don't expect that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I actually had some fun with it, you know.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I mean, I guess, really, you shouldn't diss a system, even if you look at the games, and you look at the reviews, and they all suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't listen until you play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, unless it's an N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_18]: We need to add that.
[SPEAKER_18]: However, you draw some interesting parallels here because you could say the same thing about an Xbox 360, no?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I'm anti-Xbox.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know, because you said you're Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I have played Xbox, though, and I think that's the difference.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's interesting about this, and I'm kind of just thinking out loud here, this is all kind of coming together as I'm sitting here talking, which is not normal for me to just talk out my ass, but you got the PSP thing going on, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: And the PSP
[SPEAKER_18]: If you put the PSP and the DS side by side, and you want a system that is strictly the better gaming system, I honestly think it's the DS is the better gaming system.
[SPEAKER_18]: But of course, it also depends on the kind of games you like.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, the DS has a different type of game, so you got that.
[SPEAKER_18]: But the PSP...
[SPEAKER_18]: The PSP is a sexy ass system for one, but the PSP allows you to do so much else on it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Especially when you consider this 2.6 firmware upgrade.
[SPEAKER_18]: You either can upgrade your firmware or you don't upgrade your firmware.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can upgrade your firmware and get podcasts.
[SPEAKER_18]: and get pictures and get the internet wirelessly and get movies downloaded from the internet and get MP3s so it's practically like having an iPod or you can not upgrade your firmware to 1.5 and download that cool ass top down shooter.
[SPEAKER_18]: You cannot upgrade your firmware and get all the homebrew applications including homemade shooters and emulators.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although if all you want to buy a portable system for is to play NES games, that's a whole other issue.
[SPEAKER_18]: So that's where the PSP really excels is at being a multimedia system.
[SPEAKER_18]: So now flash forward to the current competition we've got going on here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not a lot of great games for the Xbox 360 right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hopefully some good ones on the way.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hopefully some good ones along the way.
[SPEAKER_18]: But the Xbox 360 trying to sell itself as more as the multimedia thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: The little white box that Microsoft wants in every living room.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which is very interesting because that is how I see Sony positioning itself as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sony wants to be that little box in everybody's living room as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_18]: GameSpoiler
[SPEAKER_18]: I think Iwata is a fucking genius.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think he's taken the company in a brilliant direction.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, but it is a big gamble as well.
[SPEAKER_18]: It is.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I think... They don't really have anywhere else to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they just keep trying to battle Sony and Microsoft on their grounds, they're going to lose.
[SPEAKER_18]: The revolution could crash and burn.
[SPEAKER_18]: It could be another N-Gage and it wouldn't matter because they've still sold 50 kabillion Game Boys.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think a billion is an actual number now because Nintendo has sold that many Game Boys in different forms.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, there's still more Game Boys than PS2s, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, Nintendo has dominated the handheld market, and I really don't see anybody posing a real threat to that anytime soon, not even the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: The PSP is bringing in a new market, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think the PSP is getting the same people that the Game Boy and DS is getting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because it's not a gaming system at heart.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an entertainment-on-the-go system.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm getting yelled at in the chat room for calling the DS a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, it's not really a Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Technically, the DS is not a Game Boy, but give me this.
[SPEAKER_18]: It does have a Game Boy Advance slot, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: So that's what a lot of people are considering when they buy a DS is, oh, this will play all my Game Boy Advance games.
[SPEAKER_18]: So while it might not be a Game Boy per se and it doesn't carry the Game Boy brand, it is the evolved form of the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it still can't play Tetris.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it still can't play Tetris.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it could play if they re-release Tetris or whatever.
[SPEAKER_18]: And since they re-released Dr. Mario and Puzzle League recently on one cartridge.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you notice they're not calling it Pokemon Puzzle League?
[SPEAKER_18]: They're just calling it Puzzle League.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought that was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Since they re-released that on one cartridge.
[SPEAKER_01]: Has that come out over here?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm seeing ad banners for it on the internet, so I think it's out.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not a game I'm interested in because I actually have both games on other consoles.
[SPEAKER_15]: It came out back in November.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_18]: But it's not something I really care about.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I didn't notice either because I already have both those games.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I'm sure it's a great Christmas title.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, Xander, appreciate the call.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm glad to hear that the PSP was, you know, you had a good experience with it because that sucks to be a fanboy of something and then get really let down.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's a bad thing to be a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, if you just stick to one thing, you'll never broaden your horizons.
[SPEAKER_18]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_18]: Be careful when you get narrow-minded.
[SPEAKER_18]: And especially in the case of Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_18]: When the Xbox first came out, I hated it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I thought it was a crap system because, remember the golden rule of gaming, the system is only as good as the games that are on it, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: And the Xbox had nothing going for it until they started getting DDR, they started getting Fable, they started getting Halo.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I like Halo.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know a lot of people don't.
[SPEAKER_18]: But they started getting some more games.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: They started reaching out into other areas that weren't just sports and shooters.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know?
[SPEAKER_18]: But that's just me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a Buffy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and they did have a Buffy game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which is worth something.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, Xander, we gotta let you go so we can go to break.
[SPEAKER_18]: But thanks for calling as always, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Any other thoughts for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_01]: Your taste in music still sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I have a microphone and you don't.
[SPEAKER_18]: So that's what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Later.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just for that, Xander's going to start his own radio station.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's going to be Sky Sucks A Lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, Extifer.
[SPEAKER_18]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_18]: Do we have a microphone?
[SPEAKER_18]: We can say hello to Extifer.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: How are you, my friend?
[SPEAKER_17]: I am fine, my friend.
[SPEAKER_17]: Are you guys going out or something?
[SPEAKER_17]: You have your sock.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to put this on and go.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to Chipotle.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yum, yum.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is it getting really cold out there?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because we had to turn on the air.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're burning up in here.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: I like the coldness.
[SPEAKER_18]: So you guys are leaving for a little bit so we can leave the door open?
[SPEAKER_18]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Did you want to do a movie review real quick before you go?
[SPEAKER_17]: Are they waiting for you or what?
[SPEAKER_17]: I could do a Diet Coke.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anybody else want anything from Chipotle?
[SPEAKER_17]: I want some hot beans.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hot beans?
[SPEAKER_18]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do you want to do a movie review or do you want to wait until you get back or what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sure, I'll do a movie review.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's do a movie review.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because, you know, Live 365 might pull the plug on us tonight, and in which case, you know, we want to make sure that we got your movie review in.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why would they pull the plug on you?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because we're letting you on the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because we eat through a feeding tube.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_17]: I saw Sarah Silverman's...
[SPEAKER_12]: The Pussy?
[SPEAKER_12]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_12]: Jesus is Magic.
[SPEAKER_12]: And she's officially now my favorite comedian because she made jokes about waxed assholes and that was just like...
[SPEAKER_12]: Sera Silverman's like...
[SPEAKER_12]: No, there was 6 million people that died in that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And her niece is like, no, what's the difference?
[SPEAKER_12]: And she goes, well, 60 million is unforgivable.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you're easily offended, do not see this movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, she's so funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: Everything is, nothing is off limits.
[SPEAKER_18]: She talks about black people, Asians...
[SPEAKER_12]: Jews, Women, Men, 9-11, Holocaust, AIDS American Airlines have a slogan Don't ruin all the jokes That one's the best because it'll make you like That offended people in the audience I don't need you alienating our listeners I don't care, I really don't care Your listeners like me enough to know that I really don't care So it was a good movie, I really liked it
[SPEAKER_12]: The musical numbers were kind of weird, but... And then there was a weird masturbating scene in it, which was kind of weird, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really hot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, but, otherwise, it was a good movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go see it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You may want to wait for it to come out on video.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two cocks up and a flaccid... Two cocks and a flaccid cock.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, that's two cocks and a half.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Two cocks and a pussy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Look, this segment's over.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get out.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: What kind of ranking scale is that?
[SPEAKER_18]: I give it two cocks and a pussy.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a three-way.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a three... You're so weird.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to go to a break, kids, and try to get some air, because we're dying in the hotbox.
[SPEAKER_18]: And hopefully we'll be back, and either the plug will get pulled off... Hotbox.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hopefully we'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you got a kid act like her father, if the baby ain't yours, then hey, why bother?
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't try, boy.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm bad, boy.
On a day
[SPEAKER_09]: From the Step Squad to Orange Cloud, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_09]: Holla!
[SPEAKER_09]: We are the winners!
[SPEAKER_18]: And that break you heard Inside Your Heart by Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_18]: Before that, A Day Like Today from In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_18]: DJ Simon with Air.
[SPEAKER_18]: You get it?
[SPEAKER_18]: Joke, because we said we're breaking for air.
[SPEAKER_18]: And my baby mama from DDR Solo starting that set off.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hope you enjoyed that mix of music.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here we are back on the show and we may or may not get the plug pulled.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see pretty soon here if we're going to get the plug pulled on us for maintenance.
[SPEAKER_18]: So again, if we go down, we are going to be down all night.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we apologize.
[SPEAKER_18]: But we thank you, of course, for sticking with us and listening, especially after last week because last week was kind of sucky because we had the plague, all of us.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's so weird now because I don't feel sick at all, no remnants or anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I thank
[SPEAKER_18]: I still have the plague I know you still have the plague, but the mini-plague is gone
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to take that Airborne stuff more often now.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to take one of those every day, see what happens.
[SPEAKER_18]: See if it makes me a strong boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could just take a multivitamin.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've thought about that, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: But the thing I like about Airborne is that it actually makes a drink, kind of.
[SPEAKER_18]: And the drink's not bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I've had worse things in my life, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's one of those acquired taste kind of things.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, I'm curious here, because we're getting into the Christmas season.
[SPEAKER_18]: First, I want to know, what's on your Christmas list?
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to know what's on our host's Christmas list.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's on your Christmas list?
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe gaming-wise, or maybe just anything-wise.
[SPEAKER_18]: And what your plans are for this lovely Christmas break coming up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Or Hanukkah, you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_18]: When I say Christmas, I mean all that, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: We are not going to be politically correct on this program.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're putting it all under the label of Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: which is probably not extremely politically correct, but you know how it goes.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, Loki, I'll start with you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's on your Christmas list, and what are you going to do for the holidays?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't really have anything on my Christmas list since I've already bought my 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just, probably an HDTV, I guess, if I were to ever get one.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be almost impossible because they're expensive.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, other than that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's not really any games I want.
[SPEAKER_15]: I
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to wait, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dead or Alive, I guess I could try to go get that since that's supposed to come out this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Assuming it doesn't get pushed back again.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just in time for the holiday.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're airing the commercials on TV and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's coming out next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: The 29th.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just in time for the gift certificates and holiday returns.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, maybe I'll get that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not a huge fighting game fan, but it looked good, so...
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh no, there's really not too much I want.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just, I don't know, HGTV, I guess I could need one of those.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to finish my cabinet.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need time to finish my cabinet.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to finish it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Get the other controllers done.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm kind of holding back because I don't have any place to store them if I were to finish them.
[SPEAKER_15]: Storage is a big issue.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, but as far as Christmas plans go, uh, playing a lot of Xbox Live, hopefully, because I did pay for a year of it, and I want to kind of get some use out of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, and also, I'm supposed to go to my sister's house for Christmas, but she's local, so, um, that's pretty much it, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just going to be pretty low-key.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha, low-key.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see, what else do I want?
[SPEAKER_18]: I kind of want an Xbox 360, and I kind of don't.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, you can wait, but if somebody wanted to give me one for Christmas, hey, I wouldn't mind.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd get that other Xbox out of there, get the other Xbox in there, the 360, because it definitely is pretty, and I do happen to have an HDTV, so it looks very pretty.
[SPEAKER_18]: I already kind of bought myself an early Christmas present.
[SPEAKER_18]: I bought myself a new phone, because my old phone, this is what I did last weekend, since we kind of ended up not doing a show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a new phone here, and it actually takes video, which is an incredibly useless feature.
[SPEAKER_18]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_18]: She wants to see Brokeback Mountain, too, which I really want to see, of course, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I don't think that's going to be out here on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: Isn't that a limited release thing?
[SPEAKER_18]: I think they're afraid of releasing it in the red states, so to speak, because I guess...
[SPEAKER_18]: People in red states, quote-unquote, can't appreciate a good gay cowboy movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I've read the book, and there's more to it than the gay cowboy thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: The media's really putting the spin on it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just like, oh my god, it's gay cowboys fucking.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, it's not gay cowboys fucking is not what the movie's about.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a tale of forbidden love.
[SPEAKER_18]: Romeo and Juliet was a tale about forbidden love, okay?
[SPEAKER_18]: That is what the movie is really about.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not about...
[SPEAKER_18]: Jake Gyllenhaal doing Heath Ledger in the booty hole.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although, that might be a plus.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, what are your Christmas wishes and what do you have planned for this Christmas?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a memory foam contour pillow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a Sobakawa pillow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very, very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't really want any video game systems because I already own them all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want a copy of Emerald Dragon for the PC Engine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've wanted that game for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, Panorama Cotton for the Master System.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone must have tossed down $600 on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not supposed to doubt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also want a tapeworm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like one that won't kill me, but that will eat all my extra food.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd actually like my appetite back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'd like to be over the plague.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want a hippopotamus for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want a penguin for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a compound.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that we can hole up in it and drink red Kool-Aid.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I need season 8 of Stargate box set.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very much so.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Sony Ericsson Vodafone new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need that too.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what movie, because you brought up a good point about hippopotamuses and the animals we want for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_18]: Do you know what movie I finally saw because nobody would go see it with me in the theater?
[SPEAKER_03]: Madagascar?
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: March of the Penguins.
[SPEAKER_18]: I finally saw it on DVD.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what the big surprise was about March of the Penguins?
[SPEAKER_18]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_18]: I love penguins, love penguins, but the movie was very boring.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a coffee pot, like a nice one, that does lattes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sort of like the big machines they have at Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I want the Foamy The Squirrel DVDs, even though Foamy's voice gives me a headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's all about the guy that works at Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: I didn't know they actually released that on DVD now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, they're from the Squirrels DVDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually I want the Squirrely Wrath t-shirt too.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, we need to release the DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: We sure do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe that'll be an upcoming event for 2006.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have our own best of DVD release.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_18]: We've got a lot of stuff in store for 2006 here at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least I think we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Including me moving to Antarctica.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know the t-shirt thing is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've got to talk to you guys about that after the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: But the t-shirts are happening, kids.
[SPEAKER_18]: There will be shirts very, very soon.
[SPEAKER_18]: Like January soon, we're hoping.
[SPEAKER_18]: If we get our logo done and everything, we're going to have shirts.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's very exciting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because you guys have been begging us for shirts for a long time.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we're going to make that happen very soon.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's kind of our Christmas present to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: because we love our fans.
[SPEAKER_18]: In addition to doing this show all the time.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, well, it looks like we got past 8 o'clock and we're still going.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I'm thinking that means unless Live 365 is being slow, we are safe from getting dropped tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: So that's good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's move on into the cage match, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's do an Orange Lounge, good old-fashioned beat-down cage match type thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: The way the cage match works is we're going to play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_18]: And you guys are going to pick your favorite, and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's money, music, and video game music program.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, so you guys are just going to vote for your favorite.
[SPEAKER_18]: Two weeks ago, since we didn't do a show last week, we had this song win and it's actually a DDR artist who actually won the cage match.
[SPEAKER_18]: The artist's name is Tess.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's Tess and the song is called The Second You Sleep, I Stay To Watch You Fade Away.
[SPEAKER_18]: And we're going to go ahead and play this song for you guys.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you only get a clip because it actually already won a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_18]: So you only get a clip of it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's going for a third week, second win tonight in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_18]: So enjoy or don't, it's your decision.
[SPEAKER_18]: But it is last week's winner.
[SPEAKER_18]: Here it is, song number one, Tess, The Second You Sleep.
[SPEAKER_18]: Enjoy.
I say to watch you fade away I dream of you tonight Tomorrow you'll be gone
[SPEAKER_18]: Wasn't that a great fade?
[SPEAKER_04]: You ruined it the internet, Rob.
[SPEAKER_18]: Song one there, Tess, I stay to watch you fade away.
[SPEAKER_18]: Will it stand the test of the battle of two other songs?
[SPEAKER_18]: I almost sounded like a Soul Calibur controller.
[SPEAKER_18]: Two other songs here tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Song number two is DarkSakura's pick.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, what did you pick for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a song I've been meaning to put in the cage for a while because we really, really need drum and bass represented.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's one of my favorite DJs and one of my favorite singers, and it's actually one of my all-time favorite songs ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's DJ Crush and Estero with Final Home.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played it on my show a couple times, so our listeners might find it familiar.
[SPEAKER_18]: DJ Crush with Estero, Final Home is song number two.
[SPEAKER_18]: Enjoy!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: Song number two in tonight's cage match was DJ Crush featuring Astero with Final Home.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's go around and see if that was judged as being a good song or a poopy song by our judges.
[SPEAKER_18]: Us, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song is sexy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets a ten.
[SPEAKER_18]: A sexy ten from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not that sexy.
[SPEAKER_15]: It gets an eight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not As Sexy 8 from Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know if I would call that drum and bass.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's trip-hop before I would call it drum and bass.
[SPEAKER_04]: But DJ Crush is almost all drum and bass.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, that's a little more trip-hop to me, but it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_18]: It doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_18]: Call it whatever the fuck you want.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's still a fine song.
[SPEAKER_18]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a song I could imagine myself having sex to, which is always a good thing, so I give it a 9.
[SPEAKER_18]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, let's get into song number 3 tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki picked song number 3.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, what'd you pick for us?
[SPEAKER_15]: I picked something completely last minute.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have not even listened to this yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: So this is a suicide pick from Loki, basically.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, originally this week I had wanted to pick a remix of the Contra theme for some reason.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did download something, but it was too long.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was like seven minutes long because it was kind of a medley.
[SPEAKER_15]: But this is another remix.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is actually from Contra Shattered Soldier.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the remix is called Spread Your Fire Against.
[SPEAKER_18]: At first I thought this song was called Spread Your Legs, because I just saw the spread your.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, Spread Your Fire Against Me.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's by Brain Cells and Dennis.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's song number three, and Loki better hope it's good, or else he's going to look like an ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_18]: Enjoy.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I hope that you live and there's no use to me And I know you're trying to steal your mind off of the TV
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: We will try to verify why he's holding on There's no use in falling out, wasting our precious time They won't learn from their mistakes, so you need that to die
I was left in prison asking every threat to resign Die Die
A dreaded total fighter With a fucking US Army I'll look inside till you have enough Kill them all with no remorse, no!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: Song number three.
[SPEAKER_18]: God, I love that challenge.
[SPEAKER_18]: Song number three, Brain Cells and Dennis with Spread Your Fire Against Me, which apparently is a remix from Contra's Shattered Soldier.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Does that make you want to spread your fire or spread your hate?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes me feel like I should worship Satan or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it gets a minus 666.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: It gets a positive 666 to counteract the minus 666.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it effectively has a zero?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_18]: Good thinking, Loki.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good thinking.
[SPEAKER_18]: That song does make me want to smoke crack and worship Satan.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, you know, actually it kind of reminded me of Gwar a little bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I started thinking about...
[SPEAKER_18]: I know Gwar is a lot cooler, but then I just imagine these giant outfits, because the thing I love about Gwar, like, fuck the music with Gwar, but just them getting up in those giant costumes and thrashing about, where they all look like Shao Kahn from Mortal Kombat, and they're on stage thrashing about, is really badass.
[SPEAKER_18]: And so I kind of thought about that, and that made me giggle a lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: So that song gets like a five for the number of times I laughed.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, but it's not up to us.
[SPEAKER_18]: We are not the final judges.
[SPEAKER_18]: You are.
[SPEAKER_18]: You kids that listen to this program out there and are in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: You are the final say.
[SPEAKER_18]: So let's see the three songs you get to vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Song number one, as a reminder, is Tess with The Second You Sleep, I Stay To Watch You Fade Away.
[SPEAKER_18]: And song number two you can vote for tonight is DJ Crush and Astero with a song called Final Home.
[SPEAKER_18]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Brain Cells and Dennis with Spread Your Fire Against Me.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a good time.
[SPEAKER_18]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I hope it does well.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's up to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_18]: So send in your votes now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, it looks like we didn't get the plug pulled on us, so we get to continue to do a show here.
[SPEAKER_18]: How's OLR Town going?
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you finally just close the gate and say, fuck you all, and now you and Jamie are playing?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, but Harold's been the only one that's joined.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I am taking this time to write OLR message in a bottle spam.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, propaganda.
[SPEAKER_15]: Propaganda, yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good, good thinking.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was my idea.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, what is this?
[SPEAKER_18]: You guys are going to spam Orange Lounge Radio across Animal Crossing World by what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Using a bottle?
[SPEAKER_18]: How does this work?
[SPEAKER_04]: The message in the bottle, you basically write whatever you want, put it in the bottle and drop it in the ocean.
[SPEAKER_18]: Message in a bottle, message... Penfold.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, um... It's like supposed to go to somebody else's random village, so they'll get... You should listen to Orange Dawn Radio because we said so.
[SPEAKER_18]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see if it works.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, after the cage match is usually where I go over to you and I say, Hey Loki, what's going on in the sim scene?
[SPEAKER_18]: And you usually will say nothing, but I thought I would humor this tonight and see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: More sim file contests.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm actually, Stepmania is doing one, their official sim file contest through stepmania.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Are they encouraging people to use their own MP3s, or encouraging people to use commercial MP3s for this?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, they're...
[SPEAKER_15]: They're encouraging people to use royalty-free MP3s or MP3s that they have the permission of the artist to use.
[SPEAKER_18]: So in other words, they will be forced to come up with something original.
[SPEAKER_15]: Something original.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then, so there's a contest going on there.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I think OSC4 was just finishing up.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, and Siberia Style 3 has been released.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Stepmania theme.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all that's going on in the world.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, tell me about something going on in the hack and crack world, because we've got to fill time here while we get cage match votes, Tally.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, apparently... Last call for cage match votes, by the way.
[SPEAKER_15]: Homebrew stuff, they've gotten it to run now through version 2.5 and 2.6, using the same workaround that they've used to create that trainer for Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so they're actually using that to port Homebrew to the PSP on firmwares 2.5 and 2.6.
[SPEAKER_15]: So what that means is probably there'll be another firmware coming out for the PSP to break all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then what'll happen is they'll come out with something else to break that and the cycle keeps going on and on.
[SPEAKER_15]: And other things, there's actually been some pretty cool stuff for like the 360 being put on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_15]: One of them being more downloadable cars for Ridge Racer 6, which makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And those are free.
[SPEAKER_15]: They've also added some music from the other games.
[SPEAKER_15]: I saw some stuff, Warp Rider and stuff from I think Ridge Racer for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure that was in other ones as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: But there's a lot of music in Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's like four virtual CDs worth of music on there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: XBOX360
[SPEAKER_15]: It is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cameo's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been playing that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I am kind of digging it a bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a little easy, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what I've found.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm sure it gets a lot harder throughout the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's still pretty.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Ridge Racer is really fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like that game a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Call of Duty 2, the multiplayer, is really fun in that
[SPEAKER_15]: Just, I like the multiplayer a lot in my game.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, I don't know, just overall pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm thinking about maybe picking up another game here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not sure what I want to pick up, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Definitely going to get Dead or Alive 4 when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Been actually pretty excited.
[SPEAKER_15]: They've been showing some pictures for...
[SPEAKER_15]: Blow up everything!
[SPEAKER_15]: They sort of had a commercial like that for Mercenaries
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, Mercenaries, when it came out, um, on the PlayStation 2 and Xbox, you know, I was the commercial, blow up buildings, blow them up again, you know, blow up tanks, fire rockets, you know, it was just the whole commercial dedicated to that, and it was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a lot better than those commercials that they have at the PSP.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like a nut you can play with outside, or it's like carpet you can watch outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like carpet you can munch outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, well they have, like, they're talking about the PSP and being able to play it outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: Have you ever tried to play PSP outside?
[SPEAKER_18]: You can't see shit on the screen outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, to be fair, it goes for most systems.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can't really see the DS outside.
[SPEAKER_15]: Exactly, but why are they trying to push it that you can play it outside?
[SPEAKER_18]: Which is why I never fucking understood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only at night.
[SPEAKER_18]: What was that fucking game on Game Boy Advance that was the sun?
[SPEAKER_18]: It was Konami, and you had to do the sun.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that what it's called?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck that game.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, seriously, fuck it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's here.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was so stupid, that sun thing encouraging me to go outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't see my game when I go outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, actually, that's the way you had to play it for those old systems that didn't have backlights, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: The ones that do, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can't see them now.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Chat Room requested some more happy.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we have nothing but nauseously happy songs this break.
[SPEAKER_18]: And for some reason I don't have Jenny Rahm in here, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: I may have to fix that.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I thought of something better than Jenny Rahm, and we're going to start it off with that really, like, annoyingly happy song from In the Groove.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we're going to start off with that, and we'll be back with more Orange Andreo after this.
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
We've got a winner!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: Mr. Random Person on the Street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of the Orange Lounge mainlining music in Moore's show?
[SPEAKER_14]: The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's...
[SPEAKER_14]: on Earthly.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like being at a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
[SPEAKER_18]: Lucha Libre on Telemundo!
[SPEAKER_18]: Telemundo, Telemundo, Telemundo!
[SPEAKER_18]: I love that stuff, and they have the best talk shows.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sure, I can't understand half the shit they're saying, but I can pick up enough words so I kinda know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do love Mexican wrestling.
[SPEAKER_18]: La lucha libre!
[SPEAKER_18]: No, anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, yeah, anyway, hi.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know where that came from.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, we decided that since we did do a happy, happy bouncy break, that we will actually do a very dark, depressing break next.
[SPEAKER_18]: So that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to do our emo break next.
[SPEAKER_18]: We can kind of offset that a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, now they're having a discussion here in the chat room talking about Sirius versus XM, which are the dueling satellite radios here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, have you guys ever looked into getting satellite radio?
[SPEAKER_04]: My new stereo is XM compatible, but I haven't.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know that's funny because mine is Sirius compatible.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm in the same boat where I haven't really decided to get that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm tempted though with the Stern thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not that I'm a huge Howard Stern fan, but I think he's interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'd be interested to hear what he has to say on the new show.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I'm sure it'll be all over the internet and stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I've been tempted to get Sirius.
[SPEAKER_18]: But DarkSakura says that we should get on satellite radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I tend to agree.
[SPEAKER_18]: We should be on satellite radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you know Adam Curry has a show on, I think it's Sirius.
[SPEAKER_18]: And he does a show about podcasting.
[SPEAKER_18]: and I think he plays clips from different podcasts.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I've actually submitted our show, I don't know, months ago, I submitted that little promo we did to the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've never heard back.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, you know, the best way that you could hear us on one of these stations would be to email the fuck out of these people and say, hey, have you heard of Orange Orange Radio?
[SPEAKER_18]: You should include them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Syndicate, syndicate.
[SPEAKER_18]: And it's tough, too, because when we first started our podcast, there was...
[SPEAKER_18]: very few other gaming podcasts out there only a few people have jumped on the bandwagon early and very very few of them are still around I can only think of like I think maybe two other podcasts I can think of that have been around just as long if not longer than we are that are still going regularly a lot of them kind of tapered off but now there are literally like at least a hundred video game podcasts out there on the internet right now so it's tough for us to stand out from the rest you know it's getting pretty competitive out there
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: We won that little thing, and that was nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that was strictly because of our fans.
[SPEAKER_18]: But we just want to have fun with this.
[SPEAKER_18]: And we want to bring more people, because we're a very interactive show.
[SPEAKER_18]: We like to think that's one thing that maybe sets ourselves apart from the others, is that we're a very interactive show.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, something to think about.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shall we hear who won tonight's cage match, boys and girls?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, let's!
[SPEAKER_18]: The winner of tonight's cage match was...
[SPEAKER_18]: Tess, once again.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because everybody loves some generic trance in their life.
[SPEAKER_18]: Enjoy that, Tess.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, I like that song an awful lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can't say a lot negative.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although I was very disappointed at the voting turnout.
[SPEAKER_18]: Very few votes.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is the lowest voting turnout I've seen since Election Day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, so more voting people.
[SPEAKER_18]: Shame, shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get the word out there.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm trying to go to our chat room there, www.orangemonster.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're talking about... In the chat room there.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're talking...
[SPEAKER_18]: They're talking about, um, why are they talking about Don and Drew?
[SPEAKER_18]: That podcast, that's a very, oh, maybe they're trying to talk about podcasts that have been around.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm talking about strictly video game podcasts.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know Don and Drew have been around since, like, podcasting started.
[SPEAKER_18]: That they were the first, like, big name couple that got on the, you know, the iPod thing and started talking about their sex life or whatever it is they do.
[SPEAKER_18]: I've only listened to a little bit of the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to be honest, kids, I don't listen to a lot of podcasts.
[SPEAKER_18]: I totally support podcasting.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think podcasting is truly the wave of the future and I support it.
[SPEAKER_18]: But as somebody who's trying to put together an original podcast, I don't really listen to a lot of others.
[SPEAKER_18]: Which is a little bit of a controversial standpoint because you think I could stand to learn things by listening to other podcasts.
[SPEAKER_18]: At the same time, I want to make sure our show is purely original.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Yanni doesn't listen to anybody else so that all of his music is original.
[SPEAKER_18]: But Yanni sucks.
[SPEAKER_18]: Not really, I like some of Yanni's music If you're into, you know, screaming opera pigs No, I'm kidding Yanni's good if you like that kind of music So what are you saying, we're the Yanni of podcasting?
[SPEAKER_18]: Only cooler Alright, anyway I'm feeling a little angsty So I think it's time to get into the FUs of the week What do you kids think?
[SPEAKER_18]: You want to do some angst?
[SPEAKER_04]: Angst up, yo.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, let's do some angst here.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, of course, you know I'm always going to go over and start with you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, by the way, guys, you can submit your FUs of the week right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Go to www.orangemonstrator.com and click on chat and send a private message to Sky with your FU of the week, if you have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you know we've got to get ours out first because we are some angsty motherfuckers.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, DarkSakura, why is it we do the FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_18]: Grr, argh.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to, uh, the abundant amounts of rain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, because, uh, you know, it just makes it really hard to drive when everybody else on the road is being a big dipshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is the case, I've passed something like three accidents on the way here today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another F you goes, of course, to the plague for not releasing me from its evil grip lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Another one goes toward my utter lack of appetite from being sick because I've dropped 15 pounds in a month and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: So like none of my clothes fit me anymore and I can't really afford to go buy new ones right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to the rock that flew off of the road and landed in my windshield and then cracked two days later so that now I have a big split across the lower half of my windshield from one end to the other and have to pay to have my windshield replaced.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh, that really, uh, sort of hacks me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, an FU goes to the general stupidity on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's the expected.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, one more.
[SPEAKER_04]: All those people who misuse the apostrophe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck y'all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, what FUs do you have for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'd like to second the stupid driver FU.
[SPEAKER_18]: I keep seeing, you know, this torrential rain coming down and people driving with their headlights off still or in the fog and they're driving extremely fast in the fog without their headlights on and then they wonder why they get in the car accidents.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stupid people out there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, also, um, I want to say if, fuck you to, um, the whole launch lineup for the 360, because there's not that much that's out there that I want to get, and I'm kind of dying to get another game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, and then, finally, um, fuck Best Buy for just overall sucking, and, you know, unfortunately I do have a $100, um, gift card to Best Buy, so I actually go there, but...
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't want no shortage
[SPEAKER_18]: I would say my FU, I'm going to third the FU because it seems like, to driving, because when it seems like it starts raining in this state, people forget how to drive.
[SPEAKER_18]: So FU to that.
[SPEAKER_18]: FU to the fact that I've got like a million and one things I need to do this next week and not enough time to do it.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to just angst in general and not feeling happy with certain things and where you're at and just, God, having all this bullshit happen to me around Christmas, what is it about the fucking holidays and what is it about winter time that just makes the shit hit the fan?
[SPEAKER_18]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_18]: So 2005 can go on and get the fuck out of here because we need a new year.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need a clean slate and I need time to get all my errands done so I don't have to work all freaking day.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's getting old.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's go to the chatroom FU, shall we?
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see what our chatroom angst is tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ron Chan would like to say FU to my job for keeping me late tonight for work and an FU to me for not taking my TV to the shop sooner since now I have no TV here.
[SPEAKER_18]: NintendoManiac64 says, F you to more Mario Kart DS Disconnectors.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to a deer hitting our van and taking out half of its grill and killing the left light.
[SPEAKER_18]: F you to Sony, die already like your products do.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkTetsuya says, F you to Ultramix 3 again.
[SPEAKER_18]: First Rainbow Flyer, now Gamma and the couple?
[SPEAKER_18]: When will PlayStation 2 fans finally get to love?
[SPEAKER_18]: Sakurina says, F you to requesting Sabrina from Pops.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know if I have it, dude.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe somewhere.
[SPEAKER_18]: And F you to being nervous and not approaching girls.
[SPEAKER_18]: Final F you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck you, almighty snow god.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get snow while Oregon does.
[SPEAKER_18]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_18]: You make me want to listen to Rizlem remix, you pitiful being.
[SPEAKER_18]: ProPanda21 says, F you to crappy heavy metal, crap, and to panda burritos, not polluting the world with their goodness.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: And F you to my rainbow queen of the cosmos strap-on for being broken.
[SPEAKER_18]: Xander C says, F you to, uh, well, nothing, I'm happy tonight, very happy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I know, F you to unhappy people.
[SPEAKER_18]: Roz says, F you to my brother for sitting on my right arm.
[SPEAKER_18]: It hurts to move and I suck at using my left arm and hand.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkKnight says, my FU goes to my car for crushing my cell phone screen, now I know what to get myself for Christmas Saturday, and an FU to my job for opening at 7am this morning, know damn well that no one shops that fucking early on a Sunday, I may have to to get my Christmas shopping done, I don't know, AZM Buddy Paul says, FU to final exams, and FU to my dependence on sleep,
[SPEAKER_18]: and some FUs coming from Sharks Girl.
[SPEAKER_18]: FU to miles 12 to 22 of the marathon because hot damn, not only was it hard, but they friggin' ran out of ice in Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_18]: 80 degrees and 10 miles is bad with no ice, but damn it, I did it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that was our last FU tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: And congratulations to Sharks Girl, by the way, for running that marathon there.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's a long way to... I mean, God, I've done the 6 mile marathon and I thought that was bad, but 22, that's... Oh, shit, that's a lot.
[SPEAKER_18]: NintendoManiac64 also wants to add F you to Rainbow, I'm thinking Rainbow Road, in Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_18]: Seriously, the first 10 seconds decide the entire race.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's it, no more F yous, none.
[SPEAKER_18]: You're done, you're cut off.
[SPEAKER_18]: All of you.
[SPEAKER_18]: I want nothing but happiness from here on out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Except for the break, which will be emo, which I'm very excited about.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we're getting down to the wire here.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's almost the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, the next time we do a live show is going to be 2006, I think, because we're not going to be here next week live.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think we're going to have a tape thingy-ma-bobber going on.
[SPEAKER_18]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura's F'd Up Christmas?
[SPEAKER_18]: Or what were we going to do next week?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_18]: We were going to pre-tape some fucking stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we need to do... I think we should do the most fucked up Christmas songs we can find.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like Christmas Speed.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, fuck Christmas Speed, seriously, I fucking hate that CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, we should play it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, so we'll do the Orange Lingerie O'Merry fucking Christmas special.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I've got to look forward to it.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then that, what, New Year's?
[SPEAKER_18]: And we're going to be here on New Year's Day, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll be back on New Year's Day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because nobody does anything on, like, New Year's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless I'm, like, still drunk.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, let's see, here's the thing, is that New Year's Day, guess what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki has that Monday off work.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have that Monday off work.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what this means.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to kick off 2006.
[SPEAKER_18]: And would that be 169 or that would be 168?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know what we could do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know that I should be making this suggestion on the air.
[SPEAKER_18]: Try me.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm sure you both are invited to Julie's thing at her condo.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I was thinking I can bring my laptop.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might be able to record a little something-something when the new year comes up.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'm making apple pie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now I want to try some of that apple pie.
[SPEAKER_18]: That sounds good.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, I heard if you drink a whole thing of cop syrup that you'll hallucinate.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll do something fun for the New Year's Day show.
[SPEAKER_18]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: More drinking.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, DDR Freak is not doing their top DDR songs of the year or whatever, so maybe we'll have to pick up the slack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to talk to Iggy.
[SPEAKER_18]: and see if we can steal that from DDR Freak since they're apparently not doing one this year because they would have done it by now, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because that thing, that poll ran like what, all of December?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to have to talk.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's still doing the radio station.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's public news now.
[SPEAKER_18]: They posted that.
[SPEAKER_18]: We know she's not the forum's goddess anymore but she's still doing their radio, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll talk to Iggy.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll invite Iggy over to get drunk with us.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_18]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: That would be a good time.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll all get drunk.
[SPEAKER_18]: Be good times.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Episode 200 of Orange Launch Radio shows up next year.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's going to be crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, we've been doing this for a while.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, you know what's interesting is, you know what else this kind of marks three years?
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, it'll be one more week, but in this next week.
[SPEAKER_18]: What, Christmas Eve is this next week, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: This marks three years, three years since DDR Extreme came out in arcades.
[SPEAKER_18]: That mix is officially three years old now, and basically three years since DDR essentially died in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_18]: I know it's sad.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, they've had a good life at home.
[SPEAKER_18]: But In the Groove is out, and whether you love it or hate it, it's trying to pick up the slack that DDR kind of left behind in the arcades.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then the home mix is a whole other story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tommy needs to step it up.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, maybe this will be the year, but of course we said that last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and what happened?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nah, nada.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although they did have some good home mixes this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I have to say they've been giving us love with the home mixes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Extreme 2 was good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ultramix 3 was a little... could have been better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of us were more arcade players than we were home players.
[SPEAKER_18]: The problem with...
[SPEAKER_18]: What's going on is that, you know, and this is, to Endegroove's credit, whether you love it or hate it, what it's trying to do is it's trying to keep that arcade scene going.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that is how, I mean, let's face it, that is how we all met, the three of us here that do this show.
[SPEAKER_18]: We met around a DDR machine, because it used to be the kind of thing that would attract people to come together and play and have a good time together, and we'd all meet at the arcade at a certain night.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'd have a, what do we call it, Bombani night or DDR night, I don't remember what we called it.
[SPEAKER_18]: We used to do Wednesdays over at Roosevelt Golf Land,
[SPEAKER_18]: and, you know, doing the arcade thing.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's kind of how we all met, but now that's kind of gone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Although some arcades have enough of an In the Groove community where that has kind of picked up the slack.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I don't know, I never really got into In the Groove, but maybe that's because, maybe that's not necessarily In the Groove's fault.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is something I was thinking about.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe it's not necessarily In the Groove's fault.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, let's start it off with, I think this song is pretty fucking depressing, so we're going to start off with a little bit of Silhouette of My Mind.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is definitely an emo song.
[SPEAKER_18]: So we'll be back with more, so since we did a happy break, we're going to do the depressing as fuck break, and then we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_18]: So enjoy this, and we'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio
I need to leave, I need to make love
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
I'm ready now, will I fall down if it all becomes too late?
If I die, I'll die before I die
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move marathon.
[SPEAKER_09]: No!
[SPEAKER_18]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_18]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Crap-free Vivani Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Welcome back, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_18]: I hope you enjoyed that break of sadness and tragicness.
[SPEAKER_18]: Deutz de Fatima.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ghosts, I am gothic and silhouette of my mind.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was a pretty emotional break.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think I had a movement in my bowels during that break.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to do a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge, but first, actually, we're going to go to our Skype line and open it up one more time there.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Interact With Us if you wish to call the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: And oh, look, we're already getting a call.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hello, Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_18]: How are you, my friend?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you guys?
[SPEAKER_18]: Good.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a couple of things I want to talk about real quick.
[SPEAKER_18]: First, I played Flow to Urban Dance Groove.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you get yourself a little closer to your mic, buddy?
[SPEAKER_18]: We're having a hard time hearing you.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you got to play Flow?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, to Urban Dance Groove.
[SPEAKER_18]: Much better.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, how was that?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's Def Jam meets Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is this a good thing or a bad thing?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: At first I felt kind of offended it was so bad, but yet it was just so funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: What kind of songs are in this game?
[SPEAKER_18]: There's a lot of old school stuff like this, and there's a lot of new school stuff I've never even heard of.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: How is the interface?
[SPEAKER_18]: How's the design of the game?
[SPEAKER_18]: Does it flow?
[SPEAKER_18]: Pretty much it does.
[SPEAKER_18]: The dance steps are a little bit too easy, though.
[SPEAKER_18]: Really?
[SPEAKER_18]: No really hard mode or anything?
[SPEAKER_18]: I think the levels are like DDR Mario Mix.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ooh, that's no good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, okay, but I guess if you're new to dance games, which maybe they're thinking the target audience for Flow is or is not the same group that plays DDR or whatever, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe that's just a warm-up.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't even know what Ubiisoft is thinking because I remember one day I'm coming home and I see flyers for 187 Ride or Die and that game was really horrible.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, a lot of black people play video games.
[SPEAKER_18]: At least when I watched the video game awards on Spike TV, I would have thought only black people play video games for the parts I watched.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: It was just me.
[SPEAKER_18]: I tell you this, when I play DDR, I know I don't feel alone when I play.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Ray, stuff aside.
[SPEAKER_18]: How does flow stack up?
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, is it a worthy purchase for the music game fan, or is it a piece of crap?
[SPEAKER_18]: Wait till it drops to 19.
[SPEAKER_18]: Wait till it drops to 19?
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that with... Oh, no, because it's for PlayStation, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, so that you can get the pads separately.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Wait for it to drop to 19.
[SPEAKER_18]: Dark Knight has a question.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you crunk in the game?
[SPEAKER_18]: Only when you buy a 40-ounce to go with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, anything else going on in the world around him?
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, a couple of things.
[SPEAKER_18]: To answer Loki's question, I've actually seen people drink a full bottle of cork syrup and get crazy at the raves.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you hear that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: He's seen people drink the bottle of cough syrup and get crazy at the raves.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: In response to... Listen to Red with Tess and MC Chris.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, um... This one is for you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_18]: I was... I was coming home off of work tonight and this kid was asking his mom about getting GTA.
[SPEAKER_18]: And she's like, no, you can't get it because it's...
[SPEAKER_18]: You're too young for it.
[SPEAKER_18]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_18]: So he starts getting all mad and she's like, I'm gonna ask my father to get it.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's like, well, you do that, you're still not gonna get it, so I'm gonna tell him not to.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then he goes, you know what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Fuck you, I'm gonna get it anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: The next part was priceless.
[SPEAKER_18]: She grabbed him by his baggy pants like, you wanna say fuck you?
[SPEAKER_18]: You wanna say fuck... She proceeded to beat his ass.
[SPEAKER_18]: That is beautiful.
[SPEAKER_18]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_18]: Big Mama, that's all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_18]: She has donated a Crucian carp to Blathers, and Blathers says, When I hear Crucian carp, I think to myself, taco.
[SPEAKER_18]: Indeed, fish taco.
[SPEAKER_18]: What, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That just cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Taco!
[SPEAKER_18]: You can see where this show is gone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Half our show is being done in Animal Crossing tonight, actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now you got me thinking of YTMND.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, we should take a picture of that or something and get it on YTMND.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate those things.
[SPEAKER_18]: What is some good stuff on YTMND this week?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because I don't follow YTMND, but I know you do.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's some good stuff on GearTheManNow, dawg?
[SPEAKER_18]: The Foreign DuckTales Translations.
[SPEAKER_18]: Foreign DuckTales Translations.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, there's one where it sounds like they're saying Taco Nazi.
[SPEAKER_18]: Only on the internet, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_18]: Only on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did see something fun on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: That Garrett posted.
[SPEAKER_18]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't end up watching it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The how to eat sushi like a snooty bitch.
[SPEAKER_18]: Does it have talking in it?
[SPEAKER_18]: Can we play it on the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's all in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: It might be funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it's linked on my live journal.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, well, anything else you want to say to our listeners, Ron Chen?
[SPEAKER_18]: One more thing about what's going on on the internet.
[SPEAKER_18]: I found something called Genghis Khan.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a German pop band.
[SPEAKER_18]: They're doing this song and dance.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's just so funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to post a couple of links to it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, check it out.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not Genghis Khan!
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not that?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a German pop group called Genghis Khan.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's a German word for Genghis.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, link us in the chat room, all right?
[SPEAKER_18]: That I will.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_18]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Have a good one, my friend.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you for calling in.
[SPEAKER_18]: You too.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_18]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: Our good buddy, Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to get into Ask Orange Lounge in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: But first, I'm going to log into LiveJournal so I can get that link here that DarkSakura posted there in her blog.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, what... I've got to bring it up here, though, so that I can get the audio out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, tell us again what this thing is all about here that we're going to watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: The proper way to eat sushi, even directions as to how you enter the place, to how you pour your beer for people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really, a lot of that is just polite custom, but it's really overblowing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It totally makes fun of a lot of things that people do at sushi restaurants.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now, it's not super long, is it?
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll let it kind of start here, and if it's too long, then we'll just kind of... Might have to translate.
[SPEAKER_18]: The snack most commonly associated with Japan.
[SPEAKER_18]: A shop that sells sushi is called a sushi-ya.
[SPEAKER_18]: Most Japanese eat at one every day.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is the entrance to a Sushiya.
[SPEAKER_18]: To pass through the short curtain called Noren,
[SPEAKER_18]: From the lower left corner of the third partition, find the spot 3.2 inches up at an angle of 48 degrees.
[SPEAKER_18]: Place your hand like this and peel open.
[SPEAKER_18]: If you arrive less than 30 minutes before closing, ask, are you still open?
[SPEAKER_13]: On entering the premises, inside,
[SPEAKER_18]: 2 people.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is the number in your group.
[SPEAKER_18]: In a group of 3, say.
[SPEAKER_18]: 3 people.
[SPEAKER_18]: In a group of 4, say.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay, this is getting boring.
[SPEAKER_18]: When does this get good?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just the whole thing is silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should always show a little guilt in your eyes if you're alone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Why would you be guilty if you're alone?
[SPEAKER_18]: What if you're on business or something?
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, we actually, we used to have a place here locally called Sushiya, so I think that's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I'm sad that Sushiya is closed.
[SPEAKER_04]: These two men look like they're going to get it on.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_18]: They were hella flirting.
[SPEAKER_18]: Did you see that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is this seat taken?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll post it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, post the link in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: Where did those faces come from?
[SPEAKER_18]: Blanca in Animal Crossing there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is OLR Town still open?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did a zombie face on her.
[SPEAKER_15]: OLR Town is currently closed at the moment, but I can open it back up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Open it back up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's go to some Ask Orange Lounge, boys and girls, because we promised it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_18]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_18]: Will we find out the best of 2005 or is the best yet to come in the next two weeks?
[SPEAKER_18]: Nintendo Maniac 64 says, Hey Loki, what do you think about gay sex?
[SPEAKER_18]: Now that's one of the best jokes of 2005 right there.
[SPEAKER_18]: One of the best Orange Lounge Radio jokes of 2005.
[SPEAKER_18]: You don't have a response to that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: Um, gay sex, that's sex and gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, Loki, what do you think about gay sex?
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, it's so much fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sky, what do you think about Big Dick?
[SPEAKER_18]: What the fuck kind of question is that?
[SPEAKER_18]: It's size is relative, people.
[SPEAKER_18]: Doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not the size, it's how you use it.
[SPEAKER_18]: When you hear my name, well, username, Nintendomaniac64, what about me do you think of?
[SPEAKER_18]: The fact that you like Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, I... The toilet.
[SPEAKER_18]: The toilet.
[SPEAKER_18]: I think about all that fucking snaking that you do in Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_18]: What language is the best other than English?
[SPEAKER_18]: I like this question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Swahili.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: What's the best language?
[SPEAKER_18]: Other than English?
[SPEAKER_15]: Finnish.
[SPEAKER_15]: Other than English?
[SPEAKER_18]: Swedish.
[SPEAKER_18]: I would say Pig Latin.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it would be.
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, VXJasonXV, our faithful webmaster, says, Dear Orange Launch Radio, would you like a new website?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_18]: OMG, yes, please.
[SPEAKER_18]: As long as we can update the news easy on the new one, yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: I actually, I want to talk to you offline about that, Jason, because of something later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am going to say something on record.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am taking Flash next semester.
[SPEAKER_18]: Scare.
[SPEAKER_18]: She's going to make her own YTMNDs.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to make something special.
[SPEAKER_18]: Rene would like to know, is Akira Yamaoka gay?
[SPEAKER_18]: I hope not, because he's going to be my next husband.
[SPEAKER_18]: I saw this on some web form.
[SPEAKER_18]: They were seriously debating if he was gay or not.
[SPEAKER_18]: I could swear that there's some interview out there, and Rice Princess pointed this out to me, where he said that the first song he wrote, or one of the songs he wrote on piano, was about some girl.
[SPEAKER_18]: So I don't think he's gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: And when I, you know, I am gay, so I have gaydar.
[SPEAKER_18]: When I met him, because I actually met him at E3 a couple years ago, he didn't strike me as gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, does it really matter, though?
[SPEAKER_18]: He struck me as hot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Does it really matter if he's gay?
[SPEAKER_18]: Although the shirt he wore was kind of gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, that was gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't really care if he's gay or not.
[SPEAKER_18]: He can make good music.
[SPEAKER_18]: But I know that's a big controversial thing on the internet right now.
[SPEAKER_18]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_18]: What is the... Oh, maybe that's why we got rid of this microphone.
[SPEAKER_18]: This is the buzzing microphone.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_18]: And what is the ultimate Bomani song when listened to in moderation?
[SPEAKER_18]: Ooh, the ultimate Bomani song.
[SPEAKER_18]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_18]: The ultimate Bomani song.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: My butt, the ass mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, I still like, um, what was it, um, moving on.
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a real fond place for drifting away, but I also love, love, love, and this doesn't even have to be in moderation, I could just listen to this on repeat all day long, Skulk, from Ultimix 2, I just, I absolutely love that song.
[SPEAKER_19]: Love it!
[SPEAKER_18]: Sakurina wants to know how does one know if he or she has an STD?
[SPEAKER_18]: More precisely, how do you get it checked?
[SPEAKER_18]: How does one know if he or she has an STD?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, there are signs.
[SPEAKER_18]: There's lots and lots of different types of STDs, so the best way to find out really is to get tested.
[SPEAKER_18]: Get tested for STDs, and that's how you're going to know, because the doctor can shove something in your pee hole and find out that way.
[SPEAKER_18]: Or, you know, there's tests you can do, blood tests and things.
[SPEAKER_18]: It just depends what STD you're looking for.
[SPEAKER_18]: I mean, crabs, well, if your pubes itch a lot and there's little things bouncing, no, not really, you can't always see it, you probably have crabs.
[SPEAKER_18]: If something's wrong, go to the doctor.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're itchy, use a cream.
[SPEAKER_18]: You can look up symptoms on a site like WebMD, or I can tell you from my background, I work for an insurance company, a lot of insurance companies have, well, wait, you're Canadian though, so I don't know what to tell you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Never mind, I forgot he's Canadian, so it's an entirely different ballgame.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know if they have advice nurses, something like that in Canada, but if they have something like that, check it out.
[SPEAKER_18]: They can call on the phone, because they have that here.
[SPEAKER_18]: Insurance companies have that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anything else you want to add, Loki?
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to add that I drew a penis on Blanka's face, and this will be going to some random user's DS out there, and I'm glad that a little kid's going to see a penis on Blanka's face, and it's going to have my credit to it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_18]: Xander C wants to know, why aren't more people happy?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm happy, so should everyone else be happy.
[SPEAKER_18]: But if they think about geometry, they should want to kill people, like me, because I am the cool, right?
[SPEAKER_18]: Dude, what drugs are you on, seriously?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: What kind of things make you happy?
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm changing this question a little bit.
[SPEAKER_18]: What makes you happy?
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, what makes you happy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, pleasure makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_18]: Pleasure makes you happy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Any pleasure makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, what makes you happy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, a day off of work.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm surprised you didn't say fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I like fire, but I can get that anytime I want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's like sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, but I can't always get a day off of work when I want it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, a day off of work, just to do whatever I want to.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know what makes me happy?
[SPEAKER_18]: Abba.
[SPEAKER_18]: Abba makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Abba makes everybody happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You cannot help but be happy listening to Abba.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bear.
[SPEAKER_18]: By the gorillas?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: or Truth or Dare.
[SPEAKER_18]: Truth or Dare can make me happy when things go my way.
[SPEAKER_18]: I play Truth or Dare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now with my new stereo, that song sounds completely fabulous in my car and I get really hyper and drive fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: My car makes me happy too.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, NeoDudeZero.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hey, did you hear about all the new games in development for the DS?
[SPEAKER_18]: One will raise your IQ as you play it and the other teaches little girls how to orgasm.
[SPEAKER_09]: That one's not coming out as conceptual.
[SPEAKER_18]: What's this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_18]: Mike?
[SPEAKER_18]: So the game is not coming out, it's just a conceptual game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Where's this all from?
[SPEAKER_18]: Is this like a website or something?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's this little game you play with like a rabbit, and it supposedly teaches you the way to rub out orgasms, you make the rabbit happy.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it's like Masturbation Technique 101 or something, the game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Illusion asks a question that simply says, vagina.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm sorry, not vagina.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not a statement.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's vagina?
[SPEAKER_09]: Chup, chup, chup, chup, chup.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tasty.
[SPEAKER_18]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know what you want me to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for bringing us to Crashing a Hulk!
[SPEAKER_18]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_18]: You broke our show.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, uh, since you broke our show, here's some, uh, more ABBA to make us happy again.
[SPEAKER_18]: This show has just gotten weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: More ABBA.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we need more cowbells.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play Don't Fear the Reaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can dance, you can jive Having the time of your life Okay, this show's gotten too gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_18]: Too gay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Nintendo Maniac64 says, Can I erase someone in Mario Kart DS?
[SPEAKER_18]: I won't even snake, but I will powerslide insanely on turns, so fear.
[SPEAKER_18]: Um...
[SPEAKER_18]: I have a copy of Mario Kart DS in the other room, but I'm too busy playing Final Fantasy Advance 4.
[SPEAKER_18]: If I'm going to turn that fucking thing on, I'm beating Final Fantasy Advance 4, because I haven't beaten a video game in forever.
[SPEAKER_18]: I love Final Fantasy 4, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's so great.
[SPEAKER_18]: So great.
[SPEAKER_18]: But ask our chat room.
[SPEAKER_18]: I actually did one specifically just for friend codes in all of the available games.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because we had one for Mario Kart DS, but since more and more games are going to come out that have friend code adding ability, I thought I'd just put it up there.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good deal.
[SPEAKER_18]: But be sure in that thread you say who you're adding because in a lot of these games you have to have both people on the list.
[SPEAKER_18]: So make sure you say who you're adding.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, there's those other websites too.
[SPEAKER_18]: DSMeet, and I want to say one of our listeners, BigRedPimp, had another one that's a popular DSMeeting site.
[SPEAKER_18]: But you know, stick to the Orange Lounge cult.
[SPEAKER_18]: Stick to our forums.
[SPEAKER_18]: Illusion had another question and the question was Waterloo?
[SPEAKER_18]: I could do this all night, you guys.
[SPEAKER_18]: I could do it all night long.
[SPEAKER_18]: AZM Buddy Paul wants to know, Skye, are you the dancing queen?
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, I'm a terrible dancer, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, this is great, because Rob Hat does the choo-choo dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only way I can describe it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, I think it was Eddie or somebody used to label me as, I would roll down the window when I dance.
[SPEAKER_18]: When I play DDR, I'm always rolling down the window.
[SPEAKER_18]: The choo-choo dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had never really seen you do the choo-choo dance until we went to Asylum.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, keep in mind, this is the goth night at one of our local clubs.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they played Girls and Boys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to go back in there because it was blur.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Rob gets out there and does the choo-choo dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sitting there just watching Rob, and I'm drunk off my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Singing along while Rob's doing the choo-choo dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's not so much the choo-choo dance as it is the white people dance.
[SPEAKER_18]: You know, somebody needs to teach me how to dance.
[SPEAKER_18]: See, I need to befriend... Is this a movie somewhere, maybe?
[SPEAKER_18]: I need to befriend a black person with rhythm to teach me how to dance.
[SPEAKER_18]: And, like, I enter a competition and win a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_18]: Is that White Man Can't Jump?
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_18]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I remember about that movie is what's her name who decided that she was going to be on Jeopardy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the only thing about that movie I remember.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't remember any of that.
[SPEAKER_18]: I actually never saw that movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Something I should probably share there.
[SPEAKER_18]: I never even saw that movie.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some folks in the chat room are getting a little angsty because we're playing so much ABBA, and they want to hear some disco prints from We Heart Katamari, I don't know, maybe like as alternate disco, so... That's all you get.
[SPEAKER_18]: That reminds me, me and Mike Katamari comes out to the BSP this week for the Japanese, which means I'll have it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Really, this week?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_17]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_18]: No more ABBA requests.
[SPEAKER_18]: Stop ABBA... God damn, now I have all these requests for ABBA.
[SPEAKER_04]: The secret of me and my Katamari is that all the music is going to be done by me and my... Doop-be-doop-be-doop-be-doop-doop-doop.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't do... Yeah, they did, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a really cool song that they did, though, that wasn't in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll put it in the cage match one day.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I haven't already.
[SPEAKER_18]: Wasn't that... Were they the ones that did Lion Eddie?
[SPEAKER_18]: No, no, that's Smile Decay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they did Takeru...
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh yeah, I like that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you so much for tuning in and listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm glad we didn't get the plug pulled on us.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's always good news to not get the plug pulled on us.
[SPEAKER_18]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_18]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_18]: My final thought is I just found the money rock.
[SPEAKER_18]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_18]: My final thought is time.
[SPEAKER_18]: Need more.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reject false icons and someone give me a cure for the plague.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, that's going to do it for tonight's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: The final word of the show, one word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Next week, oh, next week we will not be live, but we will be doing something taped, so if you're around, tune in anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: And of course, stay tuned to the podcast.
[SPEAKER_18]: We will have a new podcast one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have to figure out how we're going to tape that, but we'll do that one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_18]: And that's that.
[SPEAKER_18]: Then we'll see you back here on New Year's Day for the first Orange Lounge Radio of 2006, live.
[SPEAKER_18]: And maybe some drinking going on.
[SPEAKER_18]: We'll see what happens, if you're good.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have a fun month ahead of us.
[SPEAKER_18]: We sure do.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, the final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_18]: One word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, what's it going to be?
[SPEAKER_05]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_05]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silent Night, Holy Night All is calm, all is bright from your presence
[SPEAKER_09]: Mara Lanshan, Holy Impasson, Tantalum White, Sleepin' Heavenly,
[SPEAKER_09]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
Thank you very much.
All young brothers in motherland shine Holy infant so tender and mild Sleep in heavenly peace
Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: and this is the part where