[SPEAKER_08]: Ascension!
[SPEAKER_08]: Attention.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_18]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: You are tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio and we are all set for episode number 166 tonight, December 4th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to talk a little bit about what's going on at that game festival that none of us were cool enough to actually go to.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I hear there's a lot of cell phone action going on, so we're going to talk a little bit about that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Of course, how was your week, how was your day, cage match and all that fun stuff you chatters know and love.
[SPEAKER_15]: So come on board, we'll start right after this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are live and this is episode number 166 for this December the 4th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're tuned into Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want and this is Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_15]: Your home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_15]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_15]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_15]: In that corner, the happiest bunny on the farm is DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like burritos.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Was it a steak burrito?
[SPEAKER_15]: It was a vegetarian burrito.
[SPEAKER_15]: A veggie burrito.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like beans.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Beans make me poop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a voice.
[SPEAKER_15]: La la la la la la la.
[SPEAKER_15]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_15]: No hacking tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I have codeine in my body.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_15]: Drugs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love my opiates.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also joining us, say hello to the other drug fiend, Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate burritos.
[SPEAKER_15]: You hate burritos?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do they make you poop too?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I just hate all Mexican food.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except for chips and salsa, but that's kind of borderline.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you ever had the chips and salsa at Chipotle?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because they have lime chips.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, their chips have just a hint of lime.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been to Sharky's.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have really good chips and salsa.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then just homemade chips and salsa.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have good carnitas at Felipe's by my house.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is that a mom-pa type place, Felipe's?
[SPEAKER_05]: Subtitles by the Amara.org community
[SPEAKER_05]: We should go eat there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know we should.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I love Grandma.
[SPEAKER_15]: She's so sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go have a staff meeting there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, how do you say Grandma in Spanish?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure someone in chat will tell me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Abuelita?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, that sounds kind of... Right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Say hello also as well to birthday girl DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, now they all know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi guys!
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy birthday!
[SPEAKER_04]: One year younger than you, sir.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, so you are 34.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, yeah, whatever.
Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, they don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's always the joke about me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody says, you're 30.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm like, I'm not 30.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm good at being 30.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, everyone's going to scream happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, guys, I'm using the microphone tonight that sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want everybody to know.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, if I cut in and out, deal with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you cut out, we'll cheer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then we're going to come back and have ourselves a show because we want to talk about DDR stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there's new videos for 2DX to talk about.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's also new Guitar Freaks V2 and Drum Mania music.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then there's dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_15]: As usual.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it wouldn't be a show if we couldn't have some dick and fart jokes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And musical burping.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back after this, and this breaks in Bomani Potpourri.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to start it off with something I do every time I eat a lot of beans.
[SPEAKER_15]: Drop the bomb here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, drop the bomb.
Outro Music
Thank you for watching!
I lost my way in the dark I've been waiting for you, but you know better You're not the same as I am
[SPEAKER_08]: You show me life like that in the hour Made me by your way, I love
One, two, three, four!
Yeah!
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: We put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio and happy December to you all.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is our first show for December.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Decemberween!
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you been naughty or nice this year?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will Santa be bringing you lots of joy and wonderful gifts this year?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will he be bringing you charcoal?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I found charcoal, little plastic charcoals filled with candy at Target.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, that's cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a cute idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to put some in Dan's stocking.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I thought he brought just real coal, which coal is actually worth quite a bit from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_15]: My skill in mining has gone up by one point.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel, what did you get for your birthday?
[SPEAKER_15]: I was having sex with your cake during the break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, her cake, she has this cake thing and it has a big hole in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I didn't really, guys, I didn't really have sex with a cake, but I pretended like I was going to have sex with a cake.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that was my way of frosting it.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Naughty, naughty, naughty.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so going to get coal in my stocking.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what I'm going to get in my stocking this year?
[SPEAKER_15]: A pig's head.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what I'm going to get in my stocking this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to give you a do-it-yourself taxidermy kit.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I get a pig's head, I would so deep fry it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, I'm sorry, Angel, the birthday girl.
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your birthday?
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you get any presents?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just this necklace thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cute, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a fused necklace from... Well, you can buy them at ThinkGeek.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like this piece of glass that they've, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: I got one of those, and I got a little model of an Air Force One.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, another playing dad in my collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: That nobody knew about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway!
[SPEAKER_04]: LED guys, get it?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're gonna do that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so, um, nothing much other than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a party in there last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got lots of digital toys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, I was a bad friend because I didn't have a chance to go out today.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually went to, but the sad thing is I was at the mall for like five minutes, but most of that time was spent trying to find a parking space because my friend really wanted to go and run in and get something, and it totally escaped my mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, I was going to get Angel something.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'll have a present for you later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'll just make your birthday last longer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can put it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna whack you with a bug net.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I could do that in real life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, you don't live that far from me, do you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, here's a rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to chop down your tree.
[SPEAKER_04]: Throwing rock across this highway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anywho, well, happy birthday from us at OLR to you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we need to sing to Angel, everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: We need to sing happy birthday to Angel, Orange Lounge Radio style, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ready, everybody?
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, give the mic to Loki so he can help out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: One, two, three.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy birthday to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy birthday, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy birthday, fuck Angel.
[SPEAKER_15]: In a good way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy birthday, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I got a platinum record for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody shoot the singer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should totally be a loud singer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Happy birthday, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_09]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your day, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: I spent most of the week having the plague, but I decided that it might be the T-virus.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, isn't that what AIDS is?
[SPEAKER_15]: No!
[SPEAKER_15]: Those are T-cells.
[SPEAKER_09]: I pity the foo who don't understand the difference.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, the T-virus was the zombie virus in Resident Evil in the first game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I figured that if you ever start seeing Itchy Tasty show up on my live journal, like the entry before that would be Ugly Face So Shot Him, and then the next one Itchy Tasty, then you'd know that I turned into a zombie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then of course I'd be in here eating everybody's brains.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you sniffing my spicy brains?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I wasn't sniffing your spicy brains.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, but I did have fun yesterday because I felt kind of better and I had already made plans.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, I went over to, uh, our friend Tia's house to, uh, make dinner, which I made chicken and green beans, which I will post pictures of in the chat room because she took pictures of the food I cooked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then me and her and her roommate went to the thrift store.
[SPEAKER_05]: But on the way there, we were sort of like in the ghetto part of town that we, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: Saw Popeye's fried chicken and ate fried chicken in my car while listening to The Cure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fried chicken and biscuits with The Cure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Friday, I'm in love with a chicken wing.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's like listening to pictures of you.
[SPEAKER_05]: with eating, chowing down on fried chicken.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's that commercial that uses pictures of you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do I watch TV?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm asking hypothetically.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the Kodak, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that's two colors.
[SPEAKER_15]: They show that before the movies, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that was like in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the last time you probably watched TV.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Kodak thing, they show this in the movies, too, you know, and they have the pictures of you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: It might be a digital camera.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't ever see the cursor laying out like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's another picture of me and her with cowboy hats, which I will post in the chat room in a moment.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that's going to be your new picture on whatever Orange Lounge Radio album art we switch to.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to have the one in the plaid beanie, which I have to go back and buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, the Plaidbury thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because we're all going to have new pictures, and there's a... Did I even tell you guys about the new intro for the podcast that's coming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Rob, for keeping us in the loop and making executive decisions.
[SPEAKER_15]: I totally forgot about... You said that we could have potentially one, but that person is doing it, for sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we have to screen it when it's done to make sure we like it, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, you knew.
[SPEAKER_15]: Liar!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, Jamie's trying to fuck with me.
[SPEAKER_15]: She is a zombie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Off with her head!
[SPEAKER_15]: Kill her!
[SPEAKER_05]: Butt!
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I do have a butt.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very big.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_15]: It's time like these, you guys are glad we don't have the OLR webcam, because I just showed my butt to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't show the skin, but I showed my jeans.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm wearing tight jeans today, because my butt did get bigger, therefore my jeans are tighter.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those are
[SPEAKER_05]: I had the coolest jeans though in the 80s because you remember during the Samantha Fox days how it was really cool to have all ripped up jeans Naughty girls need love too Well I, my mom would not let me cut my jeans, I was so pissed off so I went roller skating and I ran into the wall And back then at the roller rink the wall was made out of carpet And that carpet burned the knees out of my jeans
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: um but back to uh my life yes i remember being young in the 80s maybe just maybe naughty girls need love too it's one of my favorite songs ever i do not like big butts i'm trying to get rid of mine
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, well I'll talk about it during my, I made a I Like Big Butts reference this weekend, but anyway, I'm sorry, I'll get to it later.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also found out during the whole time that I've had my degenerative disease that I dropped something like 16 pounds during the month of November.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I couldn't eat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is funny because I bet that makes you the biggest loser and you weren't even playing the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also found out that I really like eggnog flavored things, like eggnog ice cream, because I had some last night.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, the eggnog stuff that they do at like Starbucks and stuff, the eggnog lattes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do this at my work.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, and, and, and, and, the eggnog ice cream at Baskin Robbins.
[SPEAKER_05]: This stuff is the best thing ever, because I love ice cream.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excuse me, that was my latte saying hi.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything else you want to share about your week and your day in the 80s?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did really shitty homework all day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then after the show, I'm going to go home and do more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just thought I'd let you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: What kind of homework?
[SPEAKER_05]: Illustrator this morning, Dreamweaver when I get home.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm going to be doing my geography homework during lunch tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Geography.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so glad that class is good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have jury duty on the 19th.
[SPEAKER_15]: Billy, if you're taking geography, maybe you can answer a question for me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is Canada a state or not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Canada is a country.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because a lot of people just say it's another state.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it has territories.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoever thinks Canada is a state is a dipshit.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just wanted to piss off Socorina and whatever Canadian listeners we have, so... No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't you just hear what I just said?
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoever says that Canada is a state...
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoever legitimately thinks that.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know there's people out there that think that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, they're dipshits.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Canada's just one big state.
[SPEAKER_05]: They need to be drug out into the street, and then someone needs to... And then the Queen of England is the governor of Canada.
[SPEAKER_14]: It makes perfect sense that Canada's a state.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's how Alaska's attached to the rest of the United States.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they need to be taken out into the middle of the street, and then someone needs to get, like, a big stinky sweat, you know, sweat sock, and then put a tennis ball in it and beat them in the head with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: A wet one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, fresh from the football player's foot.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's just another state where they have, you know, healthcare.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, I'm teasing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Of course I'm not that stupid.
[SPEAKER_15]: And dirty French people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have to say, having known quite a number of French Canadians during my time of living in Mobile...
[SPEAKER_05]: And I try not to make generalizations about people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I prefer the French to the French Canadians.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Sakurina's from Quebec.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know several people from Quebec.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm saying in general.
[SPEAKER_15]: You make them cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't make our listeners cry again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't talking about you specifically.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't make the listeners cry again.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's like the third time this month.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we're only on the fourth.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, okay, right cola is yummy.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're talking about cola.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, I see they're talking.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dude, did Canada invent Tab?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because if they did, seriously, nuke them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tab is awful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually, I was actually suggesting to my, well, I wanted to suggest to my husband that we move to Canada.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's cold.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like cold.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitch!
[SPEAKER_05]: But there is, and I'm going to go ahead and say this now, there is the possibility of us moving in a year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does not mean I will no longer be doing the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll just convert all my money.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next Christmas, I'm going to convert all my money to Canadian dollars and then go shopping and then come back.
[SPEAKER_15]: We probably have other Canadian listeners who are listening and going, these people are jerks.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's alright, we had to make fun of this continent for once, you know, because it's always, you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what, you know what, I love Canada because I could get gay married there if I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_05]: But honestly, if I move to any country, it's going to be to the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because seriously, I'm so pissed off at our government.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate this situation here.
[SPEAKER_05]: So hopefully, I'm going to say this publicly on the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: If any, I want to be hired by zombie flesh eaters, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_14]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_14]: My week was okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I kicked the crap out of the rest of my colleagues in Grand Theft Auto, per usual.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now we're actually going to start keeping stats now, just because I want to know how badly I'm winning.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other than that, I've been just waiting for my 360 to come in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Talked to people at GameStop, and they haven't even gotten another shipment in.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, yay Microsoft!
[SPEAKER_14]: Meanwhile, Microsoft launched in Europe with less than expected 360s because, you know, those should have come over here instead of sending them to the UK.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we got ours.
[SPEAKER_05]: It freezes all the time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, then I was also waiting for my accessories to show up at my work, and those still haven't come in either because Microsoft, once again, is slow on sending something out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I swear to God, they just, like, screw everything up.
[SPEAKER_14]: They really don't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_14]: because you know it makes perfect sense let's go ahead we're really short on units in the United States let's go ahead and launch in another country so that they're also disappointed in our launch as well that'd make perfect sense
[SPEAKER_14]: and then what next week they're going to do Japan and then Japanese just won't give a shit because none of them are buying it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, I hear more people give a shit about Xbox 360 than like the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was reading some article.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, because there's no info about the Revolution.
[SPEAKER_14]: The 360 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then... FYI, boys and girls, we did just have a big ass net split in our chat room so folks are dropping like flies but, you know, life goes on so just keep trying.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other than that, that's pretty much the main part of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really do anything of importance other than kick crap out of my colleagues in Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I rock.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, super.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel!
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel, Angel, Angel.
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: School.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grr.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finals next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I get to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: No more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then school's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I get to go back to my parents' house for like ten days.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're all on the same server now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty funny, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I refuse to play on that server.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm already playing on two other servers.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are welcome to play with me.
[SPEAKER_15]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_15]: I barely play World of Warcraft anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_15]: I do, however, play Dragon Quest.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't played a lot of games at all this week, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really, it's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've just kind of done World of Warcraft when I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most of the week's been dedicated to school, so... Yeah, and then my birthday, so... Nothing really happened this week, per se.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just World of Warcraft when I could, and then homework...
[SPEAKER_04]: and then sleep and then school and you know the regular usual grind so I've had a very boring week aside from today so it's all good
[SPEAKER_15]: My week and my day.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I had a pretty good week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just really busy, work stuff and all that good things.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really wasn't getting a lot of sleep this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, this was my week where it was like energy drinks kept me through this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I never drink those energy drinks because they're horrible for you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, Extifer, who's not here tonight because he's on the road right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Extifer was telling me about how those energy drinks sent his brother to the hospital for
[SPEAKER_15]: because his brother drank too many of those things, like the Buku and the Rockstar and all that shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've got to be careful with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Use them once in a while if you absolutely need to, but otherwise, that stuff will kill you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why are your eyes lighting up like it's a new Christmas toy, Loki?
[SPEAKER_15]: Your eyes are lighting up like, oh my gosh, I'm so excited, I'm going to go drink a bunch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you want to go to the hospital?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I don't like the hospital, but I think I can handle it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll drink that with alcohol.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be perfect.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like Red Bull and vodka, because you don't really drink that much of it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But like, okay, this is seriously bad, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Wednesday, I had a Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thursday, I had a Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_15]: Friday, I had a Rockstar.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I should not be drinking that much energy drinks.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're sounding like Pam Anderson.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good job, you're funny, you're a funny man And even though I'm drinking diet, I don't get what Can somebody explain to me how diet Rockstar is different from Rockstar?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like carbs and sugar, but otherwise it's still bad for you Oh, it's just probably made with Splendor or whatever the fuck, I don't know
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't taste the difference, but... I think that they're all nasty, especially Red Bull, which looks and tastes like piss.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, actually, Red Bull, to me... Now, not that I really know what this tastes like, but actually a lesbian told me this, is that Red Bull tastes like pussy.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it looks like pee.
[SPEAKER_15]: Obviously, I don't know this to be true, because I've never really eaten pussy, because, you know, I am a homosexual.
[SPEAKER_15]: However... Well, I did date girls in college and stuff, but, you know, I never, you know, did that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh-huh
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, I don't remember where I was going with that, I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Train derailed, show derailed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see, back on topic, back on topic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, let's see, I saw a friend of mine this weekend, a couple of friends of mine this weekend who I hadn't seen in a while, so that was cool, and I saw some Karaoke Revolution Partey.
[SPEAKER_15]: which was fun and um but karaoke revolution party is kind of overdone for me now I think I think I've seen too much of it like if I hear another fucking person saying I will always love you I'm going to force them to drink a gallon of Red Bull or something because I can't stand to hear people sing those songs anymore um however all in all good times and um
[SPEAKER_15]: I ate a lot of food this weekend.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've been in a mood.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, I have to say, I'm going to be absolutely honest.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've had male PMS all week long.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: I suspect, and I probably shouldn't be laughing about this or bringing this up on the show, but I suspect that I'm one of those people that probably gets really affected by the weather, the seasonal disorder, whatever, because seriously...
[SPEAKER_15]: I always get male PMS in December when the seasons start changing around here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, always.
[SPEAKER_15]: And so this week I've been kind of PMS-y and I haven't wanted to do a whole lot except nap.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, that's the reality.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's not me making shit up for radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the reality is that I really haven't done a lot this week because I've been sad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I forgot to mention, I bought another game for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: It makes a total of five now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Five games for a system I don't own.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just find that to be ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_15]: When are you getting your Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you figured it out yet?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm thinking sometime before the apocalypse, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, they were telling me, they said by Christmas.
[SPEAKER_14]: and they said I was halfway down the list.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, I actually got to see the list and I'm not quite halfway down the list.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm more of, oh, I don't know, five names from the bottom of the list.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, oh, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have there been more shipments of Xbox 360 since the first?
[SPEAKER_14]: Not to GameStop, at least.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got ours.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I mean, like, in general.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, yeah, but you have someone that works for GameStop.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm talking about average Joes here.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, hell, let's talk about my boss, who, you know, one of our co-workers, you know, their boyfriend works for GameStop, and he ordered his after mine, and he got it on lunch day.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gee, I wonder how that works.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I know you didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not talking about you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just saying that, you know...
[SPEAKER_14]: It's impossible to get one.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyways, no, they haven't really gotten one, at least not at the GameStop that's by my house.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I asked them if they had any more shipments since launch, and they said they hadn't gotten anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe next week, maybe whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I don't know, it's taking so long.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're only making it worse for themselves now that they're launched in two different countries.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, if they didn't have enough units before...
[SPEAKER_14]: Dork
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I'm just tired.
[SPEAKER_14]: The whole thing is I'm just... I have these games, and I've been waiting, you know, it'll be, you know, a couple weeks now for this thing, and I'm just kind of tired of waiting.
[SPEAKER_15]: At $60 a game, that's about $300 in games you have right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's all credit.
[SPEAKER_14]: All store credit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I paid not one cent for any of those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I'm not worried about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the thing is, it's just...
[SPEAKER_14]: I really kind of want the system now since I paid for it and you know waiting at you know GameStop it's going to take me forever even if they do get their shipment in I'm not going to be on that shipment so I've got to wait and I'll be waiting till next year by that time hell my work will have them then it's just retarded so I might as well just go ahead and you know pick one up at GameStop or Best Buy or whatever and then just you know cancel my pre-order there and get my money back
[SPEAKER_15]: I think we should go and kick Microsoft in the balls for what they're doing with this.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, seriously, this is stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then they keep advertising their system and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're not in fucking stores, you morons.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I haven't seen any Xbox 360 in stores now.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not around, and their whole marketing is retarded.
[SPEAKER_14]: They really need to just...
[SPEAKER_14]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_14]: They should have, this whole worldwide launch is the most retarded thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, first off, they can't really say, oh yeah, we did a worldwide launch.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_14]: You failed at that.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, you can't even, you know, hold that above everyone else's heads.
[SPEAKER_14]: They should have just launched in one country at first, a couple months later launch in another country, and later another country.
[SPEAKER_14]: Poor Australia.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's kind of giving you an idea of when units are actually going to be in stores.
[SPEAKER_14]: March?
[SPEAKER_14]: They better hope that Sony isn't like, oh yeah, we're going to be able to launch in a couple months with our PS3.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_15]: Earth to Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to have a break, and when we come back from a break, we're going to open up the Skype line, and your comments, because it's not broken this week, and we'll have that.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll be back after this mix of music from various Bomani games.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio and other news and some movie time, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_08]: See together, see together See together, see together See together, see together See together, see together Yacht in the moonlight, you dance in the shadow Rain drops the dream of a dream The night is the moment of salvation, shall things ever run?
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: From the front, FZ-24, a rescue team is approaching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_15]: We're back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and before the break we were talking a little bit about our weeks and our days, and now of course we need to get into talking a little bit about what's going on with those music games we know, and love, and adore.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm hearing that there's some pretty big news going on with Beatmania US.
[SPEAKER_15]: A buddy of mine in chat told me about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to see if I can get him to call in in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I guess some big stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: I heard that the game festival was this weekend, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: That was the big festival that went on in San Francisco where they had a bunch of games that were being shown.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was kind of like...
[SPEAKER_15]: E3 but the X Games or something so I don't know how to explain it what they were doing but apparently Beatmania didn't show up the first day because of a really stupid mistake not on Konami's end but on some festival planning end so they didn't have Beatmania USA the first day but I think it did finally make an appearance this weekend so we probably know a little bit more about it so I'm going to see if we can get somebody who might have been there to tell us a little more about it first hand however
[SPEAKER_15]: We do have news about what's going on with Beatmania over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_15]: Beatmania 2DX 13th style, also known as Beatmania 2DX Distorted.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I think they are going back to saying 2DX 13, but they're still not saying 13th style or anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: So whatever you want to call it, Distorted I guess would be the official name.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're actually location testing right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some folks snuck in a camera.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is like a high security place.
[SPEAKER_15]: These kids could probably get arrested for what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_15]: To bring joy to us all, they snuck a camera in there and recorded some of what was going on on the location test and some of the songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't seen this, but I hear that there's a pretty awesome video for a new song called Starfield.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sunfield, which, you know, obviously the name sounds an awful lot like Starfield.
[SPEAKER_15]: But there's a pretty awesome video, and one of our chatters, Siggy, suggested that we watch it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I said, sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's watch it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do a little bit of Orange Lounge Movie Time.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is the location test for Sunfield.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you guys might be able to hear a little bit of the song in the background here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, go with it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, the interface is kind of easy, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only one I saw was the Akira Yamaoka IP2 list video.
[SPEAKER_15]: This looks a lot better quality.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, look at that!
[SPEAKER_15]: Little nice feed reader there on the side.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that was carried over from another style though.
[SPEAKER_13]: This definitely sounds nothing like Starfield.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the BABY TRANNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNN
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, hey, Tran's all grown up now.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's Tran, she's got the ball.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now Tran is flying on a colored something.
It's a walker!
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a walker!
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, cute.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, is that like Mommy Tran and Baby Tran?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here, play with your head.
[SPEAKER_13]: Time to change the diaper, Baby Tran.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now back to the words I can't read because they're a bit of an angle.
[SPEAKER_13]: Driving into a smile.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ingrid!
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's what the lyrics are telling us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Happiness time, I think, driving us through the smile.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that's all the buzzers say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at that, you can almost see the reflection of the guy.
We're gonna go have him arrested.
[SPEAKER_15]: The video to iFutureList, which is over on that computer somewhere, it's pretty cool because you can actually see Akira Yamaoka really well in the video.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let me describe the video like this.
[SPEAKER_15]: One word.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shades.
[SPEAKER_15]: I swear to God, that was a part of the video that stuck out in my mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Check that out, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those location test videos are posted over on Bomani Style.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you can go check that out if you want.
[SPEAKER_15]: We post them on our website, but that's not really our thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: We don't want to tread on somebody else's territory.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the pirating of 2DX videos has always been Bomani Style's forte.
[SPEAKER_15]: So have at it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, we're going to open up the Skype line, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure you kids want to call us and let us know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: So the Skype line's open.
[SPEAKER_15]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, hello there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, I think I can get you now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you hear us?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep, I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_15]: And who might this be?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, you're speaking two to one and only Mel to the Bizzle.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, Mel to the Bizzle.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you, Mel Bizzle, Mr. Bizzle?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, yes, okay, you're just a little, you're a little bit intermittent in it out there, but... That's, that's, uh, that's because Loki is downloading porn on the other computer.
[SPEAKER_15]: I am not doing any of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's downloading lots and lots of pornography and it's messing up our bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I like Christopher's computer.
[SPEAKER_00]: And, uh, it was... Yeah, I'm not surprised that Splooge is, uh, getting through the tubes of, uh, connection right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was the game festival?
[SPEAKER_15]: You went to the game festival, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it was pretty cool, you know, gaming music experience, but I think, and I know you can definitely feel where I'm coming from when I say this.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you've been to E3, it's kind of like going to Vegas, you know, like of video gaming.
[SPEAKER_00]: Everything's out there, it's so grandiose, you know, it's the whole nine.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you go to a game, it's kind of like taking a side trip to Reno.
Yeah!
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like going to Reno.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I definitely hear that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, did you see any cool new things there at the Game and Music Experience or whatever the hell it was called?
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a couple, yeah, the Game and Music Experience.
[SPEAKER_00]: There were a couple new things.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I know most of the Orange Zones radio people want to hear about 2DX and I think you kind of got the scoop that 2DX wasn't there until like today.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, what happened with the scoop was, I don't know if you heard the full story, but essentially, first off, Friday, they didn't even put the freaking ROM in the display case.
[SPEAKER_00]: Granted, remember, this is games doing this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Konami and, like, all the other companies, they're not running their own boots.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is, like, all done by union members and, you know, like they really know about video games.
[SPEAKER_15]: So putting a lot of trust in people and then them fucking it up, basically.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, so, okay, so, anyway, Jason, you know, he wasn't even going to be there this weekend, Jason, you know?
[SPEAKER_00]: So he comes down and he finds out, you know, what the F is going on.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so we talk to the, you know, coordinator, and then they say, yeah, we can't find a ROM.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's like, okay, great.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not only is our game not being displayed, but now, you know, there's a loose ROM, and this could be some serious trouble.
[SPEAKER_00]: So he has to run back down to Konami, get the ROM, and get, like, a debug PS2, and, you know, bring that back up, like, Friday, like, at midnight or so.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, like, Saturday, you know, we figure we're going to have everything up and running.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, the geniuses that ran the, you know, the whole place
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, put into ROM this time, but they used their own PS2 and not the one that Jason brought.
[SPEAKER_00]: So what happened was you could play the game all the way up to select a song.
[SPEAKER_00]: When you select a song, the thing froze.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then when the thing froze, people thought, oh great, this is, you know, a bugged ROM.
[SPEAKER_00]: This is going to be the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is going to be the best game ever is what they were thinking.
[SPEAKER_00]: Tell us, tell us, tell us!
[SPEAKER_00]: Tell us what?
[SPEAKER_00]: Tell us, tell us!
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't hold back anymore, tell us, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, so, alright, so 2DX, you know, I got to check that out.
[SPEAKER_00]: The build looked a lot like, you know, 9th South, pretty much like what you see.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looked a little cleaner this time.
[SPEAKER_00]: As far as song lists, they didn't reveal a whole heck of a lot because, you know, of course they still want to keep a lot of their stuff under wraps.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's a lot of new songs that he said.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's kind of cool the way they set it up because, like, you know how Beat Me is supposed to have 5-key and 7-key functionality?
[SPEAKER_00]: The way you like it in a select screen, you can either choose Beatmania or Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that's kind of like a neat little spin on that.
[SPEAKER_00]: And one little spin that, I don't know if anyone's mentioned this or not, but one thing that America does have, actually let's keep, another thing, well, actually before we get to that, another thing they keep is they actually use unhappy guy naming conventions now.
[SPEAKER_00]: So now things are like beginner or easy or hyper and then, you know, hard.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I thought that was a neat twist.
[SPEAKER_00]: But like, yeah, the main thing that I heard that was confirmed was, you know, it's the how, like, when you watch top-digit videos, or like, you know, you play a song, you triple-aid it, and you think, oh man, how can I prove to people I did this besides the score?
[SPEAKER_00]: 2DXUSA will be offering, you can save your replays.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, so you can save replays of songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you going to be able to do anything with the internet?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_15]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you going to be able to do anything with the internet?
[SPEAKER_00]: That wasn't mentioned.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know about internet online play, but I do know that instant replays of your in-game are available.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very interesting!
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, you know, there were a couple.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then we were talking about the Konami style, like the new US controllers.
[SPEAKER_00]: because the thing was they didn't have it on display at games that weekend because essentially, A, it felt like a little bit, you know, getting tested out and stuff, and B, they basically didn't want to get it jacked or broken.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you know how, like, when you go to a place that's open to the public, you know, 2DX will get, I mean, come on, Roseville Golf Land, enough said.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, gotcha, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: So they don't so much click, but they don't stick like the old controller does so much.
[SPEAKER_00]: They have a little bit more click than the normal home style controllers, but not as much like total perfect click like say an arcade style.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the cover shot.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's the cover shot of the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you going to be able to flip?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I guess you could still do the flip around the controller thing for either side.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_00]: As far as I know, yeah, you can flip it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it's weird because it's rounded on one side now.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not a completely rectangular controller.
[SPEAKER_15]: It looks like a finger.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's kind of rounded on one side, so that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything else you want to share about what was going on with Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_00]: Let me think, as far as like five key songs and seven key songs, I mean, I don't know, I can't remember what the E3 list was like, but as far as like five key songs, I remember seeing like Hunting for You, Bossa Nova de Fabian, they had Battle Breaks, which I didn't see at E3.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, Brattle Bricks, what else was there?
[SPEAKER_00]: Metal Gear, Salting, Paranoia Max.
[SPEAKER_00]: So yeah, that was like kind of default list almost for E3, except maybe like one or two songs.
[SPEAKER_00]: R7 Key, I mean, the hardest song I saw was Shining Colors, so we thought I'd E3 also.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they also have like the M-Step.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is that song from Six Style?
[SPEAKER_00]: Was it Six Style?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, Six Style.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Shotaro Hirata song, that's like the two-step song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, the M-Step 2-1?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, they had that song.
[SPEAKER_00]: They had GMD on there, which is surprising.
[SPEAKER_15]: GMD, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, complicated, like trigonometry.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was like third style, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's an old song.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, yeah, and the cool thing was they kept a lot of the 2DX videos crossed over to this version.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, like, you know, GMD with the pop locker and the breaker, yeah, you get to see that on there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now, were the anothers there or not?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what they're asking in chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, another, I can't remember, I tried playing, like, Shining Polaris, another, but I can't remember if it was or not, you know, because I haven't played that song in a long time.
[SPEAKER_00]: But as far as I know, um, well, from what Jason had told me, as far as another, I heard it's something you have to, uh, possibly might be something you have to unlock.
[SPEAKER_15]: It might be an unlock feature then, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see any of the DJ art, the goalie art, the art that shows up when you beat songs?
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see any of the art, the artwork, the, like, the DJs on the completion screens?
[SPEAKER_00]: They didn't have any artwork, like, you know, when you get, like, you know, the certain gallery unlocks.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, I did not see that at the time.
[SPEAKER_00]: They just only had the staff screen.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that may still be a work in progress.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, it's still a work in progress, you never know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I mean, I hear, like, well, the one thing that somewhat disappointed me was 5C Beat Mania doesn't have their old, like, you know, 16-bit or whatever, like the, you know, those little block type videos.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, the old style videos.
[SPEAKER_00]: But they, you know, kind of managed to make it a little more sleeker and, like, more or less, you know, recreate some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I hear some...
[SPEAKER_00]: Some songs get absolute total new video makeovers, but there really isn't any word which ones or just yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: That pretty much sums up 2DX.
[SPEAKER_00]: What I'll probably do is I'll post on Orange Lounge there a full song list that I did see there because I have it on my video camcorder.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh yeah, and what else?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I think that pretty much sums up 2DX's game for today.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, like I said, a lot of stuff I was able to prioritize just, you know, kind of, you know, because he wasn't really there to, like, answer questions or anything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, well, I mean, that's pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess maybe it might have been out there about the recording thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was hidden.
[SPEAKER_15]: Somebody in their chat room was saying it was kind of hidden on the Music of a New Redirection site.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's not exactly hidden.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's listed right on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_14]: But I didn't know about that before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it says right on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's under Game Overview.
[SPEAKER_14]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess that recording thing has been known.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't know that, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so save your performances and play them back for your friends.
[SPEAKER_15]: Somebody in chat said something about it, that it's actually on the Music in Every Direction site.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: I totally missed that when I looked at the site there.
[SPEAKER_15]: But that's cool about the song list.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did not know about M2 Step Version 1.
[SPEAKER_14]: It does say there's also internet rankings.
[SPEAKER_15]: Really?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, thank you for the inside scoop, Mel, and we'll be looking forward to seeing the song list and videos and other reactions over on OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_00]: I might probably do a more extensive game write-up on Orange Lounge as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Did you see any... There are a lot of other cool things there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you see any of the live shows, like Freeze Pop or Zonk?
[SPEAKER_00]: See live shows?
[SPEAKER_00]: You mean as far as the bands or the demos?
[SPEAKER_15]: The bands.
[SPEAKER_00]: The bands?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, how are the bands?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh man, yeah, yeah, I actually got to see Zonka Friday night.
[SPEAKER_15]: Awesome, how was it?
[SPEAKER_00]: It was pretty cool, I mean, it's like the first time I've seen the dance since the lead singer actually had her kid a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I mean, they always put on a great show live, they're one of those acts that, I mean, they may, I mean, they sound pretty decent, like when you listen to it, like, you know, your headphones are both, to see them live, they actually have, they have great showmanship.
[SPEAKER_15]: Great, great.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm hoping that maybe we can talk to him at some point, because I want to ask him about Love This Feelin' and Tittle Tattle and all that stuff, so we'll see in the future, some point, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'll work on scoring you an interview, because, you know, me and Dave, you know, we gotta like that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Mel, thank you for calling in and giving us the scoop.
[SPEAKER_15]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stay tuned to orangelaunchradio.com for more info.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, no prob.
[SPEAKER_00]: Peace out, people.
[SPEAKER_00]: Time to go listen and make some dinner on the meanwhile.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: A little difficulty there with the connection, it sounds like there.
[SPEAKER_15]: But Mel, we can clearly hear him.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's having a hard time understanding us, I think.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we can clearly hear him talking about Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_15]: Didn't end up actually getting shown at game until today, but it does look like that they are going to call 2DX is the other mode in Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then we have M2 Step 1 and all that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, I don't know if he said 2DX was the other mode.
[SPEAKER_15]: He actually said it was 2DX.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's Beatmania 2DX, and it's also Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's on all their screens.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's in the screenshot.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wish, I wish, I've been great.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, but that's nice, though, that they call it at least 2DX, and like a little bit of a throwback to what's going on on the Japanese side.
[SPEAKER_15]: The M two-step song is in it.
[SPEAKER_15]: In My Eyes, Hitchhiker...
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that's from these screen caps we see, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, these are probably the latest build, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: These are ones that are on Music in Every Direction.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was the one, GMD, M02 step, version 1.01.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a dumb name for a song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: We are getting hammered on the Skype line tonight, so we better hurry up and get to another call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, Sky, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, Siggy, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: You forgot to mention V. Fuck V. I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck V. It's done.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't care about V anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: V was cool like three years ago, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: I want some W. Don't call back until you guys tell me that W's in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, next we're going to have H for Handel.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, that was nerdy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excuse me, I was a music major at one time.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: But no, I understand that the fanboys would be very pissed if V didn't show up, so we do have to mention some V. Well, other than that, I have to make some correction.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: You said that the 2DX13 distorted location test is going on right now?
[SPEAKER_15]: It just finished, right?
[SPEAKER_23]: But it just finished.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, I remember reading, I think you and Chad or somebody had said something that it had just finished.
[SPEAKER_15]: But yeah, it was going on, so it just finished though.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's too bad.
[SPEAKER_23]: Anyway, are you going to play the Guitadora V2 songs?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, I'm going to do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to play them next break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to pick four that you sent me with cool titles and do them next break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, go with the Vanilla Ninja song first since it's your favorite.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, fuck yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love Vanilla Ninja.
[SPEAKER_15]: What song did they put in in V2 by them?
[SPEAKER_15]: Metal Queen.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll definitely play that one.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think about all this Beatmania US news?
[SPEAKER_23]: I was a little disappointed when I found out that it wasn't shown yesterday, thanks to Rich, who was there yesterday.
[SPEAKER_15]: A little technical foul up there, but now we understand what's going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think about the recording mode?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_23]: Hmm, yeah, I'll think about that, but I wasn't surprised.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, seems like, I guess, I think, I think it shows that Konami might be kind of looking on what's going out there on the internet right now, like, what do the fans of 2DX seem to really get into, and what do they want in the game, and maybe they kind of picked up on the whole, like, you know, VJ Army tracking thing, and maybe they thought it was something they could build into the game, don't know, just a thought, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, Siggy, anything else you want to share with us?
[SPEAKER_23]: Well, nothing much else at the moment, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I appreciate the call as always.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to get to some other calls because we're getting hammered tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: But have a good one, okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Siggy reminding us that Gita Dora V2 stuff is ready to go.
[SPEAKER_15]: He sent us some songs from there.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're going to check that out during the next break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I'm excited to hear some of this stuff, so we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lots and lots to pick from.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my gosh, I'm just going to pick the one that was on the line first.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, who is this?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's Antenna Man 64.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello Nintendomaniac64, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh, playing Mario Kart as we speak.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: Still playing?
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you able to find friends on there?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because every time I go in to do a friends matchup, my friends are never online.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't even bother anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: I pretty much do rivals mode a lot.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't done Rivals, but I hear that Rivals is a good way to find people at your own skill level, so I need to do that one more often because otherwise I get my ass kicked almost every time.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I need to get matched up against some seven-year-olds so I can have a sense of accomplishment when I actually beat it.
[SPEAKER_15]: But...
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I actually played Mario Kart DS this last week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I played with several other people that have DSs, and we actually played the mode where you can broadcast the game, you can download the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: What I thought was kind of cool, and I haven't really seen this in a lot of DS games, is that you can mix and match people that have the game and people that don't have the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can play multiplayer mode with people that do and don't have the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: And basically, anybody that doesn't have the game will be a shy guy,
[SPEAKER_15]: which isn't even a character that you can unlock in the normal game so I thought that was kind of weird because I hear the Shy Guy actually has like just a perfectly balanced average car so my friends are actually doing very well with the Shy Guy cars but everybody else who has the game will get to pick from any character and unfortunately when you're playing with anybody that doesn't have the game you can only pick from one battle track and I think eight of the typical race courses.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can do anything in the first Retro Cup and in the first Mario DS Cup.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was a good time.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, maybe the Shire is supposed to give a bit of a handicap for those people who don't have it, so they don't have as much practice.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, that might be a good point, is that they do the balanced car because those people don't have practice, like the rest of us addicts do.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you going to be online with Animal Crossing this week?
[SPEAKER_22]: I might pick up the game, but maybe not this week.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm still kind of thinking about it, because I didn't really... I'm not too much of an Animal Crossing fan, but the online sounds really cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm excited about this.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can understand, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: Animal Crossing is a very quirky sort of game, so I can see where...
[SPEAKER_15]: It might not be, like, you're jumping at the chance, trying to get it, so, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I'm very curious to see how the online stuff is going to work, too, because we don't really know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, we hear how things are supposed to work, but we haven't really seen it in motion a whole lot except E3, which wasn't exactly a tell-all type situation.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, my L button on my DS is crapped out.
[SPEAKER_22]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can you do a warranty thing?
[SPEAKER_22]: Did you email Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_22]: Unfortunately, my DS just came out of warranty.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_22]: That is so typical.
[SPEAKER_22]: But what?
[SPEAKER_22]: We got it on a credit card that will actually allow us to extend the warranty for just, I don't know how long, but apparently they can cover it, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: that's pretty awesome I never would have thought of that and that's actually probably a good tip especially this time of year for people that are listening if your shit breaks especially like
[SPEAKER_15]: Goddamn my microphone.
[SPEAKER_15]: If your stuff breaks, don't just check with the manufacturer, check with your credit card company because there may be some type of extension warranty or something else that might be available to you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sorry to break your ears there.
[SPEAKER_15]: I swear to God, this mic is so fiery.
[SPEAKER_15]: There might be something else available to you on your credit card warranty that goes beyond the manufacturer.
[SPEAKER_15]: There, finally.
[SPEAKER_15]: So check out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good tip.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for reminding us.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, yeah, I pretty much just use the X button for items now.
[SPEAKER_15]: But see, that's tough with the finger and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need my L button.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love my L button.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I mean, at first I didn't think I'd be able to do it, but all I do is I just move my... My thumb is still holding down A. My nail actually hits the X button, not my actual finger.
[SPEAKER_22]: So if I had cut my nails, I probably wouldn't be able to hit X. Well, a good incentive not to be biting those nails.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't bite them nails.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except I just bit one of them.
[SPEAKER_22]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_22]: I got other stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Last night I went on a huge StepMania song downloading spree.
[SPEAKER_22]: And what'd you find?
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything good?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I did find some official DDR songs and stuff, like Butterfly, Mr. Wonderful, things like those.
[SPEAKER_22]: That shit's old.
[SPEAKER_22]: That shit is so old.
[SPEAKER_22]: I know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't have any kind of PlayStation and stuff, so I've never even played the games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that's where the simulator stuff can be kind of fun, is that you can download the old shit you might have missed out on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, and I actually completely recreated Sandstorm on every difficulty.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's a lot of Raven.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, well, Nintendo Maniac, we've got to let you go because we're going to try and get at least one more call before we go to break, but thank you for calling in, and good luck with that L button.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, I'm winning.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm winning.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, kick some ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Kick some ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have fun, buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_15]: One more call, call, call, call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see, how about this one?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, this is SSJ100 Matt here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, SSJ100 Matt here.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_24]: Actually, I got some minor news for myself.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got special advanced press screenings to the movie Grandma's Boy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Grandma's Blood, oh, this is the Adam Sandler movie where he plays like a game tester or something, huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Did you actually see the movie?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, no, the advanced screening is for this Thursday.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not Adam Sandler, it's, what's his name, I don't remember the guy's name.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob Schneider?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not Rob Schneider.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought it was Adam Sandler.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know him.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, he, it's Happy Madness.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alan something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Happy Madison is the one doing the production.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't remember who.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, some person.
[SPEAKER_15]: So how did you manage to get this ticket?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, the television studio that I worked at was giving out, like, it's like, okay, we have 12 tickets, who wants them?
[SPEAKER_24]: And I just jumped on top of two, so.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that was easy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those fell in your lap, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_15]: That must be nice.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, the premiere is Thursday, and they're going to make a big deal out of it, and they're going to have EA Sports going to be showing off games before the screening.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm looking at some of these people who are in the movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't recognize any of these people at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, there's Rob Schneider is in it, and David Spade, and Kevin Nealon.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, this is like an early 90s Saturday Night Live thing going on here.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, and the old woman from... Doris Roberts' grandma.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm trying to look at the poster here.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love Internet Movie Database.
[SPEAKER_15]: It answers all my movie questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: They didn't pay me to say that, even.
[SPEAKER_15]: I really do love this one.
[SPEAKER_15]: Linda Cardellini... Oh, they've got a lot of people in this movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, well, that should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_24]: Supposedly, Kevin Nealon's supposed to show up, so...
[SPEAKER_24]: Hopefully I can give him my business card or something so he can hire me for a movie or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the Hollywood way.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was I going to say about this movie?
[SPEAKER_15]: You'll call back and let us know if it's good or not, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Next week?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners?
[SPEAKER_15]: Besides rubbing it in that you get to go to a movie premiere and we don't?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, the movie comes out January 6th, so... That's not a good sign because January is when the studios unload their crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: Didn't Resident Evil 2 come out in January?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, but a wonderful movie called BloodRayne is coming out in January.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like I said, that's when the studios unload all our crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: It might be fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just let us know if it makes gamers look like dumbasses or not, because I'm very interested to see what happens with another gaming movie and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have fun at the movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let us know how it goes.
[SPEAKER_15]: All righty?
[SPEAKER_15]: All right, later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep, bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Call there from SSJ100 Matt, who, by the way, is looking for a job in the industry.
[SPEAKER_15]: So if you know a rich producer, he wants a job, so give him a job.
[SPEAKER_15]: We want a job, too, actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: We could use a job.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would sell My Immortal Soul to do Orange Lounge on TV or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how to do it on TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Radio is fun, but...
[SPEAKER_15]: Gita Dora V
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it's called Twinkleberry.
[SPEAKER_15]: How can it be bad?
[SPEAKER_05]: It sounds too much like Dingleberry.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to hear a Tara song.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm really curious if Model DD7 has anything to do with the other model song that's been in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Then we'll hear it.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's been like tons of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll be back after this with more Orange Launch Radio and maybe some more Skype if you kids are good.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
Well, I only want love tonight Give me your heart
[SPEAKER_08]: Tart, tart,
[SPEAKER_08]: My favorite thing on that day was him, but if you compare it to a tart, it's too much for me, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: A tart, a tart, a magical tart, a tart, I'm scared of the aftertaste.
[SPEAKER_08]: A tart, a tart, another tart, a tart, a sweet and painful tart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next time.
Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a time when magic suddenly melted.
[SPEAKER_08]: It became more and more dangerous than before.
[SPEAKER_08]: The tart was a tart.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Please subscribe to our channel!
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to be bothered by the noise.
I don't want to be bothered by the noise.
I don't want to lose hope in an age when the sun is about to rise.
I'm going to fly over the sky.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
and many more.
[SPEAKER_08]: From the Step Squad to Orange Lab, this GDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_08]: Holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler, holler!
[SPEAKER_15]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: And in that break we heard a whole clusterfuck of music from Gita Dora V2.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I understand that people are leaving listening to our show to go watch other things on television, like the Boondocks or Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_15]: TV addicts, you need to get off of your butts.
[SPEAKER_15]: You bitches need to get a TiVo or a BitTorrent.
[SPEAKER_14]: Screw TiVo.
[SPEAKER_14]: BitTorrent, yeah, BitTorrent is the way to go.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's on before the show is even on.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's on demand.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can...
[SPEAKER_14]: You can literally, if you have news groups, I do this almost every week.
[SPEAKER_14]: When I get done with the show, I go watch my episode of Family Guy.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: After the show!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's how you do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm just poking fun at people that dare ditch us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the government has access to it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh no, the government knows I watch Will and Grace.
[SPEAKER_15]: What am I going to do?
[SPEAKER_15]: The government might think I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, um... Where were we going?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hail in a handbasket!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm driving this car, turning it around.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, I was going to get to the cage match pretty soon here because I know we want to do a cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have a song, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, of course I have a song because I didn't win last week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know, just making sure because I hadn't seen it yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just making sure you had a song somewhere.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, um...
[SPEAKER_15]: I want to mention this really quick though, which I think, oh, two things I want to mention real quick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Somebody brought it up in the chat room during break and I was talking about energies at the top of the show, or energies, energy drinks at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_15]: And somebody in chat reminded us about the Final Fantasy energy drink that's coming out called Potion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you heard of this?
[SPEAKER_15]: I swear to God I'm not making this shit up.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's this new energy drink coming out called... Wait, somebody give me a web link.
[SPEAKER_15]: I read about this on the... It should be Hypotion.
[SPEAKER_15]: Internet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hypotion will be the one that's like...
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Diet or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want an ether.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want Phoenix down.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_15]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Final Fantasy XII Potion.
[SPEAKER_15]: And this is what it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a food tie-in there.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we're looking at it there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is this on... Oh, it's on Gamebrink.com is what it is here.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's some type of tie-in to Final Fantasy XII here.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wish I could zoom in on the product.
[SPEAKER_15]: It looks an awful lot like balls or Powerade.
[SPEAKER_15]: But actually I like the play on it because it looks like it's actually in a potion or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: March 2006 is when this stuff goes on sale.
[SPEAKER_15]: The drink supposedly makes you relax like herb tea and tastes mystical.
[SPEAKER_15]: It contains nutritional supplements so that the company can claim the drinker might recover real life hit points.
[SPEAKER_15]: And if you drink this, you're a nerd.
[SPEAKER_15]: A really big nerd.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will I go up a level?
[SPEAKER_15]: What was the other thing I wanted to do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Will I do the little dance?
[SPEAKER_15]: The little throw my arms up?
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you played the Final Fantasy XII demo?
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the bottles.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wait, have you played the Final Fantasy XII demo?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, and I'm not going to because I played it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's sexy.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's different than the E3 one.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's way different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not from what everybody in the universe else has told me.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, they're lying.
[SPEAKER_15]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love these bottles, they're cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll get it just for the bottles.
[SPEAKER_15]: What else did I want to mention?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yes, Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_15]: On the cell phones, you guys pretty soon are going to be able to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why you would want to play DDR on your cell phone is beyond me, but they were showing this supposedly at the Game Festival, and I completely forgot to ask Mel about this because he was there, but he probably wasn't even looking for it because my god, who gives a shit about mobile gaming?
[SPEAKER_15]: I know I don't.
[SPEAKER_15]: But...
[SPEAKER_15]: We actually ran a story about this on OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_15]: This part of it is kind of old news that you can buy the mobile ringtones that feature DDR songs, but what may be kind of news to you is that they did show in the Games on the Go area at the Game Festival that they will be doing DDR on mobile phones.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is probably just a port of what we've seen happen in Japan, because I believe they already have this in Japan.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, a couple, and they have like Max 300 I've seen.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, you got a bigger picture.
[SPEAKER_15]: That looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, sorry, Jamie was showing me the potions.
[SPEAKER_15]: So yeah, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's DDR on the cell phone, but funny enough, the screenshot I saw was Max 300.
[SPEAKER_15]: And why you would want to play that on a cell phone, I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: Especially if there's no dance pad hookup.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like an exercise in futility.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even if there was a dance pad hookup, that would be stupid.
[SPEAKER_15]: The only use I would see for this is if you are a freestyler who needs your steps on the go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like if you're going to be in an upcoming tournament or something, you need to take a quick look at those steps before you go up on stage, like one more time, run through the routine in your mind.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's where DDR on the cell phone would be a good idea.
[SPEAKER_15]: The rest of this?
[SPEAKER_15]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll probably buy it anyway because I'm a consumer whore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie's showing me the bigger pictures of potion.
[SPEAKER_15]: That looks very nice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pretty bottles.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would rather buy a lot of Final Fantasy potion than DDR on the cell phone.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's do tonight's cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's where we put three songs and battle against each other to the death.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there are fatalities involved.
[SPEAKER_15]: And one song emerges as the victor.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you guys in chat have the final say on which one of these songs is the winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: The winning song, by the way, goes in a rotation all week long.
[SPEAKER_15]: All freaking week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bomani and Video Game Music program.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: So let's get it started, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, an old friend band of Jamie's made it.
[SPEAKER_15]: A friendly old band, a jolly old time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Blur was the band, and the song was called Crazy Beat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Is it crazy enough to win for a second week in a row?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're going to play a clip for you guys, so you can judge if you liked us or not, and wanted to win for the second week in a row.
[SPEAKER_15]: So here it is, song one in tonight's Cage Match, Blur with Crazy Beat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy.
I love my brothers on Saturday night
[SPEAKER_09]: I love my sister and I love her tonight Break out!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
[SPEAKER_15]: Song numero uno in tonight's cage match, Blur with Crazy Beats.
[SPEAKER_15]: You only get a clip of that, though, because if you wanted to hear the whole thing, you should have been listening last week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Honestly, kids.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, song number two in tonight's cage match comes to us via the Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, what did you pick for us tonight, sir?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, picked something from Alien 316, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, see, they should have been Alien 314, because then they could have been Alien Pie.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm lame.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, um, yeah, so this is a song from Alien 316, which you might remember from Ultramix 1 with C-Square, or was it, wait, Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_14]: By the way, it's Alien 613.
[SPEAKER_14]: 613, whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: 313, whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who gives a crap?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alien and some number.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, uh, this is the song All For Nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alien number 613 with All For Nothing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy song number 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, was that a number 10 or a number 2?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, it was more like a number 5.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just cause...
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it was cool, but it didn't really do anything, just repeated the same little lick over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really had nothing this week that I hadn't already picked.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I thought that song was pretty good for me to poop on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll give it a 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's move on to song number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: Song number three tonight is my pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I also picked a former Bomani artist because I like this song.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's actually a song that she actually released in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Tess.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the song is called The Second You Sleep, I Stay to Watch You Fade Away.
[SPEAKER_15]: And Tess, of course, did Justify My Love and all that stuff for DDR.
[SPEAKER_15]: So here it is, Tess, here on Orange Lounge Radio, song number three.
[SPEAKER_08]: by your side you close the door so
Hey, I say to watch you fade away, I dream of you tonight, tomorrow you're gone
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish by God you'd say
[SPEAKER_15]: Song number three in tonight's cage match, Tess, with The Second You Sleep by Stay to Watch You Fade Away.
[SPEAKER_15]: Would you like to stay to watch that song, or would you like it to fade away?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fade, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Generic Trance.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although that one was not as annoying as the usual one, so it gives a seven.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd like to know how you can watch music.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shut up and rate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It gives a seven.
[SPEAKER_15]: and I'll rate that too because everybody else is kind of in and out.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will rate that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like the melody in that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think that's what sets it apart from other blah trance songs is I like the melody an awful lot in that song and the harmony and everything is great.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I give that song a nine because I like it.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let us recap, shall we, the three songs you can vote for tonight in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can either vote for last week's winner, song number one, Blur with Crazy Beat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or you can vote for song number two, Alien number 613 with All For Nothing.
[SPEAKER_15]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is The Second You Sleep by Stay To Watch You Fade Away by Tess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote for song numero uno, dos, or tres.
[SPEAKER_15]: And we will see which song emerges victorious.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is the part of the show where I go over to Loki and I say, Hey, Loki, you know that Sim scene that's out there where people are playing Beatmania on their PSPs and shit?
[SPEAKER_15]: What is going on in the Sim scene?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I could care less, but I know our listeners want to know.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, Loki, what's up?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, just more stuff with DDR, um, OSC4, they are now in their In The Groove division, and they have the results for the keyboard, um, division of sim files out there.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what the difference would be with In The Groove sim files, I guess that's not quite impossible, but pretty impossible?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyways, if anyone cares, I will go into the results here of who won the keyboard section, which I don't even really, I haven't checked out any of the entries, so God knows.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, and it doesn't exist.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, anyways, in other... That's one of those Bomani-style bug things, like you can't log in on the forums or...
[SPEAKER_15]: PoopTow, it's weird.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyways, who cares?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have a secret account on Bobani Style.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not actually Sky, because somehow I got locked out of that account, like I can't get in it or access it at all, so I have a secret name.
Secret.
[SPEAKER_03]: Secret.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, on top of that, the other thing was all the sim files for Ultramix 3 have been released.
[SPEAKER_14]: All of them.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh good, that means all the MP3s are out there, so people can stop whining for them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have them.
[SPEAKER_14]: But no, they're up there.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can find them at BomaniISO.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever that BitTorrent tracker was that has all the stuff that people steal and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all that's going on, really.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dead.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nothing going on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, it's Christmas.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody's taking a break from the sim scene because they're bored.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: However...
[SPEAKER_14]: We do have to, in a typical fashion, it is time to see how many really bad Max remixes have been released this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, so starting off.
[SPEAKER_14]: And of course, if you guys were looking for those 2DX distorted clips, you can actually find them in their media shop.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have four different videos on there, so you can check those out.
[SPEAKER_14]: But,
[SPEAKER_14]: If you really want to check out what everybody is looking for, and that's really horrible Max remixes, you can also check those out in their sim file form there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And let's see, for this week, looks like it's been a pretty light week actually.
[SPEAKER_14]: We've got Max Max, Max Stink, Max 340, Max Wizard, Max Attack.
[SPEAKER_14]: Twice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Max My Butt.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Paranoia Fart Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't check and see how many Paranoia remixes there are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still waiting for the Safari Trans Mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: Keep waiting.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'll get your Safari Trans Mix before I'll get my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd fill time, but I'm tallying cage match votes, so it's up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: And of course, you know, to cover the wonderful Paranoia remixes, we have Paranoia Survivor Another, Paranoia Trickmaster Edit, Paranoia Survivor Max 580, Paranoia Sky, Paranoia Agent Theme, that one I'm kind of interested to see what that is, Paranoia Eternal Freeze, Paranoia Zombie, Rotelda Paranoia,
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's lame.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want Max the final, and then I want Konami to threaten to sue anyone who puts out another Max remix, and so people can't do it anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I just, I'm sick of Max remixes, I really am.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Maximizer now, don't you know?
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck Maximizer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maximizer wasn't even a freaking Max remix at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck Maximizer, fuck Joni and Spesh Max, Super Max, Max My Ass, whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Fuck Max, fuck Legend of Max, seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: They should make one called Extremer.
[SPEAKER_15]: What was the middle one?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't even remember what the real ones are called anymore.
[SPEAKER_15]: Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_15]: Max Unlimited should have been where it stopped.
[SPEAKER_15]: That should have been the last one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, The Legend of Max was a good place to stop it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because that was cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was kind of a song to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Paranoia, like Paranoia Respect, that was a good one to end it on.
[SPEAKER_09]: That should be it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're done.
[SPEAKER_14]: And same with B4U.
[SPEAKER_14]: B4U was a good point to stop those remixes as well.
[SPEAKER_15]: And what the fuck was that Max song that was in the Max Heart Attack one in Extreme Japan?
[SPEAKER_14]: Max Period.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was bullshit.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was absolute bullshit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Max Period makes me on my period.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, we are going to go to a small break, and when we come back from this small break, we might do some more Skype calls, if you're good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Otherwise, we're going to do the FUs of the week, so we'll see what kind of mood we're in when we come back from this.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we will do both at some point, so don't get your panties in a bunch.
[SPEAKER_15]: In this break, in celebration of Angel's new necklace, we're going to do a couple LED songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll start it off with a little Love is Dreaminess, and we'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge!
DarkSakura
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: So much for making the world a dream come true
[SPEAKER_15]: Gaming Radio, so uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cracks me up every time.
[SPEAKER_15]: See, it sounds like he says tax cunts.
[SPEAKER_15]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_15]: It totally does.
[SPEAKER_15]: Welcome back to Orange Lawn Radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_15]: LED in that break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just nothing but LED.
[SPEAKER_15]: Love is dreaminess, nebula grasper, something wonderful, photogenic.
[SPEAKER_15]: All in that break.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm being a comedic genius in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_15]: And in fact, I don't know, I joined in a game here.
[SPEAKER_15]: Somebody just asked, oh, I'm not even going to try to pronounce his name.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm totally going to butcher this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Milfululi, Milfululi?
[SPEAKER_15]: I probably fucked that up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Says, what's black and white and red all over?
[SPEAKER_15]: And everybody, you know, is putting their own answers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I put a zebra that I just shot.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rini said a nun in a blender.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or a sunburnt penguin.
[SPEAKER_15]: So everybody's a comedian these days, actually.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I left the nun in a blender.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Michael Jackson.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because he has that red costume that he wears, and it's black and white around him.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're hella dumb.
[SPEAKER_15]: You said hella.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm from Northern California.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have to say hella.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess I might as well acknowledge the fact that the one and only LankyStyle is sitting in the room with us right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: How you doing, Mr. LankyStyle?
[SPEAKER_15]: Why'd you do that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Now this show's just taken a big turn for the worse.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, this show took a turn for the worse two and a half years ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: What, um, what's up?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's when Loki joined.
[SPEAKER_15]: I are funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: What kind of games have you been playing this week, my friend?
[SPEAKER_15]: Bring us back to talking about video games for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dragon Quest VIII
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I love the, everybody knows I love the Dragon Quest series, but... That's funny, those are the exact same two games I've been playing, except a lot more Dragon Quest VIII, and when I have time, I'm actually like five hours into Dragon Quest VIII, and for me, that's a long time to be sitting with a game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even though it's only like probably... I'm probably like not even... About 4 or 5% of the game.
[SPEAKER_15]: I haven't even scratched the surface of that game, I know I haven't.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's fine.
[SPEAKER_15]: At least I'm getting my money's worth.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I know that I will probably completely ignore Dragon Quest this week when Animal Crossing comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is looking pretty good.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I haven't been doing a lot of reading on the features, but I mean... Who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_15]: I know it has the online... Who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's online, it's Animal Crossing, and I get a bug net.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm wondering if it's going to be fresh enough to keep me into it longer than I was the original.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody else stayed on it for... Internet, me, me...
[SPEAKER_11]: Man, that's true.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think in Animal Crossing, there should be a day called I Kill Every One Day, and I go and I shoot the people I don't like in the village and then cook them for dinner.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be the greatest Animal Crossing day ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get the, like, come here, Olivia, razor-wired bug net.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get to hit them over the head with.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Battle Royale Day on Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I told my foo-poo joke.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's this, dare I ask?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'll repeat it.
[SPEAKER_15]: How dare you interrupt my Animal Crossing rant, by the way.
[SPEAKER_15]: You will be in the Animal Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Animal Crossing has been pre-ordered already.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, what's the joke?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm going to have to retell it.
[SPEAKER_05]: These explorers, there's a legend of a bird called the Foo Poo Bird.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've told you this one before.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, the legend is that anyone who goes after the Foo Poo Bird disappears.
[SPEAKER_05]: So three explorers decide they're going to find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: One goes one way and two go off the other way.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so the one who's by himself, he hears this, and then he finds he's got poo on his head, so he wipes it off.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he vanishes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the other two are together, and all of a sudden they hear, Roar!
[SPEAKER_05]: and one of them looks up in time to get shot on in the face.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he wipes it off.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's no fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he disappears.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the other one's like, oh no!
[SPEAKER_05]: And he starts running off because he saw how it happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so right before he gets to the end of the jungle, and he's got poo on his head.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, well, crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know if I wipe this off, I'm going to disappear.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he goes home with shit on his head.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he goes home to his wife and she goes, why do you have crap on your head?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's like, because if you wipe off the poop of the foo-poo bird, then you'll disappear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well, we'll live with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they go to bed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the stink is so bad that she has to wipe it off of his head.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when she does, it disappears.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you know what the moral of the story is?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: If the fooshits wear it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please don't quit your day job.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish I could.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, that was so bad!
[SPEAKER_13]: It was so bad!
[SPEAKER_13]: So very bad!
[SPEAKER_15]: It was bad, bad, bad!
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, this brings me back to World's Worst Forward.
[SPEAKER_15]: That makes me want to go watch Deuce Bigelow, European Gigolo, just so I can hear something funny.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now that the show has been ruined.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You laughed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Get the fooshits, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is definitely an opportunity for us to go into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I told the one-eyed whore joke, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: The one-eyed whore joke?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not even going to ask.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm simply going to go to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, Jamie, why is it that we do these FUs of the week every single week?
[SPEAKER_05]: The first Seth U of the week goes to Rob for not finding my joke hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which it was, and you know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The second SU of the week goes toward certain aspects of my employment, which I am not at liberty to discuss.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another aspect goes toward me for not having the money that I want to have right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And traffic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate traffic in this area.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also a humongous SU goes to superficiality.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, that was, yeah I was going to say that was short.
[SPEAKER_05]: And having the plague, because I feel it coming upon me again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, to start off my FUs of the week, I'm actually kind of, this is not anything that has to do with me.
[SPEAKER_14]: My sister's house was actually broken into by some guy in broad daylight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now this is how retarded this guy is, and this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: The guy was breaking into the house in broad daylight.
[SPEAKER_14]: People observed him breaking into the house.
[SPEAKER_14]: First he tried the garage door and couldn't pry it open with his crowbar.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tried the front door, couldn't pry it open with his crowbar.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tried kicking in the front door, still couldn't get it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tried the side door, couldn't get that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And if the fool shits, wear it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Finally, he tried breaking the bedroom window, got in through there and stole some costume jewelry and then left.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thereby netting absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, fuck you, the stupid, retarded people.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not only that, he stopped traffic as he was running across the street to escape being caught, even though he was already seen.
[SPEAKER_14]: But he did get away because the cops took an hour to respond.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, Carmichael PD.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, um, then, um, fuck you to Microsoft for fucking up both, not only the US launch of the 360, but now the UK launch, and I know you're gonna go for 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: with the Japanese launch, but too bad the Japanese don't give a shit about your system because all the wonderful games are coming out for it, like the wonderful RPGs and DOA4 and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah, those aren't coming out at launch because they're delayed now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_14]: But hey, they can play Madden because Madden rocks, I guess.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, fuck you to GameStop for not getting any more shipments in of the 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know it's not their fault, but still though,
[SPEAKER_14]: They said I was halfway down the list.
[SPEAKER_14]: They lied to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was actually towards the bottom of the list.
[SPEAKER_14]: So fuck them for not knowing what halfway means.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also, fuck you to stupid people driving your cars because you can't.
[SPEAKER_14]: And women do not need to be driving SUVs because they're obviously too big for them to handle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stupid useless vehicle.
[SPEAKER_11]: They could...
[SPEAKER_11]: They could save that Japanese Xbox 360 launch if they would just make an Arnold Schwarzenegger game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, they love Arnold Schwarzenegger in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go play my game!
[SPEAKER_08]: Do it now!
[SPEAKER_09]: Govenator!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I guess that means it's now my turn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, I would say an F you just to the fact that I've just been feeling like shit all week and I've just been doing some crazy things.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the fact that I've just had lack of sleep and just been overall just feeling rather blah and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to the fact that I'm just an angsty person and...
[SPEAKER_15]: This F you to the fact that it's Christmas time and this time of year always sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: It just does.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope Santa... I better not say that because the FBI will come after us and say, I hope Santa brings me a bomb for Christmas so I can blow some people up.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I'm not really meaning that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't mean that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, now, you don't have the turban for that.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is horrible.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not really, I hope it's a bomb full of confetti, so I can show you my love.
[SPEAKER_16]: Full of wonderful radioactive confetti.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm on some list now.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can always do what the major retailers are doing, that's just crash a float into somebody.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want somebody to build me a Spongebob bomb of air.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hot air.
[SPEAKER_15]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there's already enough hot air in the government.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, let's go to Brad.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure Brad has some FUs that he wants to get out of his system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure, why not.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you call a deer with no eyes?
[SPEAKER_11]: No eye-deer.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you call a deer with no eyes and no legs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Still no eye-deer.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's my FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, if we were going with corny jokes for the night, then I figured, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: You are fucking lame.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel, don't run away.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's your FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, yeah, a few people that didn't say happy birthday, but you guys did, so you guys love me, yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I don't know, what else?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, it's been hella cold, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't really say that though, because people in other areas of the United States are colder, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I've been cold, so you know what, yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, who didn't go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyone?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I'm just talking to myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rise Princess, do you have anything you want to get out of your system?
[SPEAKER_15]: I see you kind of lurking over there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Any FUs of the week that you have?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I tried saying it into a microphone so that our listeners can hear.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yummy brownies?
[SPEAKER_15]: There's yummy brownies?
[SPEAKER_15]: Where's the yummy brownies?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get to the chatroom FUs, shall we?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dark Knight would like to say F you to early morning shifts during the holidays and an F you to people I work with for they are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they're supposed to be salesmen for the love of Mike.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sakurina says, F you to Konami of Hawaii, you whores, for removing the fuck from Guideka.
[SPEAKER_15]: How dare you, it sounds like shit now that you shitheads get the fuck out of my life.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to lame puns, since that's all I do.
[SPEAKER_15]: And yeah, F you to my mom for switching from OSX to Windows, what the fuck is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_15]: And F you to Loki for saying women can't drive SUVs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Truth hurts, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not as much as a woman hitting you with her SUV.
[SPEAKER_15]: If you read the article that I posted on the site, you would see that I said the exact same thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: But they're saying that it's coming back in March.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, well that means it's discontinued until March.
[SPEAKER_15]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_15]: Touch.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tomokun would also like to say, fuck Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well said.
[SPEAKER_15]: NintendoManiac64 says, F you to my DS's L button.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't play some of my GBA games on my DS efficiently now.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Mario Kart DS disconnectors that disconnect at the end of races.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to my parents who don't really trust ordering things online at all.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now how else am I supposed to use this PlayStation DDR pad when I don't even have a PS2?
[SPEAKER_15]: Besides, Step Mania isn't that fun without a pad.
[SPEAKER_15]: ProPanda21 says, F you to bras that break and stab you with their wires of evil.
[SPEAKER_15]: And to really bad foo-poo jokes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sephiroth1215 says, F you to Dead or Alive 4 being pushed back another two weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, what do you expect?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's F box.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um... F you to the shitty name MPQ and not being able to think of anything better, so I have to use Mil-Fu-Lu-Li.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to go into the arcade and not getting to play 2DX.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkTetsuya says, one last F you to AOL.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can't say I'll miss any of the following.
[SPEAKER_15]: The random disconnects, the out of memory errors, and the constant lockups.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have actually one more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you to Xbox 360 for freezing.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know they say only 3% of Xbox 360s is supposed to be doing that.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're lucky.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're a liar.
[SPEAKER_15]: You're a winner.
[SPEAKER_15]: Message to Zaku says, F you to getting up this morning to go to the supermarket only to leave without buying something.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to finals starting this week and F you to having to hold off buying my new hard drive until after the holidays because of my tight financial situation.
[SPEAKER_15]: Illusion says, F you to the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_15]: Baja and Bug, the only good thing that can come out of Christmas is Mystery Science Theater 3000 DVD sets.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Jolly Tidings.
[SPEAKER_15]: Pow, right in the kisser.
[SPEAKER_15]: Roz says, F you to my city for installing some newfangled traffic thing right before Christmas at the mall entrance.
[SPEAKER_15]: People are like, la la la, pulling in.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh shit, there's only one lane now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also, F you to the Java IRC chat because it made me late getting to the chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Neo Dude says, F you to Nintendo Wi-Fi connection because I can't connect to a WPA protected network with a DS.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now I have to buy the USB connector for $35.
[SPEAKER_15]: Big Power says, F you to the yearly December break that many TV shows go on when they have a long break with no new episodes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want my Lost and Prison break.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, and watch 24 when it comes back on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Goggle says, F the whole college application process.
[SPEAKER_15]: And F back pain.
[SPEAKER_15]: GS-191 says F you to my workplace for playing that damn Rent song over and over and over again last week.
[SPEAKER_15]: At least they were playing Daft Punk's Technologic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now we're playing sucky Christmas music now with crappy pop remixes.
[SPEAKER_15]: A late F you to Black Friday and stupid customers ask me where are the iPods, GPS, random shit when I'm in the fucking printer aisle.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you see any fucking iPods here?
[SPEAKER_15]: Look at the fucking map we gave you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Xander C says, F you to Jamie's lame jokes.
[SPEAKER_15]: You need to trout slap him.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Slap.
[SPEAKER_15]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Sky not picking up my Skype call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, buddy, I pick them up as they're coming in.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to the weather here in Florida not being cold yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to having back problems.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to bunches of stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate that bunches of stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bronchan says, F you to me for still being unemployed and still looking for a job.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn, I needs me some cash.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, F you to people who haven't paid me for fixing their computers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will upload a virus to your machine.
[SPEAKER_15]: And lastly, Spiritsnare would like to say an F you to Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Rent because it has some of the most addicting songs I've ever heard on their soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_15]: F you to Final Fantasy Potions because they probably will never make it over here except at anime conventions.
[SPEAKER_15]: Also an F you to...
[SPEAKER_15]: at $30 and not $20, even though they're not decent ports.
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn, you bitches are angsty tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, wow, wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room has turned into bra chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_15]: And what kind of things have we learned about bras?
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently underwear keeps you from being droopy like grandma when you're old.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I'm glad that my underwear does not have metal wires in it because that might be painful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Worst invention ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, but I do recall from, you know, I used to date girls and sometimes we'd get, you know, we'd get... Shut up!
[SPEAKER_15]: Why is everybody laughing at that?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, we used to sometimes get a little freaky and I used to... Going shopping with a girl and your girlfriend doesn't mean you're dating them.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_15]: I actually, I used to take girls' bras off and I remember it was a pain in the ass to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like, it's... You need... That was the sign right there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously!
[SPEAKER_15]: That's how I knew I was gay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was like, fuck this bra shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just gonna suck dick.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not that hard when you figure it out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just, you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: You can get to the point where you can just look at a broad and it pops up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Look, I give up easy.
[SPEAKER_15]: I give up easy, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm a quitter.
[SPEAKER_15]: I take the lazy way out.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: What's so damn funny?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob is more interested in putting them on than taking them off.
[SPEAKER_15]: No way.
[SPEAKER_15]: Take that both ways if you want.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, that is the gay stereotype I do not do, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Every gay person I know fits into some gay stereotype.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's some gay stereotype.
[SPEAKER_15]: Even Shane.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: What was that one time at the other apartment when I came back from the pool and there was people wearing bras with water balloon or condom breasts?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_15]: That was my surprise birthday party.
[SPEAKER_15]: There was a dress involved.
[SPEAKER_15]: I didn't wear a bra.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a bitch and hoe party and that was the whole theme.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just hoping you wasn't getting, like, hot and bothered off of it, that's all.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, you weren't wearing a bra.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell no, I was the pimp of the party.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody else was the bitch and hoe.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't understand how you can, like, teach, you know, PPOs and HMOs and all that complicated crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't talk about it!
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't unhook three little hooks from a bra.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, like, seriously?
[SPEAKER_15]: If the girls I used to date would have, like, the 20-hook bra?
[SPEAKER_15]: The 20 hook bras.
[SPEAKER_15]: Were they grandmas or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like you liked older women?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dating gorillas?
[SPEAKER_15]: No!
[SPEAKER_15]: I was dating very nice women that had bras with 20 hooks on them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, in some respects that might not be a bad thing since that involves Damon Auburn.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, stop it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So 20 hooks, were they monkey people or something?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it was a complicated bra.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would like you to meet my wonderful friend... They need to make bra... You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: Why don't they make... Here's a novel concept.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why don't they make what?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, no, let me finish.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why don't they make a bra out of Velcro?
[SPEAKER_15]: Wouldn't that be easy?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just rip, and there we go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because Velcro doesn't hold for shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, then, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I know some girls on the Itty Bitty Titty Committee who they would work just fine for.
[SPEAKER_15]: But that's the whole point.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, the fact that you wouldn't mind pulling the bra off of an Itty Bitty Titty Committee applicant shows that you're gay, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, you had a comment?
[SPEAKER_05]: I completely forgot what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I know, well, you shouldn't have dated girls who were girdles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe in my mind, maybe they weren't really 20 hooks, but in my mind, I've gone back.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I'm having nightmares of the bras.
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember looking at the back and it's like these big teeth.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't you dare touch me!
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob has braphobia.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: He has those dreams where it's really abstract.
[SPEAKER_11]: He looks at it and the hooks go down towards the horizon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Never ending bra strap.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's like my hell.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like, here, do you want to get into the gates of heaven?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just unhook the door that's very similar to a bra.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_15]: And then you have sex with women and oh man, that's crazy hell.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, anyway, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't like all this talk about me and my bra thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just writing my movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, your movie?
[SPEAKER_15]: What's your movie?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you want to plug your movie?
[SPEAKER_15]: The Life of Rob.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what people do on shows is they plug things.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you have a movie coming out you want to promote?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you don't?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you writing one?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you want to pitch one?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: We have important people listening to this program.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like my mother.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, that was something that listeners couldn't see, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bad radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_15]: And of course now our chat room just suddenly fills up with all this chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bra, bra, bra, bra, bra, bra, bra, bra, bra.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, but bra, bra, bra, bra, bra.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we were talking about bras before we got on the verbal topic.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Something related to video gaming.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I didn't have anything.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was just going to say, very rare bear.
[SPEAKER_14]: Love the inside joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least it's not cake pie.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do a break, and then we're going to come back.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to come back, and we're going to do some Skype.
[SPEAKER_15]: Skype at you, coming at you.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then Ask Orange Lounge, because we know you want to ask us some questions.
[SPEAKER_15]: And therefore, we want to give you some answers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does that sound like a plan?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm like, Jesus, I hope you're with my heart
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio, Mamani Music, and more
[SPEAKER_15]: R2-D2 Princess Leia
[SPEAKER_15]: That is so cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: Like when I push it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, bun-headed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Show it on the wall.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's Princess Leia with a bun.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is so badass.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I have lots of drugs.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I have like the most awesome keychain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, cell phone strap.
[SPEAKER_15]: What is that now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have Prince.
[SPEAKER_15]: From Katamari Damashii.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_15]: Now you just need the ringtones and then you'd be a total addict there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I can get those or midis.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's go to a call.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Who dis?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's the one and only Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's up, fellas?
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, Ron Chan.
[SPEAKER_15]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just want to point out, though, DarkSakura is not a fella.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have that effect on women.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've seen you hanging with the ladies, Ron.
[SPEAKER_15]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just a couple.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, no, I don't know where I'm going with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway... I don't think it would be possible to mistake me for a dude since I have humongous boobs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Does your bra have 20 hooks on it?
[SPEAKER_15]: That's...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Rob, just three.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: What about Velcro?
[SPEAKER_15]: What do you think of... Never mind, forget it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rob, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still addicted to Mario Kart DS.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you actually find friends online to play against?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I never do, unless I set it up on Instant Messenger.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the only way.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I'm in a chat room with a bunch of us, that's how we do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And even half the time, we can't even race each other.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, because you don't find each other on the game or something?
[SPEAKER_15]: Or what?
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't find each other.
[SPEAKER_10]: One time it was like five of us.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were going to try to get at least four of us in a race.
[SPEAKER_10]: It turned out to be me and two people.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or me and one person.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_15]: So it can't find your friends or something?
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe the lag was too great or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: What lag?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I do this at work and the router's like six feet behind me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what to tell you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not too worried about it, but I can say this.
[SPEAKER_10]: With my DS, I found plenty of wireless networks around my neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was at Rice Princess and Lanky Styles' apartment not that long ago, and I tapped into a wireless network near them, and that made me feel like an elite hacker.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was stealing bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_15]: I could go to jail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I call it sharing the wealth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you going to be getting Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe in a couple of weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, when you get it, you, me, bike racks, 3 o'clock, bring your bug net.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's on.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bring it.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's already been brought in, my friend.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: One thing from last week, you were talking about Captain Con.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went to Captain Con and we got snowed in for two days.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I get snowed in at this crazy convention in D.C., which I will be going to, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have the time approved off work.
[SPEAKER_15]: All I have to do is get a plane ticket, which are very affordable right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I'm going to be booking that sometime this week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just need to discuss travel arrangements with you, my friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure, no problem.
[SPEAKER_15]: If I get snowed in, I'm going to cry.
[SPEAKER_15]: I am from California.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've lived in California my entire life.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't do snow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Do you know this?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have never, this is going to be a crazy concept to some of you people.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have never seen snow falling from the sky in person.
[SPEAKER_15]: Never.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have and that was in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've never seen snow falling from the sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was like way down south in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was in Mobile.
[SPEAKER_15]: I've seen snow once.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's already on the ground.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not that hard to drive up to Reno and see some snow here where we live.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I've never seen snow fall from the sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: Every time it's happened in Sacramento, like the two times this ever happens since I've been alive, I was either asleep or the one other time it ever happened, I was doing an internet radio show, believe it or not, at the old college station.
[SPEAKER_15]: Crazy, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to have to get a wee now.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, it better not snow because I don't know what to do.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will cry like a little girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, what'll happen is they'll shut down the airport and get out a day later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, I will poop myself if that happens.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know how to deal with that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't do flight delays.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: That happened to a bunch of West Coast guys that came to CapsuleCon 9 two years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop scaring me!
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, we gotta go.
[SPEAKER_15]: We gotta take more calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll be there, friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: We gotta take more calls.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you're freaking me out.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm gonna have nightmares tonight about snow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Take care, my friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, there he is.
[SPEAKER_15]: He's back now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello, you are on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bienvenidos a Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: What is on your mind, my friend?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, dang.
[SPEAKER_19]: First off, who the hell is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: Who is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: Finally, we have the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Xander from Florida.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, hi, Xander from Florida.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I don't know if this is the right show to do, but I wanted to bring up the Nintendo Revolution not supporting HDTV thingy real quick.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, sure.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, um, basically I think the reason they're doing it is, um, well for one reason, because they're using standard DVDs, I think it's not really smart to be, uh, doing HD.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because, I mean, you're seeing with the, uh, Xbox 360 with, um, Oblivion, or, yeah, Oblivion, it's like gonna take up four discs or something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's one thing, another thing is the cost.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, it's just going to be a ridiculous cost to small developers to try to put HD in their games.
[SPEAKER_15]: I somewhat agree with you.
[SPEAKER_15]: I also think the reason why they're not doing it is because Loki has me convinced that the revolution is the fact that there is going to be stereoscopic 3D.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they just don't want to do that for HDTV.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would cost too much.
[SPEAKER_19]: I heard you say that too.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know if they're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think that would cost too much.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think it would fit in their $200 price range thingy.
[SPEAKER_15]: If they have a good development kit, all you need is 3D World Runner all over again.
[SPEAKER_15]: Rad Racer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can somebody explain to me what the fuck the point was of 3D and Rad Racer?
[SPEAKER_15]: It did like nothing for that game.
[SPEAKER_15]: 3D and Rad Racer did nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was so rad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: You bring up some good points.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I, owning an HDTV, it makes me sad that Nintendo is not supporting it.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, if they're doing it for cost reasons...
[SPEAKER_15]: and if they're doing it for these other reasons that they plan to do more crazy shit with their system, I'm okay with it, but remember the golden rule, a system is only a good game.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow, we've got the whole internet saying that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's the other thing also, just because they say they're not supporting HD does not mean that the
[SPEAKER_14]: It just means they're not supporting the formats of HD, you know, the aspect ratios and stuff, so it could be something completely different also.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe they'll still support progressive scan and widescreen.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe they'll support 480, what would that be, 480p.
[SPEAKER_15]: 480, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's some pretty good looking games at 480p.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe you're right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe the fact that they're not doing HDTV means they're not going to support 1080p or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: As long as my games can have some widescreen in it and some progressive...
[SPEAKER_15]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some progressive scan, some widescreen.
[SPEAKER_15]: That would be kind of cool, but I'm not going to hold my breath with Nintendo here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they're supposed to announce more... Did you hear that they have another big secret, apparently?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, that it's stereoscopic 3D.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, they're saying... They're saying... There's... Mario Mato did another speech...
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah, yeah, I heard, I read somewhere that Miyamoto did another speech.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, just to add to your argument, somebody posted this on LJ and I saw this.
[SPEAKER_15]: Miyamoto did another speech and said there's a, there's another secret coming that you kids don't know about, so just you wait for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Everyone thinks it's about the controller because he was talking about the controller at the time, but I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's, it's still the SiriusXP3 thing.
[SPEAKER_15]: What did he say about the controller?
[SPEAKER_15]: What else could they say about the controller?
[SPEAKER_15]: That you're going to use it in the stereoscopic 3D games.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe you're on to something.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: And maybe we're fucking idiots.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see soon enough.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it's fun to imagine, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we will.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be first in line.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hopefully they won't kick us out.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to let you go, buddy.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got to get to the next segment, alright?
[SPEAKER_15]: But thank you for your input.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_15]: You too.
[SPEAKER_15]: Later.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I apologize to those folks we didn't get to on Skype.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll get to you guys next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: Promise.
[SPEAKER_15]: But we promised the chatters we'd get to some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: So therefore, that's what we're going to do right now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_15]: What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe we'll find out how to unhook a bra or maybe not.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't want to finish that thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: You rhymed anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sakurina says, I want to plug DSMeet.com, which is a DS Friends code sharing site that Loki joined, apparently.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, is this true?
[SPEAKER_15]: Are these allegations true?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but I haven't visited the site since, and I was bored.
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought our buddy BigRedPimp started his own thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, and you know what's funny is because I couldn't log into that thing at all because it was broken.
[SPEAKER_15]: Email him and tell him he'll fix it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_15]: He loves you.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, Sakurina wants to know, am I the only one to think Snow by Ram when you guys talk about Snow?
[SPEAKER_15]: And I say no, you're probably not the only one to think about that song.
[SPEAKER_15]: However, that does make you a loser.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hearts, love ya.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sephiroth1215 says, What do you think is the most overrated DDR song?
[SPEAKER_15]: I say Butterfly, says Sephiroth1215.
[SPEAKER_15]: Most overrated DDR song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maxx300, hands down.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hands down, Maxx300.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'd have to agree.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maxx300.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
Huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Most overrated DDR song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Overrated DDR song, Max period.
[SPEAKER_15]: We all said Max's.
[SPEAKER_15]: And will you be my Animal Crossing friend?
[SPEAKER_15]: Only if you let me abuse your town folk.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to leave signs in your town.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and let us paint your town.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll paint your town gay.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to come gay up your town.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to give you a makeover, girlfriend!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to put up signs that just have bras on them.
[SPEAKER_15]: That should be the new Orange Lounge logo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really hope that the town lesbian comes back.
[SPEAKER_15]: By the way, I want to say just in time for Christmas, because I don't know why bras make me think of this, but the Orange Lounge t-shirt is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got a company to say they'd do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we're going to talk about that later.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Illusion wants to know, what do you think is truly, truly, truly outrageous?
[SPEAKER_15]: Jem and the Holograms or the Misfits?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not the punk band, the original Misfits.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would say, you know, Jem was the shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: The Misfits were just a bunch of fucking wannabes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except the Misfits had Jetta later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she played a black saxophone.
[SPEAKER_15]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't get cooler than that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_14]: Jem or the Misfits?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think her show sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, I think you smell like butt.
[SPEAKER_15]: Spirit Snare would like to know, what is the meaning of life, the universe, and everything to the X?
[SPEAKER_02]: Forty-two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Purple.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's forty-two, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the whole purpose of the Earth, was to calculate the meaning of life, and it's forty-two.
[SPEAKER_15]: Purple.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_15]: The meaning of life.
[SPEAKER_15]: is to listen to Orange Launch Radio every Sunday night at 6.30 Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, Jesus Christ, Rene just reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have any of the hosts had a memorable moment, oh, this is from Rene, playing any DDR or music game in front of a crowd of sorts?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have an alter ego known as Dr. Dick that does improv freestyle at some tournaments and got quite a big crowd at Pier 39 doing, what song did I do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Was it Cowgirl I did at that one?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, the first time was this Raining Men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Was it Shaft 2 or something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Shaft.
[SPEAKER_15]: And the second time Dr. Dick came out was doing Cowgirl at B3 is what it was called.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I'm the one involving you.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was one of the first times I met you.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was at the Sacramento's Cosplay and Tournament, and you did your routine dynamite rave, like, and you were dressed up all night.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah, I completely forgot.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you fucking failed.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's because I forgot my steps.
[SPEAKER_15]: You started dancing and you were like getting down and doing the whole thing and then you were like, like you froze from it and you were like, aw shit.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then you failed.
[SPEAKER_15]: That wasn't like one of the first times you... I was like, that guy rocks.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it was.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was later on.
[SPEAKER_15]: But this was pre-OLR.
[SPEAKER_15]: This was pre-OLR.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, do you have any?
[SPEAKER_15]: I can think of one.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was you and me, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let Doing Stomp to My Beat and Beating Each Other with the Orange Bats and Little Plastic Trumpets
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_15]: Catamaris
[SPEAKER_15]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And who won the cage match?
[SPEAKER_15]: Is the thing he reminded me of.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh yeah, you guys want to know who won a cage match tonight, huh?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I completely forgot to mention it a little bit ago.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tonight's cage match wiener is by, I think this is by one vote.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes, by only one vote.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Let's face it, you've missed her from DDR, that's why you let her win.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for reminding me, Renee.
[SPEAKER_15]: God, if it wasn't for you, the show would be ruined.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ron Chan wants to know, will you be doing some freestyling at KatsuCon?
[SPEAKER_15]: Ron Chan, since you asked, I will bring the hat and the garb, and Dr. Dick will make an appearance.
[SPEAKER_15]: NintendoManiac64 says, why are you guys so awesome?
[SPEAKER_15]: I found a torrent for Japanese that took 46 hours to download and I already know some sentences.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_15]: This person is making me read Japanese.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's not fair.
[SPEAKER_15]: Remember, Spanish.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think I was close.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where?
[SPEAKER_15]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Starting right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am Japanese... Japanese... What's Nihondo?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, I think he meant, why did I type that with a D when it should have been a G?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I am Japanese... Okay, it's supposed to be S-U-K-O...
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to say Skoshee.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I need to correct you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Nintendo Maniac, what he really wants to know, is a Mario Kart DS online record of 199 wins and 34 losses good?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, but it means you do need to go outside more often.
[SPEAKER_15]: Maybe race a real car.
[SPEAKER_15]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_15]: Question for Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can I race you in Mario Kart DS again?
[SPEAKER_15]: I remember that you're anti-snaking.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_15]: I guess if I'm on.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Jada2005, what is the best metal DDR pad?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I want to get one for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_15]: Red Octane's Afterburner, honestly.
[SPEAKER_15]: Roz, why wouldn't the Java IRC client work?
[SPEAKER_15]: I couldn't get into it and it made me late for the show chat.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know because that's done by another company, but I'll look into it and see if it's just you or if it breaks for us too.
[SPEAKER_15]: And if it breaks for us too, then we'll have to spank it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sephiroth 1215, by the way, had a follow-up.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay if we want to visit his village, but please don't gay it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Legend of Zaku says, how come mainstream youth media outlets such as MTV only care about rap and sports games?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because that, unfortunately, is what the people are buying, and if the people stop buying that shit, they will not promote it anymore, is my thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because of cock.
[SPEAKER_15]: Very, very Margaret Cho gay.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't have anything like that that I can find on demand.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week, honey, next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then play the first one.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: You got it.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what would be perfect for that?
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: It would be Hooray for Boobies.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hooray for Boobies would be a good one, but I don't have that.
[SPEAKER_15]: We got more questions, kids.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know we don't have that song from Beaches where Bette Midler was singing the origination of the bird?
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you ever know that you're mine here?
[SPEAKER_05]: The...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Over-the-Shoulder Boulder Holder.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember when she was singing about... Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_15]: About... Somehow you have outgayed me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otto Titzlinger.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have no idea what Titzlinger was.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well played, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well played.
[SPEAKER_15]: You have outgayed me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just my favorite song in that movie.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright, question from DarkTetsuya.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have you seen the Carl's Jr.
[SPEAKER_15]: Milkshake commercial and do you find it ironic that they used Get Busy since they had the DDR promotion last month?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, that and Let's See.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I can't... Look, why would you use... Why would you use that song when there is the completely more obvious song that you use in your milkshake commercial?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because most people listen to... Wait, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: E. Carl's Jr.
[SPEAKER_15]: See?
[SPEAKER_15]: I should produce commercials.
[SPEAKER_15]: I forgot about the DDR promotion last month.
[SPEAKER_09]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Goggles says, what is your favorite Christmas song?
[SPEAKER_15]: My favorite Christmas song is Little Drummer Boy because I get to say pa rum pa pum pum.
[SPEAKER_15]: I also, Grandma Got Run Over by a Reindeer.
[SPEAKER_15]: Close second.
[SPEAKER_05]: My favorite one is Dancing Around in Women's Underwear.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_14]: Christmas at Ground Zero.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I also like The Night Santa Went Crazy.
[SPEAKER_15]: Last one, last one.
[SPEAKER_15]: NeoDude0 wants to know, do any of you play Magic the Gathering?
I used to.
[SPEAKER_15]: I used to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had, like, all blackboarded cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were betas and alphas.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still have my 4th edition stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but I don't play it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can play sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd!
[SPEAKER_15]: Sometimes late at night you take them out and you tickle yourself with them.
[SPEAKER_15]: I need to tap my mana.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need another thrall token.
[SPEAKER_04]: Swarm me.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least I didn't say Felden's cane.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need me an acid manipulator.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hate this show.
[SPEAKER_15]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's going to do it because I hate this show.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're going to finish up and put the nail in the proverbial coffin of this program.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you folks for listening.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll be back next week with more of the same shit that you know and love.
[SPEAKER_15]: Final thought time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Angel, I hope you had a good show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And good people came over and it was all good.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's your final thought, my dear?
[SPEAKER_04]: Must get that job.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Good luck, my friend.
[SPEAKER_15]: Loki, final thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: Must eat more brownies.
[SPEAKER_15]: Stop stuffing your face with brownies.
[SPEAKER_15]: How much weight have you gained since The Biggest Gainer started?
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't checked.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't done weigh-ins in weeks.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, Extover's not here.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've been uber-sick.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: So we'll do another weigh-in next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I win anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope that I'm over the plague soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the final, the really, really major thing is reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_15]: My final thought is Velcro bras, the wave of the future.
That's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: One word, one word to sum it all up.
[SPEAKER_15]: The final word of the show, the nail in the coffin.
[SPEAKER_15]: It is Angel's birthday.
[SPEAKER_15]: I will let her have the final word.
[SPEAKER_15]: What is it, my friend?
[SPEAKER_15]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brownie!
[SPEAKER_20]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_20]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_20]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Manamana Manamana Manamana Manamana Manamana Manamana Manamana
[SPEAKER_07]: Manamana Manamana Manamana
Manamana Manamana Manamana Manamana
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_15]: We're now going to cut the wire here and send you back to Bomani Music and Video Game Music.
[SPEAKER_15]: Goodness.
[SPEAKER_15]: Have a happy week.
[SPEAKER_15]: We'll see you next Sunday.