[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, July 12, 2009, can piracy lead to malware on your DS?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Tomb Raider franchise looks ready for a reboot, and could you soon play Rock Band or Guitar Hero with no gaming console?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, Internet, and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here to do it with you guys every week is myself, Rob Roberts, and my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me tonight, the one and only Techmaster Loki in the house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Doing good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And DarkSakura is joining us a little bit late.
[SPEAKER_05]: She is in her summer class right now, and as you know, she's been having to join us late for some of the shows because she has some type of outdoor activity she has to do, some type of PE class, so she, I think, some type of...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Phone lines 1-877-GAME-OLR Our email bag, mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com It's not just about us, it's about you guys We are the place where every gamer has a voice Anyhow, it's been a fun week, I hope, for you guys out there Just another summer week for those of you folks that are on a break from school or what have you I hope you're making the most of it and getting some good gaming time in We're going to start off the show tonight as we always do, talking about our gaming weeks a little bit Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just playing Grand Theft Auto 4, just still tweaking the editing to make sure everything's balanced.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was creating one weapon that's basically a nuke, and it wasn't getting to the size that a nuke should be, or at least, you know, relatively in scale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, if I actually created a full-size nuke in the game, that would kind of be pointless since it would destroy the entire map.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: I want something a little bit bigger than say 20 square feet or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm working on making that a little bit bigger.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think I figured out a way to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's funny because we just can't stop giggling once we fire that and the whole screen gets really this big bright green glow and everything like explodes and it's funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, the game has gotten so ridiculous now that it's just an absolute blast and really kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: Not resembling Grand Theft Auto anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: You talk a lot about your Grand Theft Auto playing on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we all kind of have the grasp that you do this on your lunch break at work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lunch break and our 15-minute break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, so it's all gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, for those folks that are new to Orange Lingerie and maybe haven't listened before, Loki works in game distribution.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he literally, for eight hours a day, kind of eats, lives, sleeps video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not as glamorous.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not even.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wild Dark Sakura is approaching.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quick, throw the pester ball.
[SPEAKER_05]: She just got out of the shower.
[SPEAKER_05]: She'll be joining us in just a moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: She came in to make faces in the studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You play actual video games on your lunch break to decompress and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: The guys you play with, are they all also game salesmen?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the deal?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: One way or another, they sort of are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, before we used to have a mix, we had just all of our game reps playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right now, we have myself, my friend Jason, who actually moved into the games department, so now he's a game sales rep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our friend Rob Nelson, who's in our video sales department, but way back in the day, he was actually in game sales, and he likes games, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then my boss, Rob, who's also...
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, so you play video games on lunch with your boss?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your job ain't so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, but I kick the crap out of him.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish I could play, like, Grand Theft Auto with my boss.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the thing is... Of course, I don't think she really plays video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But see, now, you know, because we play on the consoles that I own, I've modded all those consoles, so now I can take...
[SPEAKER_06]: An image of Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, I have bought copies, so I guess sort of it's legal, because I do actually own enough copies for all the systems, and I actually have lost and damned on all the systems, so that's pretty expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, so we actually do play their modified copies of Grand Theft Auto 4, but we play with our own rule set, and you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Video Capture Device
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's nuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Overseas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Naughty, naughty, but no, we appreciate the support either way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just don't get fired over Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, we'd have some folks that would listen, and I know they were using JustinTV to do it, so... And some folks, for whatever weird reason, like to look at us while we're doing this.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we would also, like, play video games, usually during the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know towards the end there, before the summer months, we would, like, kind of show games before they were actually out, because Loki is also a crazy import gamer, and would get a lot of games from Japan that he can play on his Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: or we're going to go back to studio my place and the place that's there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So either way, we're looking at getting a more intricate setup with Justin TV where we're going to have a switchboard where we can go between like a shot of us in studio, a shot of the game we're playing, maybe something that's a zoom in on the guest or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of some multi-camera angles, believe it or not, should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is hopefully in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, I didn't mean to derail your gaming week, Loki, but I don't know if you have anything else.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deathwishing says I should make a gun that shoots fish.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't do that, unfortunately, in Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can make guns that shoot a lot of things, but fish is not one of those things.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw is asking why not Studio Loki if it exists?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I just think with babies on the way, Studio Loki is not really going to be a viable option.
[SPEAKER_05]: Plus, I don't think you have really any extra space there.
[SPEAKER_06]: A middle bedroom, but it's kind of...
[SPEAKER_06]: Small.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, so is this space.
[SPEAKER_05]: We make this work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, actually, it would be bigger than this space.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Studio Loki is always a possibility in a situation where one of us is going to be gone or something, but especially once Loki has the kids there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will have an HDTV in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: The wife keeps saying that I can't put it in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, well, you have to put it in our bedroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, well, I don't have cable blocks for that, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura is toweling off from the shower.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, she's wearing nothing but a towel right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Too bad that we don't have that, JustinTV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, she's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's wearing very unglamorous sweatpants and a DDR Spot t-shirt.
[SPEAKER_03]: These aren't sweatpants.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are actually comfortable man pajamas.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: From a distance, they look like sweatpants.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I was actually going to say, we actually had another idea about doing some rearranging that would involve opening up a whole wall in this room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that would give us, in fact, it was actually almost specifically for us using this as a studio full time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we would be making some more room in here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're actually thinking about moving the pinballs into that room and moving our living room into the pinball room.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for that sake, that actually moves the subwoofer from away from that back wall so that we're not getting, oh, and by the way, Sega did BOOM!
[SPEAKER_05]: I look forward to the week where Sega does BOOM!
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be a great video game, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just call it Boom!
[SPEAKER_05]: With an explanation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Copyright Orange Jones Radio 2009.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't had a dream game in a long time called Boom.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just needs to be called Subwoofer Noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, my little brother, Phillip, so cute when he was little, then he grew up, what happened?
[SPEAKER_03]: He used to call it the Hoover Darn, because dam was a bad word.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because dam's a bad word, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, so I sort of inherited calling it the Hoover Darn.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, we went to the Hoover Dam, and it was hot, and there was water.
[SPEAKER_05]: I took pictures of said water.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God you're here, because I would have never known that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, where the hell is my IRC?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, we got lots of frozen yogurt, and I had a few very cool new experiences and met cool people that I had heard of but never got to see, so it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a very good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, did you meet OLR listeners?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or were these, like, other people?
[SPEAKER_03]: Other people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I went to go see Sauce.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, because tiara friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: and I had really a great, great time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was very relaxing to watch the first season of Dexter.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And watch the first season of True Blood.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that show too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I finally got to see Repo the Genetic Opera.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, I love Anthony Head in that.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's just like, oh!
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Repo in general.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's the only thing I've seen Sarah Brightman in that her voice hasn't irritated me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, she's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, if you've listened to the show for any length of time, or I guess I should say a long time, you know that I've been involved with Rocky Horror Picture Show for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Repo really is kind of like a lot like it, in a sense, where it's that very glamorous musical type thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I love Repo.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really do enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to have to pick that up on Blu-ray so I can watch it in all the HD glory.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have an extra copy on Blu-ray if you want to buy one cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I got an extra one for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you're interested in it, let me know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm interested in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also actually did a little bit of gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually bought some games that we never got to play.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I got my SNES emulator running on Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I played some of the game that we'll be talking about later.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see, so we're going to have an inspired Classic Game of the Week this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we will.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's not Captain America and the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did purchase that, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan and I did when I got back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goldanthro in our chatroom at chat.orangelearnsradio.com put, Lol, my mom is watching True Blood right now in my family's living room.
[SPEAKER_05]: No joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: She loves that show.
[SPEAKER_03]: God, that show's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: True Blood is also a trending topic on Twitter right now, I noticed, as I'm checking the ULR account.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it must be a good show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never watched it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just something you'll have to watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's its own type of... It's like vampires and stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but it's vampires going public.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got a lot of human rights parallels and different things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So like Heroes, but with vampires?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't watch Heroes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of lost on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we also saw Drag Me to Hell.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we paid $2 a piece for it, so it was well worth the money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, it was like, I think either that or The Hangover, and I hate stupid type of- Buddy comedies?
[SPEAKER_03]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really don't like this kind of movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: And while other people may love them to death, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying that your taste is awful, I'm just saying that's not my kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, but, going to see a Sam Raimi movie, you know, how can you go wrong with Sam Raimi?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's dying to say something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just going to say what I saw this week too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw Transformers, Revenge of the Fallen, and Bruno.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I never have I seen so many people walk out of Bruno.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm iffy on Bruno because I have this bad feeling I'm going to get really offended even though I usually find that kind of stuff funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm waiting for Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pink Penguin and a Tutu
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure how to take this because, you know, sure, I'm gay or whatever, but I like to think I'm still a guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you like penguins.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do love penguins.
[SPEAKER_03]: I should tell you why it made me think of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because of Rocky.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: When he did the cell block pingo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, that was so many years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you were wearing the little pink thing too.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you're not helping my whole manly man case here, so you wouldn't mind telling us about the rest of your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you like penguins.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it wasn't... Don't jump to conclusions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a lot of pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: We went to the Pinball Hall of Fame.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was in pain by the time we were done, but it was well worth the agony.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the worst pinball table ever, and it's also one of the most rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played pinball circus.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's worth playing once, but it's crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's probably why they only made two of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually went and played a really good Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, I've got the table, but ours is kind of messed up.
[SPEAKER_03]: So playing on our messed up table here helped my skills on the really nice table there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Tiara and I took turns, sort of, on the longest multi-ball session ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: of Star Trek The Next Generation.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I played the Data East Star Trek pinball.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played... I did not play Captain Fantastic, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I did play Theater of Magic.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I played Medieval Madness.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Super Mario Brothers pinball table.
[SPEAKER_03]: The adult one, not the child one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I played Bride of Pinbot and Pinbot.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't have a jackpot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wandered around the place twice looking for a jackpot, but they didn't have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, where is this place?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I missed that part.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Pinball Hall of Fame.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we drove by the Liberace Museum.
[SPEAKER_03]: And all I could think of was, my mom would like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go to the Pinball Hall of Fame Go to the Pinball Hall of Fame
[SPEAKER_03]: and you have to eat at this place that Tiara took me to called, I think it's Toto's.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like a margarita brunch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know I'm going to go visit Sauce if I'm there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not on the strip.
[SPEAKER_03]: We avoided the strip like plague.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'll make Sauce take us out to all the nice places.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a very, very good time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got woken up by a kitten a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan in the Bed
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, DVDs!
[SPEAKER_03]: So it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I had a great time, and I have to thank her and her family for putting up with me for the time I was there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had a great time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm glad you had fun in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now I know all the good stuff I need to go do, hopefully, if I go visit before the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's just making his schedule work and my schedule work because he's going to art school now.
[SPEAKER_05]: He starts art school Monday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, he's... You're going to have to forget that whole manly man thing I was mentioning earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's studying to be an interior designer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to sit down and talk with him.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so supportive.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would actually love to sit down and talk with him about fabric for a project I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: He would probably love to talk that shop, especially once he's had some of his classes down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, enough about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me talk about the stuff that I've been doing this week in regards to video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played pretty much two video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went back to play Final Fantasy IV The After Years because, as you know, I beat the main scenario, but now there's all the spin-off scenarios, so I actually beat the Rydia scenario, which...
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you were playing an outline?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the main story felt there were more twists and things that made it interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love, love the twist at the end of the main story because it involves introducing a new class to the game, which I love the idea of, and I hope one shows up in Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to spoil it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you really want to know, go play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's a new class.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a combination of two existing classes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'll have to tell me off the air because I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will.
[SPEAKER_05]: LOST ODYSSEY
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, I love Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am about caught up to where I was before, which is where I'm right at the end of the first disc, and I've got three more discs to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you'll probably be hearing about this game over the next month or so as I play a little more each week to try and beat it, because I want to see what happens at the end of the story, because I never played that far before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got sucked into raiding and wow, or moved on to another game, because I think it came out during a busy period.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly Overlooked RPG on the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why haters hated it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I think maybe they hated it because in some ways it's kind of linear and a little more restrictive.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the more Final Fantasy X style of there's no world map, but you go to select areas and the areas are their own little maps, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still enjoy the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, uh, yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that was pretty much my game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really just those two games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't play anything new new that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: No new Xbox Live Arcade games or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even remember what came out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was this a big week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard now, I heard that Madballs game is out next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know where I heard that?
[SPEAKER_05]: On a Facebook ad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft in chatroom asks Will Rob finish the game or will his gamer ADD kick in the middle of the game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to OLR
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkCharger in chat says those dream sequences in Lost Odyssey were one of the best things about the game it's too bad none of them were actually visualized or maybe that was a good thing
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think in some ways those stories were best left to the imagination.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like reading a book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do you read a book?
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can make up your own visualizations.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the cool thing about it was that it did things that books can't do with the text and the music and the backgrounds that you would see and the shifts in the backgrounds that did add some visual impact, but without showing you what people look like.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like deep thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: In a way, it was, but you make it sound so stupid, and I'm sorry, it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haters gonna hate, I don't even care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, before we get into some gaming news tonight and gaming discussion, we want to take care of some housekeeping, of which we don't have a whole lot of right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: No shows off in the near future or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still no idea what's going on for PAX, if anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think both Loki and DarkSakura are out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I sadly may have to skip it, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to though, I'm still going to try and make it work.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the week right after my crazy week in Reno that I have planned.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, crazy crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm still hoping to do PAX, I should know in the next couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I would love to see you guys at PAX if that happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, we'll keep you posted here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Join our Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've been getting some ads this week and really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then of course we have our live journal community at Orange Lounge and our Facebook group, the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I would plug MySpace too, but does anyone really use that anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, start us off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, there is a big ol' rumor, or possibly leak, I guess, of a relaunch of the Tomb Raider series.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now I know you're thinking, hey, wait a second, didn't that already happen?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it did.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey, let's relaunch it again, because, you know, the first relaunch didn't quite work out for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: It is oddly deserted, and an uneasy feeling settles as strange sounds emerge from the shadows.
[SPEAKER_06]: With only her determination, inner strength, and resourcefulness to help her, Laura must overcome the challenge of harsh and unforgiving journeys that will take her across a vast island wilderness and into deep...
[SPEAKER_06]: Deep, Claustrophobic, and Menacing Underground Tombs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Felicia's actually going to be in tombs in Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's more of like a scary game, and that's what GameGuru says in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's rumored to be survival horror, and I think that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and they're also saying, I guess, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and, you know, you gotta love the survey leaks, but Joystick, the blog that ran the story, they actually were contacted by the Nielsen Entertainment Group to remove the image and the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Nielsen, like the ratings people on television, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Nielsen ratings?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they have a similar name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Crystal Dynamics is hiring folks to work on an installment of a AAA franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Toby Gard, the series creator, is a leading design group for an unannounced project and Eidos is terrible at keeping its secret games under wraps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's probably going to happen and I bet you anything next year you'll have another Tomb Raider game that hopefully won't suck as much as the last one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tomb Raider's interesting because Tomb Raider, I remember Tomb Raider 2 and the original Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those were really revolutionary PC games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that franchise, to me anyway, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, chatters, if we have Tomb Raider fans.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the franchise really kind of, it felt like so much more of the same, more of the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that whole 3D platformer thing was so overdone, I think, amongst the PlayStation 2 and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole thing felt very...
[SPEAKER_05]: to me, like, you know, after a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, whereas I think those original games were very revolutionary, I think the later ones just bored the shit out of me, and I had no interest in playing them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's very interesting to me, well, A, that this is a reboot of a reboot of a reboot at this point, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And that if they're changing the genre up a little bit, that's really interesting to me as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that they might be going a more survival horror route, which seems to be, I guess, all the rage these days with your, you know, Saw and your...
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Hill and your Resident Evils.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's even funny, though, because when I saw the picture of Lara Croft, it reminded me of someone from Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the look of it looked very much like Jill or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what's interesting is that they're talking about doing a movie franchise reboot, too, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could this be playing into that at all?
[SPEAKER_05]: Could the movie franchise be going more...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the thing, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: To me, I don't give a crap if they reboot this because I have lost interest in this series.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I never had interest in this series, so... Great!
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'd like to see them try something different, but it's not going to probably get me to play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But hey.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what if the game is really good, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: What if you hear it's as awesome as Resident Evil 4 or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't care for Resident Evil 4 either.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, I didn't play Resident Evil 4, but I don't care for Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, what if it plays like Grand Theft Auto 4?
[SPEAKER_05]: It will never play like Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw in chat says, Megan Fox would have to do the English accent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angelina Jolie does have a pretty good English accent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joshi16 says, Megan Fox would have to actually do something interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xlink says, the hell with this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where's my pressure luck game?
[SPEAKER_02]: You have that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, there is that DVD game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got that for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that shows how many people actually care about Tomb Raider, at least in our chat room, if our chat is any indication.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, it was all about Tomb Raider 2, locking the butler in the freezer, and then breaking Lara Croft's neck.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was all about Topless Mod.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was really the start of that whole craze of every game on the PC has a booby mod, and it was Tomb Raider, the old school Tomb Raider where you could run around as naked Lara.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, alright, I guess a lot of our folks don't really seem to care about the whole Tomb Raider reboot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you disagree.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before I get into the next story, I want to mention this chat comment from earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: RobX327 in chat says, Hey Rob, a big game did come out this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Battlefield 1943 on Xbox Live Arcade and PSN.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, not really my type of game, but good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know there's tons of people that are really into Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_05]: That had a really long line at E3 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kept giving them away and I never got one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that I would have played it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not my kind of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: No disrespect to those who enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to play Battlefield 1942, I think, and I was just really terrible at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried playing that on the PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just not very good at those kind of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that is a big game this week, but certainly for one particular genre.
[SPEAKER_05]: For a role-play gamer fan like me, not as much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, alright, anyhow, let's move on to some other gaming news, and speaking of roleplaying games, Dragon Quest IX is definitely highly anticipated, and of course it's so highly anticipated there are folks trying to get the game before it is actually out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, there's actually a leaked version of Dragon Quest IX that's showing up on some, uh,
[SPEAKER_05]: D.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: Owata
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I was reading about this whole story about the whole fake ROMs, and I thought this was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've heard this kind of thing before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Haven't you heard about the musicians who put the fake music out there to stop the pirates?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was Madonna's last album, but the one before it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She put out these tracks on the internet that would play the first 30 seconds of the song, and then the rest of it would be her going, What the fuck do you think you're doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really funny, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it would play the first few seconds of the song, and then, what the fuck do you think you're doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is essentially, this is like the game version of that, in a way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, now, not to say that this was something that Square Enix did themselves.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was probably some anti-piracy people just doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you have seen this kind of thing happen before, like the original EarthBound.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no vitamin D
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think game companies might be doing this on purpose?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think there's any chance at all Square Enix could be behind something like this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think they should be?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, because it's not going to really stop anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, really, a lot of people will download it and then they'll post, Hey, by the way, this is not the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually a hacked thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really going to affect just a small group of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they found a fix for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: It really accomplished nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of times there will be these... We've talked about them before, different anti-piracy stuff that they have, especially on DS games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It tricks people for a while and it stops them from being able to play it, but then eventually they fix it and patch it and it's done.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they found a way to unbrick all those DSs already?
[SPEAKER_06]: I was looking up something because I was actually looking at...
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't really want to pirate the game because I don't really it's a full Japanese game and it's RPG it's just like I don't have time to play it for one and two it's all in Japanese I wouldn't know what the hell is going on so it's just not interesting but I was kind of curious to see if they did find a fix for that stuff and there was someone talking about ways to fix it and there was like apparently a way to fix it if you'd done something else I don't remember what it was but yeah apparently there are ways to fix it if you did you know brick it
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Frisbee in chat says, you can't just break someone's DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's what they're saying, that they break these things somehow.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how you do it, but it must do something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It overwrote something that was on their actual firmware.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it just kind of tweaked something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, is it what these pirates deserve?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think it's what people deserve for being so overeager or careless?
[SPEAKER_06]: ToplessMod
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm borderline interested in Dragon Quest IX.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've listened to the show before, you know I have this weird thing about handheld gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll come out over here eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's going to come out over here, but I don't know if I really want it because of the fact it's on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know how I feel about handheld gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then again, I did play Final Fantasy IV.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've played Final Fantasy II and I on PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll probably get this, but I'm going to wait and see the reviews first.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of actually glad it's out in Japan for a little while before it comes out here that way I kind of hear if it's good or not the one I really liked Dragon Quest VIII though on PlayStation 2 that was a pretty good RPG that's another one I need to go back and finish along with Final Fantasy XII but I have to go get my PlayStation 2 and hook it up because my 3 is not backwards compatible lame
[SPEAKER_02]: Mine is... Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy IV is not like a kid's thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just old school graphics.
[SPEAKER_11]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_11]: The Mystic Quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's what I remember as a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hell no, it's not Mystic Quest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Final Fantasy IV hard type.
[SPEAKER_05]: The original Japanese one where you get random battles way more often than you did in the American release and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm a...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm probably going to finish Final Fantasy 4 the after years but for right now I wanted to go to something a little more new school and I remembered I really wanted to beat Lost Odyssey and for some weird reason I actually do kind of want to play Blue Dragon even though that wasn't nearly as good I just kind of want to finish that so who knows anyhow VXJasonXV in chat is frowning saying I liked Mystic Quest I beat Mystic Quest actually I did play that all the way through it was not like it was a very hard game to beat yeah it wasn't terrible it just wasn't Final Fantasy at all
[SPEAKER_11]: It really wasn't originally a Final Fantasy game anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, do you know in Japan that game was released as Final Fantasy USA?
[SPEAKER_05]: Boy, didn't that make us look stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But now, keep in mind, though, now whenever games released in America, they get re-released in Japan as international versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because typically, especially with Square games, we start getting extra stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, for example, Final Fantasy VII, if I'm right, it got a re-release.
[SPEAKER_05]: X did, I know for sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, X did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we got another weapon released.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Shermie
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: A sheep skin, a sheep fur rug At least it's not a severed head But it's like right in the corner under the computer table So it's really in a dark little corner And Shermie has made this like her little bed I think it's very cute Yeah, it's definitely covered with Shermie hair Yeah But, well, when we had, it actually, part of it got ruined because of her to start with But I also spilled Kool-Aid on it
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, I didn't mean to get away from video gaming with kitty talk, but yeah, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, if you want to go ahead and get into the next thing for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, if you want to join us in our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com is the place to be live on this Sunday evening as we tape on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there was talk about Sony getting the Netflix service, and it's coming to the Bravia TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: to the PlayStation Bravia.
[SPEAKER_03]: To the Bravia internet capable TVs.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's actually nothing mentioned about it coming to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's hints of it coming to the Wii, but nothing yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, they're...
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony is actually saying right off the bat that they were going to look into content for the PlayStation Network, but they don't have anything regarding the Netflix to announce at this time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think... Yeah, they probably just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony might actually not want it on their platform because they have their service on there and they don't want it to compete with their service.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they're greedy little bastards.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like Netflix.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Netflix streaming content still leaves a lot to be desired.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are looking at the back catalog of movies that most people missed the first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do have a few...
[SPEAKER_05]: Decent movies on there now that they have the Stars play especially.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do get some stuff that's recently to cable movies, but that's about as recent as you get with a lot of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now they have some of the Disney movies too, I will say, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's still a lot of room for improvement.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say the thing I like Netflix for best is the TV shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do have a lot of the NBC shows and stuff on demand type stuff, and you can get that, but
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, there's still a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess Sony has the TV service too, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's the competition.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Xbox has their on-demand stuff too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The separate program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they just want people to buy their stupid HDTVs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the best thing about this, though, is it's certain HDTVs and you have to have it hooked up a certain way.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just like a really small percentage of people actually going to be using this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it's neat I guess, but until it's actually supported on all their TVs, then...
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at some chat comments from chat.orangelandreda.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tigerclaw asks, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are those Bravia TVs come equipped with built-in Wi-Fi?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm guessing they must if they have the Netflix service in them.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of the thing to do with a lot of appliances now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like tons of things are coming out with Wi-Fi enabled.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have little radios now that are like internet radios basically that use Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: They hook right into Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's getting, I guess, so cheap, the technology.
[SPEAKER_05]: that you're starting to see it in a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty soon my toaster's going to have Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's yelling from the kitchen, you can put Linux on a toaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can, but also just have the toaster connected to Wi-Fi where it goes, ding, the toast is done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe it would pop a message on all your computers, toast is done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would you leave your toast to toast?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura wants to make a comment on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of devices have Wi-Fi in them, so I would not be surprised at all if the TV has Wi-Fi somehow built in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Attack of the Clock goes on to say some Blu-ray players have built-in Wi-Fi but cost more as opposed to the ones built with LAN.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's true because to get your Blu-ray firmware updates, you have to be connected to the internet somehow, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Charger in chat says, seems funny that even standalone Blu-ray players offer it from Samsung and LG.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard about that too, the whole Blu-ray slash Netflix players.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've heard about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deathwishing is asking for less movie news, more gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess you could tie this into gaming somehow because let's face it, those gaming consoles, the 360 and PlayStation 3, the movies are a big part of the business and kind of how they're getting into more and more homes, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because maybe mom and dad and grandma aren't so interested in playing Tomb Raider on it, but they'd be more interested in downloading movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watching Tomb Raider on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, probably not.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the other comment we had in here?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to add your comments, chat.orangelaundry.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkCharger also says, seems funny that even standalone Blu-ray players... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I read that one already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where was the one?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, but DarkCharger said, my guess is Sony doesn't want it because it competes with their own service in their eyes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess we'll see what develops.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's inevitable it'll get something streaming soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: More along the Netflix model at some point, but maybe because Sony owns its own movie studio and wants to do something different.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Harmonix basically thinks, and this is according to Josh Randall, their boss, he thinks that the music game genre could actually leave the consoles and actually go to more of their own standalone peripherals, basically the plug-and-play type game things.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know we've already kind of seen this with some things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they're not very...
[SPEAKER_06]: D.D.R.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the DDR brand.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came with a mat, but it didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: The mat didn't do a damn thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was obviously made for three-year-olds, just for them to jump on the mat pretending they're actually doing something.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it would just play these cheesy Flash music videos on the TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the kind of shit three- and four-year-olds love, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I forgive them for that, even if they did slap the DDR label on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jack's Pacific, G2 Game Girl, Hannah Montana,
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Video Game, which you will play on Amazon, and I actually did watch this earlier this week just to see what the hell this was, because I knew it was crap, and I really had low expectations for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what, hey, for the non-experienced...
[SPEAKER_06]: A six-year-old.
[SPEAKER_06]: For a six-year-old.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't give a crap, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: For $30, you know, $33.27, you can get this guitar that plug and plays into your TV, and you can actually play with Hannah Montana songs, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: but I mean until the technology becomes cheap enough to where they can really pack a lot of oomph inside of a little plastic controller I don't think this is really going to take off
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what if though?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I'm sure this guy who made the comment has to be aware this type of thing has already been attempted.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we've never seen anything on a large scale level.
[SPEAKER_05]: This kind of ties in in a way to the fact that like Wi-Fi is in all of our devices now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't think you would see something like this get released for $30.
[SPEAKER_05]: But don't you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 1 level hardware in one of these things really cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe even PlayStation 2 level hardware in one of these things really cheap where you can even go on and download songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking this guy's talking about not so much this crap that they make for six-year-olds to easily amuse them for a while so you don't have to listen to them whine, but something that the more adult gamers can take seriously and more importantly, download songs onto.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be the big thing about these.
[SPEAKER_05]: They probably...
[SPEAKER_05]: If you bypass Xbox Live Marketplace, you bypass Sony's thing and Nintendo's thing, what is one big thing this is really about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Cutting out the middleman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Making more money from the download songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it'll take off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just because they are limited to what they can do with the hardware right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I think if it could be done, it would be done.
[SPEAKER_06]: because I mean obviously everyone wants to make money and they're always trying to come up with these knockoff games if anything I could see them doing something you know and I'm surprised Konami hasn't done this yet because they did this with you know some of their Frogger and Yu-Gi-Oh games where they have these things that you basically buy it's a USB thumb drive you plug it in your computer connects you to the internet and you play a game
[SPEAKER_05]: I have one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Frogger, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, so you get something like this that's either DDR or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You plug the mat into your PC, boom, you're playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you plug in the guitar into your PC and you're playing Guitar Freaks or Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully not Rock Revolution, but actually Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have tons of this stuff for the TV, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is huge.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, even some hardcore gamers like this stuff because you have a lot of those classic video games inside the joystick.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the flashback systems are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: The flashback systems are actually, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: Atari 2600s
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, guys, in chat, would you guys be interested?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's say they could build something like this that would be at a PlayStation 2 level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's say that you could basically get Rock Band on a PlayStation 2 without needing the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or even, let's think, even beyond this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you be interested in this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, through, like, say, a cable provider, like Comcast or something like that, you're, you know, plugging your controller into the actual...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Saga Channel Saga Channel Saga Channel
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of surprised that cable has not tried to get back into this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially with Comcast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially, you know, I know them because they're the local provider here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting into DVR and movies on demand and telephones now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Jason says, totally not worth the investment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember liking the thing as a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason says there's no other way to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not yet anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just... I understand you can buy these peripherals and stuff now, and they are expensive, but at least you can use them for a few games and get some use out of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the flashback systems are good for what they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's some old... It's hard to win 600 games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can hack them, though, so you can actually plug in your own cartridges.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cheap thrills.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's what you give your kids to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, we'll see what happens with the music games in the future.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it'll happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it'll happen by Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe not this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: They better hurry up and do it, though, before the music... Because, you know, Guitar Hero is forcing the music game series to jump the shark.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it'll be interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumor is going around the internet this week that possibly we have a Kane and Lynch fiasco part 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember this?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a whole fiasco.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it part 3?
[SPEAKER_06]: They did Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_06]: The last Tomb Raider game they did the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well look, let's catch people up if you forgot.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was this whole fiasco with GameSpot where it was rumored, it was never really proved one way or the other, that Eidos was buying off GameSpot to give Kane and Lynch essentially decent reviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I remember it kind of resulted, wasn't that the reason why some people...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: I think was what happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: And these are basically, this isn't the first time this has happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: Back in November 2008, Eidos basically was putting the same type of pressure on publishers saying that if you're planning on reviewing Tomb Raider Underworld at less than an 8.0, Eidos will need you to hold your review until Monday.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you're going to put it out now, you can put it out at a higher review.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was like, seriously, you're going to attempt to do that?
[SPEAKER_06]: In their defense, I understand why they're doing that because obviously they want the positive buzz going into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I'm going to say Batman Arkham Asylum is going to be a horrible game because it's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks good.
[SPEAKER_06]: But...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just want to clarify now, now that we've kind of said that, I do want to state this because this is important, is that Kotaku ran an update to their version of the story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eidos apparently contacted them, extremely denying the story, saying, quote, With regards, an article posted on Ram Raider, which was the original site, which, by the way, Ram Raider?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I understand what they're, like, the, you know, RAM that you have in a computer, but I don't want to, I don't want to make enemies, but Ram Raider?
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just begging to be made fun of.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just a blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's literally like a blog run at blogspot.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like the name of the bad porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope nobody from that site listens to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mean to make fun, but look at all the attention and extra views you're getting this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, Eidos said, With regards to the article posted on Ram Raider alleging that Eidos has fixed review scores for Batman Arkham Asylum, we want to state that no discussions have been held about review scores with any magazines.
[SPEAKER_05]: In short, there is simply not one shred of truth in this article except for the title of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is from John Brook, the head of UK marketing for Eidos.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they deny it, saying this is not true.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be fair to them...
[SPEAKER_05]: What a good lie that would be to say that any magazine that puts it on the cover and has a review score of 90% or above is kind of breaking the rules a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it'll be interesting to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think one way you could prove this story true is what sites have their reviews up by a certain day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they all good news?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: and also if they're coming out and saying oh this is the exclusive review of this I hate exclusive reviews of anything because that's retarded this is my exclusive impression of this game
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your early review.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what it is, your early review.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, what's going to happen is it's going to leak out because it's Eidos and because it's a game that they're probably going to ship early.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's going to leak out to the internet and everyone will know if it's crap or not and it will be already out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're going to have a bunch of independent blog sites and stuff giving their reviews, breaking all the other embargoes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not going to get what you want anyway, so too bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is how things work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is a darn shame because if Batman is a good game, even this rumor sadly puts a little blemish on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to be honest, not one that's actually that important.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, even amongst all the hardcore gamers, the people that listen to these shows and read the blogs...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the audience for Batman Arkham Asylum is way bigger.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, when you consider there's lots of Batman fans out there, the people that saw The Dark Knight, which was, you know, just a huge grossing movie and everything, I think there's a big casual gaming audience for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by casual gaming, I mean the college kids who think video games are cool but don't obsess about them like the rest of us do, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think they give a shit about the ratings.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's going to be a big game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it will be, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, coming out in August, there's really only Madden, this...
[SPEAKER_06]: Wolfenstein, and maybe Section 8.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are the big games for August.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is probably going to be better than Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd say it's at least the second top two of the month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some comments from our chatroom at chat.orangelonsradio.com live on this Sunday evening, July the 12th.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkCharger says, let's not forget that it could also go the other way around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, we'll give you a good review.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we please break this embargo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting perspective.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could it be that sometimes the offering party is not the game company, but the over-eager site that wants to get the first jump on the review?
[SPEAKER_06]: All it's about is hits and subscriptions is really what it comes down to because...
[SPEAKER_06]: If they have the review early, then everybody picks up, oh hey, such and such site or magazine has a review early.
[SPEAKER_06]: They put a link to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody goes and visits it or looks at the magazine to see what the impressions are on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then if it's the other way around, hey, we'll give you a good review if you let us break the embargo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a problem with that anyways because, once again, there are certain websites, IGN, that like to have exclusive reviews about games and stuff like that just to get more page hits.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's all they really care about is just hits to their site.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure that they make a lot of negotiations with these people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, we've seen it firsthand, negotiations about breaking embargoes and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a tool to make these sites feel special and to get more hits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby in chat says, True story, I was doing a review of a certain game series and was allowed to somewhat break the embargo.
[SPEAKER_05]: The embargo was midnight on Monday morning and my show is on Sunday night if I like the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they wouldn't let me break the embargo if I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling you guys, I've been saying it for seven goddamn years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Independent is the only people you can trust.
[SPEAKER_05]: Believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Believe it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, I don't care enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Eidos isn't doing anything for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: They aren't giving me anything for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: They aren't treating me special.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do I care?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care either way.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, big deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: If their game sucks, their game sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it's good, good for them because they haven't had a lot of games that didn't suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mini Ninjas looks good though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give them that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, we'll move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, we'll continue to be as honest as possible in our reviews of games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we have something called integrity.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got some more gaming news to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Release date's coming up, as well as a quick break before too long.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we are seeing something that's a little kind of old, coming out in an old way.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's new.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's old, but it's new, but it's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's
[SPEAKER_03]: A new item done in an old way of an old franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell us what the hell it is already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mega Man!
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have the Mega Man demo released for the Atari 2600.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was done for the IM 8-bit show, and it's actually on Atari's Atari Ages forum now, so you can go download and play it on your emulator.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, if you want to hear some of the sweet Atari 2600 music, here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: See if you recognize what stage this is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: with the same little mini monsters, the little dudes that are on the ground crawling back and forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: But still, I mean, neat concept, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but they're moving right.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then horrible Flickr when the guy gets to Elect Man.
[SPEAKER_05]: But hey, you know, there's only so much you can do with the hardware.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some games you can make Flickr work for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, yeah, you know, it's interesting, it's neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think it's more of a novel thing from, oh, that's, you know, oh, it's Atari 2200, ooh.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this does beg the question, why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it can.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a labor of love.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's the only way you can justify it because, I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's something that you'll download and you'll play for five minutes and you'll go, oh, that's kind of cool and tell your friend, oh, ha ha ha, look at this and then you're done.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the sad thing is it probably took the guy five days to put it all together, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or even longer, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe, maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can make a whole Metroid game in a day with a Metroid level editor.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, with the Atari games, you just have to know your basic programming and they're done.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could probably do that in a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason in our chatroom, VXJasonXV, says, They do what they want, or I'm sorry, they do what they must because they can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And honestly, actually, I think that's about the most accurate way to describe it.
[SPEAKER_03]: He can do it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fine, do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Free country, your server space.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well we're going to do what we must because we can right now with some release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, take it away with the US releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not much coming out this week, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got a couple Greatest Hits games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Transformers on the PSP is now Greatest Hits.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm surprised it took this long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty Road to Victory is now Greatest Hits as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both of those can be found for $20 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brand new stuff, Sherlock Holmes Mystery of the Mummy on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out on the PlayStation 2, the PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: NCAA Football 2010 is your big game for the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ripping off on the Cookie Mama franchise, Science Papa coming out on the Wii and DS this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that from the same company?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's from Activision.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tony Hawk Project 8, also hitting greatest hits on PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of PSP greatest hits this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Marvel Ultimate Alliance, also greatest hits on PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then the last game this week, Birthday Party Bash.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically a birthday party in a box with coloring sheets and fun stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a generic party game and that's available on the Wii from Take-Two.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a slow week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and a whole ton of controller skins for all your favorite college football teams available on Xbox 360 and PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, moving on to Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing on Xbox 360 this week, but there is a game on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Professional Baseball Spirits Version 6 is out this week from Konami in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is like a very realistic type of baseball game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know baseball is pretty popular over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a very realistic looking game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a pretty cool looking baseball game with all the Japanese teams and such, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it's an officially licensed thing or what.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not that familiar with this series.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the graphics look pretty good from the screenshots I can see.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really the only big release on the PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going to the Nintendo Wii, the only game that's out on there is Nihon Yakyukiku Shounen Batting Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, that's right, another baseball game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this one's on the Wii, and it is not the same type of game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not from Konami either.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's from a company called Alpha Unit.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Awatama is another game out this week on the Nintendo DS and quickly going to the PSP there really isn't a whole lot out unless you are a fan of Ys Ys 1 and 2 Chronicles is the big game this week on the PSP so check that out I have that on the PC Engine
[SPEAKER_05]: That's really it as far as release dates go this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way though, I do want to quickly say one thing I noticed that's being marketed here on this site where I get the Japanese release dates from, this new Korean thing called the Wiz.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you heard of this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a little handheld device that looks like I guess you could say like a Game Boy Advance is what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what it is, it's actually a little mini computer that is like it's 533 megahertz with a 3D accelerator open source platform Linux operating system on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's this tiny
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they've got a few of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, they were showing off some of those at like the last, not last E3, but the last E3 went before that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe this has been out a while and I'm just now noticing it because it's on sale or something, but it just looks neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does video and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they're out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of open source platforms.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the other one was like GPX2 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember what it was called.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: on the 17th Planet Commando for PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: There are two big games coming out this fall from Activision and EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tar Hero 5 and The Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those games are definitely going to be very hot sellers on all platforms.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing is, this is also kind of a test for Activision and EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the first game...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a feeling this may be a start of another new trend.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if you remember with Xbox Live Arcade and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Top price at one point was $10 or 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then there was one game out there that decided, hey, you know what, let's try to charge $1,200 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't Luminous the first one that went to $15?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is Luminous or maybe... I'm not sure what the other one might have been.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a feeling that the trend now with the Wii where $49.99 seemed to be the kind of the cap because I mean after all a lot of the Wii games that are out there were being developed at the same time on the PlayStation 2 and really there is a limitation what they can do with the hardware but I guess they're thinking now that the features are close enough to each other that now it warrants a higher price point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if everybody's noticed that it's a higher price point and how many people actually game on the Wii with Guitar Hero and stuff but that's kind of a disturbing trend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alphacatanagram asks, was it the Penny Arcade game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that was the first $20 game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that was the first $20 game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then DarkCharger says, I checked out Major Nelson's site and lots of users are unhappy about the $1,200 price point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, you have to kind of look at both sides of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course people are going to be pissed they have to pay more.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you have to kind of wonder, is it justified?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: For an in-depth game like the Penny Arcade game and Luminous and even the, well, Luminous nickel and dimed us to death a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'll say more.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Penny Arcade game, Braid,
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of these games are worth $10 to $15.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You may not think so, but in my mind, the stuff that really was for $5 was the remakes of 80s video games where they didn't really do much to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking about the Pac-Mans, the Gyruses, the Froggers, those old school games where they didn't really do that much to it but re-skin it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was $5.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of this other stuff that they're building from the ground up, you know what, face it, a lot of it's worth $10 if not more.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's my problem though.
[SPEAKER_06]: My problem is that these games...
[SPEAKER_06]: Guitar Hero 5 Guitar Hero 5 Guitar Hero 5
[SPEAKER_06]: The only difference is you'll probably get download content with the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is fine, because right now I don't think World Tour has download content on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they do, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I don't think they do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Rock Band 2 is the only one that does it right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so maybe they feel that they're more justified for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, you're kind of ripping off the consumer who's going to go and purchase more tracks online for more money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Making you more money in the long run.
[SPEAKER_06]: But...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no way that these two games, like on the 360 and PS3, are going to play exactly the same as the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, graphically, it's impossible that they're going to look the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that's not that important for a guitar hero game, but who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that the fact that
[SPEAKER_06]: All the Wii games out there have been $49.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why should this change?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, Guitar Hero Metallica and stuff, the last few Guitar Hero games have been the same price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why change it now?
[SPEAKER_06]: And same with Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I know Beatles, it's going to be a more, I guess, developed game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a whole different style to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, I'm sure that the graphics aren't going to suffer too much on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: but still though, I think it's a rip off and I think we're going to start seeing more games where it's like oh but look at all these extra features that we added in, but you know what, you would have added those features anyways if you charged a $50 game and maybe you should, because a lot of these Wii games out there aren't just I can't justify the price point
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta be honest, I don't blame them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, on one level, it's the same damn game that you get on the PlayStation 3 and the Xbox 360, so why shouldn't they be paying the same price?
[SPEAKER_05]: Granted, I know the Wii is a more limiting system, but at the same time, I mean, that's Nintendo's fault, not the developer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, okay, so World Tour on the Wii does have download content, according to Actdeft, um, so, then that, then really, if they've done the same stuff on World Tour already, and Rock Band 2, if they both have download content, they're not really developing a new engine, I don't think, for these games, other than the art style, so, I don't see where the cost is coming into play.
[SPEAKER_05]: The cost isn't... I don't think... It's not an extra cost, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same cost.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same price point that they have on the other systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I know it sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: $60 for a game is very expensive, but it's not like you're... You and I aren't going to buy this game on the Wii anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to be spending the extra $10 to get it on one of the better systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: When I say better, I mean with the better graphics and things that are tailored a little more to these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But...
[SPEAKER_05]: In a way, I don't really fault the developer for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're charging the same price for the same game that they have on these other systems.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it can't technically pull off the same thing, that's Nintendo's fault.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: If people don't have a problem with this now, then don't balk at it when more of your favorite games come out at a $60 price point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait until Nintendo figures this out that they can charge $60 for your next Mario game or your Metroid game and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: People aren't going to balk at it, then why shouldn't they charge those prices?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let them shoot themselves in the foot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I want to go back to the thing about the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the games really aren't worth $60, they're not going to sell.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be a backlash.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait and see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would think twice about putting down $60 for some of the crap Nintendo puts out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is almost like the same thing that GameStop does with their Wii accessories, where they charge $5 over retail for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because most consumers on the Wii don't know any better.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's what it's going to come down to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well, this Guitar Hero is $60 this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well, I'll just pay $60, and that's what it's going to come down to.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if no one's really putting up a fuss about it, then yeah, people are going to start having to pay more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really care, because like I said, I don't play these games on the Wii, so they can do whatever they want, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just looking out for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go back though and say quickly about the Xbox Live thing because there's a lot of people that think all the games should be $5 or that all the games should be no more than $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, look, how can you say that the games should all be $10 and then you turn around and plunk down $10.25, $10.50 even, $11 in some cities to go see a movie that might stink and it's only 90 minutes long to maybe two and a half hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: I, I, honestly, I think a $15 price point for a lot of games is justified.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not all of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of them are real stinkers and don't have a thrill that lasts very long.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think $15, hell, even $20 for some of the games is actually kind of justified.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's good about Xbox Live and even the PlayStation Network?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's demos.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can check them out first.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, whereas like a movie, you can't, I mean, I guess the trailer is sort of the demo for the movie, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't really check out Wii games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, granted, you can probably get a good idea of what Guitar Hero 5 is going to be like and Beals Rock Band, but there are no demos on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: None.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless you go to a kiosk.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is too bad because I would actually probably buy more Wii things if I could demo them first.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've bought, I think, four games on the Wii, WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought that Bit.Trip Beat, and I need to get the new one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought Defend Your Castle, but that was only like a day one WiiWare, I want to see what a WiiWare game looks like type of thing, which, you know, wasn't a terrible game, but it wasn't great either.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought the Gradius Reimagining, which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Joshi16 in chat says, the demo saved me $15 on Battlefield 1943.
[SPEAKER_05]: It isn't bad, just not for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think, you know, again, I think we talked about, you know, Battlefield 1943 definitely appeals to fans of a certain genre.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to be fair, you know, with the Wii and music games are involved, they've actually been charging the same price points for bundles, like their, you know, instrument bundles and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bringing this up to everybody so that you notice because you might not have.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it is a big deal and you should let them know if you don't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, one more story for you guys before we get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's kind of one of those things where I really just want to let this guy rest in peace already.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think we have to bring it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a story about Michael Jackson.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, what's going on right now, the MJJ Production Company, this is the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Michael Jackson's production company
[SPEAKER_05]: at MJJ Productions for several months and supposedly it's going to be out this holiday season so that's before he obviously died they were already working on this game they have not said what the game is no information about the developer what the heck it's about some people are wondering but they did say Michael Jackson loved games did you see the pictures of his arcade?
[SPEAKER_05]: dude I wanted to buy the Beatmania machine they were only asking like a thousand dollars for it I want the pinball tables
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, but unfortunately now that he passed away, all that stuff's going to triple in value, so there's no way I can have it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if he had still been alive, I was so going to get that Beatmania machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: How awesome would that be to own something that Michael Jackson once had?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was saving the money to get that Beatmania machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not even kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I looked at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you what I've been bidding against you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_06]: Didn't he have a DDR machine?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he had a DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have totally bought that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyway, but regardless, unfortunately now, none of us are going to be able to afford that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want any of his arcade games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have room for arcade games.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still want a DDR machine, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have that garage.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could totally... Wouldn't you love, in the OLR studio, at the old one anyway, a Beat Media machine sitting in the corner?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're not really all that hard to find.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just have to know where to look.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want the one that Michael Jackson had.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's got a story behind it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: One possible idea is that maybe this isn't a new game, but it could be like Moonwalker on Xbox Live Arcade, which considering the flurry of Genesis revivals we've seen is certainly a possibility.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows, maybe even Space Channel 5, because Michael Jackson did play a role in Part 2, but somehow they didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think if anything it would be like... He had a major role in 2, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it would be like a music game that had to tie in with his new comeback tour that he was going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, Frisbee has an interesting comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about SingStar Michael Jackson?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not a bad thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially now.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love to see a Michael Jackson rock band game.
[SPEAKER_06]: would be so awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's inevitable you're going to see something maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that'll be the next rock band game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would actually be pretty sweet, I've got to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does a lot of his music cater to the rock band series of instruments?
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they played instruments, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: They had guitars and drums.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had Slash.
[SPEAKER_06]: Therefore, it will work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess it could happen, but I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to talk about, since they went all out for the Beatles with the whole re-skinning and re-imagining of the game's interface, I think Michael Jackson is at that same level.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right up there with ABBA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, in all seriousness, Michael Jackson is definitely at that level.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you change your mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Journey.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm the first in line?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honey, I'm still free.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, or Journey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take a chance on Michael.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let's face it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Despite my personal taste, Michael Jackson is universally at that level where I could see them doing a whole game about him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Marissa Cungusto in chat confirms there are guitar parts on 70% of his songs, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I just made it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that a guitar her world tour?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I hope it's not a Guitar Hero game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that sad that I say that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it's not Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it's Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: But just looking at the Beatles versus Van Halen, you can just tell which one had more effort put into it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, developers of Van Halen who spent time on it, but you just didn't spend enough time.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: The classic game of the week is Seiken Densetsu 3 and it is the sequel to what we got as Secret of Mana.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hear a little clip.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right now our adventures are in a little cave.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sadly all of the music that I found was either tantra music or boss battle stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I found this leading up to a boss battle.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other one I think was a boss battle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... I'll play that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this one is actually very unique.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a bunch of different classes.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have six characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each of them have their own stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you play them in a combination.
[SPEAKER_03]: So basically the way that you start, it's got the same type of real-time combat.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got the same ring menu as Secret of Mana.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just different.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got, of course, your magic attributes on each character that sort of changes exactly how well they can use certain things.
[SPEAKER_03]: You also can change your class by going light or dark, and then light-light, light-dark, dark-light, and dark-dark.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you'd use a you'd change up the first one at level 18 with a mana stone or the next one is 38 with a special item so it's sort of different also with most of your enemies you can actually run away from them you can disengage your fight but your boss battles you pretty much end up locked in to your boss battles so you've got all that
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... You can, um... When you defeat all the enemies on screen, you can actually get a treasure chest, and it has a prize in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: but the difference that instead of setting their range and aggression you actually set how they actually fight in battle like whether or not they want to do support or area effect or an individual target or if you're going to use your full power gauge or if you're going to use your full magic gauge or if they're going to use magic if you control how they cast their magic
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, but you've got your, um, as far as the leveling up, you've also got your, you know, like I said, the class system.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can change to a light class or a dark class, and you've got different abilities based on each of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you also have a different day of the week, um, where an elemental spirit is in charge of that day, and based on that day, that type of magic will be stronger.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, you have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Luna Day for Moon, Salamander Day for Fire, Undine Day for Water, Dryad Day for Wood, Djinn Day for Wind, Gnome Day for Earth, and Mana Holy Day where all of your magic is balanced.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, you'd have, of course, a different elemental showing on your screen to indicate what day it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, with this one, you play as, um, different characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, they've actually been, um, there is a very fantastic fan translation, um, in English that actually even has all the in-game sprites translated into English.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, um, it is a 100% translation.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember when that first came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a big fucking deal when that thing first came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a big, big deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But your characters in this are... You have Angela, who is a princess with magic power.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have Duran, who is a swordsman.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have Hawkeye, who is a thief.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bryce, who is...
[SPEAKER_03]: from the Wind Kingdom, Kevin, you have Charlotte, the Dark Prince.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got all these different characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when you start off with your six, you start off with a main character and then choose two to partner with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you are playing through different, you know, the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can play through it a different time each time based on who your main person is and then who's having an out with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really is, especially with that translation, it really is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it is seriously the best play.
[SPEAKER_03]: For anyone who...
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, the only way really to play this hack, unless you've got some kind of cartridge conversion kit, is through an emulator, and I can say right now it runs very, very well in the different ones that I've played it on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it plays on Linux!
[SPEAKER_03]: You can do good games on Linux.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I think it's well worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that boss right there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looks like a giant pumpkin head.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the actual name of the boss is Ms.
[SPEAKER_05]: Palm.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the bosses in the game is Jenova.
[SPEAKER_03]: With a G instead of a J. Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I totally think that it is... I think, honestly, for SNES RPGs, this one is about the pinnacle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I apologize if I missed it somewhere in your review, but any word on why Square didn't release this over here?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just pure stupidity?
[SPEAKER_05]: Lack of faith?
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that Secret of Evermore did not live up to expectations?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, um, actually, um, I'm trying to do some look over.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said that, um, that Secret of Evermore was supposed to have been Seiken Densetsu 3, but they brought out something else?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really know the whole...
[SPEAKER_05]: Secret of Evermore was Square USA.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was one of the only games Square USA ever did.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might be the only game Square USA ever did.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it didn't do that hot over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I owned it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a bad game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not super.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, part of the other reason is that they were saying that Square was deciding not to translate any more titles for a long time, and they said that it would have been too costly to produce.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, I mean, hey, someone, you know, picked it up and did it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I honestly would love to see them buy the fan translation, you know, pay for the time and effort that went into translating it, and bring it out on the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to do it for this Part A of Orange Lounge Radio, but there's plenty more of the show to come.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're just going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got still more stories to talk about in Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Rapid Fire News, your emails, the FUs of the week, and some more stories, including a story on Scribblenauts, and, wait for it, nudity in Part B. That's right, we're going to get naked in Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, just kidding, but we're going to talk about nudity.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: www.allgames.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Worms for iPod and iPod Touch
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, it has 14 multiplayer unlockable items and 50 different challenges to do by yourself.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can customize your team names.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so, it's worms.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want to be Team Worm, you can.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can be Team Wiggle Worm if you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd rather be dewormed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I be Team Worm in my pants?
[SPEAKER_03]: How about some Xbox stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox Live Arcade Summer of Arcade Games has dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Turtles in Time reshelled to be on the 22nd of July.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marvel vs. Capcom 2 with 56 characters coming the week after that.
[SPEAKER_03]: August 5th is Explosion Man and it's a character who can explode himself at will.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, he gets very angry and explodes himself.
[SPEAKER_05]: That musical cue is entirely planned.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's 50 single player and 50 multiplayer levels.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trials HD on the 12th of August.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a motorbike racer, 50 tracks, 2 modes, custom, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shadow Complex on the 19th of August, which is a side-scrolling adventure game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metroidvania game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Metroidvania.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they will all be 1200 Microsoft points except for Explosion Man which will be 800 points and also some stuff for Guitar Hero 5 actually there are
[SPEAKER_03]: 24 songs already confirmed.
[SPEAKER_03]: There will be 84 bands appearing in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we've got Band of Horses, Beastie Boys, Beck, Billy Squire, Blur, Bob Dylan, Children of Bodom,
[SPEAKER_03]: Coldplay, Darkest Hour, David Bowie, Deep Purple, Elliot Smith, Iggy Pop, Jeff Beck, John Mellencamp, Kings of Leon, Queens of the Stone Age, Rose Hill Drive, Santana, The Bronx, Thrice, Tom Petty, Running Down a Dream, Vampire Weekend, and Wolf Mother.
[SPEAKER_03]: And... That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's also interesting, though, is before that got announced, there was actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: or not all of all of the things that on the rumor list ended up being on the confirmed list right yes okay just want to make sure that's clear yes um of course uh you know Queen and David Bowie Under Pressure um let's see here also a couple Tom Petty songs uh Tom Petty Running Down a Dream uh Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers American Girl um
[SPEAKER_06]: They even have the gorillas in the game with Feel Good Ink, which will be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blursong2, Bon Jovi You Give Love a Bad Name, and many, many more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say, if that is real, which it sounds like it is It's actually a pretty freaking good list for Guitar Hero As much crap as I've given the Guitar Hero franchise I will say this song list does make me want to buy Guitar Hero 5 It's a pretty good song list Assuming that it's all correct Which it probably is Yes
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, and then a little bit of bad news.
[SPEAKER_06]: We talked about last week that there was a rumor that maybe the PSP Go was a little bit faster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, that, you know, they may have upped the processor to 480 MHz.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, unfortunately that wouldn't be the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, actually that processor speed was referring to the USB speed and not the CPU.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, no, the PSP Go is still not worth your $250.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, and then finally, um,
[SPEAKER_06]: EA made a boo-boo this week posting on their Twitter an announcement for Command & Conquer 4 and kind of jumping the gun a bit actually it did get later officially announced in the next coming days but apparently it was kind of funny because they had the announcement EA Los Angeles announces the development of Command & Conquer 4 and then they had a link to a press release that wasn't there yet so later they added a press release and it was announced dope
[SPEAKER_06]: But still funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aren't you a big fan of Command & Conquer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but I haven't really... I'm a fan of Red Alert, and I actually skipped the last one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know why, but... Yeah, I'm a fan of editing those to death, just like I do Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: on his Twitter actually Quan Chi who is from Mortal Kombat 4 originally the character design for that character showed up on his Twitter so it looks like there was definitely some stuff planned unfortunately now though according to Ed Boon quote right now I don't see it happening apparently all the code though for the characters was just about done but unfortunately now all the attention is focused on Mortal Kombat 9 I guess you can thank all of Midway's recent troubles for that
[SPEAKER_05]: One thing that you can download right now, though, for free even, Elder Scrolls 2, Daggerfall.
[SPEAKER_05]: You may have heard of Elder Scrolls 4, Oblivion, because that was a huge game a couple years ago, and I'm sure Elder Scrolls 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm surprised there's not been an announcement of this, but I guess Fallout 3 was where Bethesda was putting all their resources.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm pretty sure next year, I bet you next E3 you're going to see Elder Scrolls 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: one more story for you guys tonight that has to do with the ever asked about Kid Icarus game apparently somebody had asked Miyamoto about it at E3 and his response WAIT PLEASE actually he didn't say it really like that I just said it that way for dramatic effect but he did say wait please I'm really surprised how popular that is but you're the first person to ask this at E3 was apparently his comment about that
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe that was the first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that was the first time someone had the balls to ask him about it at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I know it's something a lot of people are asking.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the first time that you've asked me about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, but that's better than no.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people are maybe reading a bit too much into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, by the way, I love that response.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to use that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to try to use that on the show more often.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does seem a little bit hopeful, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see though.
[SPEAKER_05]: Perhaps that's another thing that's coming to E3 2010, but of course that's just what all the fanboys think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just like as Frisbee says in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Heal, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cure, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about the game, please?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about emails, please?
[SPEAKER_05]: Every week you guys send us your emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and we take a few of them and we read them right here on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura is going to dive into the mailbag head first, pull out some of her favorite emails and read them for you tonight in our mailbag segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoa, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not the mailbag song.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the crap?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about this instead?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here is the mailbag song.
[SPEAKER_05]: There, much better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Correct song, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, please!
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at Orangelandreda.com DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: For what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way... Explanation, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've had 3D games that used glasses.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had... The Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about Master System games.
[SPEAKER_03]: You remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the 3D glasses for the Master System games.
[SPEAKER_03]: and a few NES games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, there was a version of... Rad Racer had 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was a game that actually was a predecessor to Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was called Adventure 3D World or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, 3D World Runner.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Hooper.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, that's been out and it's failed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but a lot of those were just like little, they were flash-in-the-pan stupid things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, let's say there was a legitimate console based around, and let's face it, technology's come a long way since the days of the amazing red, I'm sorry, the amazing red seizure-inducing headache machine, aka the Virtual Boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Technology's come a long way since then.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, what if they did
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at what they're doing with a lot of 3D movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you haven't seen Up in 3D, it's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of these technologies that they're doing with 3D movies, I could see something like this going towards video gaming in the near future, perhaps in the next generation of consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's more what our emailer is asking about, maybe not so much this flash-in-the-pan crap we've seen in the past.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if they built a whole new console with today's technology out of 3D gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Would it be something you'd be interested in?
[SPEAKER_05]: My honest answer is no, because 3D gaming...
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw Nightmare in 3D twice, so I really think the 3D just, it suits movies more, it really does, or like those little 3D rides like, you know, the Muppet Show in 3D, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: or Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's my honest answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I see the game that convinces me I need the 3D, then I'll be a little more sold on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think it's one of those things where I think the great 3D game idea hasn't been fully realized yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it a possibility in the future?
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to see 3D games again.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're inching closer and closer to the holodeck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wish.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next up is from Robert M. Thank you very much for getting the podcast caught up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lately I haven't been able to tune in live due to long work hours as your show here in the Midwest runs until 11pm and I get up around 5am to get ready for the bus.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm wondering why Blackwolf isn't yet caught up with his show especially since he's able to get his Friday night show on the feed the next day like clockwork.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looking forward to this week's show.
[SPEAKER_03]: I won't answer for anybody else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, we can't answer for anybody else, but we will say it's a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do know for a fact he does edit the show, not in a way that's going to edit the content of the show, but he does it to make it sound very professional.
[SPEAKER_05]: He takes out a lot of the dead air and things that we really should do, but are too lazy to.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you guys think it's just easy to slap it together and put it on the podcast, but it does take me a good...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, and I'm sure for Bobby who edits his show even further for contextual purposes, it's even more so.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, cut the dude some slack.
[SPEAKER_05]: He works hard doing two shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: One more quick note, I gave my impressions of Phase a year or so ago, and recently upgraded my old video iPod due to dead pixels to an 80GB iPod Classic.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really improves playing games, the older unit had to search for the games and would usually give a game could not be played message before finally successfully loading.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whereas the game loads on this immediately on the classic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, the battery life is far improved.
[SPEAKER_03]: Between the solitaire game that comes with it and recently the iPod version, not to be confused with the iPhone one of Peggle, it's admittedly been a while since I've played my DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_03]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: I probably won't get LEGO Rock Band, but I would get a Rock Band LEGO set in a heartbeat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is interesting how far iPod gaming has come.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, FaZe is only, what, like a year and a half, two years old?
[SPEAKER_05]: It is very interesting to see how far the games have come.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we've gone from FaZe to TapTap Revenge to, you know, Peggle on the iPhone is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you guys got it during the 99 cent deal because at a buck is a steal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Way got that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Way got that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, I don't know if you... We tried to post about it on the Twitter because I don't think we had it during a show time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Columns and Puyo Puyo was free for a limited time over the 4th of July weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You texted me about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't a fan of how the game controlled.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't try it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yaris
[SPEAKER_03]: Last email from Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hell, the Strong Bad games weren't even announced at that point, not to mention a forthcoming announcement on Wallace and Gromit.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember mentioning how cool Monkey Island and Loom were.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now here I am, a year later, waiting to play a brand new Monkey Island game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanted to give a toast to video games and how...
[SPEAKER_03]: They bring us such joy before popping the cork on episode one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also want you guys to pat yourselves on the back to always being there for being the outsiders looking into the world of video games and for making a lengthy show that helps me in the long hours of work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you know that OLR is a special tab that people cannot add to their personalized Yahoo front page?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how I found the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Completely by accident.
[SPEAKER_03]: Accidentally awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: How do you do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never even heard of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's RSS feeds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never really looked into that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: The email I sent a while back about chocolate and flowers, that was a punch-out Wii reference.
[SPEAKER_03]: PPS, I heard Loom is coming out on Steam soon, is that true?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh hell yeah, my ass has downloaded it already Oh god, yeah, like a ton of the LucasArts stuff came out this week I'll tell you what, I came close to buying Loom on freaking TurboGrafx Nice I found a place in town that has it, but they want like 35 bucks for it Still I'm close, I'm close What store is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm giving them advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: She told me off air just now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm giving... I'll go ahead and say it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fair game.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're pretty good guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: A little high priced, but... They have arcade machines in their store, which is kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've never been there.
[SPEAKER_05]: In all the years I've... I've only been there once.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should check it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They sell Saturn games.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were going to go to... They actually do case mods and they do disc resurfacing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jeff and I were going to go to Deny House today, but the realist in me knew I wouldn't be able to get out of bed early enough to go because it's the weekend and this is where I catch up on my sleep.
[SPEAKER_05]: But don't they sell arcade games out there once in a while, too?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna go on a spree at Denyos, just wait.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trader Dan moved out there too, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't sell full-size arcade games out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: You'd be hard-pressed to find that stuff, because you'd have to have... I found cocktail tables and sit-down ones there the last time I went to Denyos.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's this one guy that's outside of the flea market proper that has arcade games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like in that little outside place where the guy sells the mini-donuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't been to Niall's in like six years.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, it's a giant flea market, by the way, for those that have no idea what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little place here locally in town.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we actually did just buy a game from Fair Game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We bought Captain America and the Avengers for Genesis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the SNES one is ass!
[SPEAKER_03]: And Dan totally reminded me of something, and I totally think this is the truest thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny when you go fight the Mandarin, and he's like, Behold my power!
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you kill him in five seconds.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: So make sure in your emails you tell us your opinion on anything you send us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't want to say don't send us stories because sometimes we do get some cool stuff that we hadn't heard.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if it was a big story that ran on every blog, yes, we probably heard of it and are talking about it during the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we want to know your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's always about your voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every gamer has a voice, remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: So mailback at orangelaunchradio.com is the place to send your emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about some more gaming stories with a few more stories before your phone calls tonight at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got about five stories for you guys first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh, it's another rumor about PSP 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my goodness.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yes, of course, you know, with the PSP Go coming out, I guess they've got to be working on a sequel to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: because hey, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, the rumor is that the PSP2 is apparently already in development and that according to some inside info that Eurogamer is allegedly claiming that they got their hands on information that imagine technology's power VR tech will be an important part of the device.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is without getting into too many technical specifics.
[SPEAKER_06]: The chip codename Hydra will allow for 133 million polygons
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, PlayStation 2 quality graphics, it kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently the chip, I guess, will act as both the GPU and CPU simultaneously, increasing power efficiency and helping the other areas of the programming for the device.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's just rumor right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm still not fully sure I understand what the Hydra chip does.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not as big into hardware stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: What exactly will the Hydra chip mean for this system?
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, it's just a powerful chip that's going to process both the graphics stuff and the actual game processing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just a chip that's using PowerVR technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just going to basically make games look like the PlayStation 2
[SPEAKER_06]: Able to be played on a portable system.
[SPEAKER_05]: But will it blend?
[SPEAKER_06]: Everything blends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's the important thing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting, though, that we are getting all these details about the PSP2 with the PSP Go still on the horizon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, this is something that's happened at Sony camp before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not to pinpoint that that only happens to Sony, because I seem to remember this whole little, like... The Gizmodo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you kind of hear about these things, or the newer N-Gage while the other N-Gage was still out, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: That was the Gizmondo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, by the way, we're going to release a widescreen version of the system before the actual system comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that didn't help.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw in chat says, a graphic chip that powerful also means low battery life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless they figure out something, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what if this is just a unit?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm surprised we don't see a unit that just plugs right into the wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not even talking about with a charger or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just flip out the little plug thing and just plug it right in the wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wouldn't that be cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's supposed to be a portable system.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why the hell do I have to be tethered to a wall?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: To charge it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, the battery is built in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like a cell phone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then they couldn't sell you the replacement batteries or the upgrade batteries or all the other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm not even talking about, like, okay, because probably folks are going, you retard DS and PSP do that where you plug them into the wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm talking about without even an AC adapter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you just flick out the little, like, you know, I don't, you flick out the little plug in the back and just plug it right in your wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like your cell phone, like you said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, not all cell phones have that either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, here's... Why don't they do something like... Well, actually, they're sort of working on technology for that, where you can charge stuff wirelessly, where you actually have... For example, they have Wii batteries that you can get for the remotes that will actually charge through...
[SPEAKER_06]: everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Black magic, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is, wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, they have them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, they sell them now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can buy them.
[SPEAKER_06]: You basically sit the controller onto the pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't have any contacts.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can leave that stupid silicon thing on it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently it charges through the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of scary because I don't want electricity flying through the air and electrocuting me, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is kind of strange how that works.
[SPEAKER_05]: Technology's weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I want to say Energizer had... Frisbee says it's powered by hamsters.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just going to believe that, that there's miniature hamsters and those things that power them instead of electricity flying through the air like a bad science fiction movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll see if I can find the information on it because it's just...
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes it sound like... Remember those globes?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure they still have them, but they were popular when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd see on Mr. Wizard's World and shit, the big globes that had the lightning in them.
[SPEAKER_11]: This still does at Spencer's, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then when you put your fingers on the edge of them, the lightning bolts jump to your fingers.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I think of when I hear this whole charging through the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think my house is going to turn into one of those globes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I know... Oh, this is one of them, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it the InCharge?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's not one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I want to say it was Energizer or something like that that put it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was one battery company.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember who put it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's crazy looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Energizer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: It uses induction charging, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And...
[SPEAKER_06]: Energizer Wiimote Wireless Induction Charger That's scary shit Black magic I say, it's black magic It's a witch!
[SPEAKER_03]: Burn the witch!
[SPEAKER_03]: We found a witch, may we burn her?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dragon Age Origins
[SPEAKER_05]: and apparently Bioware is currently debating if the game should contain full frontal nudity because the game does have some sex scenes in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: More cock!
[SPEAKER_05]: So, apparently the sex will be portrayed in cutscene-controlled environments only.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is not going to be any type of gameplay, so sorry, no hot coffee minigame where you control the thrusting or what have you.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's part of the cinematics.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently in the game, you are going to be able to have sex with computer-controlled party members and
[SPEAKER_05]: in order to improve your relationship with them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, this game was actually shown to the press behind closed doors at E3, so that means we wouldn't have seen it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the sex scenes were not shown in full.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were cut very short after they started.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, of course, Mass Effect allowed the characters to have sex.
[SPEAKER_05]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: When VideoGamer.com asked the BioWare vice president, Greg Zeschuk,
[SPEAKER_05]: He replied, quote,
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't understand why our culture gets so wrapped up in this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Especially when, oh my god, there might be tits in a video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So what?
[SPEAKER_05]: My god, do you know how violent games have gotten?
[SPEAKER_05]: We've heard every word possible in a game at this point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, fuck, shit, cock.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've all been in a video game at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even if they weren't in the game, many kids put them in anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the name of their characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who didn't have that Final Fantasy party where all your character names were cock, piss, tits, and ball?
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I named mine after my friends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I'm getting at, though, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just being difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: If games are getting closer and closer to movies, if it fits the context of the game, why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, and it's not like we've never had it before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, God of War had it, and we've seen them in other games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Final Fantasy VII, the big deal with that was that Barret cussed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, really, what's the big deal?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just people who, you know, got a big butt up their butt.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: A butt up their butt?
[SPEAKER_05]: I said a bug up their butt I thought you said a big butt up their butt Isn't that a little redundant?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I have a big bug up their butt You've heard that phrase before
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee in chat says, because boobs are worse than decapitation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, in our culture, it seems that way, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because the people are so freaking repressed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is what I say about damn near everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: You stop making such a big fucking deal out of it, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: It stops being a big fucking deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like, okay, for example...
[SPEAKER_03]: You can say, fuck now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was always able to say fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me finish.
[SPEAKER_03]: 200 years ago, if you said, fuck, you could be put in stocks and displayed for being profane.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_03]: But you see what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our language has evolved.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our idea of morality has evolved.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could go on and on about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: it's it's just they're gonna die Rob all of those people with the big moral you know stick up their butt so I don't say you know bug up their butt they have a big butt up their butt growing up their ass they're they're gonna die it's gonna they're gonna die okay me some people gonna die you know what I mean though
[SPEAKER_03]: People are going to move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: What is morally acceptable today is going to be tame, tame, tame 30 years from now.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's always going to be repressed people out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do we have a comment in chat from Leachum6 that says, I think DarkSakura should shove Loki's butt up Rob's butt.
[SPEAKER_05]: How mature are we, people?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: How would that even work?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why am I even trying to justify a comment like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Only in our chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.OrangeLaunchRadio.com Here's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: More boobies!
[SPEAKER_03]: More cock!
[SPEAKER_03]: And not the animated porn star, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Michael Moorcock.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw it at the Lighthouse bookstore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was liking this more boobies tangent you were going down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Explain, how should gamers incorporate boobies into the games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that they should get those boob balls from realdoll.com and just put them on top of their Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then when they feel aggression at their game, they hit pause and go play with some boobies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look, I don't think you want to make the boob usage juvenile.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, which unfortunately, that's the kind of crap that ruins it for everybody is that when boobies in video games becomes more acceptable, then you're going to see more of that stuff like, you know, Boob Slapper 5000 on the Wii or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd buy that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Garbage.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's just absolute garbage.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, I think if boobs is done tastefully.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be garbage on the Wii regardless.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd rather see it all be adult garbage.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: If there were more party game collections that were all adult party games, I think that we'd get a lot more purchases.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the gaming industry is probably worried about the porn market.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could that open up the floodgates to interactive porn on the Wii or the DS?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not like there's not interactive porn on the PC already, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we've got Red Light District and Second Life and...
[SPEAKER_03]: If there is a way to put porn on something... Yeah, but Second Life doesn't count because it's furries.
[SPEAKER_03]: If there is a way to put porn on something, porn will be on something.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are obsessed with the nookie.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will... If they're not getting it in their real life, they will find some way of simulating it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just... And this is what I don't get why people are so repressed over everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just that... Hi, humans, for the most part, are wired to fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is, whether or not you want to procreate, whether or not you have an interest in whatever gender one has an interest in, or even what species one has an interest in, human beings, for the most part, are wired to fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is a genetic imperative.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is built into the DNA.
[SPEAKER_03]: And while some people are not wired to fuck, and I, you know, fully mean people, fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Asexual, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people are wired that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Most people are wired to fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Including all of those repressed right-wing, you know, Republican assholes who want to, you know, or all of those, you know, religious right people, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: How many of them have we heard of?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, having affairs with Playboy Bunnies in the 80s, or senators getting blowjobs in the bathroom, or governors running off to Argentina to go get some Argentinian nookie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking at some of the stuff in the chatroom at chat.orangeandreja.com Obviously a chat like this is getting a big response Joshi16 says DarkSakura for President 2012 More boobies, more cock Let's see, what else do we have here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Frisbee said Kevin Smith said that he was going to put more cock in his films because one of his movies got an NC-17 at first
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a little silly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, and think about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you could put this type of stuff in our culture, you could show people how to do it the safe way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, imagine if people did this, but they would stop and put on a condom first.
[SPEAKER_05]: It might help put the image of safe sex out there, which is smart.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should all be handled like it was in The Naked Gun, where they had the full-body condom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: But no, I mean, really...
[SPEAKER_03]: It is, it's, I think that it's just the whole, there's, I mean, okay, it's like the little kid who knows something is bad and he does it anyway because there's that risk involved.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's doing something naughty, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, you know, wanting to go sneak out and buy, you know, and smoke pack cigarettes even though it's really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's that same type of...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, it's something dangerous.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's something, you know, not accepted.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whereas you go to another country and it's like, so?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay, boobs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's bring it back to video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's bring it back to video games and try to close out the topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, just my point is that there should be more boobs in video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: F.U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: of the Week
[SPEAKER_05]: But we have something to, of course, inspire the angst this week, and that would be this story about a child porn collector who blamed games for fueling his obsession.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a London man who said, and I don't know why his name isn't out here, but the London Free Press didn't run it, apparently said he lived in a closed box of friendless fantasy, and it was fueled by video games, his computer, and comic books.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd work, come home, lock myself in the apartment...
[SPEAKER_05]: After a difficult childhood in foster care where he was separated from his siblings, he became a truck driver who lived by himself in squalor and clinical depression.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was in a black hole, a strange sort of world his computer created.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, I think your issues go far beyond what your computer made you do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your computers and video games don't control your actions.
[SPEAKER_05]: You, sir, control your actions.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, yeah, Facepalm, if I've ever heard that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yes, how about some angst dedicated towards this guy this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: The FU's of the week, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to the stitch that got popped and the other stitch that regressed into my hand.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all coming out on Tuesday, but they hurt.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hurts a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Big ol' fuck you to Kimberly Block and also Jason K. Singleton.
[SPEAKER_06]: You may not be familiar with them unless you live in the Sacramento area of California.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are two shysters, basically, that are using the American Disability Act to file lawsuits against numerous businesses causing them to basically settle with them to get money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard about this on the news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it was the same people, but I heard about this like 80 businesses got sued or something and the people never even visited them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and basically this is happening again.
[SPEAKER_06]: This woman has filed four lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now you may be asking yourself, why the hell do I care about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it comes back to hamburgers.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's because they are closing, they are forcing the squeeze in, which you may have seen them on the Food Network, a really small place at
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: To be fair, I think they should be able to serve the handicapped.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but they do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ring a bell, you know, or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do, and they're willing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the problem is, though, she doesn't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: She probably has never been here, and the businesses that she sued are, like, within... Like, there's two liquor stores, like, nine miles away from where she lives.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, who the fuck would drive nine miles to a liquor store?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this is Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's, like, a liquor store in every corner, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's obviously just for the money is all it's about.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this guy in Eureka or whatever the attorney is doing, he has like 164 lawsuits out there, all ADA cases, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Way to go!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for closing a historic neighborhood, or a historic restaurant.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm okay with these lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, I'm finished.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the business really is insensitive towards handicapped needs, you know, even if the person lives far away, if the business really truly is insensitive towards handicapped needs, but it sounds like these places, you know, they will make it work.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, ring the bell, honk the horn, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: They have no sugar on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know the point I'm trying to get at.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole thing is the Disability Act in and of itself is severely flawed.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are people who qualify for the Disability Act who really are perfectly innate.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, for like Handicap Parking Placards or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who... Now... Like... Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm trying to remember what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like if you have...
[SPEAKER_03]: Problems balancing your checkbook.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can actually qualify for a disabled parking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's really... The legislation on it is so flawed that almost anyone can squeeze in and qualify for some sort of thing under the Disabilities Act.
[SPEAKER_05]: It needs to be modernized.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really does need to be completely revamped.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know people personally who...
[SPEAKER_03]: definitely should have the Placard.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely qualify for the benefits under these.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's people I know who should qualify and for some reason do not.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think it's entirely unfair.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, but like
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that there is... I put this in the same category... Oh god, I'm going to get political again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just going to put this as briefly as I can.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put this in the same category as welfare.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot of room for abuse.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if people can get a free ride, they will get a free ride.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that there needs to be more enabling services.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead of, you know, pandering services.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's so stupid...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think all of this should be thrown out as frivolous.
[SPEAKER_03]: She has a personal experience in those places.
[SPEAKER_05]: That where they refuse to help her.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or accommodate her.
[SPEAKER_03]: If the business wants your money, they will accommodate you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's get back to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just have about three more stories for you guys, and then it's going to be time for you guys to call in 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you have a story for us about... I sure do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plants vs. Zombies!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out on other platforms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right now it's only on PC and Mac, but PopCap is talking about working on an Xbox Live Arcade version, I do believe, and possibly on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: If there's a way they can work it into World of Warcraft, I'm sure they will too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're so crazy with their PopCap games.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, did you hear this week about the World of Warcraft Pagle game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just now the mod within World of Warcraft, because it's very clear there is some PopCap employees that are addicted to World of Warcraft, because you've noticed these little, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's furious dry humping.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're all free, so we all win.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm not going to complain.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were all free expansions.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's brand awareness.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets all the stories covered on blogs and all that, so good for them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dry humping?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think these type of partnerships I'd like to see happen more often.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to see more mutual masturbation going on in the gaming world.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about you guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Furious humping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, a game that I don't think will have furious humping in it, Scribblenauts has been rated by the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as creative as the game is, their description of it is just as creative.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, they are talking, you know, now the ESRB is required to have...
[SPEAKER_06]: Little synopsis of the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And basically here's what they put.
[SPEAKER_06]: Scribblenauts, which is rated E10+.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is a puzzle game in which players navigate a series of traps, puzzles, and enemies to collect stars scattered throughout the colorful levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Players have the ability to summon different objects by writing slash typing in the words.
[SPEAKER_06]: Example, bike, spaceship, lion.
[SPEAKER_06]: And watch it come to life.
[SPEAKER_06]: If multiple words are entered in a sequence...
[SPEAKER_06]: Different whimsical scenarios can be triggered.
[SPEAKER_06]: A bicycle can be used to jump over a baby.
[SPEAKER_06]: A bulldozer can clear away a shark.
[SPEAKER_06]: A cabbage can be fed to a dinosaur.
[SPEAKER_06]: Players can elect to summon cartoony versions of bats, bombs, guns, and flamethrowers.
[SPEAKER_06]: These types of items can be used to destroy objects or even other summoned items.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, a club can be used to hit an animal.
[SPEAKER_06]: A stake can be attached to a baby to attract lions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rockets can be lobbed at a man.
[SPEAKER_05]: That in itself is so amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can attach a steak to a baby to attract animals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: These triggered animations are minimally depicted and usually accompanied by a popping musical sound effect, bright star-shaped flashes, or small puffs of smoke.
[SPEAKER_06]: If a player wishes to, they may type the word and vomit, which causes a beige-colored lump to appear on the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, if this is not the game of the year, I don't know what is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: On top of that, recognizing that this is going to be a success, they would like to see Scribblenauts come to other platforms.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've never limited ourselves to the DS as a platform.
[SPEAKER_06]: In our heads, we'll see what the future holds.
[SPEAKER_06]: Personally, we think that would be a hit on any platform, whether that platform would be an Xbox 360, PS3, or who knows.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's coming from Marius Falbush I thought bad things
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I bet you did after the boobie story.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think, though, this game is going to inspire folks to trade whimsical answers to scenarios on the internet, like the most wacky fucking ways to beat levels that you've ever heard of.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: It also has level swapping and custom levels.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if there's going to be one foolproof way to beat every level, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be different ways to beat levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's almost like golf.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have pars in the game where you're trying to beat the level with X number of objects spawned, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seem to remember even in the free mode that we were messing around with, there was a meter as to how many objects you could have at one time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could see them doing things with that meter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joshi16 in our chatroom, chat.orangeonsradio.com says, I want it on the PC Mac.
[SPEAKER_05]: And DarkTetsuya says, yeah, I look forward to the GameFAQs entries on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if you can summon dirty words or if the game just scolds you for trying to put them in.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it just won't recognize them.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if you put in like feces?
[SPEAKER_05]: Will it not even recognize that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It may do poop.
[SPEAKER_11]: You could do vomit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why can't you do poo?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Poop would be in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should have poop rocket.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should have tried poop rocket.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's in the dictionary.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or like poop flinging monkey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or what have you... Yeah, tiger claw brings up a good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Penis is not even a dirty word.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a scientific word.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still not in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dark Tetsuya says, so no cocks?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you should be able to put in cock and a little rooster shows up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Put in fag and a cigarette shows up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just do the literal meaning.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you remember, we talked a while, I'm sure at length about this on the show before, about the whole Wii's new demo play feature?
[SPEAKER_05]: This is where you'd be able to pause the game and just skip scenes like it was a DVD.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or get walked through certain scenarios in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: This week it was announced that through a blurb in Nikkei newspaper in Japan, the feature will be used in portable games as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means it's coming to the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, the newspaper referred to it as skip functionality, a skip feature, if you will.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's also supposed to be used for high-speed action games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows what this could bring for DS games in the future, but this does seem to be the future of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: The future of gaming?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess that's all in how the general public responds to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's that for demo play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: But do keep in mind, if you are going to use Skype to call us, please make sure you test your connection first to ECHO123.
[SPEAKER_05]: So again, that's 1-877-GAME-OLR or Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we have some last minute stories we want to get into while we wait for some calls?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there's a little bit of a delay between us and when they hear us on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're getting a call right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I lied.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, BlazBlue is a fighting game that's supposed to be the spiritual successor to Guilty Gear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the total is 12 characters that you get to play as, so you've got a smaller roster list.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they're pretty balanced, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the game is, well, I think of it as an easier Guilty Gear, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: The button layout is just four buttons.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got light, make them strong, and then a button you use to do cool shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you a big fighting game fan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, do you play a lot of the fighters that come out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually looking forward to Maul vs. Calcom 2 coming out at the end of the month, and King of Fighters 12.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so I just wanted to kind of gauge your, like, experience and love for fighting game before I ask this next question, and that would be, how does BlazBlue, in your opinion, stack up to other fighting games?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a slower Guilty Gear, I guess, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: my opinion is it's faster than Street Fighter 4 it's a really cool it's just a really cool fighting game
[SPEAKER_05]: King of Fighters 12
[SPEAKER_05]: and all these games, especially the Neo Geo ones, are coming out on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you can get these games for $10, $15 a pop, does that make $60 or $50, whatever BlazBlue costs, worth it in comparison?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, when you look at the online of those games, I have Garo, Mark of the Wolves, but from the times I played, online was total trash, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: But
[SPEAKER_07]: and BlazBlue, it's, you know, you're getting a high-definition fighter with a complete story mode and the story mode, some of the characters are, like, really interesting and, you know, you follow their path and even, like, characters, like, you know, they had me saying, wow, a fighting game can have this good a story
[SPEAKER_07]: Like sometimes I was actually laughing my ass off at some characters' wackiness.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes, you know, I was feeling bad for a character because, you know, I personally think that they're pathetic and, you know, but, you know, they just keep fighting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just got a PS3 and I just wanted to say it's awesome so far and I
[SPEAKER_07]: Best Buy, I don't know if they're doing this for all of them, but they have Valkyria Chronicles on clearance for only $15.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a great pickup and, you know, very cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's Best Buy over here in San Antonio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might have to try and find that here locally.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: One other quick question for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm always kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_05]: When people plunk down $300, $400 for a new console, I always want to ask this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why now?
[SPEAKER_05]: What made you decide to take the plunge now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Two things.
[SPEAKER_07]: One, they had this bundle going on with the Killzone 2 and Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to pick that up because I think for $400, that kind of justifies it.
[SPEAKER_07]: because in the next month we're supposed to be getting a price cut.
[SPEAKER_07]: So those two extra games, I don't know, they kind of seem to me to even it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And plus, next month in August, there's supposed to be a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Blu-ray box set that I really want to pick up.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thank you very much for your thoughts and opinions tonight and have fun with your PlayStation 3, all right?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's GS68 Hi, GS68, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to get back from California Extreme, which I'm guessing DarkSakura wasn't able to go to this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you know, DarkSakura had the issues with her hand, so if she went, she wouldn't really be able to play the video games because of her hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bummer, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I was going to go, but I had a conflict with the Rocky Reno show I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a rehearsal this weekend, and it sucked because I was in the bay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't that far away.
[SPEAKER_05]: It would have only taken me like 30 minutes to get there, but by the time we were done, California Extreme would have been done.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it just didn't...
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, when?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, did it really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up, I thought it was done at like 9 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, oh well, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't have gotten my money's worth, but I know we keep saying we're going to go every year and then some damn thing happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just the worst time of year.
[SPEAKER_05]: The summer is so, so busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you went.
[SPEAKER_05]: How did you enjoy yourself?
[SPEAKER_09]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: It felt like a little less games this year, I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's only my second year going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what kind of games did you get a chance to play?
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, for those that have never been to California Extreme before, it's basically just a bunch of old school arcade games in a convention center.
[SPEAKER_05]: You pay some money to get in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a traveling arcade.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking at older games with a few 90s, 2000s games thrown in.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't feel high school wasn't finicky, but I couldn't get on the top 10, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I saw it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I probably got a chance to play it, because when I was a kid, I'd see it in tilt all the time, but it never really interested me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Man, it looks like you guys had a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got around to playing Cosmo Gang, and if you play Point Blank to an advanced, this is like the final stage of advanced mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, the final stage of insane mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where there are a lot of... I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where, like, you have these cartoon aliens coming down trying to steal your energy cubes, and you have to shoot them to keep them away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Otherwise, if they take an energy cube, you lose.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I worked at a Namco arcade for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then I saw Pachinko Machine, which was really cool, but I never got to play because by the time I thought about playing it, it was gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are already packing it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of surreal seeing it, especially considering...
[SPEAKER_09]: The man died a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, the machines were made.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of interesting to see that out in the wild right now with all the stuff in the media.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, well, what would you say was your favorite thing that you played at the show out of everything?
[SPEAKER_09]: Once I heard of Tyler's play Rush 2049 because it had an eight-player setup.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Getting to play it the way it's intended with all eight people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there any garbage that you played where you were like, man, they should have just left this at home?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a number of games that I played and didn't really recall enjoying for too long.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: It came across a pretty interesting game called Chillers.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a game with one of those mountain gun things, and you have to shoot monsters to go on from one stage to the next, but
[SPEAKER_09]: Sometimes the things you shoot are corpses, like naked corpses in portrait chambers and such.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was very weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: That does sound very weird, but okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever makes you happy, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it sounds like you had a good time at the show, and I swear we're really going to try and make it next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just depends on the personal schedules and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hopefully no surgeries or nothing like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But any other comments about the show or for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to get a bonus involving my pictures.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well... I've been posting them lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: The picture you just posted here in chat?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, I'm going to take a look here.
[SPEAKER_09]: The pictures I've been posting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then check out the gallery.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like you've got a little gallery going on Photobucket and plugging it in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: ROGS68, glad to hear you had fun and we'll hopefully see you next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, see ya
[SPEAKER_00]: Just looking over what's been happening so far and then all of a sudden I see this little gem of a story right here regarding Battlefield 1943 where apparently it says something about at least 5 million dying in the first day of multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then they go as far as saying that they're trying to get up to 48 million kills.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I don't know, I hear Kotaku basically making a fit about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: The fact that it's tasteless.
[SPEAKER_00]: The fact that, you know, playing a World War II game and trying to rack up kills to match the amount in real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, yeah, I mean, comparing it to the real life is a little bit tacky, especially when, you know, video games are supposed to be separated from real life, and a lot of times the justification for these games to be so violent is, well, it's not real life.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, people just, I mean, I can understand people's rationale regarding, you know, having, regarding something being tasteless, but it's just a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, what happened already happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, I mean, I'm okay with the game, but the little promotion is a little tacky.
[SPEAKER_00]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_00]: Besides that, basically staying on the subject of tastelessness, another one where, you know, they're playing a, they have like a flash game, I believe, that recreates Flight 1549, the one that landed on the Hudson earlier this year.
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_00]: And so they're basically saying, I don't know, it's just on the same subject of being tasteless, though.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I guess, but at the same time, you know, isn't there someone in the world who's created an art piece out of that?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, and maybe this is what goes for World War II as well.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I remember Super Combine Massacre RPG getting, like, a lot of flack.
[SPEAKER_00]: Especially, you know, the whole slam dance thing, which pretty much blew up in their face with the fact that they supposedly got censored for that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then you see how tastelessness basically goes to the extreme in that sense, where you get censored in a festival that goes against the principles.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I guess a lot of it just has to kind of do with your interpretation of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that goes with games, that goes with art in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, if you want to be offended by it, you will.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you won't allow yourself to be offended by it, you won't.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if that makes sense as usual in the world not everybody can be pleased apparently
[SPEAKER_05]: No, sir.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, anything else on your mind this week, Zaku?
[SPEAKER_00]: Besides DDRX still sucking and just waiting to hopefully, you know, if my local arcade, Chinatown Fair, apparently follows through on what they said they were by replacing every machine with DDRX, then I'll probably see how bad it is.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's been pretty much dull on that end.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, please?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you gotta love those blanket answers trying to cover their own ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for being on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think he knows that was a reference to his story earlier tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think he knows what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll take like one more call and then we're going to wrap up for the night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, that's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here comes a call.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, this is Benjamin Anderson.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi Spazinator, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: Two things.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, I just want to agree with what you were saying earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems like a lot of people out there, especially in America, have things half-assed backwards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whether it be movies or games or whatever, you see people losing limbs, being decapitated, brutally murdered.
[SPEAKER_08]: But God forbid they show a boob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my God, this should go to DEFCON 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, to be fair, there's a lot of people that don't like the violence either.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it does seem strange in our culture.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I kind of blame the MPAA at the end of the day because they're the ones that put the more stringent NC-17 ratings on things that are slightly sexual, whereas you can have all these violent movies rated R. I think it needs to go one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_05]: Either we need to get some more fucking tits in an R-rated movie or...
[SPEAKER_05]: and that was fuck and tits, not some fucking tits, although you can get those too.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we need that in an R-rated movie, or we need these extremely violent movies to be rated NC-17.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give them the kiss of death rating as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you need to go one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's getting ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, the thing is, not to get all political and whatnot, plus I don't totally remember my history lessons, but I think...
[SPEAKER_08]: At least in part, the country was founded by ultra-conservative Puritans, like the Pilgrims, wearing the buckles on their shoes and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Burn the witch!
[SPEAKER_08]: They're a witch!
[SPEAKER_05]: Burn the witch!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they were...
[SPEAKER_08]: If I remember my history, they even made plays illegal because they considered it a form of lying.
[SPEAKER_08]: They considered anything involving the body dirty and wrong and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, we really haven't gone beyond that
[SPEAKER_05]: and like I can sit here on the internet and say fuck, shit, cock, piss, boobs I can say all of that you know and that's a great thing about freedom of speech which sadly not everyone in this world has but the thing is that we have these governing bodies that put labels on things that are broken and need to be modernized
[SPEAKER_05]: And the greatest, I mean, the biggest opinion I always use, or I should say example I always use, is a movie that came out in 1997, 1998.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of my favorite movies ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Romeo and Michelle's High School Reunion.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an innocent movie with Lisa Kudrow and Mira Sorvino about these chicks that go to their 10-year high school reunion.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's a couple sex jokes and they say the word fuck a few times.
[SPEAKER_05]: The movie is rated R. And why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is a movie like that rated R?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's practically cartoony in nature.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would let a 13, 14-year-old watch this movie, no problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any kid that's old enough to know about sex, I would much rather have them watching this movie on repeat every day for a summer than watching The Terminator.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really would.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of these things we have in our culture really need to be modernized.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I agree with you, but also at the same time, I think even you mentioned this time and time before, you know, video games have really been around for, what, 35, 40 years, whereas, like, movies have been around since, what, early, you know, 1900s, you know, there's, you know, people, you know, even, like, grandparents of the age have been going out watching movies, whereas, you know, well,
[SPEAKER_08]: Video games have always been, what, our generation and the younger kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's that kind of disconnect where the older generation think of video games as these kind of toys, toys of the kids.
[SPEAKER_08]: If something is cursing or violence or swearing it,
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: This could be the worst thing ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be a downfall of Western civilization.
[SPEAKER_08]: And don't even quote me on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't plan to profess to be a cinema expert, but it was very taboo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even if the boobies showed up, it was extremely taboo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like seeing a blowjob in a movie is this day and age.
[SPEAKER_05]: Video games, I think, just have a way to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we need to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spazinator, did you have anything else you wanted to share with us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I just want to add one more point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Conversely, even though boobs are relatively new,
[SPEAKER_08]: There's movies out there that a century ago would have been acceptable.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're not acceptable now like Force Over Nation.
[SPEAKER_08]: It came out in 1915.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was...
[SPEAKER_08]: TKK Movie
[SPEAKER_05]: Society kind of evolves.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it just seems like with video games, it's evolving slower.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't get that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Spazinator, thank you so much for being on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one, buddy, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, you too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: with his Don't Copy That 2, and apparently... Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that shit was from the 80s.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, he's from the 80s, and basically, based on the little video teaser he has, it looks like if you copy stuff off the internet, well, your parents will be dragged out in the street and beaten to death.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds pretty accurate to me, but... Yes, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, I gotta look at this here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a little preview here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see if I can fast forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, this is like a preview or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: They go through the songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me a second.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta fast forward then, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not just a copy, it's a crime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
Fucking joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You missed the beginning part of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't just sound like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Walk It Out Walk It Out
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Walking outdoors?
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently it is a rhythm game, so you know, you have to step to the beat.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there is a game in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a game to it, but it's walking outdoors.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do that for school credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: You play the game going to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: On my YouTube project this week, we went outdoors.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a lot of fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Myst will be coming to the PlayStation Network for PSP July 16th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have a single player campaign as well as a four player co-op campaign.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice, we'll have a $200 controller too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's optional.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: They never had that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a mech game, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a mech game, but it's not this mech game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's not that mech game, but it was some other game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Smith & Tinker has authorized MechTech to distribute MechWarrior 4 along with its expansions for free on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Chatters.
[SPEAKER_05]: GS68, Steel Battalion.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the game I was trying to think of.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you'll actually be able to play MechWarrior 4 for free on Battletech.com soon enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what we need in this world?
[SPEAKER_05]: Real mechs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what we need.
[SPEAKER_05]: How much would you pay to go to a place that was like an arena where nobody would really get hurt or really get blown up?
[SPEAKER_05]: It would be like laser tag, all right?
[SPEAKER_05]: But you would have real mechs that you would crawl into and get in.
[SPEAKER_05]: You mean robot jocks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Something like that, where you would actually crawl in these giant machines.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm not talking about the shit at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_05]: You would actually walk around a giant arena outside with, like, you know, like bales of hay, obstacles, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, the thing at Dave & Buster's was sweet.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Jason in chat says, they have real mechs.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a real Gundam in Japan, life-size.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they actually do have one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they were also working on, they did a Gigantor in another town.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Gundam was outside Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_05]: The mere thought gives me a semi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Carcassones coming to DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That game's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really, it needs to be some other game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally forgot the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Other?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Other game that's similar to this game that's also another board game turned Xbox Live Arcade game that I can't remember, but I played a lot of and played a lot of the board game and just...
[SPEAKER_05]: What was the other one?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't even remember, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was Carcassonne and there was... God, there was all the expansions for it, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody in chat will yell it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Catan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Settlers of Catan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what needs to be on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I need memory in my brain.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, the PlayStation Network will be getting manga as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're actually going to get some downloadable comics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, this has only been announced for the Japanese markets, but why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Neat idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually think that's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little weird, but why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: We have these Amazon e-reader books.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not manga on your PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't we see some of this, actually?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought there were some games that came out not that long ago that were kind of like this, like $20 comic books on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, you're talking about the Metal Gear Solid motion comics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, remember that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a brand new mod for Half-Life 2, Neo Tokyo, which is actually, I believe, like a Tolkien version of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been released for the Source software development kit, and I think it will be available on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I think a while back we saw there was a graffiti type device created using the Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sort of using similar things as the John Cho stuff where he created the virtual light boards.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now you have the interactive white board thing using a Wii spray can.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually apparently won a design prize.
[SPEAKER_06]: In Germany, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I guess held by the German firm International Forum Design, WeSpray was one of the 377 finalists of the prestigious award.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a lot of finalists, but okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, and then finally, um, Medal of Honor Heroes is the latest game on the PSP to be exploited to, uh, enable custom firmware and homebrew.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yes, this also works.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, they've been, actually, they've tested it on the PSP-1000.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it also works on the 3000.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, once again, going back to the beginning of the show and discussion about, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: you know countermeasures for piracy and that type of thing no matter how hard you try there's someone always trying harder so that goes for both sides
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, a little lesson learned on tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: The more you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, indeed, the more you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, I guess that's going to wrap it up for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: And before we say goodnight, though, we have to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, DarkSakura, your final thought tonight as you enjoy The Sims 3 for the rest of the evening.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm spray painting sand.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's that noise I hear.
[SPEAKER_05]: What color are you spraying sand?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm actually turning the ground into sand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm using the terrain paints.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is I'm actually kind of craving Del Taco and I'm hoping the one in Rockland is open late.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm driving out there tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want Del Taco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mmm, Del Taco.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I need to play more games this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, in the absence of playing games, I've been unpacking and I'm almost done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, thank you guys so much for downloading our show and tuning in to us and supporting independent broadcasting.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: iTunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to let us review reviewers.
[SPEAKER_05]: We demand it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for another week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys so much once again.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back for more video game news and your voices.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send us emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send us tweets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hear your voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!