tonight july 5th 2009 what happened to some games that disappeared from xbox
live details emerge on last fm connectivity with the xbox a good ps2
emulation be coming back to the PlayStation 3 well hello everybody out
there on the internet and welcome to another week of orange lounge radio we
are that show dedicated to video games video gaming gaming culture and the
gamer lifestyle and with you as always my name here is Rob Roberts and I'm
always joined by well usually joined by two people but tonight only one tech
master Loki in the house hello how are you doing time has to Loki doing fine
dark Sakura the happiest bunny on the farm who was usually here to provide her
witty commentary in the classic game of the week she's out this week sadly she
is in Las Vegas so I guess it's really not that sad because I'm sure she's
having a great time in Vegas she's hanging out with one of our olr
staffers tiara our our our our our and I'm sure they're having fun being big
giggling girls and know that I always tease them about that but I know they're
having a good time nerding it up I'm sure if there was a Star Trek
experience I'm sure they'd be there right now but sadly it's closed but yes
so they reopened it they're going to reopen it soon but it's not open yet
especially you know the worst time to close it right before the movie comes
out I know I'm a potential bummer whoops well we still have you guys in our chat
room chat that orange launch radio.com I don't know I wonder if dark Sakura might
be listening and I think her and tiara just kind of hanging out tonight they're
just kind of away so if so I expect angry text messages they shouldn't be
listening they should be gambling and seeing shows and that's right go see
Cirque du Soleil other debauchery exactly well remember what happens in
Vegas stays in Vegas so but it's it's interesting though what you guys don't
understand is that we're still at her house the studio is still at it you know
studio dark Sakura so we're here in her house when she's not here which is a
little creepy but dance here you know Dan's entertaining company right now
they're watching a movie I couldn't figure out what it was these last star
fighter thing is what it is what's happened there was maybe it looks 80s
horrific and yeah but anyhow you know they're they're doing their thing so it
looks like there was a fourth of july bash going on here because you can see
all the fireworks out in the street all the residue how was your fourth of july
I didn't buy fireworks because in California the fireworks all suck here
they're they're getting more safe and sane as the time goes on so you buy you
know $100 for the fireworks and they last like five minutes because they're
crap and so being smart and you know just plain lazy and broke this year
decided you know I'm just not gonna buy fireworks so we decided to go down to
our local mall that was doing a fireworks show and so we went kind of
sat on my sister's apartment lawn and watched them from there so that was
alright you know it's like whatever which is funny cuz Loki and I were at
the same show last night except I was in the actual mall parking lot which is
funny this is the unplanned we were at the same place yeah so took us an hour
to get out of that goddamn lot three minutes for us you suck well we were
far enough away so yeah that's what we basically did and it was okay I mean
it's just I don't know it's fourth of July how many times do you have to hear
the same songs and the same fireworks although this year they did have
smiley-face fireworks so that was kind of neat you know innovating a little bit
but yeah that was alright and then actually it's kind of funny cuz normally
we used to go to like the Folsom rodeo just because they have fireworks there
as well and actually this year the night before because they do the rodeo like
for you know three days or so so they like the Friday Saturday Sunday or maybe
this year is Thursday Friday Saturday anyways so they had fireworks each night
and unfortunately the second night apparently there was an accident and one
of the mortars shot off into the crowd burning people so don't sad I miss that
so oh well but um yeah that's pretty much it isn't like final destination
where you had a premonition to not go to know if by premonition meaning that the
rodeo sucked every year then yeah I guess well we normally don't actually go
into the rodeo we just watch it from outside but and they would they started
figuring out the people are doing that so they shot they keep shooting the
fireworks even lower and I mean that's dangerous enough but you know because
they go hey you gotta come in the rodeo to see the fireworks you know so we're
gonna shoot them ten feet above everybody it's like come on but I know
well I reading our chat room at chat that orange laundry calm looking at some
of the commentary a tiger claws suggesting we need someone to make olr
fireworks fireworks that explode into the olr logo hey I'd be down for that
except they're private I love it dark Ted see this is why can't they play
America fuck yeah during a show I said the exact same so did I I said the
exact same thing last night were you listening to the whole simulcast they
didn't yes that was crap they're playing you know god bless the USA and all they
you know patriotic stuff I was like they need to just bust out with America fuck
yeah like really something like some good rock music or something it's always
the same like crap or you know Bruce Springsteen you know even really the
music I mean it was just kind of sort of you know it I don't know just I would go
to a fireworks show like that America fuck yeah and just that the biggest fire
you could possibly imagine well since I like fire a lot not only did I see the
fireworks by the way happy 4th of July to all the other American folks listen
to our program if you're not American well I hope you had a good weekend
nonetheless and you happy Canada Day to those our friends in Canada because that
was just this past week as well three days before ours exactly and you know
what it's not really I mean a lot of people I guess celebrate independence I
just celebrate the fact they get the light stuff on fire exactly that's all I
really celebrate but I think that's something that the whole world can
celebrate okay some of those safe insane fireworks though are a little crazy okay
because like okay we really like fire so not only do we go to the public fireworks
show but then we came back and let off some of our private stash and you know
Victoria Victoria was there and she had brought her 11 year old brother like
stepbrother or something came came with her and he's pretty cool like we were
talking video games and stuff he thought it was cool that I played Xbox and had a
show on the net and all that stuff and he likes video games and stuff I guess
him and Victoria actually bought at one of the safe and stay insane stands it's
called a bazooka and it is literally a firework that you sit on your shoulder
and you're like the fuse on the other end and it shoots off like a masses
amounts of color and sparks and I'm like okay wait a minute isn't this something
that you like sit on the ground and do this whole thing when they're like no
the lady at the thing told us that you you all put it on your side like a
bazooka or is this a video game show a super scope six it's super scope six of
fireworks you have to literally like put it on your shoulder okay like I thought
it was going to be a pathetic little display like a sparkler or something no
this thing was a like it didn't last very long it was only about like 30
seconds but it shot off like monsters of color and sparks like so much that the
kid got afraid and was started backing up a little bit and we were all actually
kind of like um this can't be good but he was like scared to hold it and all
this stuff we were like just you and Victoria was just like you fucking bought
it you fucking hold it this is great so you know teaching them young so yeah and
it was it was cool we set it off and it was it was it was very amusing at least
for those 30 seconds the other thing we did during 4th July is we were watching
Comedy Central all day where they had a marathon of like stand-up comedy which
is awesome so there's a bunch of comedians and they're like oh yeah
that's that guy that I wanted to see you know it's those pretty much it yeah we
don't have any unfortunately at our club we don't have cool things like Roman
candles here yeah he's asking if I'm talking about Roman candles no you don't
point this wasn't something you point upwards you hold it like a bazooka or a
super scope six and it shoots sideways but what's shooting out looks like the
type of thing you would see in a normal safe and sane firework I don't know how
to describe this for people not in California but like you know the just
the little sparks to go you know like the little little tiny flames of red
green yellow it's not what it used to be like sparklers don't really sparkle
anymore they're just kind of a little flame and yeah they look like colors
flames sparks coming out but you know we basically use the sparklers and I was
just like you know pucks and basically but yeah I mean I've seen my friend's
dad is a firefighter and or fire chief actually and he gets you know he
confiscates all the fireworks conference gates yeah unquote stashes
them for his own fireworks and my brother was a firefighter I know all
about confidence so they have you know they had like little boxes that are
mortars and stuff you know just like stuff that if you were in any other
state you'd probably be able to get and then of course every year their thing is
that they try to light off more and more ground flowers each year so like last
year I think they lit off like 400 ground flowers I mean it was the funniest
we saw it and now I have to describe for those don't know the ground flowers I
mean everybody's probably seen these even even in places where fireworks are
legal these things are cool like you light them and they go and they start
like red and then they turn green and they shake on the ground and spin around
you can't get those anymore huh did they finally ban them no I don't think so
really we didn't have any this year they're around okay yeah so they have
those and they try their thing was as a you know big group or party and stuff
they tried to light off more and more each year I think the year we went they
were doing like 250 I mean it's been getting more and more this was many
years ago but it was the most hilarious thing I've ever seen it literally was a
pile that they meticulously you know stacked up and you know tide fuses
together and all sorts of crazy stuff and it was the loudest buzzing just like
the whole street is just full of smoke and like lights in it it's so like
breathtaking you just can't stop you have to like bust out laughing because
it's the most ridiculous thing you've ever used wanted to cry it was so
amazing it was it was crazy I wish we had video of it but it's that sounds
like you know how like you'll spend like all day setting up dominoes for just
that one minute thrill when you knock them all over basically exactly what it
sounds like to me it's gotten so big now that like you know they literally have
like four or five piles of this stuff and it like by the time it's done it's
just like there's like a block radius of justice ground flowers just left it the
whole ground flower bomb pretty much it's awesome nice that's amazing a lot
of fun
alright well hey we're at we talked a lot about fire and fireworks and I'm
sure the kids love that but let's talk about video games a little bit with how
was your gaming week
Loki how was your gaming week I didn't play much I played of course the usual
hacked Grand Theft Auto 4 and yes I have people requesting you know that I play
with them and stuff online I can't play with you guys online because our new
systems are modded so we have a special version of it and it just wouldn't work
I mean we have items that I've created and who knows if it crashed the game if
I tried playing with you guys most likely you would have you be seen as
firing off all these crazy weapons and you wouldn't be able to do that because
it's just the way it works so you know not to and also the other thing our work
games we don't invite other people in it's just the four of us or three of us
or whoever's playing that's just the way it is but um so it's not hurt not that
I'm trying to ignore anybody I'm just saying that people have been asking me
to invite him it's just like yeah I can't do that so sorry
anyways so beyond that stuff it's just getting crazy just you just stuck up
just a minute you just stuck I'm not stuck up I play with other people but
um let's see here then also I've been playing I tried angry berry I finally
got to work I found out that it actually wasn't the game broken it was actually
our internet at work is kind of it's got a weird firewall on it they have us was
the 80s 86 3000 or something like that it's some weird web filter that they
have well they've only like unblock certain ports or something so for
whatever reason like we can play live but like the community game stuff
doesn't work because community games whether you guys know it or not you
actually have to be connected to live to use any of the community games even if
you bottom and they're on your system you have to connect to live in order for
it to work that's kind of like what happens with an Xbox Live arcade game if
you're not on your own console that you bought it on the air under your account
it'll kind of check live first exactly sounds like that but you know I these
are the consoles I bought it or it's the games I bought on this console so it's
kind of annoying so for you know I didn't realize this but at work I was
getting this weird error message and it's weird too because other community
games I've gotten have worked just fine but maybe I wasn't like maybe they
changed something or whatever because I played a carny vale and that was kind of
fun but anyways so angry berry for whatever reason didn't work at work but
then I tried it again at home I redownloaded and everything and it works
fine so I played a little bit of that and that game is absolutely crazy and
very very hard and just absolutely ridiculous with you know smashing old
women with buses and all sorts of crazy stuff we talked about this a few shows
back by the way if you have no idea what he's talking about yeah it's a fighting
game where you are Barack Obama yes you're very you're Barack Obama and it's
got it's got like all sorts of crazy like enemies and stuff and all sorts of
political references so it's great so definitely we're checking out things
only like 400 Microsoft points so I think it's worth that I would like to
see a game like this but with Sarah Palin I think it would be very funny
especially now that she's not going to be the governor of Alaska anymore if
you've been watching the news at all this week I you know what else is you
going to do in her spare time but save save the world from crime that would be
funny and then other than that I actually played some more fuel this week
and tried the online stuff you know there really is no one online I did see
Rob online but you know it just so happened like he'd be in a race when I
was doing the free mode and then I'd go into a race because he was you know in a
race and then he'd be doing free mode and it's just this wasn't working out
but I mean I don't even know how exactly that works if it's like fable to where
like I have to drive to your location actually find you I'm sure you do
because that would be annoying and I don't know where anybody is so oh well
but the game is fun and you know now that I figured out how to cheat and
teleport different spots on the map to get different vista points and stuff it
makes it nice and easy but there was funny though because the first section
of the game the first little region that you're in I didn't realize that I've
only done one page of the challenges I'm like what the hell oh why is this
challenge say I'm not done I'm like I've done all six of them I'm like oh there's
a page over whoops damn it so I went by the way that happens with races too in
the second area in tsunami zone or whatever it's called there's six races
not three so just watch out for that okay why can't we put more once you get
fooled I don't know why they did it that way but it's important and as the tsunami
reef or what I think it's what's called tsunami reef because those races not
only will unlock you get your challenge Doppler the livery Doppler but you also
get three cars that are new cars when you run into them you unlock a vehicle
so it's important to play all those races if you want to get all the
vehicles yeah I do because I'm actually tired of driving as the one side I did
all those unlock codes for different vehicles nice they're kind of it but I
like the clothing so I kept the clothing but um yeah it's so fun and actually you
know I really wish I had more time to play because I would be playing it a lot
more but I've been busy with that and other things yeah and still haven't got
a chance to play Wii Wii Sports Resort let me I get to this question from Jay
rod in chat because you were talking about angry berry and it kind of brought
up community games Jay rod wants to know are those community games free to
download they're free to demo yes but they do cost money if you want to
actually buy the registered version it's just like Xbox Live Arcade so the
community games tend to be a lot cheaper and I mean the lowest price on the
community games 200 Microsoft points and another thing too I haven't really gotten
a chance to play around to get the new like kind of game making program kodu is
actually out now and 400 Microsoft points five bucks for a game that you
can make games in and send them to your friends and share stuff like that
excellent deal so definitely check that out very cool anything else for your
gaming week that's it you know I don't really have a lot to share with my
gaming week I haven't really played a whole lot of new games I'm almost
embarrassed to admit I've been playing a lot of Facebook games this week I know I
know I should hang my head in shame all the credibility I had as a gamer is kind
of shot but I don't know I've just been addicted to those crappy little Facebook
games I've been oh god I don't even know if I really want to admit this but I've
been playing one called sorority life sorority yes shut up it's like oh yeah I
did it's like something it's like mafia but it's a sorority fight it's something
my boyfriend got me hooked on but it's it's got all these little mini games to
like bejeweled and stuff I think here's what it is you know how I quit the MMOs
I think I have this inherent need to be leveling something like I'm leveling a
character in this stupid-ass sorority life game like all of three I don't know
I need to I do I need to go play something else like that but keep in
mind also I have a roommate so I can't have the TV whenever I want a period so
keep in mind that's a big reason why I don't always play like Xbox games and
you get a VGA cable for making for my monitor yeah I'm maybe I do maybe that
is something I did my computer all the time that's all I really play my 360
well here's something else I don't want to get teased too much I didn't play all
those Facebook games all week although I did play some more legitimate things
like bejeweled and text twist and they have UNO on Facebook now I don't know if
you're aware but they have UNO on Facebook that is similar to the Xbox
live one except you instead of seeing like webcams you're seeing people's
little Facebook icons and you're in a little chat room so you can actually
play UNO so you know I was checking a lot of that out this week but I also got
a new laptop this week fries on a really good deal on laptops this weekend
because it's 4th of July and all that stuff so I actually went and got a new
laptop it's a Toshiba so it's not a bad brand 2 gigahertz machine 3 gigs of RAM
separate video card inside it's not like an onboard video it's got a separated
video card $399.99 for his laptop I know it's a sweet deal but what's also sweet
about it here's where the rest of my gaming week comes into play because now
it's back to a 32-bit operating system since I don't have so much RAM or what
have you I can play game tap games again so I actually spent some time playing
civilization 4 because I missed it and that was one of the big games I would
play through game tap so I know I let out a lot of game tap hate on a previous
show because it would not work with my Windows Vista 64-bit but now I'm running
Windows 7 and yeah I installed the release candidate that we all got at e3
I decided you know what since I have a new laptop kind of like a fresh start
when better time to upgrade my OS so I upgraded to Windows 7 I haven't played
enough games on it yet I'm not familiar enough with the operating system yet I
do like it seems to be a faster version of Vista but without all the stuff that
made Vista so annoying like it's not asking me like 50 times I'm saying there
are you sure you want to install this so-and-so wants to access your computer
it's only done that when I've installed stuff otherwise it leaves me alone and
it's it's so much easier to turn off the warning messages and stuff so that was
one big improvement I noticed right off the bat I do think Windows 7 will be
better than Vista that's for sure better than XP I don't know still too
early to tell I do like though here's the one huge thing I noticed if I can
talk operating systems for a minute instead of having all your windows at
the bottom like you know how like right now you can see okay I have Firefox open
IRC Adobe Audition the mixer and all this stuff that you see there okay
instead of it that imagine that what would happen is that you'd see the
little icon in the quick launch bar that you had on XP and it's just like it's a
different color like the button looks raised because you have windows open and
then when you hover over the raised button you see little previews of all
the windows that's another huge change in Windows 7 so you save so much real
estate on the bottom of the screen with all your windows open at once that was
pretty cool so I'm noticing little things here and there but being able to
play all the old computer games I was missing from not having game tap work on
a newer OS was was kind of nice so that's cool I'm happy about that
rama in our chat room says Windows 7 release candidate will expire after a
year yes I'm aware that the two-hour shutdowns begin in March 2010 but look
that's March 2010 still a heck of a long ways away and apparently my laptop comes
with some type of free upgrade to Windows 7 anyway because I have like
Vista premium came with it I don't know they were telling me this at fries like
if I send them there is a thing that you can up it's it's gonna either be free or
a small fee I wouldn't even mind paying a small fee honestly but I you know if I
contact the manufacturer I has held on to my receipt so I can get the seven
free cuz I'm I'm sure I will prefer seven to Vista I can already tell I
prefer seven I just feel weird if I bought an operating system so I'm gonna
hold out for the pirated version look if your laptop comes with it for free I
mean oh yeah you know so I'm entitled to it right it's not a piracy thing it's it
came with my laptop no I'm thinking about my computer that's you so there
you go it's not that I don't want to pay for it it's just I don't want to pay for
it yeah Rama and chat says don't worry you get a free upgrade and let's see
Tiger class says the deals you see about home being 49 and professional being 99
it's for those about pcs with a Vista that's interesting because that means
that that means it's kind of like an apology for Windows Vista Rama and chat
goes on as of last Friday when you buy any computer you get a low cost or free
upgrade for seven that's awesome I picked a great time to upgrade didn't I
whoo nice so I was happy with my laptop purchase I'm telling you if you're in
the market for new computers right now that's a great time especially the
economy being the way it is and everything people or the you can find
some dirt cheap sales you know I've and I believe me I found those netbooks
tempting for like 200 250 dollars but seriously just spending another like
150 getting a nice nice system I'm very happy with my purchase and think about
it that is the cost of a PlayStation 3 and only 150 dollars more than the cost
of a PSP go I was listening to a old episode or a lot when I say old I mean
just a couple weeks old we were kind of in that debate about the PSP go and how
Sony is absolutely being idiotic with their price points it's what's killing
that generation 49 I mean the 249 can buy you a freaking laptop and we talk
about how you know PSP's are cool because they can do music and games and
you know kind of the thing all the things that a laptop can do well guess
what Sony a laptop costs as much as you're charging for your PSP go I this
whoever that was it's so frustrating because it's not that they're bad
systems it's just the Sony's getting it's just like when I remember the
PlayStation 3 everybody was like you know they're showing you know the system
everything and it was like yeah this looks awesome this is gonna be sweet you
know and then they're like oh and it's gonna be 599 you're like dah you stupid
you know what at least I'll give them the fact that they did have blu-ray
which at the time was an expensive technology it was fine yeah hella
fucking risky for them because at that time a winner had not been declared in
the HD DVD blu-ray war but to their credit and I'll give credit where
credits do I give Sony a hard time and I'll give them a good time when they do
things that are right they they were right they they were lucked out with
this blu-ray thing they want to say lucked out but they won out with this
blu-ray thing and that's gonna be a huge asset to them as this generation
continues I think you will see more people that decide oh I need to get a
blu-ray player why don't I just get a PlayStation 3 just like people said last
time I need to get a DVD player well I'll just get the PlayStation 2 because
it plays games you know my significant other has a PlayStation 2 doesn't play
like any video games on it uses it as a DVD player there are a lot of people out
there like that like that that will buy it as a player but kind of knowing
that oh well you know if I wanted to play games on it or had somebody
entertain I could it's good but see that's the thing though is that's good
to increase your install base but when you look at you know something like that
then think about all the people that did buy it for mainly a blu-ray player their
number is already you know for being in third place aren't that great and if you
take off you know X amount of percentage of that you know saying that these
people are only going to be using it for mainly a blu-ray player that's really
not good you know and they were kind of hoping that they would get a little bit
of a bump from you know people buying it as a cheap blu-ray player but it's not
working out for them Marissa con gusto and chat makes an interesting comment
chat that orange laundry calm if you want to join us live on this Sunday
evening as we tape at all games calm Marissa says I was talking about the
economy with new game prices the other day with a friend the prices have gone
down over the years recollecting that if a new game was $60 in 1993 for me but I
still wonder if the new titles can command the same opening price with the
unemployment rate skyrocketing well and somebody followed up in chat with Sony
sure hope so I to some extent they do say that even in a recession people will
not neglect their entertainment I mean look at movies transformers did
extraordinarily well at the box office even with the fact that tickets cost
like 1025 a pop now me movies are freaking expensive but transformers had
what the second best weekend only to the dark night I mean it's still huge
business you know it's there's a lot of freaking money a lot of people want to
see a movie a lot of people aren't willing to sacrifice you know
entertainment I mean they've made cuts throughout their life you know in
different aspects of everything and they want a little bit of a kind of a treat
for themselves for you know cutting to suffer yeah pretty much yeah I mean and
you know they can still afford to go to movies it's just you know what you got
to be smarter about if you really want to pay you know they go see a movie
don't buy the popcorn and soda there go see a matinee there you go you save
yourself a ton of money because it's just that the you know concession prices
are so expensive and the movie prices are pretty or go to the drive-in damn oh
yeah and save it the drive-in with the double features and bring it in your own
crap in the backseat and everything and hell yeah yeah the pride I'm surprised
the drive-ins do not thrive in an economy like this well you notice
member they are talking about closing the drive-in that we have in Sacramento
here for a while I always do they are every year they're talking about oh
they're talking about let's put in a 25 screen theater well because they could
charge more exactly that doesn't mean they'll have the business for fixing the
drive-in charge more for that charge a little more anyway sorry we're getting a
little bit off topic but let's see alpha kenanagram and Chad is hoping
believing the Ars Technica mole is right about the ps3 price drop in ps3 slim
since a lot of great 80 gigabyte bundles are going to sell with Wally LBP a
little big planet bundle and Metal Gear Solid 4 Killzone 2 bundle I don't know I
guess we'll get into some of the Sony news in just a little bit here when we
get into the news tonight but I I wanted to say though quickly about Sony and the
PSP go I think whereas people are willing to make sacrifices to their
entertainment there's a limit and I predict as I'm sure many of you do but I
I'm willing to kind of put it all out there I fully predict the PSP go is
going to tank and I'm not talking about like not not it's not just going to not
sell it's going to not sell horrifically like it is going to be an embarrassment
to Sony as I would predict the PSP go and it's all based off that price point
because when you put one of those puppies on the shelf next to a Nintendo
DSi that's only or an iPhone 40 or an iPhone that's $99 I'm sorry what does
Sony have to justify that PSP go with not a lot and I'm sorry fanboys I know
you got your games and I know you got your multi stuff that you can do in
there I'm sorry it is not just now they did say and then you know I know this
doesn't justify anything they did say that the processor is going to be four
times you know it's going to be a little bit faster so would be the average gamer
does not give two shits I didn't say they're not going to sell any of those
things well yeah there's plenty of Sony fanboys that'll be forking over the
money but it's going to be an embarrassment they're going to have to
cut the price and make they're going to have to that they will there will be
damage control by the even once it seems to be out like August October well then
by then they won't do they won't be able to fix it in time for this year's
holidays but next next year for the holidays it's going to be a well
especially you know they've got you know the PSP 3000 still out there now if you
really want to PSP you know if you think about it huh let's see here I can buy
this PSP system that's $100 cheaper and you know get 16 gigabytes of storage or
whatever for that for probably a lot less than $100 so there you go you save
money right there amazed at suman chat asks sky tank worse than the GBA micro
I think actually that's not a bad comparison because that was a dumb idea
to you know I think it was one of those things is like oh how cute you know
little tiny gameboy but like in practicalness you know come on those GBA
micros are a little silly I think this is actually worse because the reason why
is you're you're basically saying to your retailers okay you need to sell
these and the retailers are going well why because then this is basically a
system that you can only download games for it and you're not letting me sell
Neil vouchers for these games and stuff so why should I push your product and
that's really what's come down to it like I have some my cell through stores
that I deal with they're like I'll bring in a couple because people are going to
want them but that's it I'm not going to you know push these things at all
because why should I they're cut into my sales yeah I this is just going to be an
embarrassment it's going to set digital distribution for games back a couple
years single-handedly because then Sony's going to blame it on that that
people aren't ready for digital distribution no blame it on your price
and the fact that it's a system without a UMD drive should be cheaper see what
happened with the price you know before with the PlayStation 3 hello come on I
mean did you not learn from that at all I want to spend this whole show bitching
about Sony's price point because we've done it before but it's just it's just
frustrating as somebody who who wants to see the good in Sony and wants to see a
lot of the good stuff they have on the horizon to just watch them literally
literally take out a gun pointed at their foot and pull the trigger to watch
them literally do this in front of our eyes is frustrating as a gamer I'm sorry
as someone who tries very hard to see the good in Sony yeah anyhow let's get
into some gaming news I don't really have a lot for housekeeping tonight
visit us on Twitter at olr send us emails at mailbag orange laundry calm etc
etc Loki go ahead yes so actually I was gonna say you know we can talk a little
bit about those bundles that they had there's actually two different bundles
that are available now for a gig system which is kind of funny because they're
like kind of clearing them out you know because everybody thinks oh they're
gonna come out with some new 160 gig systems or something like that that
kind of goes back into what the Ars Technica mole said that the like a
slimmer ps3 will be coming out actually as soon as August and there's a Taiwanese
firm that said they've been awarded the manufacturing contracts for this ps3
slim system and apparently you know Engadget Chinese they reported that the
two Taiwanese manufacturing companies have been awarded contracts to build
Sony's new streamlined ps3 and according to udn.com half the orders have gone to
Taiwanese group Foxconn and the other half have gone to pigotron wasn't a
Taiwanese lawyer that tried to cease and desist the early images of the ps3
box to yes it was and apparently you know these were the manufacturers that
have I think manufactured the original ps3 so it makes sense and you know they
also said that the timing makes sense the rumor that it's gonna be released
in August because in Japan they actually have more console sales during the
summer as opposed to you know the holiday season for you know us in the
United States and Canada so you know it makes sense maybe that they're trying to
sell off all these you know ps3 80 gig systems to kind of clean out their
inventory and they're doing these kind of bundles to you know push out some
more systems to kind of make space for this new system which who knows maybe
going into our next story you know with the whole emulation thing so tell us a
little more about the emulation thing then so if you're gonna if you're gonna
open that worms let's talk about it definitely I mean if you think about okay
why would I need a ps3 you know slim system when I have you know ps3 well
there's rumors now that they may be you know bringing back the emulation this is
coming from the fact that there has been a new patent filed I guess back in
December you know I'm talking about full emulation of the emotion engine and the
motion engine was the chipset that they had in the PlayStation 2 it's basically
what you had in the no launch ps3 systems that allowed you to play the
PlayStation 2 games and then of course they took out one of those two chips
for the 80 gig system that was with Metal Gear Solid 4 and they were doing
some of that with software emulation then later on they took out all the
chips and so now you know you have no emulation but you know like they did
with the PlayStation 1 PlayStation 1 is completely you know software emulated
and you can play your discs and you can download PlayStation 1 games so you
better believe it that they're probably gonna have PlayStation 2 game downloads
here's my thing though are they really gonna you know patches in allow
everybody to play their PlayStation 2 games or are they just gonna really
strictly leave this as software emulation for the titles that are
downloaded so that you have to buy your games again do they want to piss me off
or not is basically the question that's out on the table I would hope if the
emulation is being built in there to play these old games and put them out
there on the service which makes a lot of sense as to why why now why this is
happening especially with digital distribution being so big maybe the PSP
go will leave because if this thing has a faster processor right you said the
process for maybe these PSP goes are gonna be armed to play the PlayStation
it's not gonna work because the the patents actually for the cell processor
to interpret okay so it's never mind you know unless they're shoving the micro
cell processor in the PSP go which not gonna happen all right so that train to
rail never mind so but if they're gonna do this whole thing with you know the
PlayStation 3 it's obvious that they could easily open it up so that image
is just like PlayStation 1 I can put a PlayStation 1 disk in my PlayStation 3
and play it there's no I mean people forget it is backwards compatible
PlayStation 1 but just not PlayStation 2 which you know is is noticeably missing
from the newer models anyway which I think most people have I don't have a
model I think play the old stuff see that's the thing it's like how greedy
are they is what might the real question that we need to be asking them because
they want the PlayStation 2 this still sell well they dropped it down to $99
and they still care about that system because it's still selling pretty well
sometimes outselling the PlayStation 3 but are they going to be greedy enough
to wear that when this does come out this you know if they do happen to
release this you are they going to do it as a you know patch where it will allow
you to play any PlayStation 2 game I think that would be good that would
probably get a lot of their you know people that are pissed off at them off
their backs and look really good in like a PR standpoint but if they are super
greedy they may also say hey we're just gonna limited this to you know the games
that you have to download so you have to rebuy the games you know because people
like buying games from us and we can sell them I think that they should
release it as a patch so that you can play whatever games you have because you
know what people are still gonna buy the games and you especially games that they
can't find anymore can you imagine downloading the original you know
katamari or something like that I mean that'd be fun very interesting comment
in the chat here at chat dot orange hundred dot com from game guru what do
you think of this Loki I think Sony has to kill the PlayStation 2 and get the
PlayStation 2 owners to move on that also makes sense because I think a lot
of people are clinging to the PlayStation 2 and are upgrading well
sure you put a $99 system next to a $399 system and people are you know the
average consumer again that's just looking for something to entertain their
9 and 10 year old is gonna go for the $99 system and also a lot of people are
upgrading because they're a law I have all these PlayStation 2 games you know I
don't want to buy a new system and not be able to play them which I never
understood that argument the first place if you're buying a new system you still
have your old system you can still play your old games it's not like that all
sudden your new old system is just gonna vanish you know it's not gonna you know
incinerate oh speaking as someone who stopped playing PlayStation 2 games on
the PlayStation 3 came out a lot of times it's about space wires and just
the convenience of it convenience is huge and to me owning a Wii and Xbox 360
and a PlayStation 3 there's a lot of fucking cords behind my TV and it's a
bit of a mess with all the different controllers all the different cables all
the different shit I mean and then add into that rock band instruments and so
forth my roommate probably just looks at this and goes my god this is so much
shit you know he's kind of right and to throw into that oh now I'm gonna I want
to whip out the PlayStation 2 and hook that up to and play that you know it's a
lot you know but here we are in the house of dark soccer and Dan they have
all these old systems they do whip them out once in a while and play all the old
stuff but I think it takes a certain type of gamer for that again the average
consumer I think gets annoyed with all the stuff to hook up yeah you know
there's people keep this in mind guys you know I realize as gamers who
probably download this podcast interested in the hardcore stuff there's
a lot of people out there who don't even know how to hook this shit up to their
TV they have to call somebody over to explain you maybe you've been called
before think about it haven't you ever been called to install something like
this like a VCR a DVD player a PlayStation onto somebody's TV or had to
fix it because they didn't like a wire came out they didn't know what happened
there's a lot of people that don't understand that stuff and the other
thing too though it's kind of I mean presumptuous of them to assume that
everybody that has a PlayStation 2 is gonna upgrade to a PlayStation 3 I think
a lot of people have gotten tired of their shit and I've already upgraded to
a Wii or well it's not really an upgrade but you know have gotten a Wii or have
upgraded to like a 360 or something like that and you know I was one of those
people I hated the Xbox fucking hated it I was very clear in the show that I
absolutely Sony fanboy 100% me too and then when the Xbox 360 came out it was
like okay well I'll get this in you know a PlayStation 3 later on but you know
then PlayStation 3 came out and I was like I'm not paying $600 for this
luckily you know I I go on for free so I didn't have to do that but you know if I
didn't get for free I would not be buying it so I mean it's just it's
really you know in Microsoft's really changed the way I think about them
because you know with the Xbox is just like oh my god the system's huge it's
like Microsoft learned from their mistakes Microsoft said oh okay you know
we didn't cater enough to the role-playing game fans we didn't care
enough to some of these audiences we were the casual gamer we're gonna try
and fix those things didn't happen overnight but you really see that stuff
starting to come together with a 360 Sony sat on their butt rested on their
laurels a little bit and thought people were gonna pay a premium price because
of blu-ray and all this stuff and they wouldn't really have to work into these
features and now they're kind of having paying for it a little bit trying to
play a little bit of catch-up which you know they're doing to make success
Nintendo fucking smoked weed and made the system that came to them in their
dream I don't know what they did but whatever they did worked like his
Nintendo just woo the Wii was kind of an outer space remember we all first heard
of that we were like fuck is this they redesigned the GameCube and made it you
know with some wireless controllers is basically it you know more or less so I
don't know yeah I'd be interested to see what happens but I have a feeling if
there is going to be any sort of software emulation we're gonna see it
probably by this fall j-rod interesting comments in chat here j-rod says I used
to be all about my 360 but with Microsoft's piss-poor hardware quality
I've moved on to a PlayStation 3 Rama says Microsoft doesn't have piss poor
hardware quality they jumped the gun to beat Sony and I kind of agree with both
of those comments that yeah you definitely noticed that the Microsoft
has the harder higher hardware issue and honestly that system as a piece of
hardware loud obnoxious not the most attractive thing in my living room but I
deal with it because of all the things it provides that make sense I you know
it's not actually for me the audio and the sound you know portion of this you
know system as far as how loud is and stuff doesn't really bother me I have a
computer that has countless amount of fans on it it's super loud and I really
don't care I just don't even notice it anymore just totally tune it out but yes
the yes the PlayStation 3 is immensely quiet you know compared to the 360
definitely all right well let's move on to some more news and I think we'll
continue talking about Sony news I want to talk about this some bundles and I
think this to come up a little earlier a chatter I had mentioned this but I did
just kind of want to reference this it was something we wanted to go over
tonight is that there there does appear to be some new Sony bundles on the way
apparently a Best Buy employee tipped off some of the blogs this week that
there is an 80 gigabyte PlayStation 3 out there now it has copies of Metal
Gear Solid 4 and Killzone 2 with it all for $400 so that's not too bad
considering you're getting two big games there for $400 also apparently now I
guess rumors are saying is that there's going to be another bundle that could
have LittleBigPlanet I guess with it as well. Yeah they do have it there's one I
think they do have it for LittleBigPlanet and WALL-E. The Blu-ray
interesting that's especially interesting considering WALL-E isn't a
Sony movie it's a Disney movie that's a that's a little weird to me you would
think they would throw in a Sony movie why a kung fu panda or something well
that's not so what I understand the need that you know they're obviously they're
going for the family system but it's very interesting that it's a Disney
movie like that sounds more like something Costco would do you know Costco
bundles all this stuff together they don't need the manufacturer to do it
very interesting but yeah those are some bundles I guess out there in the wild so
they are trying to add more value to the PlayStation 3 so you know it's getting
to be a little more reasonable. Definitely something that's not quite
reasonable it's a little weird is GameStop they've had some they have three
bundles that they have available as part of their Wii summer fun bundles and it's
almost like a bad joke they literally have if you buy one of these bottles you
can get a Wii bundled with a squirt gun, a Wii bundled with rubber duckies, or a Wii
bundled with pirate tattoo arm sleeves. Why? I don't know but these are crappy
little carnival gifts they're just throwing in with the Wii is that is that
really going to motivate someone to go get Nintendo Wii? Oh I want to get the
rubber ducky! It's absolutely crap because if you think about it I mean
these are like dollar store toys I mean why would it's like oh you know I got to
get a free water gun I mean it's a cheap ass water gun and you know that's the kind of
thing now with like GameStop and you know a lot of these places you know a
lot of people are like my customers I deal with you know bitching about
GameStop having the exclusives for you know different content and stuff
unlockables you know exclusive things like for example in the conduit they had
you know the all-seeing eye was blue in the game that's it it just happened to
be blue who cares you know it's like big whoop and this is kind of more like that
it's like okay where the hell did you get these free water pistols for and why
would you you know even think about bundling them with the Wii I mean why
even bother it's just crap but I don't know huh I guess they're trying to give
some added value to this but I'm not so sure value at all it's like take a dump
and put it in a bag and throw it in there you worth more than that stuff I
mean seriously it's just what the hell do you thinking the only thing it did
successfully do for them is getting people to talk about on blogs and on
this show because it's you know so asinine but that's not a positive that's
not gonna make anybody go hey I want to go purchase that GameStop because they
get crap with it I again I'm gonna go back to the Costco example Costco will
bundle in useful things with these systems like a free game or something
but now it's free sometimes you're paying a little more money you know the
extra controller but you want to go bundles Costco is a good place to go
there are some games out there they're absolute shit that seriously they could
probably purchase for really really cheap and they could throw that in there
and that would at least be something because it's least a game I can play
with you know the Wii whereas pirate tattoo sleeves I have no idea what the
hell I would use that for to be a pirate are alpha-kin anagram and chat says Rob
you would probably be a great voice actor that's like my fucking dream job
don't even joke I would love to do if there's anybody out there possibly at a
game company that is creating a game you need cheap voice acting I will I would
I will willingly be a voice actor in the game that's like my dream to do voice I
don't even care it could be like rubber ducky hunter 2009 I'll still do the
voice acting because I think that would be awesome so yeah it sounds like could
be an interesting bundle I guess for me for crap lovers a nice try there but I
think you're gonna need to like me I'll do something else too
Oh Shermy wants to get out you might know hey Shermy Oh Shermy the cat has
been hiding and I think sure me wants to get out but now sure he's afraid live on
air radio these these things happen we have cat drama going on I think sure
he's afraid now we'll just keep moving just leave the door open for a little
bit hopefully it's sure me old sneak out when we're not looking I don't really
have anything else I want to get into right this second well more stories yeah
sure well since we're talking about the we you might not even have to buy a we
because apparently the emulators for the we have been doing a pretty good job
themselves in fact the dolphin emulator which salsa does the GameCube games as
well has now gotten you know some games playable and also you know coming out in
720 or 1080p so they're able to render the games a lot higher so that kind of
gives you you know 16 16 times anti aliasing and they also had some other
filters that are thrown on top of there but it kind of gives you an impression
of what the we would look like if they came out with a we HD and honestly that
kind of has me kind of excited for like a we HD if they were ever to do that
because some of these games don't look bad actually rendered you know at a
higher resolution and granted some textures are kind of I don't know low
whereas but you know like mad world looks sweet super mario galaxy looks
pretty awesome they had some other videos I saw of punch-out look pretty
sweet but yeah there's a whole bunch of these and actually the emulator course
is available now and you can check it out wait you can actually doubt that you
could just put the we DVDs in your computer and play these games um I'm not
sure if it reads it actually off the disk I'm not sure if you need like an ISO
or something like that but I do know that it does support the we remote and
none check if you happen to have like a Bluetooth adapter huh and this is just
out there now it's out there now yeah and and the thing is endos not like
worried about this and you also need a pretty I mean you need a decent computer
to run it I mean granted your laptop would probably run this pretty well but
like some of the ones that they're showing I think they're like 4 gig
processors you know with 4 gigs of RAM you know pretty nice you know new
graphics card and that kind of thing but still though I mean that's you know it
leaves the door open because if you can emulate this stuff on a PC why not you
know what is Shermey doing sure he's finding other places to hide I don't
know just go outside kitty yeah you want to say hi to the listener
Shermey no comment comment that's a resounding no nice sorry I didn't mean to
let the kitty bring the show to a screeching halt but yeah this this is
only slightly bothersome I would think for you know Nintendo that that somebody
is actually doing HD was this a YouTube out there so YouTube they've got a whole
bunch of these actually on this is a brawl that they have done on there but I
mean it looks like nice it looks pretty cool yeah it does look pretty nice but
yeah it's do some searches online for we emailers there's actually a guy who does
our reviews of the emulators and the games and how they play in there and
stuff like that I want to say let's see here I think it's um Raini Bara Hona is
the user on YouTube re ne ba ra ho na and he has a bunch of different videos
actually watched the Metroid Prime 3 corruption one earlier but he has
reviews I think I think he's the one that's doing the reviews on him let me
get some comments from chat real quick because game guru wants to clarify PCs
can't read Nintendo optical discs so I was a little crazy there with that
comment but also tells me that Nintendo could get 720p with a firmware update to
use those four unused connections I don't know I mean keep in mind these
emulators are running off computer hardware and a Wii is running off the
hardware of two game cubes maybe it can't just simply run this with a
firmware update or I would have hoped they would have done it a long time ago
I don't know yeah I don't know either do you think Nintendo should be worried
about something like this I mean the fact that their system is being
emulated while it is still out there and some might say better than the actual
system itself they should be worried if it's actually because there are some
minor texture problems and stuff like that like there'll be some textures that
are supposed to be more transparent that aren't appearing transparent or like a
few little issues but they're definitely playable so they should be worried if
it's able to you know do that stuff and you don't necessarily need a you know we
remote and nunchuck to play this you can actually lose with keyboard and mouse
you know using the mouse as the Wii pointer or whatever and you know the
keyboard as your joysticks or whatever so yeah I guess you know I would
actually like to play a lot more of these things on here and you check them
out see what the games look like because you know mad world look really sweet it
kind of makes me wish they'd poured into the 360 or something and all they're
doing is they're just smoothing the textures basically they're in the 16
16 times it's not like it was going back to reprogram these things or anything or
any more work went into them or anything like that no not really and because the
reason this was actually I mean this is the dolphin emulator was for the Game
Cube and they just modified it to work with the Wii when the Wii came out
because it's basically GameCube hardware and you know almost the same type of
instruction set so I don't know I mean it's just you know goes to show you that
the Wii is really you know very similar to a GameCube and kind of wish that they
would do like a Wii HD because at the same time here's what they could do with
their games they could upscale all the games that you have come out and they
could you do some new or higher def games or something like that or you can
spend the money and just get a new an upscaler for your you know home
entertainment system and you can just do the same thing with Wii so well
apparently there is a new Final Fantasy game on the way and it looks like this
game is being made for the DS it was actually teased around there on the
internet and then Famitsu I don't think actually no I'm sorry it came from jump
magazine I believe is the the magazine that finally spilled the details on this
it's Final Fantasy Gaiden it's a new kind of Final Fantasy RPG for the DS it
looks a lot like the Final Fantasy 3 and Final Fantasy 4 remakes that have
happened recently but it's kind of a new story apparently it's about a boy who
must rescue a princess from a witch your very typical kind of Final Fantasy
sounding storyline their typical fantasy story although I'm sure the end of the
world will somehow be worked into it as well the battle system is of course the
one you all know and love the turn-based menu system there's apparently though
now action points when you see your status you also have yellow dots that go
with that and the actions that you want to do also have dots next to it that
indicate how much it's going to cost so think of it sounds to me like it's not
magic points but like fighting points a little different they're gonna be coming
out in the u.s. actually I'm sorry it's gonna come out in the fall in Japan that
would mean probably next year in the u.s. once they get it all translated it
sounds right yeah there you go lots of fun Final Fantasy stuff I was bringing
up here real quick I want to show you mad world running on the emulator and
this actually should post this link in chat a chat that I was ready to call
just of how sharp the game looks I mean cuz mad world it's all black and white
and the line art and stuff like that you can see how it looks a little foggy
right there that's you know the one of the problems with the emulator at least
in this game but I mean look at how sharp everything looks it's just awesome
very that is pretty neat you should share that in chat if definitely you
haven't already chat dot orange launch rated calm that does look pretty nice
yeah um let's see some other stuff we can talk about here we'll probably do
one more story and then we'll get into the classic game of the week and part B
of our show coming up a little later as well as your phone calls one eight seven
seven game olr will open up the phones a little later on in the program well
Nintendo might not be too worried about some games at least you know in this
emulator Wii Sports Resort in Japan just came out what last week and already
they've sold over 350,000 copies I'm actually selling it's the third fastest
selling we title ever and it's moved three hundred fifty three thousand eight
hundred and twenty seven copies as of June 30th so by now who knows but it's
gonna be selling I think pretty well and who knows when it hits the US I know
this thing's been selling like hotcakes already so I actually don't think you'll
see the impressive day one numbers that you're seeing over in Japan I don't
think the US audience especially those that are huge in the week are that as
tuned in to you know when games are coming out and you know we were much
more tuned in in our culture to win movies are coming out like you probably
know what movies are opening up this week and actually I don't think most
casual gamers and non hardcore gamers are as tuned in with the release dates
so I don't think you'll see this have the same type of day one sales here but
I think you'll see it grow quickly yeah definitely and I think a lot of you know
casual gamers obviously probably be picking this up for like Christmas or
you know the holidays there's a long period of time you know period of time
and I mean look at like Mario Kart Wii it still sells really well only you
know mark no Mario Party 8 that stuff sells really well it's just a lot of
these games are just evergreen will sell for the life of the system so I could
definitely see this lasting a long time and it probably will end up selling
quite a bit and it could also be like we play whereas people bought this you know
they could be buying this for we motion plus you know save some money that way
and they get a game with it so I could definitely see something like that
happening yeah I just don't think you know I think when it comes out here
you're gonna see I bet you that first week oh I didn't sell nearly as well in
the u.s. is it in Japan oh my gosh it's it's a failure for Nintendo mmm give it
a couple months give it a couple months for the hardcore gamers who still love
a Nintendo to pick it up and then their friends to see it and then their friends
to see it and then CNN to do a news story on it and then Oprah to have it on
her show give it some time wrong wrong it will not be Oprah having in our show
it'll be Ellen DeGeneres because she likes hey Ellen Ellen has a very high
rated show don't don't hate don't hate on Ellen I'm just saying Oprah's not
she's more tech retarded as I'd like to put I don't know if I should admit that
I was watching Oprah but I was I was changing the channels and landed on
Oprah one day this is a couple months ago she had Facebook on her show they
were talking they were doing I know Oprah I guess has this thing where she
rips off the view now where she actually has a panelist of people on some some
days of the week I don't know but she had the dude from Facebook they're
talking about the business and I guess that was the same day that Oprah was
launching her own Facebook account or official Facebook or something it was
just like Twitter when she had Twitter on her show that site blew up remember
that yeah when they announced the official Oprah Twitter don't
underestimate the power of Oprah some might say that was the day the Twitter
jumped the shark to j-rod says people scream failure if it doesn't sell a
million in its first week remember how little big planet was a failure yeah I
mean I would actually agree with you the little big planet not only is it one of
the best games on PlayStation 3 right now period if not the best in some
circles but I think that's still a game that sells fairly well I don't know
PlayStation 3 figures that well but I have to be a consistent seller too I
don't think it's really like tapered off horrifically or anything I think you
know I don't think you can really compare Sony sales figures to Nintendo
sales figures I think horribly underrated underappreciated and it's
gonna be one of those games like katamari was where is horribly
underrated underappreciated and you know granted we all as game fans might
appreciate it and understand how awesome it is but the casual gamer they don't
understand it and you know it's sad because I think if you put it in the
hands of like someone that is more of a casual gamer and they actually played it
they would probably think it's really cool but then again there's some people
there's like oh my god controllers oh I can't I can't I can't do that although
really the only you know stuff in little big planet is run jump and occasionally
grab yeah but you have to understand these are the same people that can't
hook up their damn game systems it's all color-coded true true yellow the yellow
I mean it's matching matching colors can you not understand that I guess not some
people can't some people can't all right should we get into the classic game of
the week I think we shall did you want to say one more one more thing real
quick is really quick go electroplankton is coming to DSI where in Japan only and
of course it will be sold for oh that's a ripoff anyways it's picking their
their breaking up electroplankton because it was 10 different little
programs that you can make music with they're breaking them all up individually
the 200 Nintendo points each so $20 total seemed kind of a ripoff if you
ask me but I think that's what the game originally sold for I was to say you had
to originally buy like it was weird they didn't even market this game big time
you had to buy it through Nintendo site you can even get in stores remember yeah
and having played electroplankton I don't get what the point is I mean it
was it was neat for a second and then I put it down and never touches again so I
can't recommend buying this but hey if you're in Japan and you want to waste
you know some points there you go all right we are gonna get into the classic
game of the week we like to take a few moments here at the end of part a every
week to reflect on gaming's history and some of the games that helped bring the
games we have today out there usually dark Sakura goes through her archives
and picks a classic game of the week but since she's not here tonight the one and
only Loki it's his turn to replace her with his entry into the classic game of
the week and I believe he has picked a doozy this week so Loki what is the
classic game of the week this week classic game of the week has been a
game that I've wasted countless hours on one of my favorite games has been on
every Nintendo system it would be Mario Kart not a Super Mario Kart Super Mario
Kart yes careful well I like Mario Kart in general but Mario Kart one started
all on the Super Nintendo came out in 1992 wow that was a long time ago and
did quite well sold you know I think eight million copies worldwide and was
the I think number two title for the super NES really yeah wow that must be
only behind what Mario World even though that was the pack-in game I think so Wow
Mario World actually was it I take it back it was not number two is number
three but hey it's close enough I mean don't keep on country also I want to
point out Game Guru and chat says Mario Kart wasn't on the NES or Game Boy true
but they still called it Super Mario Kart the name of this game is Super Mario
Mario Kart yes Super Mario Kart was one of those mode seven games you race
around on kind of a flat track but of course you have little blocks and stuff
that made the course and everything they had a bunch of different theme levels
including you know the booze mansion and well they weren't really a mansion it
was kind of like Doc's almost like dark place but a Bowser's castle of course
they had the mushroom cup shell cup flower cup banana cup and you had
unlocked you know each of the I think it'd be golden those in order to unlock
the rest of the cup and of course who would forget you know who could forget
the special cup that they had there with Rainbow Road which is awesome Rainbow
Road was sweet and but the thing that I spent the most time on and oh so many
hours lost to this versus mode versus in battle mode you know we played battle
mode forever and battle mode of course you the object of the game was to pop
the other carts three balloons and you know we've wasted so much time doing
that but you'd have different shells of course the green shell was kind of
dumbfire shell that you'd shoot straight ahead you've got red shell which you
know is kind of a homing missile almost your bananas they drop behind you to you
know get out the other player also you know your mushrooms for boosts and in
the original game actually they had the feather that you get they could jump and
that was handy for jumping walls or jumping the shortcuts and stuff like
that of course later on they had more sequels for the game on practically
every Nintendo system is actually on every Nintendo system and they even made
its debut in the arcade with two arcade games Mario Kart arcade GP and GP to
the first one of course I am famous for playing drunk during my bachelor party
and which by far orange launch radios most viewed YouTube clip and I don't
remember much of it but I'm actually did play it later on it was all right and
it's not the same it doesn't have the same charm no it doesn't but uh you know
of course the original Super Mario Kart game had quite a few characters in there
you know they had some unlockable characters as well but the starting
lineup of course yet Bowser Luigi Mario peach Toad and Yoshi and you can also
unlock don't come junior and Koopa Koopa and of course the little trick is you
can shrink those down as well and yeah pretty much it and it also actually made
its way to the Guinness Book World Records gamers edition 2008 which goes
to show you that they will put pretty much anything in this book but it was
awarded the first console kart racing game and best-selling a handheld racing
game course cuz you know was it really that yes it was really the first kart
racing game interesting I wonder what they got the idea for this
they actually fact-checked that stuff that seems awfully weird I don't doubt
that it's true I mean I can't think of another one that there was but it's just
kind of interesting
yeah
but uh yeah I mean lots of fun and you know of course my car we came out last
year still pretty fun but you know it just doesn't have a charm I think of an
original Mario Kart game which is available for virtual console download I
believe remember correctly is this a good one it is I know Mario Kart 64 is I
don't know about the classic though really I don't think the classic one is
still up surprise surprise to it maybe it is and I just missed it amongst all
the other crap that they put out honestly I haven't downloaded anything
in person for a long time so it's been mainly we were this was my college dorm
years by the way do you know what the epic battles we had on this game in my
college dorm and this is probably about 96 or 97 or so I remember when the
people upstairs got a Nintendo 64 and got Mario Kart 64 oh my god that was
before I was not as big of a fan of 64 as I was this one but it was you know
still really fun to play and I think I just this one is kind of one of those
like you know sentimental type games for the love of God Nintendo when you put
out a new Mario Kart game and I know how you like doing classic tracks and stuff
is it gonna really kill you to not you know include all of the old battle
courses or something like that they always seem to find the ones that like
nobody played and let's just like bring that one back it's it's like come on
well dude in that new one they had battle course 4 and that was the one we
always played on the old school one was the you know with the squares square
square kind of looking thing yeah we used to play that one all the time so
it just wasn't the same though no I wasn't without the feather because you
get the feather you can jump or the wall oh that's true I didn't think about the
feather huh interesting all right well that's gonna do it for your classic game
of the week Super Mario Kart on the Super Nintendo good pick yeah apparently
a Super Mario Kart is not available on virtual console only Mario Kart 64 damn
it all right well hopefully soon well let's go ahead we're gonna take a break
here on Orange Lounge Radio when we come back we got more news to get into for
part B tonight and we're gonna take your calls as well 1-877-GAME-OLR so stay
tuned guys cuz we will be right back with plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio
and welcome back everybody to more of Orange Lounge Radio on this lovely
Sunday evening July the 5th of 2009 believe it or not we are halfway through
the year I can't even believe it we are still of course taping live as we always
do every week at all games radio www.allgames.com if you are listening live
come join us in chat chat.orangeloungeradio.com I don't know why we use a
separate chat from all games radio but we do we just always have because
remember Orange Lounge Radio was its own station now is at this point many years
ago I don't even remember when we pulled the plug on live 365 but it was a while
ago now it's about a year and a half ago so we've been at all games radio ever
since our our new home where we were syndicated for a while and now we're
somewhat of an all-games exclusive but of course you can always get the podcast
when I'm able to get it up to date and I apologize again that I'm not always
current but I try to be please no it's not a anti podcast thing I promise
anyway part B here we go we're gonna get to your mailbag and the FUs of the week
and the release dates we got all sorts of stuff we should go still get a cover
I'm sure though Loki has a little few more news stories for us I have tons of
news stories and let's talk about a music game because that's what's awesome
DJ Hero announced of course that they're gonna be I should say Activision
announced the DJ Hero would contain Grandmaster Flash and not only will he
be appearing in the game as himself and you know among the cast of other DJs
that are in the game but he'll also be contributing to songs including one
remix as Herbie Hancock rocket versus nerds lap dance and then also Grand
Master Flash here comes my DJ and versus Gary Newman cars I'm all about DJ Hero I
think this game looks awesome yes yes it looks really sweet I'm not surprised
though that they're including the old you know some of the old the some of the
deep famous DJ is kind of like they do in guitar here all right you have like
slash shows up and you know buckethead and some of these people so it's pretty
cool yeah so I'm very cool and you know just excited that we're gonna we're
hearing more songs coming out of it um what else was I wanted to say about DJ
Hero it's still gonna be extensive though of course is the only kind of
outside but what do you do but the thing is though is it's the only game I'm
buying this fall really out of all the stuff coming out this fall silly game
I'm buying this fall because you can't pirate the the turntable I see how you
know it really deserves my money but um yeah it's just you know with kids coming
you know really honestly I mean piracy aside you know I'm probably not gonna
be playing a lot of games in the fall we'll be playing the grant of thought oh
expansion a new one but that's for sure but really with kids coming is just like
I'll be lucky to play DJ Hero I hope we get DJ Samantha Ronson in the game though
so we can have her girlfriend Lindsay Lohan or on again off again girlfriend
make a cameo pretty awesome I think so yeah but is she any good has she
actually made music I think she's a somewhat respected DJ I think it's more
than just who her girlfriend is Sacramento not that long ago they were
promoting it on the radio I don't know I had there's a lot joking I don't think
she's a long list of other DJs I'd rather see in the game than her fine fine
I try to make a silly little joke I know that's what I do like have we heard a
lot about download content with DJ hero there will be some that's about all we
know because I know someone actually I for whatever reason they have visited
their website and actually looked at their Twitter and there was someone
asking hey is there gonna be download content and they're like of course
there's gonna be download content but not necessarily regularly like you see
in rock band because guitar heroes download content seems to be a bit more
sporadic yeah I'd be guessing that's gonna be a bit more sporadic Marissa
congusto in our chat room chat that orange laundry calm says it could be a
pixelated low hand tweeting naked pics that would be a true to life wouldn't it
a little to do life all right what else you have for us lovey also of course not
really something I would utilize and not really something you'd utilize anymore
but Twitter has come to Warcraft thanks to tweet craft a in-game client that you
can get you can now Twitter inside the confines of Warcraft this would actually
be cool believe it or not if I was like a role player I think it would be kind
of neat to have a character using a Twitter like create a character and have
them tweet about the things they're doing in World of Warcraft and I think
that's probably what most people use it for but I just hope it doesn't turn into
this whole like oh I just turned in this quest oh I just dinged to level 77 oh
we're running this instance anyone want to join because we don't really need to
fill Twitter up with that garbage I hope none of my personal friends are you
gonna use this for that but if they're using it to keep all the crack in their
vein like they play World of War crack and have Twitter at the same time like
I can also understand the need to have that crack all at once all they need now
is Facebook as well in World of Warcraft if they don't already have it and then
everybody's crack should be set I know according to the screen shot here it
doesn't look like they're using it for roleplay in fact one of the people says
thank God CNN's finally segueing from reporting on Michael Jackson's still
being dead to reporting on what happened to bubbles the chimp nice formation we
need to know right away I'm reading this stuff in chat which is great
tiger class says great now you can tweet when you're in a wow raid SSJ 100 Matt
says at Rob I just got a four strength force damn leather belt that's a all
games inside joke I'll have you know frisbee says mom bathroom nice let's
just encourage people to not have any human interaction whatsoever by putting
Twitter in World of Warcraft exactly I'm not gonna say I'm glad I left because
I'm not vindictive about the reasons I left but I am I'm I'm comfortable with
my decision and you know that there's many other games to be playing right now
and something although sorry I will say this I am kind of sad that I feel like
some people I don't talk to anymore because I don't play World of Warcraft
which is kind of sad I'm like just call me dude let's hang out let's do some
besides rating hang out in World of Warcraft
I know no it's something you may need if you really you're you know living the
sedentary lifestyle hopefully I will never need this but there is a new DS
plug-in that you can use with your DS and DS I because it actually plugs into
the DS slot and not the you know the gameboy advanced lot but it is a a
device called digit and it's for helping diabetic kids record their sugar levels
so that they can see if they're okay you know it helps them test their sugar and
I don't know so really you can turn your DS into a diabetic monitor now yeah it's
a you know sugar glucose reader and it's I'm not sure if you can use this like
well I'll tell you right now your insurance ain't gonna cover it so what
you're gonna be paying for that out-of-pocket but I guess what it is
probably it's like a diabetic monitor you know when you're diabetic you have
to track you know this I'm you have to track your glucose several times a day
it depends on how you know there's different stages of diabetes is a very
common disease like Halle Berry has diabetes a lot of very famous people
have diabetes you have to track your your sugar levels several points
throughout the day and then it's you might be what they call insulin
dependent or if your levels are really out of whack you have to inject yourself
with insulin this monitor if they're encouraging kids to use this monitor
there with their DS is probably a way to kind of track those levels but more so
for their parents to look at it I bet is it's actually kind of a neat use of
technology I actually think it's kind of a neat use of the DS this is this is a
feel-good CNN good news story of the week type thing and intended in think of
it first screw you vitality monitor alpha
kenanagram in chat says Loki yeah this looks like bears ray rebranding of the
glucose boy independent they look the same so I'm guessing bear about the tech
from the guy that made glucose boy probably possibly who knows frisbee
Aston chat where can I when can I have the Wii Fit glaucoma meter so I do think
it's a pretty pretty neat idea hey look you brought up World of Warcraft earlier
and I want to talk about this a little bit because I thought this story was
very interesting having been in a game that was ruined by gold farming or in
that particular game Gill farming the game was completely ruined by that
although they have made a motion to fix it I'll give credit where credit is due
but it came way too late anyhow there was just stories going crazy around the
net this week that China had actually banned gold farming which is a huge
industry in China it's what like 500 million dollar industry in China that it
was banned this week which is huge news well I don't know if you're aware but
not really that's not really what happened here's what China really banned
was using virtual money for gambling and will be you know punished by you know
public security authorities and miners cannot use cannot buy virtual money
here's what it really comes down to is I think it's well a it's miners too it's
not you know adults but also the fact that the real problem and and Richard
Heeks who is a professor at the University of Manchester kind of breaks
it down it's what it really is is using these fake currencies one of the big
ones is called QQ coins used to buy real I know it's funny huh used to of QQ I
don't have any real money using these QQ coins to pay for virtual game stuff
apparently some folks were using them to pay for real things and that's what the
law is to prevent using virtual currency to buy real products that's what it
comes down to and most people are when you do gold farming that's the other way
around you're paying real money for virtual items that's still okay it's the
other way around that is now illegal which isn't going to impact any of the
gold farming industry I'm sorry to say and that makes everyone go QQ exactly
because the QQ dollars are still out there that's all I got that's funny do
you think they should ban the real thing I don't know if they can that's where I'm
at I'm like you know what why bother at this point it's out there it's up to the
game makers I think to some extent to stop this shit if they want to really they
if they really wanted to stop this crap they could but most don't and really you
know as much as I see you know you know it it's not a good thing to buy money
they're kind of doing the work and earning the money they're not really
exploiting unless they're exploiting the game is cheap and get the money you know
if they're earning the money in the game and there's someone out there it's
desperate enough to pay for that money. I don't see the problem in that. I see the
problem in if they're cheating to get the money and then it screws up the whole
economy. Plus, it also depends on the game's design. Like, I don't think gold
farming is that big of an epidemic in World of Warcraft. I know it's out there,
I know it's being done, but in World of Warcraft it's not that hard to make
money. They have dailies, they have ways to make money. Gold farming is for lazy
people. If people are too lazy to make gold the hard way. Now here's the thing,
in Final Fantasy XI, you couldn't make gil that easily. You could not make gil
as easily as you can make money. And some would argue with me, you know, and
that's just ridiculous. And again, I realize the game has changed an
awful lot since I left. You know, now they have more things that are solo. I'm
talking about the old Final Fantasy XI. Things that I hope Square has learned
before Final Fantasy XIV, in other words, is that, you know, gil farming was an
epidemic and it was killing the game. Because what would happen is, yeah, what
was the only way to make gil? You camp these notorious monsters that would drop
items that would be worth millions of gil. Well guess what? All the gold farmers
are out there camping with you and they got good at it. But WoW doesn't have
that as an epidemic. So, you know, finally, years later, they changed it in Final
Fantasy where the items would bind a certain way. You know, it just took them
too damn long to do it. Lessons, again, I hope they have learned moving into Final
Fantasy XIV. Because Final Fantasy XIV has the potential to be amazing.
Rama asked in our chat room, chat.orangemanstrategy.com, now with Final
Fantasy XIV will they shut down Final Fantasy XI? Hardly. No. Will they have
to do server consolidations and things of this sort? Probably. Will they lose
players? Probably. But they'll probably charge more for Final Fantasy XIV. Not a
lot more, but they'll probably charge like 1495 or 1595 a month. Because they
could probably get away with it. So they won't care if people jump ship because
they'll end up making more money off of them. I guess XI. It's actually... I had a lot of fun with it.
I did too, you know, but I'll tell you what, Loki, I went back, tried to play
again. It's just, you know, maybe if all the people were still there, which I don't
think is gonna happen, it would be kind of cooler. But the way it is right now,
I just... I don't have the time for an MMO anyway, so... But I'm looking forward to
Final Fantasy XIV. I am definitely looking forward to Final Fantasy XIV. I'm all
over that shit. I'm not looking forward to it because I won't be able to play it,
probably. Poor thing. What you can do, come over to my house. You can play.
Just, you know, tell the wife you're coming over to hang out with Rob. We're gonna
watch movies. Bring the kids! Get them into it. No, no, no, that, you know, I... Nellie
doesn't want the kids playing video games. I mean, basically she doesn't want them
ignoring homework to play the video games. Just fine. I understand that,
because, you know what, I never did that. I always did my homework, and then, well, I
most of the time did my homework, and I didn't really, you know, play video games.
It wasn't an issue like that, but they're gonna play video games. They're, yeah,
they're gonna play video games more than the other. I think what your wife
hopefully already knows is that if you try to stop them from doing it, they're
just going to want to do it more. So you just have to find a balance, is that you
can play one out. You can use the TV for two hours. You want to watch cartoons. You
want to play video games. Whatever the F you want to do on the TV. I wouldn't say
that, obviously, but whatever the F, and me explaining it to you, whatever the F
you want to do for the TV with two hours, that's yours. But either A, once your
homework gets done first, or B, once your two hours is up, you better be doing your
homework, or you're gonna lose your TV time, you know, something like that.
That's the kind of system I think you have to do. Always homework first.
Yes. Okay, let's talk a little bit about, wait, can I say, can I say, because this is
obviously a sparked discussion in our chat room. I have to read this at
chat.orangelandtrader.com. First off, about Final Fantasy XI and Final Fantasy XIV,
SGA 100 Matt says they said they will continue to release expansion for Final Fantasy XI,
and especially now that they're doing the download expansions now, like there's
the MOG, the coup d'etat, or whatever they call it. What the hell is it called,
the new Mughal one? The coup d'etat is coming out today, I think, is
when it came out. They're doing the download ones now. They'll continue to do
that. Just like EverQuest and EverQuest 2 is that I think, unlike EverQuest and EverQuest 2,
I think you will see a lot more players on Final Fantasy XIV than XI. I think a lot of
people who left XI are gonna come back for XIV. I think that will happen.
Also, some comments on the babies. Tigerclaw says they're gonna play video games while
parents are asleep. That's true. If the TV is in the kids room with the console,
they're gonna play the video games while you sleep. TV is not gonna be in the kids room.
GS68 says, from kindergarten through third grade, my parents would only let me play video games on
weekends. And I'm thinking, you know, the kids can play not the new console games.
They gotta play the old stuff, because it also is more family-friendly, you know, whereas the new stuff,
you know, no playing Grand Theft Auto. Although, although with Grand Theft Auto, you know, I know
enough about hacking that I could probably take out the blood and stuff.
Marisa Congusto in chat says, my dad had a really good parenting strategy so I
couldn't play too many video games. He played them so I couldn't. That's more
like it. You should suggest that to the wife. I'm only playing video games
so the kids can do their homework. I'm doing you a favor. Now cook dinner.
Then she needs to learn how to play video games, I don't know. Alright. Yeah, you're gonna learn how to play video games or cook dinner.
You need to play one or the other. She's gonna cook dinner because she hates video games.
Or she'll play Animal Crossing for the rest of her life. To talk a little bit more about Sony
PlayStation. You may remember, of course, they have their PlayStation Eye-based
motion capture system that they're planning on using for some really
retarded looking ice cream cone things. But there's apparently another tech thing
that they, I guess, registered a patent for that's gonna utilize what looks like
a giant square-shaped U-thing. Almost like the U-Force. You know, kind of scary
enough, but apparently you would use this device in your hands, I guess, in
replace, you know, to replace the cosmic ice cream cone thing. But you would use it,
I guess, like a, you know, baseball bat or golf club or, you know, sword, whatever.
That thing's gonna get broken. That thing looks retarded, if you ask me. Well, maybe
it was just patented. That doesn't necessarily mean they're gonna use it. I
don't know. Just a giant U of death. applicant anagram is saying that's just
a random object, not a controller. That the U is supposed to represent some type
of object the person has in their home. And that's what I had thought I'd read
is something about that you can use this thing is supposed to be, like, so any
object can be used in the game. Which is kind of similar. Isn't that similar to what
Natal was saying, too? Yeah. It's gonna be able to scan, like, the kid's skateboard
in a little preview. Okay, well that, yeah. So something similar here, right? That'll work as
well as they show, but yeah. That's neat. I don't like the idea of those swinging
around something that even resembles a baseball bat in my house, so. Unless it's
a Nerf bat. Even then. Couldn't you just roll up a piece of paper and tell the
game it's a bat? It would work, right? Roll up the newspaper, thunk. Couldn't I
hold up the cat and say it's a baseball bat? How long is it gonna take before
someone tries to use their penis on this? It's gonna happen. That's the age-old
question about new peripherals. How long before a penis is used with it? How long?
Try 30 seconds. That's the length of time to unzip and unzip the pants and undo the
bell buckle. Scan this! Oh my god. Alright. Hey, look. We got some emails we got to
read, so let's get to the mailbag. How's that sound? Mailbag at orangelawnsradio.com
That's where you send your emails every week and we read some of our favorites
here on the show. That's exactly what I'm gonna do right now. If the Star Stalker's not here
tonight, I will read them. If you can scan its objects to be used as guns, you can
have your own laser tag. Yes, whatever happened to laser cat the video game? You
think with community games we would have this now? I'm surprised we don't.
Somebody needs to get on that. Sorry, I had the music blaring that whole time.
Mailbag at orangelawnsradio.com if you want to send us an email. Email. First email
to us tonight comes from Rick and Rick sent us an email and the subject is
Nintendo divorce notice. I would like to hereby make public my intention to
divorce Nintendo after many faithful years of devotion to each and every
Nintendo console that has been released. After investing many years of my life
playing the great library of classic games including a substantial financial
investment, I feel my relationship with the Wii is drawing to a close. We made it
past the rough patch a few years ago with the GameCube and yes I admit I did
cheat on Nintendo with Microsoft and bought an Xbox. I've already apologized
for this affair. It's in the past we moved on. And then the Wii came along and
life was good again. We had such good times together with Zelda, Metroid and
Mario but there was something wrong, something nagging in the back of my mind.
Could it be all the shovelware that was becoming more and more common? Could it
be all the ported games with waggle attached for no fucking reason? Could it
be last year's E3? Could it be all the party games? What's next? Motion control?
Yaris? The answer to all these questions is yes. You just don't seem to be trying
anymore Nintendo. Do you care? I waited and waited watching this year's E3 for a
sign that you still cared but no you let me down yet again. Why should I stay? What
can you offer me as a reason to hang around? Why shouldn't I just go and sell
my Wii and put the money towards a PlayStation 3? More Mario Galaxy you
lazy bastards that's just fat you trimmed from Galaxy One. Mario multiplayer
ported from the DS. Zelda? A painting? A frickin poster? And they said the Zelda
game actually is not gonna be very different than the first one which means
it's gonna be raining on the same engine. I'm reading this poor man's please
to the divorce court. A statement about no sword? That's it? Get fucked! Kid IKEA
RS? Oh there oh it's there it's coming news flash we don't care anymore. At the
end of the day I'm going to be a dad soon and my time will be a precious
commodity. I need to know that you are taking things seriously if not I'm
walking to the nearest Sony store. It's so sad. You used to try so hard and
produce such wonderful gaming experiences. You were top of the pile now
you're more bothered about coming on to my grandmother and small children. You
disgust me Nintendo. Regards Rick. P.S. I get custody of the Nintendog. Well we will
see how that holds up in divorce court with judge who is it in divorce court
Judge Mabel? He's Judge Mabel. Of course if he's in the UK he's not even gonna
get that joke so forget it. All right that was a well-written divorce letter
and I can't say I it's tough it's tough being a hardcore gaming fan and watching
what's going on with the Wii but at the same time I think he summed it up right
at the end they're more interested in hitting on your grandmother and little
children and they're doing a good job of it you can't deny that but you know
we're just not the bread and butter for Nintendo anymore maybe Nintendo felt
they already lost us between the 64 and the GameCube. I don't know. Well wait not
to try. But my thought is a lot of us were children or at least younger when
those systems were out I mean wouldn't you I don't know. The problem is they're
kind of catering to stupid people but they think that people like they're oh
my god you know games are so hard I can't play them well you give it to a
kid you know he's gonna figure it out I mean I was a kid I figured out how
to play video games you know it may not have been I may not have been good at it
at first but it took time I had to practice get better and you know
nowadays I think kids should do the same thing because if they're just
immediately great at it then good that gives them a self-esteem boost but they
still suck it's just the game is really easy. Now I'm looking in chat and some
folks want the emailer to understand about Metroid Other M they neglected in
their whole little statement there but J-Rod offered up this interesting
retort I can think of at least three games from both Sony and Microsoft for me
three that I want on day one Nintendo had one game during a two-hour
conference. Yeah that is true so but I mean does look cool. Metroid M does look
sweet. They just need like ten more of those. And here's the thing though
okay is it looks cool but is it actually gonna be cool? We'll see we'll give them
the benefit of the doubt we'll see but again they need ten of those. Yeah they
really do need more hits throughout the year I mean because I'm sorry but you
know people will probably be dumb enough to buy New Super Mario Brothers Wii
because it's got Mario in the name and because some parents are like oh my god
Mario I gotta buy it you know and they don't know anything about it could be
Mario teaches Sudoku and they would probably buy that crap but I don't know.
Email number two tonight of five emails we got a few to burn through tonight
email number two comes to us from serious turtle this is a very serious
turtle we need to take this very seriously guys a couple months ago I
discovered podcast alley and thus your show I forgot we were listed on podcast
alley that's an old-school podcast podcast exactly oh my lucky stars I've
been needing a show like this my whole life I don't have any friends who are
hardcore gamers like me so when I heard your show it was fantastic to hear
people like me who talked about the things I care about thanks for all the
time you invest in the show and tell Loki to stop yelling the turtle sorry I
have a problem look this this serious turtle has it has a serious issue with
you Loki and that is that you yell too damn much I got to talk to you that's
something this is great oh no totally go on a tangent but oh alright funny fine
so apparently earlier this week Nellie was convinced that I had Asperger's
syndrome isn't that kind of like it's like autism okay so she so your wife
thinks you're autistic yes yes because apparently people stricken with Asperger's
they have the tendency to be very focused on certain things or whatever
basically you know I piss her off a lot by like going on my computer and working
on something for a while and not realizing what I'm doing not realizing
it's making her angry and some of that and there is a lot of times that I do
that and I don't realize it's making her angry I don't really cuz in my mind it
justify like oh okay well I hung out with her quite a bit in stuff but you
know I guess it's not the right time to be doing that or something like that or
like all randomly blurred out stuff like like at your party or something there's
people talking about something and somehow I found a way to work in games
in there and I blurted out something completely random about like you know
like they're talking about like some song may hear something, hey that song is in
rock band you know it's supposed to be coming out in a few weeks on you know
download content or something it's like no one cares but you know for whatever
reason I feel compelled to do that all the time and I can't stop myself you
just this show just isn't enough Loki you've spent seven years okay you've
spent at least seven years of your life getting the gaming knowledge out there
in a way this radio station is perfect for you I don't think it's as per I
don't know go to a doctor and no no there's no it there's nothing that has
to do that because it's actually you're very socially you know unable to cope
with everything basically you can't well I think there's a function in society
we're not medical professionals not even gonna try and get into it but it's you
know it was funny because there's a lot of symptoms on there and they're like
they're different work fields that would be perfect okay but look you go into web
MD like yeah and you tell web MD you have certain symptoms I've got this and
this and this this every time it tells you cancer every time you go in there
and you're like oh I've got cancer I've got a rash on my ass and it kind of you
know it flames love oh you have ass cancer you know like or like or yeah
you're all yes or no it's not the Tuma anyway sorry to get off on tangent there
I just thought it was funny all right next email yes please next email stop
trying to talk about things you know nothing about all right this comes to us
from death wishing I feel like I have not been involved in your shows for a
long time have I missed a lot yes anyways now to get on with some email
material have you guys ever heard of a game called urban terror well if you
have not then there is no reason to not try the game because because well it's
absolutely free it was originally a quake 3 mod and then went into its own
standalone game I cannot describe how it plays but I guess it's a miss a miss I
think a combination of counter-strike and quake hence it being a quake 3 mod
well let's hope I don't miss the cast again I've never heard of this any urban
terror so the only thing I've heard of there was a urban chaos or something
like that game that was from idos or something that really sucked but that
sounds kind of neat email number four from shook hi everyone I've been
following this show for about three months and I can honestly say that this
is the best video game related show I've ever listened to why thank you I
encourage you guys to keep doing this show and if you're reading this on the
seventh anniversary I wish to congratulate you on the feet well you're
a week late but that's probably my fault because the seventh anniversary show
still hasn't hit the feed but thank you nonetheless seventh anniversary or not
we'll just say we'll say that's a pre grats for our eighth anniversary yeah
there you go last email tonight from the one and only spazzinator hi everyone I
thought I'd write this email for tonight show mainly to share a tidbit of info by
the looks of things Sony will be doing three things more or less in tandem this
summer rolling out the long rumor ps3 slim drop the price of the ps3 by an
unknown amount and release firmware 3.0 which by most accounts will be a fairly
big overhaul so I'm reading this email because we've addressed some of this but
we didn't really talk about new firmware most sources agree that firmware 3.0 has
certain features on it similar to what Xbox Live has reputation and griefing
procedures as well as finally being able to download game updates in the
background where there is still some debate as to whether or not firmware 3.0
will also incorporate the recently uncovered patented ps2 emulator that
will supposedly work on all ps3s my suspicions are that the emulator will
indeed be coming most likely in firmware 3.0 or at least in the next major from
where to firmware update after that my reasoning is this there's no reason for
any company Sony or any other one to patent anything unless they see a way to
make money off of it directly or indirectly seeing as the PlayStation 3
sales have been lagging behind the Wii's in the 360s hell even the ps2s these
moves that I've mentioned should in theory bolster sales which is
ultimately what Sony and some third-party developers want ultimately
this is all just hearsay educated guessing on my part until we see here
something official however given my tracker record in as far as far as relaying
info it's subsequently being true see a prior story I related regarding Capcom
releasing games on PSN odds are this will be true proven true as well well
that's a and it also bit of a it also makes sense to think about it kind of
eases them into digital distribution with ps3 games because you have the ps2
games coming out now and I'm assuming those are gonna be at a higher price
point than the PlayStation 1 games were you know for the most part I would
assume that they're gonna be maybe around you know 15 20 15 to I would say
even 15 to like $30 maybe 15 25 ish and if that does well then of course and I
mean hey let's release some PlayStation 3 games you know for more money as well
and see if we can get away with selling those so I'm not I'm pretty sure we'll
probably see this stuff layers here all right well let me finish up this email
here on a personal note I do hope that at least the emulator part is shown to
be true me too although I used to have a 60 gigabyte model PlayStation 3 with full
backwards compatibility I no longer had that due to unfortunate circumstances
and was forced to settle for a non backwards compatible model hopefully
this emulator will allow me to play my ps2 games again well thanks for taking
this email it's appreciated and keep up the excellent work this email was
brought to you by Loki's tingle costume which kindly asks him to wear it lol
thus ends the email back tonight mailbag orange launcher calm if you have an
email you want to send us in a future week sorry I think we'll cost him I do
believe that you are about 800,000 copies shy in other words yes I made the
costume yet you're gonna have to get to like 50,000 it's never gonna happen
they've stopped making the game it's done it's not gonna happen done deal you
need yet now all of you should be focusing on a new bet you can get low
you know I am not making any bets on the PSP go I'm sorry I don't know that's
gonna do because there are a lot of to be honest you know I have a problem with
people buying the iPhone because I think it's retarded but you know there are
people out there that like to spend a lot of money on stuff that's kind of you
guys are gonna have to think really hard and also Frisbee brings up a good point
Sackboy costume was better anyway let's not forget Loki did dress up as
Sackboy which is pretty exactly I have the head now in my garage I know it
scared the hell out of me when I first saw it all right some more news then
we'll get into some release dates and the FUs of the week as well let's see
here so let's talk a little bit about Xbox 360 we've got last M they've got
some information on that and how will be integrated into the new Xbox experience
apparently elastic last FM is gonna be free for gold subscribers however if you
are still remember you do get to use three hours per month and if you're a I
guess you'll have to shell out I guess another $36 a year if you're still
remember and just want to use last FM which you might as well buy a fucking
gold subscription points yeah might as well so apparently yes silver members
will be able to access I guess trial period of three hours a month and comes
with video advertising which might get into something else we'll talk about in
just a second here and I thought is this isn't now my hope was that I'd be able
to use last FM as my in-game music but that's not really what they're going for
is it this is just gonna be like a cable channel or something I guess yeah I don't
like the cable music channel instant party just add last FM or something I
don't know like I've yet to really hear what is this used for I don't know I
hope you can use like in-game music pretty cool that would be pretty cool
actually is trying out you know the custom soundtracks with fuel the other
day only two funny and it doesn't have the greatest soundtrack it really
doesn't it's it's got what I like to call excite truck syndrome where you add
new music to it instantly makes the game better you know yeah yeah so I don't
know it it's alright but um I see I've never used last FM on PC so I don't
really know if it's something that I'd be really excited about to be honest I
mean I like listening to new music and discovering new artists and stuff but I
don't think they have as eclectic tastes as I would have you know I don't know I
guess I'll check it out I am a gold number so too bad it's not live through
CC 5 instead of last FM I know right I'm saying something nice about life is
CC 5 but seriously we might almost consider going back if they could have
that on the Xbox marketplace how about we do shoutcast I know there you go how
about shoutcast exactly then you can have all games radio on there and and
which would include us of course and you know all the other great stations that
come with shoutcast but I don't know maybe an IRC let's add IRC in there too
and you won't need a PC you can just do it through the 360 exactly that's why I
would love to have this show is be able to live I mean you can already hear it
on your PSP which is cool but that's like one system out of a lot I guess
it's one nice thing I could say about the PSP is that yeah by the way we
wouldn't really go back to life this is five chat don't panic we're not really
gonna do that besides you know what's funny is that since the show is actually
kind of grown a little bit in numbers since we kind of combined with Bobby and
we have some of the holdovers from his show and I know he gets a boost from us
I don't think we could do the show on like these five anymore without being a
professional station we have too many people which is a nice compliment
certainly to you know the the listeners and the fact that the show has grown and
we're very thankful for that we actually could not afford to do this show on
like 365 anymore so don't worry that's not happening I was just making a bad
joke sheesh so it's kind of surprising is to go off completely off topic from
that Blizzard apparently is not gonna be including land support of course with
the Starcraft 2 game oh I heard about this and a lot of people pissed off
because you know land is I mean how Starcraft 2 and your Starcraft 1 and I
think when you're like counter-strike I mean those are land games right there
and you know I know land play is a huge thing especially land parties you know
like Korea and stuff and the centers the land party centers exactly well I mean
they still have play over there you know battle net stuff but I mean it's not the
same so you can still have a land party it's just that you're all gonna have to
have an internet connection yeah which in this Wi-Fi day and age shouldn't be
that difficult but still it is kind of crazy I mean if you think about it let
there is more lag I think involved with you know that because you're not just
you're playing off of a local network but I don't know that kind of sucks but
basically you know Blizzard's responding to the whole you removal of it because
everyone was pissed off there we don't currently plan to support land play in
Starcraft 2 as we are building battle net to be the ideal destination for
multiplayer gaming with Starcraft 2 and feature Blizzard entertainment games
while this was a difficult decision for us we felt that moving away from land
play and directing players to our upgrade bell net service was the best
option to ensure a quality multiplayer experience with Starcraft 2 and
safeguard against piracy as she went under madam chat says hell I'm having a
party next week and we intend on playing mass Starcraft via LAN you know here's
the thing though here's the thing it's not like you can't still get everyone in
a room together and play this game together you just have to do it on the
internet which I know kind of sucks and they want they want to do that so that
it validates your copy exactly they're trying to it's piracy yeah they're
trying to curb someone's gonna create a client that's gonna act like battle net
that you'll connect to that and you'll be able to play land with and guess who
will be doing that the pirates because they'll figure out a way around this I
kind of agree Blizzard ought to know better than this the that they're gonna
take it out and someone's gonna find a way to put it back in you know what I
mean it's it they might as well just put it in there and just encourage people to
buy the game legitimately you know have one computer on the land sneak onto the
internet and see if the other copies are validated certainly there's a way this
could be done certainly like if one computer like creeps onto the internet
battle net could somehow it's kind of tell I don't know I'm just crazy and of
course you know everyone's pissed off and what happens when people get pissed
off they start a petition and so they have a petition created you know that's
basically insisting that blizzard ad land support back I can't wait for that
question to be asked at this year's Blizzcon because that is one interesting
thing about this story is that oops they maybe should have waited to say
something about this until after Blizzcon but they said something about
it before so what's gonna be awesome is that now there's gonna be these big
panels on Starcraft then when they take questions why the hell did you take out
land support you douche can't wait next question because we did next question
no they'll say they'll get blah blah blah well we think the marketplace is
shifting and we just wanted to encourage folks to use battle net so that they
could track their achievements and everything is statistic based and if we
do the land then we can't have that you're gonna get some talk around
the answer just wait yeah just wait let's talk a little bit about the Dreamcast
yes Dreamcast is of course getting yet another game and much like the
other you know new games for the Dreamcast that have been coming out
recently is another shmup game the brand-new 2d shoot-em-up game named
ducks do you X and it's actually being sold I guess right now for $27.90 I'm not
sure if it's gonna be a disk space game or not I guess it could be since you
know Dreamcast can pretty much read any sort of burn disk and apparently I guess
they have another game that's also coming out as well the company Hugh cast
and it's I guess the title is last hope pink bullets which I guess was
co-developed by the shins hmm which Wow not heard of any of these things
apparently that's actually like the shins like the band the shins huh
interesting but yeah I mean it's it's still nice to see I guess games coming
out for the Dreamcast prequel all right well you know what guys I think it's
time to I get into the F use of the week we wouldn't want to forget it this week
so we got to get into the F use of the week and of course the story that
inspires our angst this week
this has to do with the case of the stolen we this week three teens Josh
Carter and a 16 year old and a 13 year old were all arrested on felony charges
this week because they stole their neighbors we well here's the thing the
mother 41 year old Maxine law actually helped them get rid of the we at a local
pawn shop she knew damn well the thing was stolen so they stole this thing from
the neighbor and then the parents or the mom I should say parents mom helped them
sell it off at a local pawn shop it was being reported by WF TV in Orlando the
Maxine law will probably be charged with dealing in stolen property and
contributing to the delinquency of minors you should know better you stupid
that makes me angry low-key F use the week I guess F you did not have enough
time to play games and being broke more or less
I don't really have a lot of F use this week I'm generally feeling pretty good
so I guess I would just also give an F you to not having enough hours in the
day to play video games and F you to Facebook games for being so stupidly
addicting
alright let's move on with some more gaming news we got release dates to get
to two will get to those in a little bit after another couple stories
let's talk about some free games a free yes free is good and these are actually
some pretty good free games both happen to be fighting games on the first one is
a game called vanguard princess and I guess it's a 2d freeware fighter game
developed by a looks like a Tomohaki Sugeno and apparently he is an ex cap
com employee and the game looks pretty sweet actually you know definitely on
par with like something like guilty gear even and that's available for download
apparently off of a website www.vector.co.jp that's vector and just do a
search for I guess vanguard princess and also the kind of go along with that is a
game called dark presence and dark presence is a digitized fighting game
very similar to the old Mortal Kombat games and like like Street Fighter the
movie the game where they actually captured the the faces of people they're
making a new game like this yes that is freaking awesome and actually I take
that back this is not a not a free game but apparently new arcade game is not a
new arcade game that's pretty awesome so wow that looks really crappy if it's
an arcade game I don't know well I was reading something about like it's got
more animation I guess than any game like it has ever existed so it's
supposed to be a smoother looking game then you know the Mortal Kombat games
were which I would hope you know I've been it has been many years the
technology hopefully to me it looks like one of those cheesy like games that you
would see in a movie or something like that when they're trying to create a
game in the movie that you know supposed to represent like a Mortal Kombat type
ish game you know something really low-budget but hey whatever if it comes
out and turns out be cool you know hey Mortal Kombat at the time I think you
know it looks sort of cheesy on a certain level so yeah more power to him
all right let's get into release dates shall we we're gonna travel around the
world now and talk about what is coming out around the world we're gonna start
tonight with Japan's this is a release dates I have up right now coming out in
Japan on July the 9th Major League Baseball 2009 comes to the Xbox 360 as
well as WWE legends of WrestleMania also making its way to the 360 this coming
week on July the 9th coming out on the PlayStation 3 siren gets a price drop
into PlayStation 3's best series as well as WWE legends of WrestleMania also
comes out on July the 9th moving on to some other systems we have on the
Nintendo Wii I believe is next yes nothing really coming out this week in
Japan the next big release Dragon Ball game coming out July 23rd but a little
quiet for Wii games right now which is a little strange usually they're still
pretty busy Major League Baseball 2009 also makes way the PlayStation 2 this
week kind of not surprised though that a baseball release would be kind of the
big thing in Japan this week you get some new peripherals for the DS some
Disney character headphones coming out but otherwise there's really not a lot
of new games coming out but there is a price drop coming out on hamster to
coulda so comes out I'm sorry doesn't come out gets a price drop this week
which is this happy hamster looking game no I was saying in ten dogs but it's
hamsters they do look very cute though oh no sign of Richard Gere in the game
by the way and then let's see on the PSP bleach gets a price reduction heat the
soul five another port of Major League Baseball 2009 this week and yeah looks
like this is a big week for baseball in Japan but otherwise nothing else to
really note how about the u.s. u.s. there isn't really a lot of stuff coming out
this week pretty much your big release is gonna be the bigs 2 which is coming
out on PlayStation 2 ps3 Xbox 360 and the Wii and believe the PSP also this
week we've got looks like oh the crappy game here huh and see that on there
birthday party bash on the Wii which you know apparently it's a birthday party
kit in the box I don't know if you're a mom maybe that might be interesting for
a little birthday parties for your kids also this week we've got a port of a
game that came out in the UK Sid the dummy which is a crash dummy game
something that would have probably been popular like 20 years ago coming on PSP
ps2 and the Wii we release a Bioshock and Elder Scrolls for oblivion kind of
combined together in the bundle for PC and Xbox 360 the packaged version of
Arma 2 coming on PC which is supposed to be pretty sweet
memento mori on PC and then coming out on Xbox Live and PlayStation Network
this week battlefield 1943 also on we wear this week and PC the first chapter
of the new tales of monkey island series tales of monkey island chapter 1 launch
of the screaming narwhal which sounds pretty cool and also I believe trying
is supposed to be coming out on ps3 as well on the PlayStation Network this
week as well so not really a huge huge week no not really next week I mean July
is really slow for game releases I think next week we've got like NCAA football
2010 so if you're in the college football that'd be good for you but it
really not a lot of big stuff I think at the end of the month course king of
fires 12 so that'd be cool this time of year is usually a little slow isn't it
it's always slow a little bit hey how about the release dates over in Europe
since star soccer is not here tonight allow me to say that in Europe you can
look forward to some of the downloads that we get this week as well tales of
monkey island woohoo battlefield battlefield 1943 as well in Europe this
week but if you want some of the releases in stores cross edge comes out
on PlayStation 3 this week as well as the conduit making its way to the Wii
and trying to coming out on the PC again those are all for Europe this week there
you go a couple more stories then we'll open up the skype line for you guys at
1 8 7 7 game olr to take your calls tonight on anything you want to talk
about apparently according to Sesame Street video games are ok according to
Sesame Street so as opposed to according to joystick or destructoid or Kotaku or
one of the big game blogs this week it's according to Sesame Street yes
apparently I see let's see apparently a game changer report issued by Joan
Ganz Clooney Center from the Sesame Workshop basically says that
governments the health care industry and schools should be spending less time
hating on video games and their negative effort our native negative effects and
said be conducting research on their positive effects on kids the port says
that games not only can be educational but in this day and age active as well
meaning they can be used everywhere from a history classroom to a PE class and of
course you know they're all saying the Joan Ganz Clooney Center is to foster
innovation and children's learning through digital media so that's their
kind of did you hear that Jack Voldemort you listening and yeah that's kind of
neat I hope we get a song about it that Elmo sings video games okay just do your
homework then you can play hopefully Elmo will never have to explain to
children what teabagging is in halo
there's some contest there in there that I want to do about who can write the
best Sesame Street song for something obscene in gaming nice oh my gosh gold
anthro and chat says another reason that says me Street is awesome first the
death episode and now video games kind of talking about something we talked
about last week
all right hey by the way speaking of media I don't know if you guys heard
about this but apparently they want to make a movie out of asteroids yes ah the
old-ass fucking game from 1979 that many of you know from the Atari 2600
asteroids Universal has somehow gotten the rights to make asteroids the Matthew
Lopez is writing the script it's being produced by Lorenzo de Bonaventura who's
I know produce some other stuff this is the weird thing apparently they're
universal is making a lot of movies of some weird shit right now like they they
have the rights to some Hasbro games like battleship in candy land are
supposed to be coming movies as well yeah they picked up a lot of Hasbro stuff
oh you know what where I've heard Lorenzo de Bonaventura before he's
producing that GI Joe movie that's coming out next pretty big movie so it's
not like these are no-name people but well you know pretty big movie but it's
also gonna be a pretty big flop you think so then again then again
transformers has a lot of horrible things going for it and it's still did
very well so who knows by the way the script writer Matthew Lopez had wrote
the movies bedtime stories and race to which mountain and is also wrote the
most recent draft of the sorcerers apprentice there you have it I don't
know about that you know I don't know as long as I mean where where's the movie
in the game I think it there it's not even gonna have a damn thing to do with
the game it's gonna be a space movie called asteroids whoop-dee-doo and what
is it gonna be trying to be true oh my god I shot the asteroid and it turned
into two smaller asteroids oh no quick shoot the UFO for bonus points it should
be funnier for those space invaders tiger contest says there's already an
asteroids movie it's called Armageddon yeah but Armageddon is actually like 10
years old now believe it or not it's kind of an old movie now and they did
time for an update blow up the way to make it multiple asteroids leave yeah I
guess that's true please no dancing animal crackers in the asteroids movie
please no Ben Affleck thank you very much how about we have how many more
stories you have maybe one more for the skype line two more I don't know I don't
know let's do one more then we'll open up the skype line if you want to fill
time with those stories we can okay let's see well I'm not really sad about
this but apparently NetErosy is being shut down Sony is pulling the plug on
the PlayStation 1 development community they're gonna still keep all the
libraries and stuff online but I guess it's officially shut down but honestly
they'll still developing stuff on the PlayStation 1 I mean then again I do say
that in and there are people developing on the Dreamcast but you know what I
think all the people that were developing for the PlayStation 1 should
move to the Dreamcast you know because that's the one that seems to be you
know supported the most and they have a lot of communities for that and stuff
but well for what it's worth you can play a PlayStation 1 game on the
PlayStation 3 at least there's that yeah but you can't actually you know publish
any more PlayStation 1 games and really can only swap you know the games you
make with the NetErosy with the other NetErosy users and I remember there was
a time that actually wanted a NetErosy but that didn't happen I was about 15
years ago all right let's go to the phones they're ringing already one eight
seven seven game olr if you'd like to be on the show tonight but in the meantime
we have the call hi you're on orange launch radio who's this it's the guy in
East Coast with the fastest trigger Rama hi Rama how are you doing I'm pretty
good pretty good what cons you go to this week to as I said the tiger claw I
didn't go to any conventions this week I only do the ones are on East Coast I see
and of course anime expos the big deal on the West Coast this week which by the
way I should say something about this our staffer DJ tyrant Jimmy who used to
host a show on our old network with DMN I keep this breast lol now they used to
host a show together called STFU he writes for our website once in a while
now he actually got some interviews at anime expo I believe we're gonna have
the developers of blaze blue on next week in an interview he did so it's
gonna be weird because it's not an interview we did but we're all about
getting cool like statements from folks that develop games so I'm gonna kind of
take a listen and and pick the parts we're gonna air next week and then you
get the unedited version on the website there you go that's pretty cool but I
will say this for the record ax is not a con it's a trade show it's a you know
what I saw ads for anime Expo up here in Sacramento that's how huge that frickin
thing is well they roll ads for New York anime festival here in New York and on
on on Adult Swim I'm just saying it's considered a trade show because their
board is consistent mostly people in the anime industry I see and they're mostly
sponsoring the con itself so that it's not fan produced it's pretty much that's
why Fana may always kind of puts that big fan that they really sell their
thing on fan made fan produced for the past so many years yeah most cons I've
gone to especially ones I've staffed and mostly fan based cool well that's cool
yeah and I'm sorry I would say all the good cons are fan base but um e3 is
pretty awesome for a trade show so trade shows aren't all bad anyway sorry oh no
go ahead what else did you want to call in about tonight there's a few things
that you spoke of tonight wanted to um throw back at you if you don't mind sure
all right in response earlier about the Sony PSP go and the price as I've been
saying in the chat room for the longest you're paying for the name not the
product Sony has become the IBM of now cuz back in the 80s and 90s IBM
machines were quite expensive but people bought his name IBM was on it but the
only difference was at the time IBM made good quality product Sony not so much
Sony is not Apple they need to realize that Apple can get away with that Sony
can't I know cuz I don't know if you ever noticed um if you ever pick up like
the Best Buy flyers or when Circuit City was still around in their flyers they're
always pushing the ps3s with the Sony televisions if you bought the Sony TV
and the ps3 $200 instant savings or if you bought that with rock band or guitar
hero world tour you save $300 off the complete bundle hmm it's gotten to the
point where Sony cannot sell the ps3 anyway in order for them to push them
out they got a bundle it with something you know I'm reading some interesting
comments from chat room chat that orange laundry calm j-rod and chat says I plan
on buying a PSP go on day one that thing looks pimp as hell don't get me wrong I
think the PSP go looks pretty cool but since I already have PSP there's just
not enough in it for me I don't know I'm not feeling it for two and I would be
all over that fucking thing if it was like 150 even exactly the same price as
the current PSP I would be all over it but it's the it's that 250 it's ah I
can't I can't do it I'm sorry mmm anyway I don't blame you seriously I don't
yeah but you're Sony hater I'm just kidding no I just speak the truth you
know that all right look anything else before I let you go and get some more
callers two quick things number one at the we was all about motion control
would have a shit ton of shovelware games on and as for Starcraft 2 you
don't have a shit ton of shovelware games on it where have you been say what
it does have a shit ton of shovelware games on it where have you been say if
it wasn't for the fact that it was focused on the motion control there
wouldn't be as much shovelware oh okay my bad my bad yeah gotcha I'm oh I've
been told it's only like two games I own for the week every all the other ones I'd
borrowed cuz you know yeah and what was the other thing I'm all about Starcraft
you're not needing land support it doesn't cost that much to put in a internet
connection a router and a 24 port switch to get everybody up and running together
does it do you think it's really gonna have that same feeling though well if
they do it where you log in via the application it shouldn't be that much of
an issue because it milk I have the same lag time as if you're in the same room
you know no depends on who's hosting or all that crap you know I guess true true
all right well thanks for your thoughts Rama and good luck from later j-rod I
wanted to clarify we were saying earlier he says I don't own a PSP so that's why
it's probably so attractive to me yeah I'd be I'd probably be a little more
about the PSP if I didn't already own one but still 250 I don't know hi you're
on orange launch radio who's this hello you're on orange hello hi who's this
hi who is this is Marissa yes hi what's on your mind Marissa
well thanks again I just had to say a belated congrats for last week I wasn't
able to listen in although I heard it was a good show it was a pretty good
show it sadly hasn't hit the podcast feed because I'm a lazy son of a bitch
but it will be hitting it very soon and you guys can hear was that it was a
kind of a little bit of a throwback to the old days it was cool yeah you know
as far as my own gaming week this this fourth of July weekend consisted of
watching Chris play Call of Duty and and how is that is this is this fun to watch
just play you know actually for some reason it puts me to sleep I don't know
what it is the sound of killing and bullets but I just curl up like a cat in
front of his feet and I fall asleep all the sounds of murder just make me
tired yeah I've actually distracted myself with that old you know you're
talking about people doing doing you know making games for Dreamcast and
whatnot no systems I distracted myself with Adam all the adventure game engine
and was playing an alien race game oh yeah the one you linked me to that
looks kind of freaky-deaky but tell us a little bit about this game alien rape
escape or something if you know me I love all the old adventure games oh well
how do you feel about the new monkey island game coming out I haven't even
heard about that to you now so that's cool you know I never got into monkey
island even I was younger you know I love a king's quest people and the
quest for glory people get mad at me but and Indiana Jones or the state of
Atlantis person but I try to remember that the state of Atlantis is going to
be bundled with the new indie game whoo yeah that's right yeah I remember us
reporting on the show a few weeks ago that it was gonna be coming on the Wii
with the game or something like that someday I don't know if it was a
pre-order it's been a while now but I I do I did hear that same thing on the
show I'm still obsessing over the announcement now we made that a new
feast is going to come out but I hadn't just praying every night that I don't
fuck it up isn't how it always goes with old franchises though when they
announce that there's a new one coming out you just pray that they're not gonna
fuck it up yeah well I guess the thing is like one of those took over for
looking glass although I didn't I actually like the X you know via the
platform game the Xbox game at deadly shadows most of the purists didn't like
it and it gets started out kind of lame because they called it a thief with a
four instead of the odd or something and suddenly like that so it's like four
four something now I don't know how to pronounce it but I guess it's just a
working title indeed well Marissa I need to come visit us soon and come be on the
show again I'm hoping that'll happen and you have anything else you want to share
with listeners tonight before we get to some more calls nothing that wouldn't be
sublimely silly so I have have a good night and hopefully I will be seeing you
feeling and you need to call so-and-so all right we'll do honey take care I think
I think we lost her there we go okay well I do hope Marissa comes back to
visit it's been like a hundred episodes since she's been here she's a lot of fun
I've been that long she's like it's I know we've been doing the show a fucking
long time I don't know if you're aware we have another call coming on hi you're
on orange launch radio oops we didn't really answer that call hi you're on
orange launch radio who's this hi this is fancy Nader hi spazz Nader what's on
your mind tonight um two things which are kind of related to some degree go
ahead all right you know I was you know you know you know thinking about that
comment you were making about you know someone's making asteroids movie yes
question is how the hell do you make a movie on the asteroid there's like no
narratives there I mean I can I I can see a movie being here like I'm charted
or no dear salad there's a narrative there but easy the same way the same way
dude they're making movies out of battleship in candy land they are movies
in name only or Pirates of the Caribbean there was really no plot to it you know
in the ride but they managed to make three movies and they actually were
pretty good now asteroid could be something similar where they just make
up characters and then now those characters are associated with that
franchise so and maybe that's what they want to do maybe it's type of agreement
where if they could do a good movie then they can re-release the asteroid game
with the characters in it just like they ended up going back and putting the
characters in the ride or more importantly had huge amounts of
merchandising with the parrot Pirates of the Caribbean movies I mean that the you
know Jack Sparrow figures still sell like crazy and you see tons of them at
Halloween you know he's a he's a universally loved character so I guess
that's a good point I didn't even think about if they do write the movie well
enough there there will be an audience for it but there's just not a lot of
source material to base it off of what do we know about the asteroid movie it
will be about asteroids there will probably be shooting of said asteroids
that's it that's all the script requires in some ways it's guaranteed to piss
people off less than like the Harry Potter movies like how many people
hated the third Harry Potter movie because of all the shit they cut out
sometimes it's nice to have a very thin narrative but I wouldn't you know I my
expectations for this movie are not going to be I guess that high because of
the fact there's no narrative to base it off of if that makes sense I don't know
well it could very well be good you know for all I know obviously I haven't seen
it so I can't be sure but you know I could be a little skeptical you know to
say the least well we should be skeptical it's ten dollars and twenty
five cents of our money we're gonna be spending on the movies anyway what was
the other thing you want to mention tonight oh yeah I forgot to mention in
my email because I can't really mention you know I wrote it but uh I kept it
notes earlier earlier this week and on the PlayStation Network store the only
time that the video site they got a reasonably new or new for the store
enemy series that may be appealing to some of the listeners out there it's a
devil may cry series mm-hmm and well I got popped up the first episode to try
it out and for one thing it looks pretty good I don't know about the entire
series as a whole but just based on the first episode it looks pretty good so I
don't know if any of the listening wants to check it out or you guys but really
start the first ones you know worth checking out you know that's one thing I
have yet to do on the Sony marketplace is check out one of the TV shows or
something but that's cool I know they've been kind of releasing some more anime
and things like that sort of like there's a whole Street Fighter store now
and on the PlayStation 3 I was checking out this week and they actually have
like the Street Fighter anime and some of that stuff so kind of different yeah
I think I mentioned in a previous email going back several weeks ago that I had
recommended the first angel anime series I happen to have all 24 episodes and at
least that series is very good it's kind of how to describe it's like a cross
between actually has certain elements of specs files and a little bit of
Charlie's Angels mixed in yeah it's kind of odd but in a good way definitely
definitely worth checking out and that's a bit is that available on on Sony's
marketplace yeah yeah it is I think I can't you know remember the name of the
developer but you know it's not funimation right and that's for sure but
it's pretty good all right I will definitely have to check that out on the
marketplace at some point but thank you so much for the call spaz nator you have
a good one we got to get some more calls but you take care later 1877 game olr
username on skype orange lounge radio if you want to give us a call take maybe
like one more call tonight I don't know if Lou he has any other stories you
want to get out there before we take our last call let's see here now we got a
call hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hi this is excellent hi
excellent what's on your mind buddy hey hey I have a quick question for you
guys how can a developer bring out a PC version of a game that's really great
and really good but yet have so many buggy and lot of cool issues it's not
even funny to even start to mention how many stuff there is wrong with the game
are you saying it's a PC game that came out yeah Ghostbusters a video game the
PC version is absolutely horrid easy it's not I mean there's so many complaints
from so many people they're not even issuing any patches or they're not
issuing any kind of you know saying hey look we were sorry we're trying to get
on this super duper super duper easy answer for you and what the one kind of
problem that I suppose that PC games have in general is that there is not the
same quality control that you have on the PlayStation or the Microsoft system
or even the Nintendo system is that these games go through no quality
control remember when way back when they used to have the Nintendo seal of
quality yes the Nintendo seal quality had nothing to do with the fact whether
the game was any good or not it just had to do with the fact that the game had
been officially tested was officially licensed and approved for the system and
usually the games that were like really prone to bugs and had really bad
ingression a lot of really bad things wrong with them were these games that
came out from color dreams and the other makers attention and makers that wanted
nothing to do in Nintendo kind of moving on from that now you have a lot of these
companies where you can't even really put the games out on the system unless
you go through these rigid tests you know a quality control you know and it's
it's little as you know in like the Xbox games you have to have you know things
have to be referred to as the r1 and the l1 or the back button in the start
button and then the Sony games the X button and O button you know that you
have to make sure everything is referred to by the proper name for it I mean it's
down to that kind of level of control on the PC who's there to control those
games what third-party entity has to look at those games and and review them
nobody nobody's really watching that I think it should be more viewing done
because like I said before I feel now I'm they kind of gypped out of my money
for the game and how they're looking actually forward to playing it on the PC
and it's like now to go out and find a way to get it for either the 360 now or
the ps3 in full quality and tour you know to play it till they come out some
kind of patch you know and it's just like I mean there's been more than one
more than one instance with more than one person saying hey look there's these
kind of problems I'm running on a you know high-end system and yet it's still
running like it's on a 386 computer so it's like what's going on here so
interesting comment from Xenocore in the chat room I want to kind of run this by
you there is no way an all-encompassing quality control can be run on PC games
there are way too many combinations for hardware you can check all you want and
still find bugs after release I didn't have any issues running Ghostbusters but
it does it done have secure on it however good point is that you know when
on the PlayStation on the Xbox at least you have the same hardware so there is
something to kind of but but you don't know what components are going to go
into those PC games so how can you really audit them I always thought the
games for Windows was kind of one of those types of things was a way to have
the game's quality controlled but I guess he brings up a good point you
can't really test every hardware combination out there but yeah it's true
that's very true and I just I was kind of weird because like I said I play
Fallout 3 and everyone's perfect I have no problems or anything whatsoever I
played this and it's like the whole thing is getting ready to crash at given
points it's like I just thought was kind of interesting I just well I'm sorry here
the game runs like crap x-link I would still continue to pressure the
developers professionally you know write a letter post on the forums what have
you get you know the other people you know they've been having problems of the
game to continue to helm them and you know say you're not going to support
them in the future if they don't fix their crap most definitely I hear you
I hear on that excellent good luck buddy and take care okay thank you no problem
thank you but bye and Xenocore in chat kind of makes a good point to secure on
games kind of have a reputation for running like crap that's something
important to state as well so I think we are gonna go ahead and wrap up the
skyline for tonight I'm really sorry to those that didn't get through but we do
want to wrap up and get out of here before it's too late tonight it's
already getting close to nine o'clock midnight on the East Coast do you have
any other quick stories one to get out there Loki yeah that's a quick stuff
real quick there is a website apparently it's a book project that this guy's
doing called there will be brawl and it's the artist names Greg death Greg
DeStefano and you can look at the pictures that they have there on www.
Greg DeStefano.com that's g-r-e-g-d-e-s-t-e-f-a-n-o.com and they've got some
pretty interesting pictures sadly enough that Icarus guy looks like Shane that's
kind of funny and wait let me see let me see it's sort of he maybe if Shane took
hardcore drugs how about a Wario's John Goodman yeah sort of okay that I see a
little more yes okay there you go but yeah it's interesting and then other
things there's some cool rumors going on including that there's gonna be some
little big planet download content coming soon themed after the Ghostbusters
actually this is probably less of a rumor because it's actually on media
molecules website and they have just in white text on black background who you
gonna call and of course that's from Ghostbusters so makes perfect sense that
will probably seen some stuff pretty soon from that probably just costumes
though the Hanabi festival is coming back in Europe and there's actually a
pretty good lineup of games coming with that including I saw they had an ogre
battle which is pretty cool ogre battle from the Super Nintendo pulse man from
the Sega Mega Drive bomber man 94 on turbo graphics 16 detonate twin be on
also the turbo graphics Kirby's dreamland 3 on Super Nintendo
Musha on Sega Mega Drive smash table tennis on the NES and zodas revenge
star tropics to all these coming to virtual console during the month of July
and yes that's kind of neat yeah so that's pretty awesome Star Trek Star
Trek star tropics to never come out over there no I guess not interesting over
here yes there no so that's starting actually as of last Friday so some of
that stuff's already out and dark soccer would be all over that to Tana Twimby
coming out I know she was a fan of that yes so that's pretty cool
um Konami a guest is also confirmed that they're gonna be porting over contra
rebirth for Europe in August and also drift mania with two eyes also coming to
we wear as well so you drift drift mania I guess that's how you pronounce that
top-down racing game and you know those are coming to Europe so that means that
they're localizing it for English so hopefully we'll see those over here as
well this is kind of a neat rumor apparently TMNT smash-up is going to be
getting some other characters that aren't necessarily in the Ninja Turtles
universe apparently they're also going to be getting two rabid characters one
of them is rumored to be dressed up as Sam Fisher from of course the splinter
cell series and then also rabid dressed up as a cheerleader and those are
supposed to be in you know the all-term Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles fighting
game which is kind of interesting that's some more characters they're shown for
that and it's actually some stuff from the comic that I'm not even familiar
with and then lastly I just have to mention this because I remember this
when I had a graphing calculator in high school that they were trying to port
this to the TI-83 but finally Link's Awakening has been ported to the TI-83
oh my god and it's been that long that I've been waiting you know I remember
this coming out and it's like oh my god Link's Awakening we can play it on the
TI-83 but really like those little graphing calculators can handle the
processing they can have you show me the video they can hack them so that it's an
assembly and stuff I guess it's awful sound quality but uh you know the you
know graphics are just it's okay the graphics are kind of crap but well I
mean it's a graphic and it's slow but yeah it's a graphing calculator running
the game that's crazy and I think that a lot of the stuff they probably just
programmed from scratch I don't think it's actually being emulated yeah I
can't imagine this is any fun to actually play this is just more of an
accomplishment than anything else but yeah I mean I remember you know back in
the day it used to be you know this is back when they first started porting a
like assembly stuff to the TI-85 and you can hack the calculator to run faster
than it normally could and you could do grayscale games and stuff like that the
days this is why I quit my calculus class because I was too busy programming
games nice but uh yeah and that's all I have right now all right wow we're made
it we're to the end of the show I know it's a little earlier than last week but
we're kind of at the end of the show and that's okay cuz I don't know about you
guys but after this holiday weekend I still have some things I'm trying to
take care of before I go back to work tomorrow after this whole three-day work
weekend so yeah we're gonna go ahead and wrap things up and get on out of here
for the night but thank you guys so much for listening tonight and sadly dark
soccer is not here either and you know she'll usually help banter with us for a
little while and bring her stories to table she's not here so I think it's
gonna be the end of the show believe it or not we're done we're out of here
which is also actually it's good because it gives me a chance to make sure I can
get on the network and get those other get the files that I need to upload the
show later this week because I don't want the podcast people have to wait any
longer so we're out of here believe it or not that's it have a great night
everybody let's go around everybody's final thoughts Loki your final thought
my final thought is I'm watching and someone actually took a DS light and
they've managed to turn it into an arcade cabinet or I should say put a DS
in an arcade cabinet that's crazy Wow my final thought is instead of spending
$400 on a laptop I should have just bought myself an arcade cabinet for my
house I would have been fun the real love that you know in hindsight like I
said I think before I rather bought see because we're in an apartment complex in
order to have the whole thing delivered it comes on a pallet and I mean you
can't deliver a pallet of stuff to an apartment complex you're gonna get
people looking at you funny and but man that would have been the way I've gone
it costs like a sixth of what I paid for it and just you know looks so much nicer
all right that's it guys thank you so much for tuning into our show tonight
thank you for listening to our show and supporting independent podcasting
remember we would not be out here be here without your support we really
appreciate it it's kept us going for seven years and hopefully seven more
from all of us here at orange on radio studios in Sacramento California I hope
you all have a great week we will be back next week dark Sakura will be back
I'll be here look you'll be here and we'll have some fun and talk about next
week's worth of news will you be here I hope so tune in Sunday night live at
six o'clock Pacific Standard Time right after the Bobby Black Wolf show on all
games radio or you can continue to support us through the podcast that's
okay too either way you do it thank you for your support have a wonderful week
take care guys see ya you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange
lounge radio is an orange lounge production to join us for a live show
visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific time the views and
opinions expressed on orange lounge radio do not necessarily reflect those
of the entire staff of orange lounge radio or all games calm but we're
probably right anyway see you next week