[SPEAKER_20]: It's a videotape!
[SPEAKER_20]: Put it in!
[SPEAKER_18]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_18]: Our live talk program begins now.
Boring!
[SPEAKER_07]: This video sucks!
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain nudity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hide Orange Lounge radio for the fucking children.
[SPEAKER_12]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_12]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess there's just two kinds of people, Miss Sandstone.
[SPEAKER_00]: My kind of people and assholes.
[SPEAKER_00]: One.
[SPEAKER_19]: One.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dear Diary, my teen angst bullshit has a body count.
[SPEAKER_15]: I would like
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Sky, Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: But you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Orange Lounge Radio episode number 15 and a half for this October the 13th, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, today's the 10th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Today's the 10th.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I spent all day writing the 10th.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're taping on Thursday, so let me do the math real fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the 13th.
[SPEAKER_04]: 13th of October.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are listening to a pre-taped show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Jamie and I are lazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: We want to take a weekend off.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want a weekend off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me introduce for everybody out there, by the way, if you don't know her, you should.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Jamie Summers, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, that's a first for this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now that's usually me on Under Sedation Live.
[SPEAKER_13]: That burp was brought to you by Berry Flavored Propel, a product of Gatorade.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can find out more about Propel at www.GatoradeSucksButPropelOwnsMe.com It's going to be one of those shows, I can already tell.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might know me also as Skye.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, you do!
[SPEAKER_13]: You think you know me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You will never know me.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are lost and scared.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just a puppet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I finish?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, it was an obscure wrestling reference, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Usually we'd be taking a break right now for the opening of the show, but we're not.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just going to kick right into things, start off the show here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me introduce everybody who's here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got a nice little crowd of people going on here at Scandia tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: They look very nice to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: They look kind of mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all glaring going, what the hell is going on here?
[SPEAKER_04]: This, by the way, is the site of DDR Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sacramento hosts another... Sacramento, or Sacramento, sorry, hosts another fucking tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, fabulous tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: On November 9th, and Jamie will give us more details on that later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, I would like to introduce everybody that's here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll start over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got Derek.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remembered.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I remembered your real name for once.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what would the online folks know you as?
[SPEAKER_04]: Depends how long they've been there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's say the recent folks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phalanx Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, what an evil sounding name.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, you'd get it if you read X-Men.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phalanx X-Men?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was the whole thing that they introduced the Generation X in.
[SPEAKER_11]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm original.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hee hee.
No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I see the lovely lady that's with you here tonight is a little bit radio shy.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's farting.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a nice thing to say to your lady friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should smack him.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's the nicest thing I said all day.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you have to say in response to that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just call him an ass like I always do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ass!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your name, dear?
[SPEAKER_11]: Lizzie.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're not really in the DDR community, though, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I play a little bit of DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll ask the big newbie question.
[SPEAKER_04]: What footers are you on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you on five footers or seven footers?
[SPEAKER_19]: Six, seven, something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Round of applause for the six and seven.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello everybody to J.B.
[SPEAKER_00]: Jenny Rom owned me at Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did she smack your ass and call you Papa?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's our Jenny Rom fanboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_13]: What is it about Jenny Rom that's so fucking cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know who she is Jenny Rom, you know I know what song she sings, they're annoying She has like this annoying, high-ass voice It's just like He doesn't know He just likes Oh, that was Oh shit, that's me She's like Too Much Coffee Woman Oh, the lady on the megaphone?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Jenny Rom Oh, Jenny Rom, oh, I'm sorry
[SPEAKER_13]: You wouldn't be making fun of the... Someone put her processor on overdrive.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-oh, he said the line.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, ass!
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I said Almas.
[SPEAKER_13]: He said Almas.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, Satan!
[SPEAKER_13]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be one of those shows where we have to fight with a loudspeaker the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is an experimental show, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me remind you.
[SPEAKER_20]: And remember, if you can't be... And remember, if you can't be an athlete, be an athletic supporter.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, I like Grease.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate that damn movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen it 50 million times.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know all the damn songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Grease is classic.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's on DVD now.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it's Satan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grease is Satan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is Grease Satan?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because my sister watched it like five times a day for like three weeks straight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Grease came out when I was like two.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was enjoying her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, when I was eight years old, I watched the movie Clue every day for an entire summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you're back on my good side.
[SPEAKER_04]: You better stay there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's like four endings.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, three.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's three.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're making actually a Grease 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: They better not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_13]: And by the way, Clue had Tim Curry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Tim Curry kicked ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what else was Tim Curry in?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rocky.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would they make a great Grease 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Grease 3 starring the Olivia Project.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you never been there?
[SPEAKER_13]: You had a car in the first, the cars in the first one.
[SPEAKER_13]: You had microphones in the second, microphones, motorcycles in the second one.
[SPEAKER_13]: What are you going to have next, a moped?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a high school reunion.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's bringing back the original cast, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like instead of Romy and Michelle, it's John and Olivia's high school reunion?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, we're a Bomani show, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're listening to... You said Olivia Project, so it counts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, okay, yeah, sorry, I made a reference.
Xanadu!
[SPEAKER_05]: I forgot that other song, but... Xanadu!
[SPEAKER_04]: Xanadu!
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which was also a good movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, Jamie, you said you'd be the only person... Yes, Xanadu was a movie that came out in 1990, I mean 1980.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, name me one other person in the Xanadu fan club.
[SPEAKER_13]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: Who else is in the Xanadu fan club but me?
[SPEAKER_13]: And my friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: And your friend, who's your friend?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, my friend, Gwen, who listens in Maryland, who's trying to listen anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Gwen.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you happen to be listening, then hi.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to put a plug in for the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's probably people there chatting, even though we're not really doing a show tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: People there all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have no life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, hi, JB.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we're kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love our chatters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since he's here, he's got... Since he's here, he's not in this chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he could be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it retains, he might be there Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_09]: How is this for a paradox?
Huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Twilight Zone.
[SPEAKER_04]: To join our chat room, just go to any other site IRC server like irc.eggheads.org and you're just going to join Channel Pound, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to get interviewed.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's some other people here I want to interview while they're here too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will go kidnap people.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to get Keith before he leaves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should say, actually I should start this week's episode by saying, you're listening to the most extreme station of all things Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can touch on that a little bit now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get into it in more depth later, because we're getting people to interview.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about, what is so extreme about this week's show?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, first off... What the fuck was that right now?
[SPEAKER_21]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's corny as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, we do have a new record holder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, before the show, Loki, world record champion on Conjoined Twin Galaxies, except we didn't have a video camera to tape it, so it won't count.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, when we do get a camera...
[SPEAKER_04]: He will, except Black Lab has sworn to me he will destroy the world record no matter where it's at.
[SPEAKER_04]: He will train long and hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to be like Sylvester Stallone in Rocky.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's going to beat that record.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: The record was so sad that actually me, who can't perfect the tackle or shit, beat the record by like a good 40 or 50 million points.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's freaking cold out here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I could have played the last song, Dynamite Rave, doing freestyle and still would have beat that stupid record.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can say Raven, he can't play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can go back and edit it in the show later.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need a hug!
[SPEAKER_04]: The person we wanted to interview left.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about Jer?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is Jer still in there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jer's gonna come.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, dude, go interview that guy over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is the gazebo empty?
[SPEAKER_13]: The gazebo?
[SPEAKER_04]: The gazebo.
[SPEAKER_04]: The gazebo we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can do anything we want while this show's going.
[SPEAKER_04]: We migrate to the gazebo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're walking over to the gazebo.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you can't swim in the pond, but you can be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should interview everybody that comes to the 18th hole and do golf claps and shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, the listeners couldn't hear you.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should interview everybody that comes to the 18th hole and clap for them and stuff, even though they suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, now this is a great table.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a big table.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wind shielded.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wind shielded.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, this is like the carpet that they put on the walls at roller rinks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you guys on that side are going to have to raise your hand if you want to talk, so I can hand you a microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you can't yell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Slighty song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I finally passed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's talk about DDR Extreme.
Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Sexstream!
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's change.
[SPEAKER_04]: Derek, let's change.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't change for anyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can sit on that side of the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll sit on this side.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is really great radio, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, other side of the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I guess, I always saw Loki as kind of our news desk of the show, so I'll let him talk about DDR Extreme, even though he's not prepared to.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm sure he'll have something nice to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, Loki now doing news for Team Guilo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually have a comment about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is kind of an F-you to myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was viciously pointed out by DJ Paranoia to have copied his list and put it on Team Guilo, which is a big, big, big, big, big, big note of if you don't give credit.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's plagiarism.
[SPEAKER_02]: And anyways, to begin with, okay, first off, I copied Black Lab's list to begin with, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: And that list... Yeah, it doesn't matter about him.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I took his list at first.
[SPEAKER_02]: It didn't have any frickin' names on it or none of the artists' names, so that kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I borrowed his list.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to put... I mean, shit, man, I'm putting this list up, like, way early in the morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so damn tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do that, and then finally it doesn't hit me until he's like, "'Ass, thanks for stealing my list.'"
[SPEAKER_02]: So I've been hearing about it for like the last three days.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, gave big credit to him and their, you know, Bomani style for translating Naoki's journal to make it actually legible.
[SPEAKER_02]: The big question is, did you guys kiss and make up?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I kissed ass, I sent him emails, PMs, I even apologized to Spigamas in the DDR Maniacs chatroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully some way he got the message that I am gratefully sorry and would be happy to make it up to him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe he shared resources for some story or whatnot.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, there will be no putting out, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, that's not happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think I've gone, you know, above and beyond to apologize for a simple mistake.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that got fixed within a couple hours.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've gone down and apologized.
[SPEAKER_13]: And look, if he gives you hell for it, just use the Nifty at Global Gate translator because it does it nearly perfectly anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it wasn't that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just I used his list that had the names on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoop-de-de-doo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoop-de-shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I could have just done the list myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm not plagiarizing anymore, but if I were, I certainly would reformat the shit so it wouldn't look anything like anyone else's.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just plagiarized Black Lab, because that's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't matter, he's in our... He's probably in the chatroom right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's nobody important.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, Black Lab, I didn't mean that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but anyways, yeah, so I'm doing news now.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of sucks because now I have to be on top of all the news stories instead of browsing the internet and, you know, chatting in chat rooms.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're on top, going down, bending over backwards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good lord, you're an acrobat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Down, down, down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, but one of the things I was able to have that no one else did have is I actually got those clips from the DDR Max USA, all the new samples.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're supposedly going to be in there because everyone gave me shit about that too, saying, oh, how do you know that shit's going to be in there?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not confirmed?
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I really give a shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just ripping samples for people to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a comment on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they're not going to be in the game, why do they exist?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, the old stuff, I understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami?
[SPEAKER_04]: Lazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Certainly.
[SPEAKER_04]: They leave the old stuff from Max Japan in there, like Ghost and things like that, and they sneak in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, but these new remixes weren't just done for the hell of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know, maybe Naoki gets bored one night, he's doing his nails, like, hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe I'll remix, uh... Dear Diary, I ran out of black fingernail polish, so I decided to remix a new song with my best buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would they be in there if they're not going to be in the final game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it just specifically throw us off?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, even if it is just there to throw us off, hey, it's a new Bomani remix clip, that's newsworthy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, then the fact that Kakumei was in there, okay, the clip for Kakumei, and they're like,
[SPEAKER_02]: and some guys like, no, that got cut and so did Ghost.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know for sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I'm actually developing the game, so I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's your source?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm all, well, shit, man, if you guys got information, start sharing instead of calling me, telling me I'm wrong, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Start sharing some info.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless you work for Konami or you're sleeping with someone who works for Konami, we just can't believe you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just going to have to all wait until, you know, the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll get right on sleeping with everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: You whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would anybody at this table put out for information on Max?
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are sad and pathetic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob, first of all, my fiance manages a GameStop.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't have to put out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just comes with the job.
[SPEAKER_04]: But does he get information about Konami?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like game releases, but he doesn't really get... No, the reps come to the store.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have information that I can't talk about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd go down on some chick at Konami to get information.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because you'd be getting some.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dear Diary, I went to America one day, and there was this guy there who said he'd put out for information about DDR.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I put out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I said chick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, oh wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shit, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: First of all.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ever see The Crying Game?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Crying Game 2 is starring Naoki Midea.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would not want my name mispronounced.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a pronunciation argument going on over there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just really, really white.
[SPEAKER_13]: Would you want someone to mispronounce your name?
[SPEAKER_13]: They do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, how can you mispronounce Derek?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark.
[SPEAKER_13]: We can call you Dirk.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, asshole.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, DDR Extreme, the very gay-ass name that they applied to DDR Max 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: No offense, Drew.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, if they got it DDR Cock Sucking Edition, yes, that would be it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR Ass Fuck Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bar and Grill.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so here's what I'm picturing from DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're gonna have extreme clips in the background, possibly people doing extreme things.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be extreme songs, and I'm going to get extremely bored with this.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyway, they had a little voting thing going on that we mentioned last week, announcing some of the... They didn't do it in Florida.
[SPEAKER_13]: As long as there are no songs by extreme.
[SPEAKER_13]: They went out in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, let me guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to throw out an idea here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could the next Max be...
[SPEAKER_02]: Max Extreme?
[SPEAKER_10]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the remix of Max 300 by Erotic, Max Sexstream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Max.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have sex with your ex.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, dude, that would be fucking sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Max, don't have sex with your ex.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, it would be evil, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, that song is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so some of the new songs that they were mentioning that were up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're possibly going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not confirmed to be in there, but possibly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Start with Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got V and A. Fuck you, Loki, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which together is VA.
[SPEAKER_02]: VA.
[SPEAKER_13]: For the veterans or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: From Guitar Freaks, there's Elise, 100 Seconds, and something else that's not Fire or Jet World because I really... Yeah, I want a Jet World.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would have been sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fire from...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a hold on me from, what is it, ParaPara, which everyone's just like, this is crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I agree, you know, I'd rather have, I mean, even like Kingdom of Rock.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, Kingdom of Rock would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kingdom of Rock or even like Burning Desire.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deluxe, fucking Deluxe in DDR, that would rule.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the microphone, Derek.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like the only dance I know, I look so gay doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, we should have Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, first off, just because these, you know, became, these were on, you know, the top of the list here, doesn't mean that they're not going to throw other stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it's very possible.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would be happy if Cosmic Cowgirl was in Max.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I wonder how long this DDR Extreme is going to last.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, and what... One week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just because I think they changed interface designs.
[SPEAKER_13]: One week since this game came out.
[SPEAKER_13]: One week since I looked at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The question is, how often will it be bootlegged?
[SPEAKER_04]: Will it be a bigger or more rampant bootleg than Moodleg?
[SPEAKER_04]: Moodleg?
[SPEAKER_11]: Moodleg?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was born for radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we were having a discussion in the DDR Maniacs chatroom today.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were saying hi to all our friends in the DDR Maniacs chatroom.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_04]: Love ya.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry, yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm an optimist.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got lots of fans over there, don't we?
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're all the fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm speaking to the one fan, Twen, and talking to him today.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we were discussing the fact that DDR Extreme, since it is so extreme, should have a fog machine and lasers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because who doesn't like a good laser?
[SPEAKER_04]: As I said earlier on another chat board, I said it should be, it's kind of a joke I used earlier, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Sex Stream with a big pole in the middle.
[SPEAKER_04]: and all erotic set of songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: You remember what I was saying the other night?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: That it needs the butt pad so you can have booty mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're gonna put a button on the bar so you can like rub your ass against the bar.
[SPEAKER_13]: We need the grind.
[SPEAKER_04]: What were you saying JB?
[SPEAKER_10]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, what they're going to do is they're going to have a nice little chair in front of the pads itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sitting on the chair will be a mannequin.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you bump and grind against the mannequin to get some bonus points there.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's going to be one of those real dolls of Naoki.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's got session mode with Boonga Boonga.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, what's scary is...
[SPEAKER_02]: Eek!
[SPEAKER_02]: Beat it, beat it
[SPEAKER_02]: You can either have Beat It by DJ Alligator Project or Erotic.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's my watch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says, this will explode.
[SPEAKER_04]: This watch has the time of your doom.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's my 007 watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the doomsday clock.
[SPEAKER_13]: They gave out to all the managers of GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: 11.59 and ticking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
The time is .59.
[SPEAKER_13]: Time to die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, what nerds are we?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what other cool things can we expect to see in DDR Extreme?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes, JB.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about Gillette?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't want no short dick, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember that song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'm going to play that during one of the breaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I remember when I'm putting this show together, when I get back home and editing it, I'll put Gillette as one of the songs we'll play.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight's a good song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll try to play that for you if I remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's the one song that I definitely want played.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Children of the Sandstorm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now explain this mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was looking for a sandstorm because I actually did not have it on my computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just couldn't get enough of last week's joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was Sunday night after I got home.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I found, for people who are familiar with it, Robert Miles did a song called Children.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I found that mixed with Sandstorm.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was actually pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a huge song when I was in high school.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes me feel so old.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a good mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it was basically cut and paste type, but it was done very smoothly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, JB left you a present, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, JB, explain the present that you left for Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, it was Dynamite R3, or R5.
[SPEAKER_04]: And explain, tell us a little bit about Dynamite R5.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Dynamite Rave and R5 mixed together.
[SPEAKER_13]: Excellent, very good, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I must listen to this right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are in the gazebo overlooking the lovely course here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see... This is... We've got a castle right in front of us.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we're not at Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's... Assholes?
[SPEAKER_05]: And their stuff's messed up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, Initial D took my money, but I'm addicted to that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fuck the money for a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to talk about Initial D. Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki had something to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... Yeah, I'm guessing we'll hear... Supposedly what's going to be happening week to week with Naoki...
[SPEAKER_21]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another song was announced for DVR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is going to be a new Ryu, whatever her damn name is, Kosuka or... I Blow Naoki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I Blow Naoki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ryu, I Blow Naoki.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's doing a song that's called... Shit, I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's some stupid song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be like Candy, but it's supposed to be heavy metal or rock or some crap like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Wee, wee, wee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wee, wee, wee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, you guys keep going.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna run in and see if anyone else showed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, um, Naoki's Journal sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're supposed to be doing, like, some interviews or questionnaires with, uh, staff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're like, we give a shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seeing what the staff thinks about DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're probably all gonna say, uh, Naoki's gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_13]: And meanwhile over here, you're hearing voices.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I keep hearing somebody saying my name, and it's not JB.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, they're going...
[SPEAKER_11]: Big fuck!
[SPEAKER_11]: It just sounds like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, since we have this big gap of space here, I'm going to go ahead and do the sim update for this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we actually have news this week, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's my turn to excuse myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take the mic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, here's what's going on in the sim world here.
[SPEAKER_02]: First off, you have a new release of Set Mania.
[SPEAKER_02]: Set Mania, actually, it's kind of been called Beta 6 Release 2, or what they're calling it is Beta 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so Beta 7's out now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've
[SPEAKER_02]: Got it at home.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't gotten to try it out yet, but StepMania hasn't disappointed me yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: My StepMania doesn't work on my computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You used to not like StepMania back in the early versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a liar.
[SPEAKER_02]: StepMania really did disappoint me back in version 1.6, 1.6.5, that area, because it didn't load, and it sucked, and it was really slow, and it was a piece of shit, and DWI kicked his ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, since then, since they've gone actually doing public updates, where there's like 30 people working on updating this thing instead of 2, it's gotten a lot better.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you've got now, you have pump support, para-para support, you also have easy-to-dancer support in there, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which means what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Which means you can play those games on that simulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not everybody knows that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well... She didn't know!
[SPEAKER_05]: Derek's a little slow.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm fat and I didn't eat today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, other than that, let's see, on a personal note, I'm putting up DWIs on the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've actually got my own site that's going to be started here pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: LeachFromLoki.com Hey!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not a bad name.
[SPEAKER_02]: I rule.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna call that Leech from Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome, though, because I found a site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like gamers.com or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Gamers Club, I believe it's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 50 megs of web space free and unlimited bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unlimited bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shit, I can put stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one will worry about my site going down.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's super orgasmic.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to have my DWIs on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, really hard to find rare 8-style DWIs.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's free, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll be doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe get a couple of sites if I run out of my 50 megs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You run out of space?
[SPEAKER_02]: That kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So look for that pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll announce it later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they bog you down with banner ads or any of that crap?
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, yes, they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing is ever really free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mozilla.com, highly recommended by Orange Lounge staff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Block ads, awesome, love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'll put a link to that on my site.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure they won't like it, but I'll put a link up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, we'll have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, see, other than that, I don't know, not too much going on in the sim world.
[SPEAKER_02]: More people releasing stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Euromix DWIs are coming along pretty good on...
[SPEAKER_02]: DDR UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've actually got now the official backgrounds for Hysteria 2001 and Before You, Before is the Beat Mix, which is pretty cool looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're also going to be adding the rest of the DWIs, including Caribbean Queen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Caribbean Queen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, no more of me singing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so, are we doing interviews or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess who's back.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, just Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's coming back, and everybody that we wanted to interview left, so no interviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jared's still inside.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Jared's still inside.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'll come out here later.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's teaching a little kid how to play DDR or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: He already knows how to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I see that kid here a lot, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's like a regular here.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's past the hard stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should get him.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should interview him.
[SPEAKER_13]: He wants to be interviewed.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Get him out of here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to go.
[SPEAKER_13]: If we go inside...
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going inside?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to go inside.
[SPEAKER_04]: While we're migrating.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't this a nice, lovely, chilly afternoon?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm feeling fat and sassy.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's nighttime.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's nighttime.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, dark time.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, there's the moon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am a banana!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not a banana, that's the moon!
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it's the moon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it Mr. Moon?
[SPEAKER_04]: Look how many funny looks we're getting as we come in here.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now we're back inside.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going into the party room with these lovely people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, lovely people.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to hide in the corner where nobody can find us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we're at a much smaller table.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like I've been demoted.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, it's warm in here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought we were supposed to shrink with coldness.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was like, dang.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, somebody just failed the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey now, that's not very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to be supportive of everybody, remember?
[SPEAKER_13]: We support you!
[SPEAKER_13]: Like a good jockstrap.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are supported.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just full of jokes today.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm fucking hyper because I had cupcakes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take that off of your ear, that's my damn watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where did Loki go?
[SPEAKER_13]: He went to play his edits.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so what should we talk about now?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no fucking whistles on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have Jamie's music and I'm too lazy to put it in.
[SPEAKER_13]: So edit my damn music in.
[SPEAKER_13]: What, Katima style?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you haven't heard the Kutimu stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's basically people taking different Bimani songs and singing them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wait, I've heard that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki showed me.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're funny as hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk about it more on the show next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't you put some on the show last week?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we didn't get around to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were going to, but we had just an action-packed show last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was an extremely packed show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enough with that word.
[SPEAKER_05]: No more extreme words.
[SPEAKER_05]: Extreme Radio!
[SPEAKER_05]: You find me to be extremely annoying?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I find you extremely sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, my fuck you of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: My fuck you of the week goes towards going home and finding out that Dan ate all the lasagna last night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lasagna?
[SPEAKER_21]: I like lasagna.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that was going to be my fucking lunch today.
What a dick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_13]: My fiance.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't call him a dick, asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was a dog or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie doesn't own a dog.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can't be on our show anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're not allowed to be on the show anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: You think I'm kidding, don't you?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's in her randy mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: During the commercial break, Jamie's going to go kick the crap out of our guests.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, he ate the lasagna.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I didn't have any dinner.
[SPEAKER_04]: What'd you eat?
[SPEAKER_04]: You had to have eaten something.
[SPEAKER_13]: A microwave burrito.
[SPEAKER_13]: A dog.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't have a dog, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: She has a pretty cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a Shermie.
[SPEAKER_04]: A what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Shermie.
[SPEAKER_13]: What was his name?
[SPEAKER_13]: Shermie is his name.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have my girl kitty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shermie isn't a breed of cat.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's a Shermie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, what type of cat is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: A Shermie?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a she!
[SPEAKER_13]: You're just digging yourself deeper tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little gray cat.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a... She looks like Church from Pet Sematary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's actually a good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: You never saw Pet Sematary.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was afraid of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a scary movie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was afraid of Child's Play.
[SPEAKER_05]: That movie freaked the shit out of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't like little stabby doll things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was scared of The Wizard of Oz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute, you were scared of The Wizard of Oz?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_21]: The little mumpins.
[SPEAKER_04]: The monkeys that fly on the... The monkeys that fly out of their ass?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, it's the lollipop kids.
[SPEAKER_21]: The munchkins.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you ever see the great sequel Return to Oz?
[SPEAKER_04]: With the thing on the wheels?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you're thinking of the whiz.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, Return to Oz was good.
[SPEAKER_13]: The reason why Return to Oz was good is because it was actually based off of the book.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and Farooza Balk was in it, and she's cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Wizard of Oz was not true to the book, because she went and met all of the witches.
[SPEAKER_13]: She met the Good Witch of the North, the Good Witch of the South, killed one of them, and then killed the other.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there was no balance, and Oz fell into ruin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember the freakiest scene in Return to Oz.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's all the little heads in the jar.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was so cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry, but Monty, what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: But Monty, what?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Random Night on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_13]: You heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you know something we brought up earlier?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, ass!
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not but Monty related exactly, but it's still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Initial D. Rob is staring at me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry, listeners.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, Initial D, Mad Eurobeat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fatty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please explain.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Fat with a P or Fat with an F?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Fat with Fat.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Orange Beanie has my SNIS one that I messed up on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Explain for those who may not know about Initial D, what makes it so special?
[SPEAKER_11]: Mad European action!
[SPEAKER_04]: And?
[SPEAKER_04]: Cars!
[SPEAKER_04]: And bad animation.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the cards!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about the little cards!
[SPEAKER_13]: And shitty storyline!
[SPEAKER_13]: And, and...
[SPEAKER_13]: And yeah, neat cars.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I have my Trueno.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not going to fucking get that spoiler.
[SPEAKER_13]: That spoiler looks like shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I know I can pass the option of upgrading my car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, your name really is Fatty.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I'm lucky enough to have a four-letter handle online, so I never have...
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, whoever of our listeners who was not there the night that I made my car, if you can guess the name that's on my card, for the card that I'm using right now, I will give you a memory card.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Memory card.
[SPEAKER_04]: For what system?
[SPEAKER_13]: For a PS2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not for a PS2, for a PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: PS1.
[SPEAKER_04]: You win a DarkSakura autographed memory card.
[SPEAKER_13]: You win a DarkSakura autographed memory card.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's your first clue.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's R. You get two clues.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they're pretty easy clues if you know how to find it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The password is... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_13]: The first clue is that the word is Greek.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, now wait a minute, didn't they ban video games in Greece?
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck Greece.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, they overruled that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Second rule is that it means goal.
[SPEAKER_13]: Goal!
[SPEAKER_04]: Like soccer?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, or like, you know, a goal.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you know, because you've got to have goals.
[SPEAKER_13]: I gotta believe!
[SPEAKER_13]: So whoever can guess what the word is, who was not there the night I made it, will win a DarkSakura autographed PlayStation memory card.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or you'll win an orange bat.
[SPEAKER_13]: A DarkSakura autographed orange bat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it's the bat, I'll autograph it too, because the bat's big enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't autograph a memory card, but I can autograph a bat.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can autograph the back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a question that actually involves Bimani.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my gosh, please do share.
[SPEAKER_05]: Initial D. No.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, tonight's initial D night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, ask your question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Ohi, Ohi who needs a shovel for the trouble he's getting in on this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, because like Max 2 is coming out for PS2, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Psst, eventually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, but PS2 memo cards don't work on the machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay, good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here he comes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, this is just like DDR Max, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: What it does is you can save onto your PlayStation 2 memory card, then it has a library option where you can export edits onto memory cards for the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_13]: It actually converts them to PS1 format, then you go into your memory on your system and move it over.
[SPEAKER_04]: More or less, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's play a new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember...
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember Loki's edit contest?
[SPEAKER_04]: How I had the edit to Somewhere Over the Rainbow?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the one that I got second place in.
[SPEAKER_13]: You just held my hand.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, you're in deep shit with me right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: And me now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: You died tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_02]: I got some weird name edits tonight for people to play.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got a sexer me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got a... Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, Sex or Me, it's for gimme, gimme, gimme.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got, uh, I've got Pink Taco, I can't remember what that's for.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, wouldn't it be Pink Dinosaur?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's Pink Taco, it has nothing to do- No, I mean, it wouldn't be Dinosaur?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I've got, uh, I've got one for Shake Your Booty, it's called Shake That Ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I've got-
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got one... You know you look good when you back that ass up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got one that's called Ass Fire.
[SPEAKER_02]: What'd you do, eat at Del Taco?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but the song is pretty hard and... Ah, shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got some really fun... As JB goes off to play Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I'm turning this over to you because I feel sick.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, wait, you had a game you wanted to play, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_13]: When we come back from the break, we should play Guess What's in DarkSakura's Purse.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's in my ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, we're not going to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: A pickle!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is not the Anna Nicole Smith show, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: When we come back from break, we are going to play Guess What's in DarkSakura's Purse.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we are going to have an interview with Jer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll think of something.
[SPEAKER_04]: After break, an interview with Tajer.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whoever wins will get an autographed Propel bottle from me.
[SPEAKER_04]: After I'm done drinking it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And backwashing a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: You drink like, what, 44 ounces of soda?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's why I feel sick.
[SPEAKER_19]: They can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said I'd be willing to urinate in the bottle, too, if that would increase the value of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How nice of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so kind and generous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're such a giving person.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, well, it's break time because people have to pee.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so we're going to take a quick break, and we'll be right back after some of this very fine music here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 15 and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're pre-taped tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're not pre-taped yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're still taping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, when they hear it, it's going to be pre-taped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, forget it!
[SPEAKER_13]: Paradox!
[SPEAKER_04]: I can sing the music on the break.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to break now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cut!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know what I'm
[SPEAKER_16]: I may be a little drunk, I mean tipsy
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, we're back from break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we're Brack.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're Brack?
[SPEAKER_13]: Not Brack.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love Brack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even, what is Brack?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what I just said.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brack is from Space Ghost Coast to Coast.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is me.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's crazy and stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're Brack?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I'm Brack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, my name is Brack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, my name is Bingo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like to climb on things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I have a banana?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eek, eek.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got an F. It's eek, eek.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's eek, eek.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went over to Brittany's house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's so much fighting here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't... I can't... Hey, new game.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, there isn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to play... We're going to play a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I have to... I have to say, though, during the break, we lost to JB.
[SPEAKER_04]: So... But we gained to Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So... Hi, Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome, Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where... What is this microphone in my face for?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, they're playing Eat You Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I wanted... I wanted to interview Jer, but he's shy, so... He's playing Eat You Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he's sitting right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just shy.
Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody make faces.
[SPEAKER_04]: Totally oblivious.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we're going to play a game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, we're going to play a game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's called Guess What's in DarkSakura's Purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's in my pants?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's in my purse?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I'm being random.
[SPEAKER_13]: And no, you can't guess what's on my purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do we play What's in Jamie's Purse?
[SPEAKER_13]: You guess what's in my purse.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to name an item that is in my purse.
[SPEAKER_13]: And how is this related to Bimani?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I do have some Bimani stuff in my purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: First guess goes to Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob's junk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is my junk in your purse?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's nothing that belongs to Rob in my purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, who wants to venture another guess?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Derek.
[SPEAKER_13]: Money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, is there money in Jamie's purse?
[SPEAKER_13]: I do not have any loose money in my purse.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't say you didn't have money at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have money.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do have money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Provolactics.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you need to be prepared.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know when.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm always prepared.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't need tools.
[SPEAKER_21]: Next.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should have asked the employee.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's in my purse?
[SPEAKER_19]: A pen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, a pen.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there a pen in your purse?
[SPEAKER_13]: For extra points, guess what colors?
[SPEAKER_13]: Blue and black.
[SPEAKER_04]: Black, red, purple, green, greenish.
[SPEAKER_13]: The blue pen in my purse is actually missing, but I have a gold one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, if you mix some of these colors together, you might get blue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did have... Barf is not a color.
[SPEAKER_13]: Barf always has a distinct color.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bradley, what's in my purse?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll guess some sort of tissues.
[SPEAKER_04]: I once barfed blue Kool-Aid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not shitting you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do not have any tissues in my purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no tissues.
[SPEAKER_04]: Trainwreck Radio, is that in your purse?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, there's no Trainwreck in my purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some sort of video game promotional item.
[SPEAKER_04]: Video game promo item.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be a token.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a GameCube lanyard.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a Game Boy Advance thingy.
[SPEAKER_04]: A thingy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that the technical name for it?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a keychain.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game's not working if you sit there with your purse open for us all to look in.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I had a GameCube pen in here once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody gets one more guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's in my purse?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something to do with Happy Bunny.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know this because you bought it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's my Happy Bunny token case.
[SPEAKER_13]: It says I hate everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy Bunny kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Happy Bunny.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's in my purse?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up and tell me what's in my purse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: A planner book.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, I have two of those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, double points.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Batsmaroo planner.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a... Oh, dude, I found another pen.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a Nyago address book.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a little smushed kitty.
[SPEAKER_11]: A smushed kitty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Next.
[SPEAKER_13]: Air.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess a physical item that is not like loose particles.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not in your head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Meanie.
[SPEAKER_13]: Smack him.
[SPEAKER_13]: A notepad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Honestly, there is not a notepad in my purse.
[SPEAKER_13]: I took it out this morning.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I took it out when I wrote the rules to freestyle.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, candy bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Candy Bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have a candy bar, we win it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, she has to add an autograph.
[SPEAKER_04]: She has to autograph it first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tootsie Roll, I'll be damned.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that count?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not really a bar, it's cylindrical, but it's kind of smushed, so now it's a bar.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nat hasn't guessed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, we're playing Guess What's in Jamie's Purse.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to come over here and talk into the mic.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care how tired you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: and of course it has everything to do with demonic okay uh chapstick oh chapstick no it's in my pocket what happens if you get chapped lips i said it's in my pocket oh it's in your pocket oh okay what happens so here is what's
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So here's what's in my purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a cell phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I knew that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like playing Family Feud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Number one answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Penguin mints.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good answer, good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I'm in my second guess, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Chopsticks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sunglasses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I have bike it in my purse.
[SPEAKER_03]: A wallet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bike it in!
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the worst joke ever told on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said, no, Chopstick isn't da-da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chopstick is dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is a special camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's so special about it?
[SPEAKER_13]: The camera from the DDR Freak moderator strip in Vegas that needs to be developed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there any scandalous sex stream pictures on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Drunk people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Extremely blackmailing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Give me my thingies!
[SPEAKER_13]: RC Country.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you've got games like Matt Hoffman's Triple X, or was it Triple X BMX or whatever they're like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or BMX Triple X or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: You wonder if they're going to ever come out with like, I don't know, an X-rated version of DDR.
[SPEAKER_19]: DDR Gal's Panic Mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: That would be wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be involving me.
[SPEAKER_11]: What was that one game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, there's this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is that game that you play?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like Kix, and you're drawing the picture, and you get the naked lady, but if you... Scouts Panic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that Scouts?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Scouts Panic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's another one where it flips around, and at certain times you'll get the evil picture, the demon, and there's this techno music that plays.
[SPEAKER_09]: It goes, Everybody run!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoyed that joke, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may be the only person here who did, but... Probably the only person on all of the internet that enjoyed that joke, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: My back hurts.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is not like what they were claiming to be the funniest joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hear candy!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a quaint little party room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tell...
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any new updates on Shaft?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut your mouth!
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, tell us what you know about Shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shaft's one bad mother... Shut your mouth!
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just talking about Shaft!
[SPEAKER_04]: We can dig it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That joke will be over you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's already, but... I can tell you about Shaft.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gonna be big.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big and far!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully it won't run too long.
[SPEAKER_13]: To quote Ultra Magnus, it's big.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bigger than the Matrix.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ultra Transformers.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, Transformers are owned.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, Shaft, November 9th for all you people who are coming from everywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, we're having people fly here.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: How cartoonish of you.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: What'd you say?
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, like I was saying, we're going to try to get things started as soon as possible.
[SPEAKER_13]: That morning we're going to have an official time release on the site soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: For people who are wanting to see it, just go to sakbemani.com and click on the link to Shaft on the main bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on Jamie Schaft and you'll see all about... You can shut up about that already.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you're... But we like... You remember, you were in deep shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you're in, like, boiling diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Milk.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lactose intolerance much?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm allergic to it, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway... We're trying to promote Schaft here, not have people run away screaming, holding their...
[SPEAKER_04]: Mr. T, I pity the fool!
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, and remember, Mr. T supports Shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: He pities the foo who don't go to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's on the site with his orange afro.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe you ought to ask an incentive.
[SPEAKER_04]: An extra tenth of a point to anyone who dresses up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, people will get an extra tenth of a percentile point added if they have the following items.
[SPEAKER_13]: They dress up like an A-Team member or they wear an orange afro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only orange?
[SPEAKER_13]: Stand by to win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about red?
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange.
Why?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because it's the Wow Wow 70s.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Orange Lounge is sponsoring the tournament.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or, you know, if you wear a little, you know, French girly dress and push a shopping cart around.
I'll wear a dress.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll wear a dress.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, people named Eric are disqualified.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking about 18 Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's still recording.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here, here.
[SPEAKER_13]: How's it recording?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we dropped the microphone, the player thingy, fucking thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead air, dead air.
[SPEAKER_13]: Back to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you didn't think you could fuck up this show with two microphones and a tape recorder, but, you know, anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to have that, like, stand by.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're experiencing technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just loop stand by to win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're back from the break.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: But no, the A-Team rules should be posted.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just to go ahead and give people an idea, though, we are putting the bars back on the machine for A-Team Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, you have to.
[SPEAKER_13]: And in the interest of being old school, the A-Team Freestyle, we're thinking, is going to be on the fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not going to be the regular bar, it's going to be my bar.
[SPEAKER_03]: A.K.A.
[SPEAKER_03]: your shaft?
[SPEAKER_13]: You are encouraged to rape the bar.
[SPEAKER_13]: No!
[SPEAKER_13]: You are encouraged...
[SPEAKER_13]: 2 Knee Drop, Hand Plant, but we ask, we ask, please no Matrix Walking.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, we demand it because, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we encourage getting bloody knees on the screws, Jamie style.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, I still have the scar.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about my famous butt drop?
[SPEAKER_13]: You can do the butt drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do the butt drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to be there, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get the day off!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_04]: I ran into Derek at work the other day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went through his line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just completely random.
[SPEAKER_04]: At Targay.
[SPEAKER_13]: You work at Targay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I'm an only straight cashier.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been there before.
[SPEAKER_04]: My God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the guys that work there are just... They had to be selling firewood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just, you know, going from one topic to the other, you know, the gay cashiers at Target to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, just to go ahead and give a brief recap, we're going to have freestyle on both machines.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, for all of you people who are listening on Sunday in the future for us in the current day for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are going to be running fourth mix freestyle first, so make sure that you decide on your song at registration or pre-registration so that we can make sure that we have the machine set up for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, there's going to be no changing your mind once we get to the machine unless the song happens to be in that machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You lay down the law.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn straight, or damn gay.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of them two.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other thing we should talk about Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have door prizes out the ass at Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of that's going to be thanks to the big Shaft right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt himself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about some of the lovely door prizes people can expect to see at Shaft.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can expect to see a whole bunch of DVDs provided by ADV Films.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, lots of DVDs to be had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots and lots of DVDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you bribing people to come here?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but there will be lots and lots of DVDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots and lots and lots.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now what about tapes for those people living in the Dark Age still?
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of DVDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I suppose I could provide some tapes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we can do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you shouldn't be living in the Dark Ages.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want a LaserDisc.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come out and get some Shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Come to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mr. T ate my balls.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dun dun dun!
[SPEAKER_13]: We know what the prize is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big, big prizes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to want them.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are also going to be having a demonstration the day of tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are these door prizes?
[SPEAKER_13]: These are actual winning prizes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn it, damn it, damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want door prizes.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's not providing door prizes.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we are going to also be having a special secret demo that day.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's going to be a special demo set up of something secret.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something super.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something extreme.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we're not telling, so don't even guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I wasn't going to guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say about that new DDR, if you notice the logo, it's spelled ErkStream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not X-Stream.
[SPEAKER_04]: The R is before the X. Look at the logo.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR ErkStream.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, yeah, it is the prescription symbol.
[SPEAKER_04]: The R and the X cross.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a drug game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're promoting drug usage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're promoting drug usage.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're promoting just the Ray Bars.
[SPEAKER_21]: Am I by a bathroom because it smells like shit?
[SPEAKER_19]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a clown door.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a little penny door.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, train wreck radio.
That was a car.
[SPEAKER_13]: Back to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I feel so good, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, back to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are also planning, assuming that I can find one, we are having special trophies for our A-Team Freestyle winners.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are going to have, as a trophy...
[SPEAKER_13]: Secret prizes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we could, you know, I mean, I'm sure I'll be able to provide, like, you know, bronze replicas of certain things if you need for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: What kind of job are you running on the side, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: We give him a gold picture of Samuel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: All they ever do is tell potty jokes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pencils rage!
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, so all of you have to come to Shaft or I'll hunt you down and kick your ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: You remember, I know where you live, I saw it on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's change gears completely, if you don't turn your ass, Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to talk about another game I just got to play for the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Initial D. No, not Initial D. Drum Mania 7th Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Guitar Freaks 8th Mix is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's our other universal, fuck you to Roseville, Goughlin.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bite our ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was there anything that you enjoyed about Drum Mania 7th Mix?
[SPEAKER_13]: I enjoyed playing Another World, but I hated that it wasn't Gak singing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad I can actually pass a song now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Breakdown owned me.
[SPEAKER_05]: The video to break down rules.
It's a little girl.
It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, well, think about the How to Spring video where you had a little panda.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was cool, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pandas are cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, well, you know, all the girls doing... That's not cool?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_04]: They did put in a new panda song in there, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's the one that's got the heart in the front and the back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what it says.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you know the name of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Bradley doesn't know the name of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nobody does.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got a girl riding on a silver surfer board type thing, and there's two pandas flying with her.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silver surfer was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: You said the silver surfboard.
[SPEAKER_05]: So?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: So?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is great radio, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate Orange Lounge radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: All they ever do is fight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dear Diary, I listened to this show today called Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_13]: First of all, I hate Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_13]: Those little girls are stealing all my fender.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, wait, that's the radio show and not the... Dear Diary, today I got a new hairdo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear Diary, kill me now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totally off the topic here, but on the fourth mix...
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, Felatio, it almost owned me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Felatio?
[SPEAKER_02]: Felatio almost owned me there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody owns me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Felatio, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: But I kicked Pink Taco's ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Felatio always owns me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think about that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's gonna be me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm gonna get hit.
[SPEAKER_04]: My idea of what can make this show better, let's all get drunk and then do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're actually planning a drunk show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever the next three-day weekend is, we're doing the drunk show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know when that is for Jamie and I when we both have a holiday.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll find one.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll make one if we have to.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're getting eggnog.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's eggnog radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm allergic to that too because it's got dairy crap in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, then you can just drink tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: I used to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't drank in six months.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll give you a whiskey enema.
[SPEAKER_04]: I drank last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had Red Bull.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not an alcoholic.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Red Bull mixed with Malibu is really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds gross.
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Bull is nasty.
[SPEAKER_04]: They call it a pebble.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pebbles or pebble.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, a dyke made it, so it might have been Pebbles.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you were just too drunk to know.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, Red Bull, if you pour it into a clear glass, it is the color of urine.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of my friends says that Red Bull smells like pussy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, first of all, I don't bend over to smell my own, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If pussy smelled that good, I'd eat it every day.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm gonna need a pussy bag.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do.
[SPEAKER_13]: To quote Rob, pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can just go around going cock, cock, cock, cock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you say the C-bomb on here?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cunt.
Cunt.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is adult content.
[SPEAKER_05]: Recess?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought recess was like 6, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I never said fucking when I was like 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's bathroom humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio, we cater to 7 year olds.
[SPEAKER_13]: Poopy!
[SPEAKER_13]: Freak Poopy!
[SPEAKER_13]: Doggy Doo!
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's hear it for the DDR free filters.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: The most fun filters in the world.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have more candy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_13]: Everybody dance!
[SPEAKER_13]: This is fun!
[SPEAKER_13]: No, they can't see us dance on the radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: My anus is bleeding!
[SPEAKER_09]: For the love of God!
[SPEAKER_09]: My anus is bleeding!
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I mention these tape shows tend to get a little too weird?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wanted to remind our listeners that as they're signing off.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're still off topic, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: Bit money, bit money, bit money, bit money, bit money, bit money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about 8th Style coming out this week, hitting some places finally?
[SPEAKER_13]: Everything's off the damn boat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you to the longshoremen people who aren't working right now because we need stuff off a boat like our 8th style machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitches.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't we just go do it ourselves?
[SPEAKER_04]: You go and we'll be right behind you.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I get a dolly, I'll push that bitch here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I'm not working.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll ship that baby on in.
[SPEAKER_04]: To your house, baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll guide it to shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, during the break, I was over kind of looking at the balloon blowing up machine where our 2DX machine's going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just admiring the space.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you start air playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm not that sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, my child?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where?
My trunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, it's Jesus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Savior, you're here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn, he's real.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a message for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to hell.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got a special place in for you in hell.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, I'm taking over hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, as heard in the intro to this very show.
[SPEAKER_04]: My mother resides in hell.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm taking over hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: What are you doing tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_13]: Working.
How long do they have for you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, what are we doing tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_13]: We're having a shaft meeting.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going globaling Saturday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, we're going to go global.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to CCL to global.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck CCL and their fucking racist bastards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently Derek has a fuck you of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just fuck CCL and their fucking racist people.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the dudes told my friend he was a Nazi bastard, and then this big huge black guy told me to fuck myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I said that their machine took my coins.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said, well, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of the police?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So did you go tell the manager?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I reported it that night.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he got suspended for like two, three weeks or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then his fat ass is back again.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now he's really nice to me and smiles and waves.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet he talks shit behind your back, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think everybody does.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys probably do, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, that guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe we let Fatty on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not that fat.
[SPEAKER_13]: You never heard about my issue with CTO.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just big boned.
[SPEAKER_13]: at CCL.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you said Cecile.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not, you're not, Derek, you're not fat, you're husky.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm chunky.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chunk.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'll put an accent mark so it's chunky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Jack A on 227?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, we're two people alive in the 80s?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's a little boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm 19!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a little boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you remember the show 227 on NBC?
[SPEAKER_04]: It had the chick from Sesame Street and Jackie... Oh, Jesus Christ, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway... You've really dated yourself, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to get beat up all the time Hey, I remember when Transformers was new Yeah, Transformers kicks ass I remember when Transformers was new I remember when the Power Rangers were new Oh my god I remember seeing the He-Man movie I have that on DVD No, I mean like seeing it like when it first I don't think we saw it in the theater I saw it in the theater We didn't see it in the theater, but we saw it on tape Masters of the Universe with Dolph Lundgren We rented it for our beta Oh, fuck
[SPEAKER_19]: Dude, Beta.
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember the inside of my mom's uterus.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've done Silverhawks tapes on Beta.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Silverhawks is awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Silverhawks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that a football team?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's a Seahawks.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not a football team.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seahawks is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, Silverhawks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, it's the same thing as Thundercats except they're silver and they're hawks.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they're in space.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're in space.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Stand by to win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bow wow wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so back in the 80s, inside my mom's uterus.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Weren't the 80s great?
[SPEAKER_13]: Spider stomping power pads.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was talking about the 80s.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been watching VH1 Classics this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: VH1 Classic is the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that station.
[SPEAKER_04]: The We Are the 80s show is like the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, I saw the worst video on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Shane O'Connor one?
[SPEAKER_13]: The Shane O'Connor video, to put your hands on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is how the video goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who'd want to put their hands on Shane O'Connor?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's flowers in the background, and look, I'm Shane O'Connor, and I'm dancing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Boy, I can't dance.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, look, it's MC Lyte, and she's going to rap.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, where'd MC Lyte go?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Shane O'Connor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, I'm Sinead O'Connor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a lesbian, but I just married a guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually saw the get up before the night is over video today.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm too poor to have four.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Balani related.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, if we see the reflex on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, this sucked.
[SPEAKER_13]: It worked today.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had nothing but Duran Duran songs stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was sitting at my desk singing the reflex.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't see the reflex, but I saw a view to a kill.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the way here, I heard Rio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Eighties after eight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, this is what I started.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was sitting at my desk, and I started singing the reflex, and the girl, the temp who sits behind me, started singing it with me.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we were both sitting at our desks singing the reflex while the rest of the office was looking at us.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to run outside real fast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be back.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys take over the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Take over.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dun, dun, dun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dun, dun, dun.
[SPEAKER_21]: Twinkle.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, my name is Rob and... You don't sound gay enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too gay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just talk normal then.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, Brad.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shh, I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, anyway.
[SPEAKER_19]: So how's this stuff, this Propel water?
[SPEAKER_13]: Propel owns me.
[SPEAKER_13]: It tastes like ghetto Kool-Aid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ghetto Kool-Aid?
[SPEAKER_05]: Like with too much sugar or too much water?
[SPEAKER_13]: Too much sugar.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did not mean to explode people's speakers.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just looked out the window and there was Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob is back.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob is coming.
[SPEAKER_19]: Rob's coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I left my bag outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to get it before somebody stole it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this isn't a nice neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, some guy proposed to me in this neighborhood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: I was walking to Scandia.
[SPEAKER_13]: This was, you know, about a month ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I was going to talk to Keith about things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or Kundagi, for people who know him online.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this old guy comes out of this garden.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he comes up to me and hands me a flower and says, You know, you...
[SPEAKER_13]: A flower in the weed garden.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you need a husband?
[SPEAKER_13]: I have one, thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I walked really fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: You power walked your way out of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I power walked my way out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some dude tried to propose to me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, first of all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where, what neighborhood is this again?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I'm here, big honky girl in the middle of, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where are we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Madison and Aidy.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Hillsdale.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate when my balls stick to the side of my leg.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't need to hear this.
[SPEAKER_03]: They get sweaty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, I can't believe you missed Survivor to come to this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not missing Survivor because I own a TiVo.
[SPEAKER_04]: and those things are the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear to God, if you ruin it for me, I will never forgive you either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not listening, I'm not listening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, Mr. DJ.
[SPEAKER_13]: Only the Market Show fans would get that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who was here in Sacramento last week, by the way, but I missed it because I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so poor.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could have gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm poorer than you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's play who's poorest.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, whip it out, dude.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to see you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't want to see you whip it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, whip out your wallet.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I owe money.
[SPEAKER_04]: No change.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_05]: No dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I have bills to pay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, looks like somebody's not as poor as I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have $19.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're a boy, you're a boy, you're a boy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Bradley, you're a boy?
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, Bradley has a source of income.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_19]: He's a whore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bradley's really an international spy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have no money and no job?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_11]: I lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that quote.
[SPEAKER_03]: You mean you have no money and no job?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brad wins an eagle, sir.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brad wins a forest, yay.
[SPEAKER_05]: He gets an autographed napkin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you win a lovely autographed piece of fecal matter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Someone give me a napkin.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I get evicted is what I get.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, he won an autographed eviction notice by his landlord.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now here's the prize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Jamie's autographing this right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got owned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: By Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to sign it too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob is writing something because his hand's in the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dear Brad, I secretly am harboring a fetish for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, you have to show Jamie what I wrote.
[SPEAKER_11]: He wrote penis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sorry about penis.
[SPEAKER_11]: Penis!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like candy heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's penis heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in the next mix, in DDR Extreme, we'll have Penis Star.
[SPEAKER_10]: Penis Star.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there's Vagina Heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trainwreck!
[SPEAKER_09]: Crash!
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you look really tired.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really tired!
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew about what?
[SPEAKER_05]: That he was tired.
[SPEAKER_04]: What songs did you just play?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a secret to everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: What edits?
[SPEAKER_04]: What fun edits were you playing?
[SPEAKER_02]: What dirty themed edits did you play this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play edits.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I played Boom Boom Dollar Maniac Doubles, and then I played Wonderland Maniac, and then I played Nizibutu Maniac Doubles.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a bootylicious mix.
[SPEAKER_20]: Shake that booty.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's tokens in that game over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What game?
Fourth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's tokens in fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Three-hole one?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Three-hole critter?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, let's take the show to the fourth mix machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're going to go over to the fourth mix machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, dude, there's a lot of crazy kids on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Experimental and sucky radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, this radio doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Brad left his napkin.
[SPEAKER_04]: What an ungrateful little bastard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come back here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm grabbing this napkin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to beat Brad over the head with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to put it in the back here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is great radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your week, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_13]: My week was interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_13]: I worked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_13]: We apparently got people crowded around the machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, we got people.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_04]: One person on Max 2 and a whole crowd around 4th Mix.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's too many little kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to kill them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, what we're going to do right now, we're going to go ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, where's the clock?
[SPEAKER_04]: It said like 34 or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're going to go ahead and go to break.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we will come back.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to play more DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, and we're going to wrap up the show in one more segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: So please stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, do you have a final thought, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you want, Matt?
[SPEAKER_02]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, question.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many people does it take to play versus mode in fourth mix?
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're three or six, it looks like five.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're that young, five.
[SPEAKER_04]: One to press the button and one for each of the little arrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sound of Speed Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_14]: Ready for the race, are you ready?
Are you ready?
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you ready?
The Wraith, From Outer Space
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a journey into the sound of speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're coming back from break, and Jamie wanted to show off, so she's getting on Max 2 right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, why are you picking this song?
[SPEAKER_13]: Just because it's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you think it's overplayed to all hell?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for taking that microphone away.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was getting all tangled up.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be amazing for our listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are going to be blown away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's read off Jamie's combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, boom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4, 5, 6, 8, 9, boom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great, great, perfect.
5, 6.
4, 6, 8, 10, 11, 13, 14, 19, 20, 21.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what about this weekend?
[SPEAKER_04]: So what are we going to be doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, back to the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great, perfect.
24, 25.
9, 11.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 13, 14, 15.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4, 5.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's doing Riverdance.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_04]: Her pants are stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are your pants going to fall off while you're playing Kakumei?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll buy that for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on to the bar for dear life, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell no is right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you think this video is so generic?
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this video.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like flashing squares, flashing blocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a rave.
[SPEAKER_19]: Flashing squares.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is that song?
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell is that animation supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, ooh, I'm flying through a tunnel of color, and there's colored boxes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like a birth canal.
[SPEAKER_04]: That looks like a tunnel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It does.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: She passed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, how does it feel to be a winner?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for falling off me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to point out that Jamie, by the way, has burning feet right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burning feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's burning the floor.
[SPEAKER_13]: My pants are too big.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I was tripping over them the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now why this song?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Viking Superstar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's playing Love To Me Lite.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think we can expect to see a lot of... Wait, wait.
Oh, hell yeah.
Oh, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_19]: We fell out again for a minute.
[SPEAKER_19]: Technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I was... I'm so fucking out of breath.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was talking to the microphone pretending like it was plugged in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aren't I a stupid ass?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to be doing a freestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's facing away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, let's go around to the other side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's stand next to the carousel.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's not even looking.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those who want to check out the webcam and see this going on, you can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you can't.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the address, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: www.goatsay.cx Goat say?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's goat say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she got a 50 combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I think she just did a spin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Knee drop, knee drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she lost her balance and broke her combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck, I shouldn't have said that.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to hurt herself.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a pretty strong thud there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what the kids are up to on fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to leave Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we'll come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's a big girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: She'll be okay by herself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what they're playing over here.
[SPEAKER_19]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you insane?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is, what is this, Saints?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't even, oh, it's one of Loki's edits.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's Ninja Burrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, oh, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, you failed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you failed.
[SPEAKER_02]: You suck, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: How does it feel to suck?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looked like it was pretty hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was all six of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too bad to do that kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Game over!
[SPEAKER_04]: Pulled out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever noticed that when you put the memory card, it says inserted, and we take it out, it says pulled out?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Naoki is a very perverted person.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
What?
[SPEAKER_04]: What'd you say now?
[SPEAKER_13]: Even with my thumble, I missed four and got an A. Are you bleeding, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not bleeding, are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: She's okay!
[SPEAKER_04]: She's red, but she's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What song is she gonna pick?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we know you're fat there, you already mentioned it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're not that fat!
[SPEAKER_04]: You're husky, you're husky.
[SPEAKER_04]: I probably got a bigger belly than you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much, have you lost weight playing DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, how much?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like 40 pounds?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you stop eating fat?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, see, I lost a bunch of weight when I did wrestling, and then I worked at Jack in the Box, and I got super fat.
[SPEAKER_05]: So fuck Jack in the Box and his stupid ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, don't eat Jack in the Box chicken sandwiches.
[SPEAKER_05]: They drop them on the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for sharing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, she's spinning the disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now see, this video's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: People dancing and shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but it says heat up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the English they usually have in the background sometimes.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say is your favorite movie in all of Max 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: Max 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd have to go with Tsugaru.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why Tsugaru?
[SPEAKER_04]: Those funny-looking bald dudes with the little thing on their head spinning around.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's funny again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we need to change our mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is such great radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is better.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to harass the waitress and the interviewer and shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's always next time.
[SPEAKER_19]: They'll probably kick us out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, some of those waitresses are hella cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, but last time when we were at Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: But they have Soul Calibur 2 and Initial D, so... Fuck them all except for those two games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I bet you they're broken today.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever played this machine, the electrifying machine, the one that shocks you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it shock you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it shocks you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you serious?
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to play it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Play it live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see if it will erase the tape.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, I can't stand too close.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it will, but... Sorry, the printer doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't it four tokens?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, put one in and see how many it wants.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put one in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, it wants four.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, you're going to get hella zapped and shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright everybody, he's playing the electrifying Uncle Fester, the new adaptation.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to ask him what it feels like while he's playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: High power, and hold on to both of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on to both.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us the sensation.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't let go, don't be a puss.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not even on yet.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's vibrating.
[SPEAKER_19]: I feel something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, this is kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah, that's a...
[SPEAKER_05]: it says are you getting an electro oh my god come on you can do it take it take it no come on you're almost there you gotta get yeah yeah you gotta hit a 3000 you're almost there take it take it i smell burning flesh that's just me yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: We have... Let's see your hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it hurt?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see if it smells like burning flesh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'm in love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, how was that vibrating sensation?
[SPEAKER_13]: You should try two-player.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, two can play, you just have to hold hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Owie.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess it forms like a circuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only in America would you give a machine a dollar to beat you up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we got that arm wrestling machine that's broken.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did he get out of that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing, because the damn printer's broken.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I say to that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I sold my pants.
[SPEAKER_13]: I feel inclined to go play Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to go play Afterburner?
[SPEAKER_13]: We have a working Afterburner here in Sandia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go play Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_05]: And here we go to play the all-time favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was asking, hey Jamie, I'll ask you the same question I asked Brad while you were playing Spin the Disc.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you say is your favorite Max 2 video?
[SPEAKER_13]: Long Train Runnin'.
[SPEAKER_04]: Long train running, right on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just cause the dude looks kinda cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would say my favorite would be the whistle song, even though it's overplayed, that bunny just rules.
[SPEAKER_13]: Should I go for the classic afterburner?
[SPEAKER_04]: Classic afterburner.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or my favorite bicycle game prop cycle?
[SPEAKER_05]: Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_13]: Afterburner.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the all-time favorite, no, this is Afterburner 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you feel about the sequel?
[SPEAKER_04]: They have an old-school Afterburner machine that actually moves.
[SPEAKER_04]: You sit in the cockpit.
[SPEAKER_13]: They need the freaking space harrier.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said cock.
[SPEAKER_13]: Someone give me a token.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, honey, go get her a token.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is she, your bitch?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you feel about being bossed around by this guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going there.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm going there.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just ignore him half the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go, girl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until about 10 o'clock at night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're listening to KTMI.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sick stream.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where'd she go?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, here she comes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here she comes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our beautiful Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hey, it's a one now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, I get to hold the purse.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's four tokens to play, but it's worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can, like, go sideways in this thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it, like, vibrate and shit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: What happens?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you need... Oh, you need... She's strapping on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or in.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's strapping herself in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, she isn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's going... Oh, she's going strapless.
[SPEAKER_05]: No strap on for her tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting squishy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here you go.
Get ready.
It will move, by the way.
You gotta move back out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, back out of the way a little.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look how the monitor like totally bends at a 45 degree angle when she plays.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game kicks Beachhead's 2000's ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it doesn't have the cool, uh, bubble for the, uh, Sumo, like Sumo has.
[SPEAKER_04]: True.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not Sumo.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's, it's old school Sega.
[SPEAKER_19]: Recording their songs and shit?
[SPEAKER_19]: Nah, fuck em.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's free promotion!
[SPEAKER_19]: Kickstarter too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's reloading.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super Zappa recharge.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's getting filled.
[SPEAKER_04]: How come the machine doesn't do loop-de-loops when she does?
[SPEAKER_05]: How come the machine doesn't blow up when she does?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you die?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did it feel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it the rest of your life?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, retro gaming owns.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll play the prop cycle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's lesson of the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't drink 44 ounces of Pepsi and play Cat of Devils all day.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about don't go eat a bunch of Mongolian barbecue and then play three 8-footers in a row?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't play double catas anyways.
[SPEAKER_13]: Last time I was here, I had just gotten done eating Mongo Chow and I played Superstar, Holic, and Spin the Disc all in a row.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I should get some Mike's Hard Lemonade because I think an alien is going to pop out of my chest.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounds good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just, you know, as long as you're actually a real person.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just drink like 12 of them and in an hour you get really fucked up.
[SPEAKER_13]: You look drunk already.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki is our sweat elemental.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now Rob's going to fly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's going... I hope that this has actually sound today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to stipulate that I've never played this game in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pointers, pedal fast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't run into stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: And don't be afraid not to pedal to descend.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: You need to steer tightly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to do it tight?
[SPEAKER_13]: You have to be tight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's no sound on the machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob is going for level one.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, level two.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he's level one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Level one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that a finger or a... He's going to cliff rock.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do I do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pedal.
[SPEAKER_13]: Pedal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where do I pedal to?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can push into the... Burst the balloons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Burst it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go run into the balloons.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just in case you're supposed to be...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's supposed to make you feel like you're getting... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll just leave that alone.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob's doing pretty good for a beginner, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob's kicking ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, you got 200, 100.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I missed that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Rob has an orgasm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit, I missed one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just keep going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Smash that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hit it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there's a dude on the roof.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should have killed him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't run in.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need that.
[SPEAKER_13]: That gives you more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, get the shiny balloons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Matt.
[SPEAKER_13]: For the record, Rob is owning at this game for his first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's got an eight perfect balloon run.
[SPEAKER_13]: He just got two and one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turn around.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to get six.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to get six more balloons.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Go in the hole.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is such crap.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go down.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go down under the waterfall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here he goes.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's going down, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit, I missed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got more stuff here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, get the pink one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob goes for 10 seconds, and he has increased his time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So far his score is a whopping... He has 2,150 points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, we can't read.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now he's out of the cave, and he's going into the tent.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm flying!
[SPEAKER_05]: Now he comes out of the tent.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was locked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was wobbed.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you can't say that's another inside joke.
[SPEAKER_05]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hit that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go faster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 500.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's 200.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't read.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there's another one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you got it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got four more balloons.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Rob's going to crash.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, this game is brought to you by Doom On.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game is brought to you by, oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's Namco.
[SPEAKER_05]: A fan, what's his name?
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, Namco owns your soul.
[SPEAKER_05]: I died.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what do you think of Prop Cycle?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was actually pretty... Oh, dude, it shows... I had no sense of direction.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pop four balloons.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Rob got wing leader for his first time.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like third place.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been better if the game actually had sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I'll tell you, that was like the worst radio ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh, Matt's going to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, don't you have to pee?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_13]: Missile Command, Centipede, Millipede.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, what is Centipede and Millipede famous for?
[SPEAKER_13]: The one sound.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's your one-up noise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the difference between Centipede and Millipede?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, what's the difference between Centipede and Millipede?
[SPEAKER_13]: Millipede is faster and harder and it's longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Shaft?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's faster, harder, and longer, just like Shaft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: As Matt goes for, ooh, the hard level.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Solitaire.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, dude, that dude has wings.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he is going for it with a vengeance.
100.
[SPEAKER_13]: And another 100.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, a choo-choo train.
[SPEAKER_13]: And a train.
[SPEAKER_05]: A choo-choo.
[SPEAKER_13]: I remember this level being really hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a... He has to dive through the hole.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he got it, the one that was in the hole.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now he's heading into the cave.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, go down the hole.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to flush the potty.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happens when he gets a thousand right there?
[SPEAKER_13]: And now he is in the subway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Getting hit by... Running into poles.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game is full of poles and holes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Poles and holes.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he's got another 10 seconds, but he's only got 31 left.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's the thousand mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: What thousand?
[SPEAKER_05]: The thousand below his score.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, he's kind of good at this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And 18.
[SPEAKER_13]: He advanced one day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Day one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, he's been flying for a whole day, folks.
[SPEAKER_13]: and he's chasing another balloon around a girder and he decided not to go at it.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's going into another hole.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just me.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's me, Mario.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you're not Mario.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not Mario.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wario.
[SPEAKER_13]: See, I told you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're playing the punching game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, that chick would kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he's got another ten seconds and ran into a wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's a wall, dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's a person.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to hear about your ass.
[SPEAKER_13]: And apparently you cannot knock down the people that are in the cave.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_13]: And time is up.
[SPEAKER_13]: So how well did Loki do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Two points for one play on this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: He got 1,400 points.
[SPEAKER_13]: He completed the level.
[SPEAKER_13]: And he gets an ending.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, dude, that's Coffee Man Joe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, it's Ryo from... I made it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, the guy in Prop Cycle looks like Ryo from Digimon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's now going to day two.
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't get enough points.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually he did the first thing where you only play once.
[SPEAKER_05]: These people are scaring me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see exactly how this goddamn punching bag game... Oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: It pops down.
[SPEAKER_09]: So are we ready to close the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, where's the clock?
[SPEAKER_13]: Did we have like another minute and a half to fill?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the last segment five minutes early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We wanted to go play DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is such awful radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can we do that's exciting for listeners?
[SPEAKER_13]: Strip!
[SPEAKER_13]: I was going to say that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's start streaking through Scandia.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then we're sure not to have Tourney here.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because they don't know that I'm from here.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't know me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's take a tour around the rest of the arcade, shall we?
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go play Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where's Bubble Bobble?
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought I heard Bubble Bobble.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's just Ultracade has the Bubble Bobble sounds in it, but it doesn't have Bubble Bobble loaded yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to have it in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're playing the punching bag game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is not Punch Mania, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see what a weakling I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to get more tokens, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go ahead and do the... You know, there's two Centipede machines here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's walk around and poke at stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, everyone heard Afterburner, which I played because I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have Centipede.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have one of the best shooter games ever, Raiden Fighter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, dude, you can buy this shit for a thousand bucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, a thousand for Centipede.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can play it on my Atari 5200 at home.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, we got a Harley game.
[SPEAKER_13]: The old, old Harley game that's been out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's old?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's pretty old.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple years.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have Tekken Tag Tournament, which I've been hearing should be upgraded to a Tekken 4, but I don't know if it's going to be by 2029.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have Marvel vs. Capcom 2, a very, very fun game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Revolution X, one of the most fun gun games ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have Alien vs. Predator, Daytona USA, on cue.
[SPEAKER_13]: Daytona!
[SPEAKER_13]: We have House of the Dead 2, which you can play on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, typing of the dead is fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I've heard of that game.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have Got Left Dark Legacy.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have Golden Tee 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not 4 with a hyphen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which reminds me, the very first place I ever played Golden Tee was a little ghetto cade in Roseville called Supercade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Supercade closed this month.
[SPEAKER_04]: The guy retired.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's have a moment of silence.
[SPEAKER_04]: A moment of silence for Supercade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Supercade ruled because they have Playboy Pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I had to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I want to show off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what a weakling I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: and someone is playing Rockman Power Battles.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, he's playing Rockman.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually that's Proto Man right there.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but the game came out as Rockman.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, now Rob's going to punch the thingy.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's going to punch this thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's listen to this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, what has he become?
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob on the meter is, he hit 290.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, he gets to hit it again. 290.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think Rob gets one more try.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, you didn't even get a rating.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't register.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob did not register.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me try.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob's going to give me money to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who holds what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to probably get really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you do better than Rob, you get to autograph something for yourself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, here's the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's going to show off what a stud she is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here she goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's revving up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, cracking her knuckles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here she goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: She also got 290.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think 290 is what you get when you hit it so weak it didn't even register.
[SPEAKER_04]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Try again, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't let that scurry off.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many times did you put... I put one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I try one more?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: How come nobody's registering?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that mean... I'm going to try one more.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to do my Popeye hit, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, here we go, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Flying jump kick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you go, Jim.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to kick it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm too short.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I could even kick that high.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could, like, axe kick it or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops, I stepped on your foot.
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't feel anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you're a playboy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob went over the scale.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob is now a playboy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I bet you these two are like the lights are out.
[SPEAKER_05]: You only get one punch.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to play again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm a playboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I got one more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to headbutt it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you really?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to hurt.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, my head's too hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, I'm digging deep into my pocket.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob's digging deep into his pants.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go, Jamie, go.
[SPEAKER_04]: This may make her forget how much deep... Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: She can't reach to kick it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can actually reach the ball to kick it, but not high enough to actually kick it up into the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go, girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here she goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And... Pow.
[SPEAKER_04]: She got 210.
[SPEAKER_04]: Try again.
[SPEAKER_04]: See if it'll let you do it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hang on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's a weakling, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love her anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now to relieve myself, I'm going to go sulk.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're actually about ready to wrap up this train wreck of a show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here comes Matt, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Matt is also a Playboy, but I would like to point out I believe I was a little stronger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did he get Superman?
[SPEAKER_04]: A Playboy Superman.
[SPEAKER_04]: He got Playboy and Superman?
[SPEAKER_05]: He went over the scale.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no, what I think is lots of the lights are out, but they all light up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I think this machine is just fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, Roseville, anyone?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to tell Keith to fix his machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time to end the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final thoughts, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't have anything to drink to burp, so, uh... This is kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, bite me.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final thoughts from Derek?
[SPEAKER_05]: I already have a microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final thoughts, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh... Give me that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final thoughts from Matt?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: That chick in that police 911 too had huge tits.
[SPEAKER_02]: How can she fight crime and have huge tits at the same time?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not right.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Wonderbra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any final thoughts from the love slave?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might just get fed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's go get manga chow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they're still open.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, police brutality.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're ending this show now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks everybody for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought, the listeners are never going to let us take a week off again.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we love you anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for listening to our pre-taped madness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why does it say puff puff and his hand's in his pocket?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you guys next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be live.
[SPEAKER_13]: And our fortune cookie message of the week is, are you in joy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you guys next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week when we'll be live and you can yell at us in the chat room and tell us we suck.
[SPEAKER_05]: This time I won't be there so you don't have to worry about me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because Derek's in deep trouble.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh no, he's not in just deep trouble, he's in... Boiling diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not boiling diarrhea anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: You are now stuck somewhere in constipation land.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.