[SPEAKER_08]: It's a videotape!
[SPEAKER_08]: Put it in!
[SPEAKER_13]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our live talk program begins now.
Boring!
[SPEAKER_06]: This video sucks!
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge may contain nudity.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hide Orange Lounge radio for the fucking children.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess there's just two kinds of people, Miss Sandstone.
[SPEAKER_00]: My kind of people, and assholes.
[SPEAKER_00]: One... ...Ranma... ...is good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mashed it by that much.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's Dr. Evil's cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: How can you tell?
[SPEAKER_01]: I never forget a pussy.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would like, if I may, to take you on a strange journey.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate nature!
[SPEAKER_07]: I just wish the world would explode, and then I could take over hell.
[SPEAKER_16]: Do I look like the weather girl?
[SPEAKER_16]: Everything alright?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yep, two corpses, everything's fine.
[SPEAKER_16]: We are live and this is episode number 16 for October the 20th, 2002.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're tuned into the Bimani Scene's most extreme radio station of all things Bimani.
[SPEAKER_16]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, my lovely co-host, is stuck in a bit of traffic right now just outside of San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_16]: She gave me a call about 6 o'clock and she was stuck right before the bridge in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_16]: She, by the way, this weekend went to YowieCon.
[SPEAKER_16]: For those that don't know what Yowie is...
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not going to tell you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, filling in for Jamie tonight, we have some guests here in studio.
[SPEAKER_16]: Please say hello to the man with the perfect attendance record.
[SPEAKER_16]: It is Loki.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_16]: And of course, almost with the perfect attendance record, I think you're pretty close, say hello to Dave.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I think we have a couple more folks coming later, too, so that'll be good.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll be talking to everybody a bit later.
[SPEAKER_16]: First, we're going to take a quick break, and we're going to start it off with a song that I know has become one of Loki's favorite songs now, because he got to prove everybody right on something.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're going to start this off with a song from 2DX8Style.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's called Sakura.
[SPEAKER_16]: And do you want to say anything about Sakura?
[SPEAKER_16]: I was right.
[SPEAKER_16]: And we'll get in more to that later.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, and look who just walked in the door.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's some more guests.
[SPEAKER_16]: Everybody say hello to Brad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, Jamie did that a week ago.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was so last week, Brad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: And everybody say hello to the rice princess, Irene.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, you guys sound so thrilled.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, you're tired.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, so we're going to start this off with something from 2DX8 style and just maybe, just maybe from the new Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_16]: Extreme.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is Revenge with Sakura here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you don't stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come on.
Like Jazz and Hip Hop, it makes your body and soul a future goal
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: And now DJ Lissa, rocking it, rocking it, rocking it
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Dave's sitting there over the corner doing the little dance.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_16]: You never heard the catch-up song?
[SPEAKER_16]: After the show, I'll show you the video.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's these little Latina hoochies doing these little dance.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like they're all labeling it the new Macarena.
[SPEAKER_16]: So if there's ever a Disney's Mix 2, you know, we're going to have the ketchup song.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because we had the Macarena in the first one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, happy day.
[SPEAKER_16]: My thoughts exactly.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want to take a minute at the very top of the show here to recognize my other show that I've been participating in for the last 20 months, understudationlive.org.
[SPEAKER_16]: And for those that didn't hear, the show came to an end, I believe, two weeks ago was the last show because Live 365 was off this past week.
[SPEAKER_16]: And unfortunately, there were some circumstances that developed which caused our program to go off of air.
[SPEAKER_16]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_16]: Revival, when he's over, he's out there in Texas, he moved out to Texas, he might do something with some new co-hosts, and I definitely would support him in doing something like that.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, big thanks to everybody at understationlive.org.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now, back to Orange Lounge Radio, here we are, we're back from break last week, we were also breaking last week, breaking what, I don't know, oh, breaking all-time low listening records for our tape show, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, actually, it was fine.
[SPEAKER_16]: What did you think of that show, Brad?
[SPEAKER_16]: It was interesting, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Did you hear the show?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I had to dump the whole tape and edit it together.
[SPEAKER_16]: I heard the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was... We always tend to get a very mixed reaction from the chat room when we do those tapes.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was the second time we taped a show in advance.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that one was the one from Scandia?
[SPEAKER_16]: That was the Scandia one we taped a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: My opinion is the Golfland one was better.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because you were on it, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I wasn't on either one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought you were on the Golfland one.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was Ted...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it was better because when you went downstairs to play Hip Hop Mania, and the person was like, what are you doing here?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_16]: Keith, the wonderful, wonderful arcade technician over at Scandia that's hooking the place up with 2DX8 style, hopefully soon too, if Channel Beat...
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey you guys!
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, gee, I can't figure out who that is.
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it basically like gay anime?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like male gay anime with pretty boys?
[SPEAKER_16]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, Loki wants to contribute something.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was gay anime porn, from what I've heard.
[SPEAKER_03]: From what I understand, it's not really porn.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all implied.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all like implied porn, you know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know how you imply porno, but just like a Skinamax film.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like a gay Skinamax film, but it's animated in a Japanese style.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm glad that I never heard of this before.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's for real.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is for real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you're serious?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was like the very first time I ever played DDR was at the Rocky Horror 25th Anniversary Convention.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Irene was there.
[SPEAKER_16]: Irene was there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Irene knows about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to tell you about the actual convention the first day.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Rocky Horror Picture in one door, and right next door, the gun show.
[SPEAKER_07]: The gun show.
[SPEAKER_07]: With a bunch of hicks.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they hated Asian people, and I was so scared.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was a bunch of card-carrying NRA members mixed in with guys dressed in drag, doing the whole Frankenfurter thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you've ever seen Rocky Horror, you know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_16]: If you haven't...
[SPEAKER_16]: You should.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: Where you been?
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you been?
[SPEAKER_07]: Wake up.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go outside.
[SPEAKER_16]: Stop playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: Put the controller down.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was scary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, one thing that Travis, the host over at UnderStationLive.org recommended to me was that we should take, now that that show is going to be gone, we should take some of that and bring it to Orange Lounge and just get really random on that show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because you know UnderStationLive was supposed to be a Rocky Horror show, and in the beginning it was.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was just like we are with Bomani.
[SPEAKER_16]: Nothing but Rocky Horror for two hours, and then it just turned into Radio Hell.
[SPEAKER_16]: But it hasn't always been Radio Hell.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you want?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for calling, how may I direct your call?
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of, I guess the word would be ironic that we're talking about how sooner or later we'll get off topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And while talking about this, we're getting off topic.
[SPEAKER_16]: Nah, fuck DDR, it's old.
[SPEAKER_16]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: We had a topic?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, where are all the donuts, Rob?
[SPEAKER_16]: You have to go get them.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're poor!
[SPEAKER_16]: I can give money if you want to go get donuts, but we have a show to do.
[SPEAKER_16]: You can't get donuts now.
[SPEAKER_16]: What show?
[SPEAKER_16]: This show.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's an old joke.
[SPEAKER_16]: Old joke.
[SPEAKER_16]: Surprise, we're on the internet and we've got that many people listening.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_16]: Enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: We don't talk about our statistics over there.
[SPEAKER_16]: So!
[SPEAKER_16]: What do I want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_16]: There's so much going on.
[SPEAKER_16]: I said first we'd talk about... Gun shows.
[SPEAKER_16]: This was big news.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is actually a follow-up.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, Brad, gun shows.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is a follow-up to...
[SPEAKER_16]: www.cagames.com
[SPEAKER_16]: Then you should burn this.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is the Feat of Fury, which is this new release of a DDR simulator.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not sure if you'd want to call it a simulator, a clone.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's not an emulator.
[SPEAKER_16]: I always get criticized on this because I call things emulators to be simulators.
[SPEAKER_16]: What would you categorize this as, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just another game that's similar to DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically like Dance Magic Mode from Disney's Rave.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it just so happens to support the DWI format, sort of, because it doesn't have tempo changes, tempo stops, freeze arrows, or 12th notes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of third mix down.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's basically DDR first mix type level.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, the simulator hasn't quite progressed, you know, obviously to that level of being on the same caliber as DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's an early beta release.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're not done with everything I wanted to do yet.
[SPEAKER_16]: So it's an early beta that got released, but you can download this.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's got about, what, seven songs on it that you can play.
[SPEAKER_16]: All by the same guy, I notice, but that'll probably change with future versions.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's some decent stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to play one of the songs from Feet of Fury a little later.
[SPEAKER_16]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_16]: Some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's just like Dance Magic, as you said.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's kind of like Street Fighter meets DDR, if you can imagine that, because you've got your characters that you pick and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I know everybody got a chance to test it for the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was just kind of wondering what you guys thought.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll start.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know it's an early beta.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think it's an early beta.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's damn impressive.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, it's kind of like what I'd call a DDR first mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: As far as DDR goes, it's got a long way to go to catch up.
[SPEAKER_16]: But, I mean, it's still a first release.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's early, but it looks good.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, a lot of Dreamcast homebrewing stuff isn't that great, but Feet of Fury is coming along very nicely.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love the idea that it's going to support your own stuff, your own DWIs and things.
[SPEAKER_16]: I kind of wish there was a mode that wasn't Dance Magic, like you could play in a normal mode, but I kind of think that all that stuff is coming.
[SPEAKER_16]: They just want to get the initial stuff out the gate, and then they'll kind of add on to it.
[SPEAKER_16]: All that Freeze Arrows and Twelfth Nose, they'll probably come on to it later, but they've got to get their basic engine established first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, for smart, they'll do that.
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_16]: I think if you've got a Dreamcast and a burner, there's no reason you shouldn't be going and downloading this right now and playing it.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I understand, it's a beta and all, and I guess, you know, this is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Star, you know, this could be, there's some possibilities and things with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, who was the graphic designer on this thing, man?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some big Star Trek geek or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because what are the arrows?
[SPEAKER_04]: The arrows are the shape of... Are they?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just make the arrows the shape of the normal arrows in DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, that's the thing, is that you don't want to copy DDR, because they're probably afraid of a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, you know what, though, that if you ever play True Kiss Destination DDR, those arrows, see, those arrows look a hell of a lot like those arrows.
[SPEAKER_16]: I kind of noticed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, on the topic of those arrows, you know, it's nice to have different arrows, but you can't tell the difference between, you know, different notes, like 4th notes, you know, 8th, 16th.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they have a slight color change to them, but otherwise they're just looking like these shiny Star Trek circles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, why don't we just make them big circles, all of them?
[SPEAKER_03]: They can all be circles.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be easy to dance her, so we can't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but I think that as far as it goes of actual playing quality, it's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, like the arrows, it's really weird because they're one of the modifiers, especially, makes all the arrows spin around in place, kind of like, I forget what it is on Step Mania, do you know what the... Dizzy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dizzy mode, where all of them spin around while going up, even though they're in the same column.
[SPEAKER_05]: And with arrows that long, they kind of overlap, so you can't tell which note is which.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, right, but I mean, it's not supposed to be easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's not supposed to be impossible to read.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, true, true.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also another thing I noticed is it's way too easy to get perfects.
[SPEAKER_16]: That blink thing was the most annoying one where half the arrows would disappear at a time, they'd fade in and out.
[SPEAKER_16]: You'd be able to see half of them.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was really hard to see.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't quite get how the gameplay of the game went.
[SPEAKER_16]: Of course, maybe that's my own fault because I didn't read a manual, but hopefully they'll do a built-in tutorial later on in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think there's any story mode or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't look like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't know, like they have in, um, Puzzle, uh, Tetris, or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_05]: Puzzle Fighter?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, um... God, what's a game?
[SPEAKER_05]: God, shit!
[SPEAKER_05]: Puzzle Bobble?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bustamoo?
[SPEAKER_05]: Super...
[SPEAKER_05]: Final Fantasy?
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, here's basically what the concept of the game is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, you pick a character.
[SPEAKER_03]: Each character has a different kind of attack or modifier that they do.
[SPEAKER_03]: For instance, you know, one will have Blink, one will have Dizzy, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so...
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Yoshi, Tetris, or Yoshi?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, dammit!
[SPEAKER_03]: Forget it!
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dammit!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so basically you pick a character, and then they have different modifiers that they attack with or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So as you're going along, you have a little bar that's kind of in the middle, and as soon as that builds up, now you can do one of two things.
[SPEAKER_03]: Either you can set to auto, where once it builds up all the way along, it'll automatically unleash the attack, or you can set to manual, to where when it builds up, you can attack whenever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, with the modifier or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I like to do during that is just punch my neighbor, whoever's playing against me.
[SPEAKER_04]: When it fills up or not, whenever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whenever I feel like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more effective.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I look like a raccoon!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think they could hear you on the mic.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's for the best that they couldn't hear me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, that's pretty much what it is.
[SPEAKER_16]: Tetris Attack?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: How'd that feel when I smashed the microphone against your hand?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I said Tetris Attack earlier.
[SPEAKER_16]: Or the uber awesome, and I'm sorry, fuck all y'all, this game rules, Pokemon Puzzle League.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you mean Yoshi's Cookie?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I mean Pokemon Puzzle League.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was never released on Super Nintendo, it doesn't exist, it was always Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yoshi's Cookie
[SPEAKER_03]: What the hell are you doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're making bad radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we're doing Kentucky Fried Movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: For all our listeners who can't see.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, they're supposed to add a step editor, and I haven't tried to actually make a swap CD, but you can do that too, and I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm being told a few things by Twen in the chatroom, who is kind of the person who alerted us to this game in the first place, saying that the creator has stated that a main mode will be in the final version, cool, that's good to hear, and not only will you be able to put in your own DWIs and stuff, you'll be able to have your own graphic themes.
[SPEAKER_16]: So if you want to change the arrows, go to town.
[SPEAKER_16]: I wasn't waving, I was going like, way, yay, wow.
[SPEAKER_16]: I thought you were waving because you wanted to talk, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: But anyways... What other kinds of modes would you be looking forward to to see in a later version of Feat of Fury?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That just means I have to buy Dreamcast pads now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screw that, I'm just sticking with my PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, what I was planning to do since I'm, you know, like that, I was going to rip the songs out of that sim and put it on my sim, but, you know, that's just me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you say rip?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I said rip.
Shh, keep it quiet.
Shh.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to go ahead and play one of those songs from Feet of Fury real fast.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just going to play this one song.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're not going to go into a full break, but I thought you guys would want to hear the music that goes into it.
[SPEAKER_16]: And this is created by a guy who did all the songs in the first release of Feet of Fury, by the way.
[SPEAKER_16]: Roddy Toomin.
[SPEAKER_16]: Toomin Mim?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Also known as, and if he's listening, he's going to kill me for butchering his name.
[SPEAKER_16]: Also known as DJ Geki.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is my favorite, and the CD looks like a giant happy face.
[SPEAKER_16]: This happens to be my favorite song in the game.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is Tisanitis.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I'm going to play this for you guys so you can sample some of the music from Feet of Fury right here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, if you're just joining us, that was Titsanitis from Feet of Fear.
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't pronounce these damn names.
[SPEAKER_16]: Titsanasis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Titsanitis, I have a cream for that.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is why I'm on the internet radio and not normal radio, along with the rest of you, might I add.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was from Feet of Fury, which is a brand new Dreamcast DDR clone type game.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know what the official label of it would be, but dance magic type things.
[SPEAKER_16]: You guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: Some very interesting comments were made during that song in the room here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Basically talking how much of an old school video game that sounds like.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like level four of Blaster Master or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_03]: In defense of Blaster Master, it had better music than that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Blaster Master is the shit.
[SPEAKER_16]: Irene, I know you had some pretty interesting opinions, so why don't you share with everyone else listening?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh man, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: My plumbing was clogged.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brad is the most immature person I know.
[SPEAKER_16]: And he's like four years older than you are.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, um, Feet of Fury, is that what it's called?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Feet of Fury.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do you think it sucks?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's free!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care!
[SPEAKER_07]: But the best games in life are free!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, well, if you already have, like, third mix, fourth mix, whatever, on PlayStation, that's free.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I mean, this is, it's already been done on Disney's Rave, and I think it's just kind of cheesy, and, like, the music doesn't fit well, it doesn't dance...
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I couldn't dance to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I saw it, I wouldn't want to get it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now, do you think if Loki performed some sexual favors over there and got some of his songs on the FOF, it might be a little better?
[SPEAKER_07]: It might be a little better, but I still wouldn't play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't know, like, you know, not because of his music, but because the whole scheme of it just sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, like, if he were to put his music on a Max scheme or something like that, or Disney's Rave, yeah, sure, I'd play it.
[SPEAKER_16]: So you just want to play a copy of DDR, basically, with new songs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, not even just a copy, just DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, this is not, if you're going to even call this a knockoff of DDR, it's not very well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even if it is preliminary, it's just, it kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: Can't please everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're about a variety of opinion here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: You suck, Irene.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can never please women.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_16]: You can never please a woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you can't, Robyn.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't need to.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I think Two Panel would be better, because it's like, just running.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Dropout.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, let's just play Boom Boom Dollar.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's over left, left, right, right, left, right, left, right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, let's see, let's just play, let's see, Mickey Mouse March from Disney's Ring.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is left and right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know, I still, I still, I like Feet of Fury.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, it's not something I'm going to play every day.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's just kind of something you look at and go, yeah, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: I wonder what the next one's going to look like, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: You can look at them, not me, because I'm not going to play it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to die.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know I speak the truth.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all good.
[SPEAKER_07]: You speak the truth.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, thanks.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love you, Eileen.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now her bar got full and she punched me.
[SPEAKER_16]: I suggest we're going to take a quick break, because I need to go to potty, and I've got people yelling at me left and right to play to the channel.
[SPEAKER_16]: Are you guys destroying things back there?
[SPEAKER_16]: What the hell's going on?
[SPEAKER_16]: Dave had a little too much to drink, so he's... Oh, I'm sorry to hear that, Dave.
[SPEAKER_16]: Didn't you have a birthday recently, Dave, or am I confusing you with someone else?
[SPEAKER_16]: Who are you talking to, Rob?
[SPEAKER_16]: Did Dave leave?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's why you have to look at the computer screen all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do-do-do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get out of your house, Rob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get off your tail and go... Okay, I'm going to put on some songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll be right back and we're going to talk about Dance Dance Revolution USA and Dance Dance Revolution Extreme.
[SPEAKER_16]: So we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go, let's go, let's go!
[SPEAKER_08]: Satellite control, zero, minus one hour and fifteen seconds.
[SPEAKER_11]: Warning.
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Radio's Pomani Music and More program might be dangerous for you to listen to in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have reported incidents where exposed listening to this program in the kitchen has caused people to bust out a Sharpie pen, draw arrows on the tile, and start stomping away.
[SPEAKER_11]: A friendly public service announcement from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's episode number... Whoa, and my cell phone's going off.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, this is Jamie right now.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's see if I can pick her up on speakerphone.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let me see if I can take her on speakerphone.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jamie, are you there?
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_16]: I have a minute or two to show.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're on live right now.
[SPEAKER_16]: Say hello.
Hi, everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: What's going on, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_16]: You want to talk to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_06]: I can barely hear.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm in a restaurant.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're hungry.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: You want to say anything to our listeners?
What?
[SPEAKER_16]: Do you want to say anything to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to make sure everything was going okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Everything's going great.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're cutting out on me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_16]: You want to say anything?
[SPEAKER_16]: We've been talking about Feet of Fury.
[SPEAKER_16]: Have you played that yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I still can't hear you.
[SPEAKER_16]: We've been talking about Feet of Fury.
[SPEAKER_16]: Have you played that yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's breaking up, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right, I'll talk to you later, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now you know why we can't take phone calls on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we need to patch in an actual phone line.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, we need to patch in an actual phone line, and at some point we'll be able to take phone calls.
[SPEAKER_16]: But that was my cell phone on the speakerphone, and she couldn't hear me because I guess we get really shitty reception in this room here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Irene, you were telling a funny little story during the break.
[SPEAKER_16]: You don't want to talk about it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, we'll talk about it later.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's orange on business.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, it's orange on business.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, and you were listening, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think so.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, so unfortunately, it sounds like Jamie and them stopped to eat, so I don't think there's any way in hell she's going to make it back in time, so... Maybe they're at Dairy Queen right across the street.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, wouldn't that be funny?
[SPEAKER_16]: Why don't you tell everyone where I live, Brad?
[SPEAKER_04]: There isn't a thousand or a million fucking Dairy Queens.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, in Sacramento, there's only like, you know... Fifty.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just kidding, I'm fucking with you, I'm fucking with you, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, so, Feet of Fury...
[SPEAKER_16]: Any last thoughts on that?
[SPEAKER_16]: I know you guys were saying some more during the break.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just a quick reminder, if you are going to burn it, make sure you have the newest copy of Nero or whatever, the burning software, because I burned one.
[SPEAKER_03]: with an older copy of Nero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those bastards, they made me lose a CD.
[SPEAKER_16]: Me too, I lost two of them.
[SPEAKER_16]: But if you want to check it out, form your own opinion on the game, kind of got a mixed reaction here so far, check it out at http://www.cagames.com
[SPEAKER_16]: Cool, so moving right along, I should plug our chat room, we haven't plugged that at all tonight You're just going to join any other side IRC server like karma.othersideirc.net or irc.egheads.org And you're just going to join Channel Pound Orange Lounge And that's the same server, by the way, that hosts a lot of the other big Bomani sites So if you're in one of the Bomani chat rooms right now, chances are you're on the same server as Orange Lounge Just type to join the Channel Orange Lounge Brad, why are you taking your clothes off?
[SPEAKER_16]: We're not ready for that point of the show yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Woo-hoo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's talk about, uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's talk about sex, baby.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was your guys' week?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's been about two weeks since we've all been kind of sitting here together.
[SPEAKER_16]: How was your guys' week?
[SPEAKER_16]: Did you do anything exciting?
[SPEAKER_16]: Any Bomani news or non-Bomani news?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, I finished my site.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, you tell everybody about your site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: My DDR site.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks to Twin for registering a domain name that kind of got me started on actually finishing my site.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's leechfromloki.tk.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right, leechfromloki.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's got a pretty cool interface.
[SPEAKER_03]: All that's up there right now is just two of my originals.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got one for Fire in the Dark and one for the Quay 2 theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of like some hard rock kind of stuff, I guess.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like the layout of the site, by the way.
[SPEAKER_16]: You've got that Never Look Back thing going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the Never Look Back...
[SPEAKER_03]: G2 Arts thing is kind of my background there, and it's a pretty strange interface.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I have tons of web space.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got like 50 megs for stuff right now, and they didn't really say in the disclaimer that I couldn't have more than one site.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I guess really I have unlimited web space and unlimited bandwidth, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then maybe later on forums will be coming up because I also have the capability to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, yeah, it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can meet...
[SPEAKER_16]: We need orange lounge forms, so you might have to work that in for us.
[SPEAKER_16]: I could do that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, alright, good deal, good deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can I give an update on my site?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's 2020.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_16]: God, you suck.
[SPEAKER_16]: Just kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to attack her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Attack me first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad, you suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now you can attack her.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, by the way, for those that have been bitching about how bad the Orange Lounge site has been looking, because it's really old, SoCalKicks, by the way, one of our early listeners, being one of those people that always bitched about how bad it looked, I said, fine, SoCalKicks, you do a new site.
[SPEAKER_16]: So he said, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: So he's supposed to be working on that for us, so we'll have a new site soon.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all I can tell you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's talk about Max USA.
[SPEAKER_16]: DDR Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, Max USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you mean the one that's off by a measure?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Last time, we were here in the room talking.
[SPEAKER_16]: They had released the demo on the official PlayStation magazine, and two of the songs were off by a complete measure.
[SPEAKER_16]: However, from what I understand, they released a new demo to GameStops across America.
[SPEAKER_16]: I believe Jamie said she has one, because her fianc is a manager of a GameStop.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_16]: What's kind of assumed to be pretty damn close to the actual list going on?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know if you want to elaborate on that, Loki, because you look at more of that stuff than I do.
[SPEAKER_03]: What they did is they kind of got another list.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's pretty similar to the last one.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of things people were saying before is, there's not going to be ghosts, there's not going to be Kakumei.
[SPEAKER_03]: You guys are wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: So on this list there isn't ghosts or Kakumei because it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: More of an update, which is kind of strange because you'd think, well, gee, you know, this list got leaked out before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's not put it in when we fix the demo this time.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, well, you know what I bet, though, because that demo only came out about, what, a week after the list was leaked, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: But they probably have to do those demos to get them burned in mass and everything.
[SPEAKER_16]: That demo was probably done about six weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_16]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, one of the things that was kind of strange about it, though, is it had some newer songs on there, but those songs are the same ones from Dancing Stage Party Mix, which is kind of strange.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, we might see them in DDR Max USA, but I kind of doubt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not really sure, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I doubt it, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: The way they were in the list, they were completely out of alphabetical order from the rest.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the list wasn't alphabetical in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: The guy put them in alphabetical order.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I didn't realize that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that has nothing to do with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, man, when I saw when a man loves a woman on there, I was like, that cannot be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, but what about Be In My Paradise?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: Be In My Paradise isn't in there, either.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't think.
[SPEAKER_16]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyways, um... You remember that old game, Impossible Mission, on Commodore 64?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's what you sound like right now, when you fall off the edge.
[SPEAKER_16]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_16]: Stay a while.
[SPEAKER_16]: Stay forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get him, my robots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, so... Hi, world.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, anyways, um... Some of the things that were on there, though, like, that they mentioned, that were also in Density's Party Mix, was, uh... The Bad Touch...
[SPEAKER_11]: You and me, baby, ain't nothing but mammals
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I do understand that Dancing Stage Party Mix is for the PS1, so I don't know how that could be carried over to the PS2 list.
[SPEAKER_03]: That wouldn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could understand if Konomics had that stuff in there or something like that, and that didn't end up being in there because they were making Dancing Stage Party Mix at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: They could have been working on the engine at the same time.
[SPEAKER_16]: My theory as to why they're not in there is in that box art that was released about four weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because if... Now, one of those songs also on that list is Kylie Minogue, Can't Get You Out of My Head.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now, if that were actually in the game, I would think that would be the first name that would be on that cover.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because she's a multi-platinum-selling worldwide artist.
[SPEAKER_16]: Certainly more well-known than Darude, I would think.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think her name would have been on there at the top billing, so I don't think that song's in there.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I think it kind of voids out all the Euromix ones.
[SPEAKER_16]: But that's just my theory.
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't you think the representatives of Kylie Minogue would want you to put that kind of a thing on the cover?
[SPEAKER_16]: Saying, oh, featuring Kylie Minogue, blah blah blah Featuring Kylie Minogue's breasts
[SPEAKER_16]: I was walking down the street and...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I have a confession to make, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't... Don't worry, sweetie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not what you think.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, um... I haven't played DDR in over a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play a GaspWave file.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have one?
[SPEAKER_04]: No?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Rob, get your head out of your ass.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry, I'm being given some information.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have to see if I can give it out or not.
[SPEAKER_16]: What were you saying?
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't say it because I don't know if I can give it out or not.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I can.
[SPEAKER_16]: Basically, being told, okay, so maybe I'm wrong then with this news.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're saying the box art is outdated.
[SPEAKER_16]: The yellow burst on the cover isn't really there.
[SPEAKER_16]: It was just there for the online version.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's not on the real box art.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, okay, so maybe they changed it.
[SPEAKER_16]: But I still don't think they're there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still don't think they're there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even more important than all that, I haven't played DDR in a week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, well I haven't played DDR since yesterday at home All I gotta say is, I don't care, I have it reserved, it's coming out next Tuesday I don't give a shit I think at this point, none of us really give a shit what's on it, just release the damn thing already So we can play it I'd rather be surprised, you know I already pre-ordered it too So, well, you know what is the real dilemma here?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: That comes out the same day Grand Theft Auto Vice City comes out I'm like, shit, I can't play both I'm just gonna take the whole week off
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you make a version where it's all DDR music in the radio of Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know they've got the radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch, watch.
[SPEAKER_16]: I bet you anything the exact same day those two games come out is the day we finally get 2DX in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_16]: I bet you anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all going to happen the same day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know me and probably a bunch of other people will be ripping all those songs and step files to put in.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR Max!
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to blow your load!
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry, that's an inside room joke.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, anyways, you'll probably see the sim files out the same week, guaranteed.
[SPEAKER_16]: For what, the new stuff?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh yeah, you guys are crazy, you have those sim files around.
[SPEAKER_16]: I remember that they were already trying to find the arrow chart, we'll talk about Extreme a little later in the show, but they were already trying to find the arrow charts for Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm watching that one Japanese site that's got the Max 2 stuff, because they're the first ones to have the Max 2 arrow charts, and I'm waiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just waiting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just waiting.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, I actually want to play for you an MP3 of one of the new...
[SPEAKER_16]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_16]: You guys are so wrong.
[SPEAKER_16]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What were you doing last night, Rob, when I tried to call?
[SPEAKER_16]: I just want you to wait for the all caps line yelling at you guys right here in about two seconds.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway... Oh, not all caps.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's such rude.
[SPEAKER_16]: Or maybe you'll do that AZN type of typing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, if you like this MP3, you can go over to that site and get the rest of them.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's not the actual edit that's going to be in DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: It is edited down to a minute and a half.
[SPEAKER_16]: about, and from what I told, it's not the actual one, but it's kind of close, whatever that means.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, take it or leave it, here it is.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is... Sometimes I wish we were a TV show, and the rest of you don't.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to play from DDR Max USA, this is Venus with Just Leave Me Alone.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, you heard it here first, or you heard it here second if you were already at SoCalKicks' site.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was Venus with, you just leave me alone, and that's going to be... And Brad, you should take that advice, just leave me alone, you fucking bastard.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just leave me alone, guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: I hate you so much.
[SPEAKER_16]: Why did I invite you over here tonight?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh yeah, I needed more people here because Jamie wasn't going to be here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jamie's nice to me, you're mean.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, hi, this is one of my other roommates, Neil, what's up?
[SPEAKER_16]: Want to say hello to the Bomani world?
[SPEAKER_16]: If you could say one thing to all the Bomani nerds out there, what are you going to tell them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Get a life.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you, I knew that was coming.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now get out of the room, we're doing a show.
[SPEAKER_16]: What did you guys think of that song?
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that the first time you guys have heard that, most of you?
[SPEAKER_16]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_16]: What was that thing you were doing?
[SPEAKER_16]: You came out and you said, What the hell were you saying while that song was playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sorry, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big Jim Slade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, no, but it's better than the Fetus Fury songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like Dark Black Forest better.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think that song kicks so much ass that Dark Black Forest is going to be in DDR, but that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_16]: It ain't so bad.
[SPEAKER_16]: So if you like that,
[SPEAKER_16]: Go over to SoCalKicks.com and there's more, and maybe we'll be adding some of those to the Orange Launch playlist.
[SPEAKER_16]: However, I'm kind of holding out to get the actual rips from the actual game, which I'm sure will be out no less than 30 minutes after the game's hit shelves, if not sooner.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_16]: Can we do a list list tonight?
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you want to do a list list for?
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's do a list list for something not even related to DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: You guys think about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_16]: If we got time, we'll do one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't done anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: We haven't done the FUs of the week yet.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're still going.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_16]: What time is it?
[SPEAKER_16]: It's 8.02.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're halfway there.
[SPEAKER_16]: You guys want to do FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't have anything else to add on Max USA.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't really have any.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's really no other news on Max USA for me to report other than it's almost here.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll do Extreme after the next break, because there's a lot to say on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I have to say is, Naoki is such a chick.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: If anyone's recording the show, I want that sound clip.
[SPEAKER_03]: He can't look any more like a woman than he does now.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, is the sex change coming next?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that one picture that we have of him in the New Naoki Journal, where he's at the test location, they show a backshot of him.
[SPEAKER_03]: His hair is, like, really long, and he's wearing this, like, dress suit thing that looks like a woman's... I don't even know what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, he looks like a chick.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, next they're going to have him in the school girl outfit, so don't worry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we'll know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Depeche Mode
[SPEAKER_16]: Speaking of sound clips, this is going to be very random, but... I said I'd play that, so never mind.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just embarrassing somebody right now, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you guys during the break.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, it's not JB.
[SPEAKER_16]: If they fess up in the chatroom, then I'll say on air, but if they don't...
[SPEAKER_16]: If they don't, then I'll tell you guys during the break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, we've got some blackmail stuff for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Life is a... Shut up!
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, we won't go there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anything else to say on Max USA?
[SPEAKER_16]: No?
[SPEAKER_03]: I have some rips about it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, it's coming out earlier than expected.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't think we mentioned that.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's going to be out at the end of October.
[SPEAKER_16]: Halloween week.
[SPEAKER_03]: S is coming out, not this coming up Tuesday, but the Tuesday after, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anywhere that week, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been hearing weird things.
[SPEAKER_16]: And I'm sure we'll be doing something very special on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sandstorm, yay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, I cannot wait to play Sandstorm.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sandstorm is the best ever.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know what it's like?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like going to a giant rave.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's have some E and make out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we can be friends.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, that joke is weeks old.
[SPEAKER_16]: We can't do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did hear what the last song to unlock is, supposedly.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Drop the Bomb one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Drop the Bomb, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the new one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yay for dropping bombs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drop the bomb.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish they really would drop the goddamn bomb.
[SPEAKER_04]: That thing is so annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, one of Scottie D's finest songs, Stick Around.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know, you can see Scottie D for like half a second in the Stick Around video, right before the gerbils that make out with each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is the worst video slash song ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you're stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking of... Okay, well, anyways, this is way off topic.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's that song that's in Guitar Freak's 8th mix, or whatever, that's, um, it's Paul Terry and some other band.
[SPEAKER_03]: Man, she totally butchers that song, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to talk about Politary not being able to sing?
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that one song featuring Angel?
[SPEAKER_07]: She cannot sing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it Ultra High Heels or something like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Ultra High Heels.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, but that chick cannot sing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Politary has a voice, but that chick doesn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Megu cannot sing.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know why you listen to me?
[SPEAKER_16]: The only shitty thing about Stick Around is the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_16]: The lyrics are so awful.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're awful.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're goddamn awful.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make it bigger.
[SPEAKER_07]: Video is terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: The singing is terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: The lyrics are terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: The song is terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gee, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I have to defend it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The music itself is alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: The singing is alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Miracleman.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's cute though.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all happy and...
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid!
[SPEAKER_16]: And the video, it looks like, at the very beginning of the video, it looks like we're going to go on a safari.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, why don't I just put on the Discovery Channel?
[SPEAKER_07]: At least I'll hear better music.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, speaking of Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania, I'm glad you brought this up.
[SPEAKER_16]: I wanted to mention this real fast.
[SPEAKER_16]: For the first time, it sounds like they're going to be doing what they're calling Power Up, which is basically 8th Mix, 7th Mix Plus.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're doing a new version of Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania called the Power Up.
[SPEAKER_16]: And from what we're being told, there's going to be some new songs in it
[SPEAKER_16]: Begin by Ryu Kisoka, which is one of the B4U chicks, if I'm not mistaken.
[SPEAKER_16]: Ryu, oh sorry, I missed the I, my bad.
[SPEAKER_16]: Power Up.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_16]: And they're returning.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're putting in some more of the old songs that are coming back, like Fire in the Dark, and On Our Way.
[SPEAKER_16]: How about Haru Spring?
[SPEAKER_16]: Isn't Haru Spring in?
[SPEAKER_16]: Those bastards.
[SPEAKER_16]: I only played it once, and Jamie made me play Another World, and then I played some other... Oh, I played the one where you do the steel drums.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Kachaka.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kachaka.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: My third favorite song.
[SPEAKER_16]: I got a shitty grade, but I did good.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, what's the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Extra Stage is called, it's in Japanese, but it's really, really fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is it the Orange Lounge song?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got the characters, but the two girls, you know, but I don't think it's Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the coolest song ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: So cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Extra Stage on Drum Mania Guitars.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sure some people in our chat room will fill us in on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really hyper and peppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We honky, we don't know how to read Japanese.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, let's take a break.
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you guys want to play?
[SPEAKER_16]: I have no ideas.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any requests in here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Play ABBA.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, no ABBA.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_16]: No?
[SPEAKER_16]: We will do ABBA.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was only kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, we're going to do... You got me started.
[SPEAKER_16]: We did Hyper Boundary Gate before the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: You were in the other room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or we could do Michael Bolton.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Michael Bolton?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to do... When a man becomes a woman.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll do some ABBA.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're going to do erotic covering ABBA, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's what we're going to play.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, in the meantime, we're going to start this set off with... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I like this one.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is one of my favorite songs from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll start off with this.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're listening to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll be right back, and then we're going to talk about DDR Extreme and the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Also, if you want to send me your FUs of the week over private message, you can do that now in the chat room, and we'll get to that coming back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's my only fight Now I didn't dream Now everything is new
Don't go wasting your emotion Lay all your love on me Don't go sharing your devotion Lay all your love
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_16]: I had to play that again, because everybody in here, Dave was laughing so hard the first time, the others couldn't hear it, so, I know we've got more people joining us since we started the show, but it's very rare we get a new promo around here, so, had to play that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: I got a clarification during the break, by the way, you are listening to Orange Launch Radio, we were talking about Guitar Freaks 8th and Drum Mania 7th before the break, and thank you to Arcadian42 who's filling us in, saying that the extra stage is called Mikene Ko Rock.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, not Mechanical, it's Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mikaniko.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mikaniko.
[SPEAKER_16]: Rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like Mechanical, but... Remember there's that cat, Parfait, the cat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, the cute little cat.
[SPEAKER_16]: Aw, if Justin's listening, I'm sure he likes that.
[SPEAKER_16]: We gotta have them back on the show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_16]: Justin and Mike, they were here a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, a few months ago with this man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they need to return my freaking Beatmania 5-key controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: About time I got that thing back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they're both listening, so if you want to put out a special shout-out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Need controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Want the controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't play Beatmania without a controller.
[SPEAKER_16]: And Arcadian thinks that the long version extra stage is something like Sumi, Nagra, Kanojo, but not sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: The bonus stage extra stage is crap.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's okay, but it's not worth playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that song, Power.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: Power.
[SPEAKER_16]: You just like Power, don't you?
[SPEAKER_03]: Power, and I also like Candy Star.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't really like that one.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was expecting to play the actual Candy.
[SPEAKER_16]: It could be worse, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: It could have had Crash.
[SPEAKER_16]: Crash is the Ingress version of one of those songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, Breakdown, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why the hell can't I... God, I can't think of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but see, it's bad because they have Under Control.
[SPEAKER_05]: The worst song ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: The middle isn't that bad, but the beginning is Crash and Burn, Crash and Burn the whole time.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's annoying.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sounds like GWAR or something.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, DDR Mike says you'll get it back when they go to Shafton.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, go do Shaft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: Everybody should go to Shaft.
[SPEAKER_16]: Come get some Shaft on November 9th over at Scandia.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I'm working on those flyers, so we'll have those.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, let's do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jamie's not here, but if she were here...
[SPEAKER_16]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_16]: Brad, you have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hangovers.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, why is that?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, they're not fun.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's why you're supposed to drink bread and eat water when you're getting drunk.
[SPEAKER_16]: Drink bread and eat water.
[SPEAKER_16]: Is that what I just said?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm dyslexic, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dyslexic?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, that's not that big of a deal.
[SPEAKER_16]: How about you, Rob?
[SPEAKER_16]: Do you have an FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_16]: Do I have an FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not sure yet.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go to the others.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, how about Dave?
[SPEAKER_16]: Dave, do you have an FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to all my teachers at school for giving me way too much homework.
[SPEAKER_05]: I missed, like, one day of school, I think, like, two weeks ago, and somehow it was the one day where all the teachers assigned about ten assignments for the next two weeks of school, and so I missed that day, and now I've got a million assignments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck you, teachers!
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you're listening!
[SPEAKER_00]: Go away!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_00]: You get detention for a whole year!
[SPEAKER_04]: Some advice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't miss school.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay in school, kids!
[SPEAKER_04]: Be cool, stay in school!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so what if you're sick?
[SPEAKER_08]: Step into a Slim Jim!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, anyways, uh, my FQ of the week has... Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I was going to stay in school, then I threw up over someone else's backpack.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eww!
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, okay, go to the office.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grody!
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't give me a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not much is funnier than vomit, seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, my F.U.
[SPEAKER_03]: of the week, once again, goes to Golfland Sunsplash.
[SPEAKER_16]: Again!
[SPEAKER_16]: Big fat surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, let's start with the fact that initial D's broken already.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?!
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them is broken.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, that's unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_16]: Unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because of that one being broken, I had to wait for over half an hour to play one game of it today.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like the new DDR or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unacceptable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, that and also because the fact that they're advertising that MechWarrior 4 is in the Sumo, but for some reason it's not there anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't play MechWarrior 4.
[SPEAKER_16]: So those bastards that put in money... Wait a minute, I played MechWarrior 4 on that thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now.
[SPEAKER_16]: So somebody downgraded it?
[SPEAKER_16]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_16]: Major props to those guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: Major props.
[SPEAKER_16]: That takes talent to be that stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fucking Speed Demon game!
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate that game!
[SPEAKER_05]: I own that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still own that game for almost free.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not for free because I have to pay for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But... You could always steal little kids' tokens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or... Rent it for a small fee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do that when I can just play like a dollar and win a thousand tickets?
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you going to do with the tickets?
[SPEAKER_04]: You win like a thousand tickets and then what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You get to take something that's worth a dollar?
[SPEAKER_05]: You get stuck!
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought...
[SPEAKER_05]: I spent probably about $5 or $4 playing that game, which is a lot of money, and I got a Glitter CD rack, which holds... Ooh, Glitter!
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Mariah Carey Glitter?
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks kind of like the inside of one of those lava lamp type things with all the tons of balls in them like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it lights up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: It holds many CDs, and I... I have balls, I just don't like balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Irene, do you have any FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, let's change topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you like balls?
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um, I'm kind of sort of pissed off at my car because it kind of broke down, but I'm even more pissed off at book and automotive stores for not carrying the repair manual for my car, so fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_16]: You have another FU, Brad?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you already did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, drink that bread, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for ya.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have an FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about time.
[SPEAKER_16]: My FU of the week is to Brad for being such an asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you're special and you get Baclois.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, I am special.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, my mommy told me so.
[SPEAKER_16]: My FU of the week would go to the entire week itself.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not going to talk about it on the show, but for those that know me, it was a really shitty week.
[SPEAKER_16]: So let's just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_16]: So that's my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's to the whole week.
[SPEAKER_16]: The whole damn thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Fuck it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's get to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_16]: I hate myself and I want to die.
[SPEAKER_16]: I slashed my wrist the other day.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't do that, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, you would probably be here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's talk about the chatroom FUs, those that have been sent to me, shall we?
How are you?
[SPEAKER_16]: You want to read one?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, read SoCalKicks' then.
[SPEAKER_16]: Read that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: SoCalKick says, FooSky, actually he means F-U, F-U Sky for saving that sound clip.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know that Me So Hungry one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you everyone who can't understand what I said, it's Hungy, not Hunky, and fuck you PSATs because I got worried for nothing, they were the easiest shit ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I read that it said hongi, I just thought it sounded funnier as hongi.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, SoCalCake.
[SPEAKER_16]: Twin sent me some FUs earlier.
[SPEAKER_16]: People stomping on the PPP machine, which makes no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, I saw some girl playing it completely with her feet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess she didn't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: that they're, you know... It's a hand game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's infrared sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Russian Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: You use your feet to hit all the heroes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there's like a gun there for you to shoot yourself, you know, Russian Roulette.
[SPEAKER_16]: Did you ever think, by the way, if they did release an American version of PPP, the catch-up song would be on it?
[SPEAKER_16]: I bet you anything.
[SPEAKER_16]: An F you to the chat room for somehow going into invite only on Friday night.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, that was my fault.
[SPEAKER_16]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm only human, you ass!
[SPEAKER_16]: F you to JB's dad for wanting to go online so he had to leave.
[SPEAKER_16]: But he's back now, so never mind.
[SPEAKER_16]: Black Lab sent me one before he had to go.
[SPEAKER_16]: He was here earlier, but he had to go.
[SPEAKER_16]: He says, fuck his parents' shitty computer for being slow and the only computer in the house.
[SPEAKER_16]: Fuck his little brother for being such a little dickhead this weekend that he's had to watch him.
[SPEAKER_16]: And fuck Star Fox Adventures on GameCube for being too goddamn easy since I beat it in 13 hours flat.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, I only played it for five minutes, and I knew it sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't even have to play it, and I can tell it sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, 23rd Magus says, fuck you to the cold virus for keeping me home all weekend.
[SPEAKER_16]: I would have been at RVGL Saturday for Arcade Mania for once.
[SPEAKER_16]: Fuck the cold.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: You didn't miss anything.
[SPEAKER_16]: All the machines are broken.
[SPEAKER_16]: JB says, uh, his FU is to RVGL.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, little kids like to grab asses at RVGL.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's learned.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, isn't that something?
[SPEAKER_05]: And, uh, he told me this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was literal as in, I think, like, really literal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like,
[SPEAKER_05]: Very little kid, like a girl or something, I don't know, like four or eight or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least it was a chick grabbing his ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, if there was a five-year-old kid grabbing his ass, that would be kind of creepy.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's Anna Nicole Smith Jr.
[SPEAKER_16]: Either way, it's illegal, so come on.
[SPEAKER_16]: JB would also like to state that Jenny Rom will be his future wife.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sorry, I was Japanese for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wife!
[SPEAKER_16]: Watch the movie Simone.
[SPEAKER_16]: DDR Mike says that... Oh, this isn't an FU.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's telling me when he's going to come visit.
[SPEAKER_16]: Never mind, that's not an FU.
[SPEAKER_16]: DCB says FU to himself for coming in late.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's one tardy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Detention for a whole week.
[SPEAKER_16]: For DCB.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know, some guy in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_16]: These people, they're all my best friends.
[SPEAKER_16]: I keep tabs on them all the time.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I don't know, they just come in on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_16]: I read their FUs and they're happy.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's how this show works.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jazz says, FU to negative, immature people who seemingly can only solve problems with violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: But violence is the only way.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki...
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do they use violence?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't they use cellos?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's violence, dear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like guns.
[SPEAKER_16]: Jazz is cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Slinky says, F you to Roseville Golf Land because it's a shithole and everything is broken.
[SPEAKER_16]: The game room and Scandi are 600 times better.
[SPEAKER_16]: Once again, getting into local DDR politics on this...
[SPEAKER_16]: International Program, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Everybody should know what a shithole Roseville Golf Land is.
[SPEAKER_16]: Exactly, maybe one of the assholes from Golf Land will be listening.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know what I heard?
[SPEAKER_16]: You remember that one time that I went over there and took pictures of all the broken shit?
[SPEAKER_16]: Some of the employees got online and saw that, and they were pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pissed about what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That I'm telling the truth?
[SPEAKER_16]: God!
[SPEAKER_16]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, I'm going to do it again!
[SPEAKER_16]: Just for that!
[SPEAKER_16]: And then I'm going to take pictures of you when you're picking your nose and taking breaks when you shouldn't be and telling off little kids and pissing in the cokes and whatever you do over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you!
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate you!
[SPEAKER_16]: Die!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but see, like, they just really actually did the first pecking that they've done in a couple of months and they fixed Guitar Freaks and Keep Working.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you went there now, a lot of stuff wouldn't be broken.
[SPEAKER_03]: They turned up...
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, if you went there now, I'm sorry, you'd probably see everything broken again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I went there earlier today.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Guitar Freaks was turned up really loud, nice and loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drum Mania is turned down almost to silent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me add that I played Guitar Freaks for the first time in a long time a couple days ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: and my ears were ringing afterwards.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was so loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they don't realize that these games are based on music and you need to kind of make it sound good or else it's not worth playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to play Godard Freaks in silence.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm told that Roseville isn't the only golf land that's having problems apparently.
[SPEAKER_16]: SHGL got their 2DX screen fixed.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't even...
[SPEAKER_16]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_16]: I burped on the radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't even know that SHGL got 2DX back, but apparently they did.
[SPEAKER_16]: They got their screen fixed, and now it's broken again.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, hey, it runs in the family, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: We should just go to all the golf lands and quote, end quote, overplay the games and make all of them...
[SPEAKER_07]: you know, wanting the arcade doctor and then they'll see how bad it's going to affect yeah I need to pay a visit to the arcade doctor is that all the girlfriends do that or is that just Roseville who cares I think they know what I am implying but they'll see how much it suffers you know, like you know
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they'll see how much people don't like it, and then they won't get any business, and they'll die.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the thing is, you can't go play the games if they're all broken already.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not going to make any money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the ones that are still working, we should just overplay them.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, don't quote.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyway, I want to finish up.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's some FUs.
[SPEAKER_16]: DDR Mike did send an FU after.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, yes, Irene, you have an FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not quote, unquote.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's quote, end quote.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would you unquote something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody please tell me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: End quote.
[SPEAKER_07]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_16]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_16]: DDR Mike says, F you to Mountain Mike's left side pad down arrow because it's stuck for three minutes straight on Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, wait, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, good for freeze arrows.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have another F you.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys...
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody hates me.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have any vanilla Cokes, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go buy one yourself.
[SPEAKER_16]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sick of buying you people crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just ghetto poor this week.
[SPEAKER_16]: I haven't been to the store.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to the store after the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Not that I'll do you any good until next week, but hey, just thought you'd enjoy doing that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't worry, I'll bring Krispy Kreme one day.
[SPEAKER_16]: Some advice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get a job.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then Slinky's follow-up is that Japanese people own us all, and that's not local.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just remember I said his local mom.
[SPEAKER_03]: And their simple kick-ass, I might add.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's enough, Harspring.
[SPEAKER_16]: Or as SoCalKick says, shine loose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move along here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, thank you, teacher.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you for telling us how to run the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_16]: We need to hurry up.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're not going to get to do listless if we don't talk about DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screw that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wait until next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, let's talk about DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_16]: Why don't you do a sim file update for us, Loki, and then lead on into DDR Extreme if you want.
[SPEAKER_16]: Go for it, dude.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're the one who wants to change topics.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's all you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's start off with Step Mania.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Beta 6, Release Candidate 3, better known as...
[SPEAKER_03]: Step Mania Version 3 Final.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to be going, hopefully it should be the final one.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of fixes done there.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's available now from Sourceforge.com or whatever their site is.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a link on DDR Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played it a little bit today.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a lot faster, so just go try that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, DDR East Coast Invasion is back up.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had some server problems earlier this week and everyone thought they were gone for good, but they're back, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Go check them out.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any new contests by them coming up?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they're doing right now one of the things, it's kind of like to get the most popular character in all the DDR games.
[SPEAKER_03]: They finished with the female characters and I believe, ah shit, I can't remember her name.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alice?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alice, I don't know, I just...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just thinking, oh, Emmy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, Emmy.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, not Emmy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alice, there's Alice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Alice, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, she won, so they're starting with... Big surprise, see.
[SPEAKER_16]: I could have told you that contest in two seconds, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, sim file-wise, supposedly there's a couple people working on making a Sakura DWI.
[SPEAKER_03]: Other than that, not really much going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: My site coming up, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be adding tons more content on there, so be looking for some more of that stuff later this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to fix a few files before I can put them on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, a couple things to state.
[SPEAKER_05]: First, on StepMania, the coolest thing is that you can speed up the speed of the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the coolest.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not like how fast the arrows go, but the actual song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I think it's up to 1.5 times the actual speed now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: But anyways, um... Oh my gods, I can beat Max Unlimited S4R with two times speed!
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my gods, Dizzy!
[SPEAKER_16]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so, other than that, I mean, other than stuff we mentioned, you know, Feet of Fury, Beta's out, you know, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: No updates for DWI, but I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've abandoned all hope for them, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I missed this, but were there any new released characters online for the... No, they're doing... Okay, there's number six.
[SPEAKER_03]: He has two more people that I don't really care about because I don't play DDR PC anymore because it sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, there will be another character released next Friday, so they're doing them every two weeks now.
[SPEAKER_16]: I noticed it's on my payday Friday, so there are at least two characters to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are all these freaky, weird characters, and no one plays that game, so it really doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aside from that, like I said, my site.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking, you know, maybe once I get things going a little bit, since DDR East Coast Evasion does their own tourney mixes, I might actually run one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually have prizes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know me, in my edit contest, I had tons of prizes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, oh yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: And you'll be doing all those door prizes at Shaft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I'll clean out my prize closet there.
[SPEAKER_16]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, you're cleaning out your closet?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha ha, anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, and now DDR Max Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Max Extreme!
[SPEAKER_03]: They've been doing the testing started this Friday back there in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: And people have been playing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually a bunch of new songs have come out.
[SPEAKER_03]: A couple to mention.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be a new Revenge song.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all 16th and 32nd notes.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it's 60 beats per minute.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's 65 beats per minute, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it called DDR Extreme?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not Max Extreme?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's called Bag.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What a name for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, um... Big Asian groove.
[SPEAKER_03]: New Paranoia coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Paranoia Survivor.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's, um... It goes from 135 BPM to, like, 267... 270.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that should be pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_16]: Isn't there something that you have to do on that song?
[SPEAKER_16]: Like, you double A it and you can get an extra stage or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no...
Legend of Max
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, supposedly if you double A Legend of Max, you get Sakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'd like to point out, I was correct, and I called it a long time ago that Sakura is going to be the bonus song.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're the shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, so I know that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we haven't really heard, I guess, if there's another extra stage, a different one, if there's Paranoia Survivor, if someone double A's that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Every time I hear that, I think of that Destiny's Child song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a survivor, I'm gonna make it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, it's like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You double, uh, parent a survivor, you get to vote somebody out of the arcade.
[SPEAKER_16]: Or as 23rd Magus says, out-stomp, out-wink, out-dance.
[SPEAKER_16]: What's out-wink?
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: What do you wink when you play DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: Out-twink.
[SPEAKER_04]: Out-twink?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, twink, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've heard the word twink before, but it has absolutely nothing to do with DDR.
[SPEAKER_16]: I guarantee you that.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm not going to elaborate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, let's see if we can pull up the song list here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, yeah, yeah, I can pull you up the song list.
[SPEAKER_16]: For those that don't know, one of the big people that gives us information on the Japanese location test is the guy known as Aaron in Japan.
[SPEAKER_16]: His website's over at aaroninjapan.com.
[SPEAKER_16]: WildSide IrresistibleMint
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever that means.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speed Over Beethoven, which is, you know, on Speed 9, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then there's also We Are The Champions, a cover of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are the champions, my friends.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then We Will Rock You is also there.
[SPEAKER_16]: So it's a Queenie mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_16]: Big Gay DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see, we've got... Twink Revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of the older songs coming back.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got Damn Darium, Rhythm and Police, Synchronized Love, I Believe in Miracles, If You Were Here.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know there's a larger song list out there that has a lot more of the older rituals.
[SPEAKER_16]: From what I understand, every Max 2 track is back.
[SPEAKER_03]: And from what somebody else was saying... Every Max 2 track and every Max 1 track is going to be back.
[SPEAKER_16]: Except for Telephone Operator, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Telephone Operator and Follow Me are still gone, from what I heard, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: But Ghost is back, and all the good ones are back, except Telephone Operator.
[SPEAKER_16]: I love Telephone Operator.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bye Bye Baby Balloons back, much to our enjoyment.
[SPEAKER_16]: But from what I hear is that initially you don't see them on the list, that you have to sort your list a different way to see them.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: That doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, I think that it's a huge list.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, you didn't see them right away.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, they're going to have an unlock system similar to Max 2, except it's going to be fewer points in between, a ton more unlocks instead.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to have also, like before we've mentioned, the non-stop mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to actually have a Player's Best non-stop that you can play on there, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be the top four songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Arcadian can get out the pen and pencil again and start writing down Player's Best every week.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: I remember when Forthmix was out and he was writing them down every week.
[SPEAKER_16]: And it was like, Casey Kasem's Top 40 in the Player's Best.
[SPEAKER_16]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry I had to be here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Inside joke, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, of course, you know, not to be any surprise at all, drop the bomb, the SystemFX mix.
[SPEAKER_16]: Of course, they couldn't stay U.S.
[SPEAKER_16]: exclusive for very long.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there are still some... Oh, I'm sure you'll see the Dynamite Rave one on there, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure that's going to be in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So cold, so cold.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, So In Love, Kind Lady.
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't know those were going to be on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind Lady.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: V, of course, they said V was an 8-footer.
[SPEAKER_16]: Love, Love, Sugar, DJ Taka featuring Noria
[SPEAKER_03]: Lamor et Libierte, Kiss Kiss Kiss, Feeling of Love, Moba Moga, Frozen Ray, Miracle Moon, L.A.D.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lifestyle, Destiny Lovers,
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it's the LED version.
[SPEAKER_16]: And this is too cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: From Mambo a Go-Go, Gamalande Couple is on there.
[SPEAKER_16]: That rules.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to have to play that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And not on this list right here, because this is an old list.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jet World is on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jet World's on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: The steps could be cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let me scroll on down and see if I see some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_16]: A, Colors, at least 100 seconds
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_03]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: 230 songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Supposed to be in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: My final.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the test is only, what, 50% done?
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't know when it was going to be released.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard rumors of end of the year, early spring.
[SPEAKER_16]: We've heard late December and early January.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right in time for New Year's Eve.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, shit, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: That machine right there will definitely own.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's no doubt about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: 230 songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: The question is, how soon before it breaks in our local golf land?
[SPEAKER_03]: Golf land, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be Scandia, man.
[SPEAKER_16]: And there's also another report, Aaron in Japan mentions that Shine was AAA'd on Heavy within two hours by one of those insane Japanese dancers, Yosaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course we don't want to obviously reveal to any Konami people that someone got pictures from the test location, but someone did get pictures from the test location.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone that's a website we might be looking at right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And supposedly they should be leaked out a couple weeks from now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a lot to look for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really know if it's going to reveal anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_16]: Probably it's just going to be more kind of screenshots.
[SPEAKER_16]: I like those.
[SPEAKER_16]: When Max 2 was first out, they got a lot of up-close screenshots.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm waiting for those kind of shots.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are people that have access to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have access to them because I'm not on that board, and I don't know Aaron, so obviously I can't get access to them.
[SPEAKER_03]: He hasn't passed.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're protected, so there's no way for us to get him, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see what else is here, if there's any other exciting news to share.
[SPEAKER_03]: No new upgrade for the cabinet as posted a long time ago on Team Boilo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the same software.
[SPEAKER_03]: It should be an easy upgrade.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're saying that Speed Over Beethoven is the best new song.
[SPEAKER_16]: A lot of people are saying that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to see if I can get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I can get that from one of the... I've heard it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's... I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not good at classic music.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on Speed 9, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on Speed 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on that one song.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like... I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the one...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll see if I can get that for you guys and play it next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know somebody who has Speed 9.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll get a copy of that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, we'll play that for you guys next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't have it right now.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: If somebody in the chat room has it, feel free to send it to me.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll play it before the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty much all that's up with DDR Extreme, other than the very girly shot picture of Naoki.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have pictures from test location.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, Naoki's diary.
[SPEAKER_16]: We haven't talked about Naoki's diary.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a filler.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was nothing new.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was him bitching about more songs we don't really care about, and it was also talking about... Wow, wow, my life is so traumatic.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were interviewing some people that were working on it and asking him stupid questions like, what's your favorite character in...
[SPEAKER_16]: Like our listless.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hey, stupid things can only be done on this show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Listen up.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think we're going to take another quick break and then we're going to wrap up this show.
[SPEAKER_16]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, you said wrapping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was terrible, right?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_16]: What shall we play in this break?
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's start off with... You want to hear Miracle Moon?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, let's hear Miracle Moon.
[SPEAKER_16]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: We'll be right back to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, as promised, we were able to get a copy of that Speed Over Beethoven song.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you very much to DDR Mike for sending that to me.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're going to play it for you right now.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is going to be a DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_16]: It'll be an edited down version.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is the full version, though, so you guys can get a sample of it.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is Rose with Speed Over Beethoven.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speed Over Beethoven
[SPEAKER_06]: I need you one again, I can't leave with music on to save your life It's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over It's over, it's over, it's over
[SPEAKER_06]: Lalalala, lalalalala Into the night, you make me cry I need your love, to save my life I need you wanna get on and play with Listen to the song and our melody It sets you free You need your love, to save your life I need you wanna get on and play with You gotta save your life Into the night, you make me cry I need your love, to save my life
Music on a figure
[SPEAKER_10]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter D, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_16]: We apologize for the awkward end there to that Speed Over Beethoven song, but that was right out of a non-stop, the Speed 9 album.
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't have time to edit that together, because that just got sent to me.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, we hope you enjoyed that, though.
[SPEAKER_16]: That was a pretty cool song.
[SPEAKER_16]: What did you guys think of that?
[SPEAKER_16]: It was...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I kind of like that a little more than Beethoven's Virus even, a little bit, just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could have fooled me that it was a Jimmy Ronson.
[SPEAKER_16]: So what was that call that was more important than the show, Brad?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just thought I'd put you on the spot.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're winding down the end of the show here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_16]: I see you want to have a conversation this year while I try to do the show in this year.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_16]: I can do that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, anything else you guys wanted to get out of your systems before the show was done?
[SPEAKER_16]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, there's no other things you guys want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about... Sex.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Irene said it, but it kind of didn't get picked up on the mic.
[SPEAKER_16]: What would you like to talk about sex, Irene?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_16]: You can't relate sex to the money in any way?
[SPEAKER_16]: Outside of erotic songs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm sure you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, like, they should, you know, how you were saying about the announcer, you know, relating it to, like, a guy jizzing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you fail a song, you should say, oh, well, premature ejaculation happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that would be funny if the announcers had that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is it.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the money shot.
69 Combo!
Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be like that Saturday Night Live sketch where they had herbal essences for men.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they were like, they were doing the organs like, You know, because you know how, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, I don't know how.
[SPEAKER_16]: Boy, this show went right down the toilet real fast, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, yeah, right, when we said, uh, this is Orange Lounge Radio, uh... Let's see, to the latest, greatest, uh... Yeah, anyways... He said... Rob, Rob said... Rob said that's what it should say when you get a 69 combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It puts the lotion on its skin or it gets the hose again.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wait, you watched Silence of the Lambs today?
[SPEAKER_16]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: They were scary and good.
[SPEAKER_16]: Did you never see them before?
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw them when I was like 10, but I don't remember what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went and saw that Rules of Attraction.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, how was that?
[SPEAKER_16]: I hear there's some pretty scandalous stuff in that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pretty, it's a stylish film, I would say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, a lot of stuff that's, like, backwards and weird shit going on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it starts in, you know, it's one of those movies that starts in the middle of the movie and then goes back and then comes to the middle again and then goes forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I saw, uh, The Transporter on, I think, Saturday.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I won't spoil it, but it's like the guy there is like the master pimp of everything.
[SPEAKER_16]: I heard that that movie was a piece of shit, but that was just what I heard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who did you hear it from?
[SPEAKER_07]: I heard the radio show was a piece of... No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw Spirited Away.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just going to say, you guys went and saw Spirited Away, and that's of interest to a lot of DDR people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on!
[SPEAKER_04]: You said... Hold on what?
[SPEAKER_16]: You like Showgirls, Rob, so... But I like Showgirls for its comic value.
[SPEAKER_16]: There is much comic value to be having Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was really funny on TV where they tried to censor all the boobies.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, the VH... Yes, you have to see Showgirls on VH1.
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't see Showgirls for the first time on VH1, but watch it for the second time on VH1 where they have to... Follow your Showgirls DVD?
[SPEAKER_04]: You sure can, honey.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ruin the effect of the insult.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you can, darling.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, yes, tell us about Spirited Away.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now, was the dub as crappy as the sub?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I mean, was it crappier than the sub?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_16]: Spirited Away was a great movie.
[SPEAKER_16]: I just want to know if they fucked up the dub.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, the dub... Okay, I personally, I used to... When Princess Mononoke came out here, you know, in America, and I went and saw it in the theaters...
[SPEAKER_04]: I was saying, and a lot of people were saying, that it was the greatest dub so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was nothing as good.
[SPEAKER_04]: This, in my opinion, is better.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no annoying Claire Danes.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, seriously, the dub is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody does a great job.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no overacting in it at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they didn't change anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: That didn't need to be changed.
[SPEAKER_04]: The names are pretty much all the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were a couple jokes thrown in that weren't in the original, but they were funny, and they made, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't ruin anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody should really go see that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw the sub-version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the best films I've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Disney did not make it, for all you people who don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of people listening will know, but I have this feeling a lot of the parents in the theater were like, Disney, it's a Disney movie, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Studio Ghibli and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm talking to myself now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Miyazaki who made the movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what he was trying to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also saw part of Initial D, the anime series, after playing the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, that anime rocks.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hello, and welcome to Last Week.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to mention something.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's video game related.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just heard that they're making a sequel to Final Fantasy X, which is pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, now, from what I hear... From what I hear...
[SPEAKER_16]: In the US, those two sequels that they're making to Final Fantasy X, there's a Yuna story and there's a Riku.
[SPEAKER_16]: There's a Yuna story and a Riku story.
[SPEAKER_16]: And in Japan, those are going to be released as separate games, FF10, 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_16]: And please keep in mind, my word is not gospel.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm just spreading dirty rumors I've heard.
[SPEAKER_16]: So if I'm wrong, then whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen screenshots.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, no, no.
[SPEAKER_16]: I know they exist, but this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: This is the thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: You know how Final Fantasy XI, it's online in Japan, and it's kind of been a bit of a wreck because they've had a lot of problems with the servers.
[SPEAKER_16]: They won't release the hard drives here in America, so there's really no way they're going to be able to release Final Fantasy XI in America.
[SPEAKER_16]: And playing online games in America is kind of... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know any online game I've ever seen that people take it seriously, except EverQuest, which is where people take it way too seriously.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I think Final Fantasy Online in America would kind of be stupid anyway.
[SPEAKER_16]: Ultima Online.
[SPEAKER_16]: But what's going to happen, since they can't do it on the PlayStation 2 because they have no hard drive, they're going to release it on the computer as Final Fantasy Online.
[SPEAKER_16]: Final Fantasy XI here in America is going to be those side stories.
[SPEAKER_16]: They're going to release them as one game here in America.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's just what I've heard.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what's really strange about it is Yuna looks like freaking Lara Croft.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's got two pistols and I don't know, it's just weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's carrying forbidden machina?
[SPEAKER_03]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's violating the teachings.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think she said screw the teachings in Final Fantasy X in the first place.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that and supposedly machina has taken over... Spoiler free show, please.
[SPEAKER_16]: Spoiler free show.
[SPEAKER_16]: I haven't really played through X. Come on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this machina taking over Spira is after X anyway, so it has nothing to do with X.
[SPEAKER_16]: Spoiler free show plays that includes you people in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_16]: God damn, so not everybody's finished the game yet.
[SPEAKER_16]: Some of us are just now getting our US PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of us wasted all their money buying a Japanese PS2 and can't afford to get an American one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and those people play 2DX, so they suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't know me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sit down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk to the hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sitting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, other than that, there's also, supposedly they're selling now a, um, international PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plays both US and Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't believe that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, it's on YesAsia.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, no, that, you know what, it's tricky, I saw that, it's just the way they worded it.
[SPEAKER_16]: We go back and read it very carefully, it's not, it's not an all-region DVD, they just try to make it sound like that, so.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_16]: If I'm wrong, then, fuck em'.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right, we're running a little over.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want to finish up the last show.
[SPEAKER_16]: Final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any final thoughts from you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Check out my site if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's www.leachfromloki.tk All right, any final thoughts from Dave?
[SPEAKER_05]: Go watch Initial D. It is cool.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any final thoughts from Brad?
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I'm sorry, you weren't done?
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is that I am done now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pass it on.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any final thoughts from you, Mr. Brad?
[SPEAKER_04]: It puts the lotion on its skin and puts it in the basket.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_16]: Any final thoughts from you, Irene?
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_16]: Bye, that's it?
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: Every track that I've got, which is everything, except for, I don't think I have all the eighths, but I've got just about everything.
[SPEAKER_16]: So we're going to play 2DX music all night long until I feel like shutting it off, which will be a couple hours.
[SPEAKER_16]: So enjoy that, you guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all I've got to say for now.
[SPEAKER_16]: So good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks for listening to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_16]: On behalf of Jamie, who couldn't make it, and I, thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_16]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.