[SPEAKER_17]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: Our live talk program begins now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain sexual and adult content and many instances of the F-word, which is not safe for children.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn you, stop calling here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it 4215, pussy whee?
[SPEAKER_07]: You bitch!
[SPEAKER_07]: Now let me check this, it goes 2-1-2, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_07]: You have no morals, darling.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd also like to add that I have my father's gun in a scorching case of herpes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Kiss my great news.
[SPEAKER_20]: Mecca lecca hi, mecca hi-dee-ho.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, I hate throwing up in public.
[SPEAKER_12]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_12]: Fucker, yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm the size of my face.
[SPEAKER_05]: From the state of California, in the great nation of the USA, on the planet Earth, it is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're tuned in to Bomani's newest and greatest radio station of all things Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me better as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: With me, as always, is a lovely co-host who has 12 lovely vanilla cans, might I add.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's DarkSakura, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a bill of coke.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crack.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is episode number one for June 23rd, 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got a whole lot of people in studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello, studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other first things you want to say, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_11]: Uh, hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: That works for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty then, we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be talking about the first show and lots of other firsts and whatever the hell else we feel like.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can view our webcam on our website at http://orangelounge.skie.cx Join us in our chat room at Channel Pound Orange Lounge on irc.eggheads.org or karma.othersideirc.net We'll be giving that out for the rest of the show, won't we, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yes, quite often.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty then.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the very first break song, I'm going to play something for the Fantasia album.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Vanessa May with Destiny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's Vanessa May at Freaky Rocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't it, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Vanessa May Owens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is my destiny.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
I met you when you were sleeping
[SPEAKER_09]: Baby, no, no, nobody's love, no, nobody's love, no, nobody's love, yeah, baby Bye-bye, baby balloon Bye-bye, baby balloon
[SPEAKER_17]: Bitch, get a new song!
[SPEAKER_17]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: It was Brad's idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: He just claimed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was all Brad's idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's your fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to blame somebody for this talk show train wreck, just blame Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I think the idea came to us, what, probably back in January or February?
[SPEAKER_04]: When was the first time you guessed it on the other show, Under Sedation Live, that we participate in?
[SPEAKER_06]: That was in January or so, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it was this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was probably back in January.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was after I got my new computer, so that had to have been in January.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, when Jamie was on the first Under Sedation Live that she was on, which is another show that I co-host, you can visit that website at http://undersedationlive.org or it's actually one of our friends on the playlist, or on the Live 365 site.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you go to Live 365 and take a look at our fellow broadcasters, we have the Under Sedation Live listed there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the show that I co-host on Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'd also like to say, if Travis happens to be out there listening tonight,
[SPEAKER_04]: I really appreciate all the help, and this drink's for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That relates to last night's show, don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, probably back when Jamie hosted this show in January, we thought, you know, we ought to do a Bomani Talk thing for Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just not, you know, because Under Station Live kind of...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Two game rooms going.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got one in the back.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you look at the webcam on our website, http://orangelounge.sky.cx, you can see on the webcam there's some people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're playing Max in there right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the other room.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then in here we've got Keys Pounding, which you can probably hear because we've got Brad in here playing some 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yell something to the people out at home, Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to talk into the mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, okay.
Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of firsts, since it is the first show, we are kind of expecting that there's going to be a lot of issues tonight, so please bear with us throughout all the technical difficulties and everything else going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the communal microphone over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have the communal microphone that everybody's going to have to talk into, which Irene has pretty much parked herself near, so I think we'll know who we'll be hearing from most of the night over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: First experiences with Bimani, because it's kind of something you see once, you play it once, and then you're pretty much stuck with it for the rest of your life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially if you're listening to this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've actually gone out of your way to tune into a Bimani-focused radio program, you're obviously a very ill person who's come down with a Bimani flu.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or you've succumbed to my threats.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, they're not dorks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Jamie, what was your very first Bomani experience?
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the first time you... I know you, out of probably most people here, I'm not sure because we haven't really compared everybody's notes yet, but out of most people here, you were probably the very first person to play DDR and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: To go way back in time, let's go to 1999.
[SPEAKER_06]: Around February or March, I first heard of Beatmania and thought, oh, that looks kind of dorky.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I actually had Beatmania 98 on my computer, so that was my ever first Beatmania experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, how many of us started with BM98?
[SPEAKER_06]: Raise your hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be me and Brad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I went to Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had heard of Dance Dance Revolution and said, that game looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to go play Best to Move.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was in a Best to Move 2 tournament at AX1999.
[SPEAKER_06]: Spent like an hour owning everybody before I got a faulty controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so I went over and was looking at these people because I heard Shake Your Booty playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was DDR Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that was my first DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't actually really play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I hit like 2000.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I saw the first one on PlayStation and got hooked then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I borrowed my friend's game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Couldn't pass Butterfly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was asleep one night, woke up the next morning, and just, like, passed Butterfly at random.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I didn't see my first DVR machine until AX2000.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was the third mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was $2 a game, and, well, I dished out $2 a game, slept in the room, and there went my addiction.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I started off with the Dreamcast, and nobody can say anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sega owns.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't bite me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, Sink is making games for the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their third-party stuff is looking pretty good, so I've got to give them some credit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give them lots of credit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, DDR Club on the Dreamcast is much better than the PlayStation version because they had to split the PlayStation version into two CDs, and that kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: But on Dreamcast, it's all in one nice, shiny little package.
[SPEAKER_04]: My first DDR experience was, and funny enough, you know, the show that this is kind of spun off of is a Rocky Horror themed show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually first discovered DDR at a Rocky Horror convention.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this was, hell, I don't even know, I think it was 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting so old.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think in October of 2000, we were at a convention in Las Vegas at the Hard Rock Hotel, and they were showing the movie Friday and Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we decided, you know what, once a week's enough, so we're not going to go Friday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just going to go out to the arcade, and we're just going to play games, because that's what we want to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there was one of those big dancing machines with the flashing seizure lights, and we all wanted to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was your first night too, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you wish to add about... About DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we play our first game together?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I think it was just me by myself first, because you guys were pussy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you're like, we're white, we can't play this, let the Asian do it first, and then we'll look cool, you know, after.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we were at Circus Circus, and what was it, a 1.5?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was the old USA Machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I distinctly remember the song Butterfly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember it was the spinning discs that you can choose from instead of the song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that much.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we fucking sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember passing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We passed the first song.
[SPEAKER_04]: And didn't I pass Boom Boom Dollar the first time?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you passed the second song and I was like sleeping by then because I failed like the first three steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to take this moment to give Irene an inside joke and then the maid.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the best joke ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shush, Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, this show's going to suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So after that, we came back home to Sacramento, land of nothingness, and we thought that was pretty much it, that was the only time we were going to play DDR, and then we found that Roseville Golf Land...
[SPEAKER_04]: ended up getting its own DDR machine sometime in, I think, what, December of 2000?
[SPEAKER_04]: They picked up the Super Elite USA mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember it being toward the end of the summer, because I had been playing at Country Club Lanes, the evil place, and then I heard, hey, there's a USA machine over at Roosevelt Golf Land, went over there, and that's when I met lots of people.
[SPEAKER_06]: I met Danielle first and through her I met Brad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I met a bunch of people at Milpitas Golf Land on that first road trip to find Parapara.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the sacramenstrals.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, the sacramenstrals.
[SPEAKER_06]: We, you know, suck so bad we bleed, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we don't die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: We suck so bad we bleed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyone else in the room care to share their first Bimani story?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we're really desperate for material right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because everyone's convinced we're never going to fill a two-hour show of Bimani Talks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have to prove them wrong, even if we have to bullshit for just two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's got the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody runs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_04]: Matt, would like to share a story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: My first experience with Bimani, I'd have to say it started back, I believe it was the year 2000, with...
[SPEAKER_02]: Phantomacon, I saw someone playing 5 key Beatmania 2nd Mix and actually it was really cool, what song that hooked me was the theme for Metal Gear Solid and from there I went and bought everything for Beatmania played it a couple times and put it away and then next year comes around, 2001 and I saw them playing DDR 4th Mix which was really awesome
[SPEAKER_02]: That game I really got into.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I actually got a chance to play it first time in Lake Tahoe and I found out I had no rhythm whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, I sort of looked like
[SPEAKER_02]: Steve Martin and The Jerk
[SPEAKER_02]: So then, you know, flash forward back to about a year ago, I come to find out after I moved from El Dorado Hills to Orangeville that Roseville's got, you know, 4th and a USA machine, and I had, during the time, picked up also my own home version of 4th and 3rd with two pads, and I'd been practicing on Pink Dinosaur and La Senorita.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so then I started playing at Roseville constantly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to do nine hours a weekend and actually I think I still do about nine hours a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me to cut you off for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad, Brad, Brad, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song is banned in this house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do not play 250 BPM in this house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody in this house has nightmares about that freaking crack baby in the video.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, nine hours a week for a whole year so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anybody else want to share their first story?
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad, I'd love to hear your story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put the controller down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's somebody.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the doorbell rings.
[SPEAKER_06]: More victims!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is your life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or this is our show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, before we go on to whoever our guest is, I actually would like to make a mention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is just a general shout out.
[SPEAKER_06]: This goes to DDR Freak Radio, all the other Bimani radio stations out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys own and keep doing it because we need to keep Bimani on the air and keep everything alive too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree, we need to keep doing shit like Bomani X Radio, all those other radio stations out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who else is broadcasting?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know there's a user on DDR Freak who has their own station.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's probably about 10 different stations.
[SPEAKER_04]: You put Bomani into live365.com, you're going to get about 10 different stations that come up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's commotion going on at the door there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Paul's here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, Paul?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to give a shout out to all those other Bomani stations out there, because especially, if you might have heard this past week, I believe it was Thursday, the new royalty rates for internet radio came down.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to have to pay 7 cents for every song heard by 1,000 listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now granted, this station will never, ever, ever have 1,000 listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if it does, we have ways to control that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't it retroactive too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: This whole Bomani thing, I'm sure since we're pretty much whoring out Bomani, they really don't give a crap what we're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they probably wouldn't come after us.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, for everybody else out there, for all the other shows out there, this is a really stupid thing that they're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just trying to charge us for every little thing we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're not going to take it!
[SPEAKER_06]: There's two roots to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of them is greed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Number two is called having something crawl up your ass and die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: That happened to me Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't even care about people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's anal greed.
[SPEAKER_06]: That doesn't sound right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like anal spider?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like anal spider.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anal spider is cool because they do beat mania stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my anal spider noise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's do that again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's not quite what I remember from the song.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was it Macho Gang?
[SPEAKER_04]: You kind of have to get on that base of the...
[SPEAKER_04]: A penny just stuck to me, isn't that crazy?
[SPEAKER_04]: As Rob goes off on another tangent.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's the dying giraffe sound from the South Park movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Paul's here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Paul, say hi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give Paul the microphone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let the adults have the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't make out with the microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other words, don't perform sexual acts on the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Believe me, if we've gone how many months now of playing Bomani and never shutting up about it, like the afternoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to say I don't have a life outside of Bomani because I try to.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's not everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we certainly can fill up two hours of a show.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we spent 15 minutes on each game alone, that would be two hours or more.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's two hours a week that we can fill.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're talking about firsts.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we want to know everybody's first experience with Bimani and why they're so addicted.
[SPEAKER_04]: So tell us how you lost your Bimani virginity.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's the heroin needles that shoot out when you do a good job, or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Paul, that was a question to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, tell us about your first experience.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I started out with DDR and it just...
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my goodness!
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't believe it!
[SPEAKER_22]: Everything's ruined!
[SPEAKER_22]: Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_22]: Here's a little number I tossed off recently at the kettlebell.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not singing with it this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doesn't it all be nice to have a penis?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't it frightfully good to have a dog?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's well to have a stiffy, it's divine to own a dick From the tiniest little tadger to the world's biggest prick So three chows for your Willy or John Thomas Hooray for your one-eyed trouser snake
[SPEAKER_12]: Your piece of pork, your wife's best friend, your party, or your cock.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can wrap it up in ribbons, you can slip it in your sock.
[SPEAKER_12]: But don't take it out in public, or they will stick you in the dock.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you won't become a bad little big woman.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't say I don't have enough sound effects to fill up a show or you're going to get subjected to crap like that for two hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Travis' collection of... No, I got these on my very own thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob's a big boy now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie was up until 4 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: downloading this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, Brad, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do we know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tell us what we know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what should be in Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our good friend Wesley Willis.
[SPEAKER_03]: You remember Wesley Willis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I do remember Wesley Willis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have any Wesley Willis?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have Wesley Willis.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to play Wesley Willis right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe at the end of the show I'll play Wesley Willis.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be the end credits, though, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's time for a break.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll stop talking now.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back for the break, we'll talk about... Why don't we talk about... Everybody in the community is talking about this this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Solo 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it safe for the children?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't anybody thinking of the children when we come back?
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: A dream, that is real
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is it always the same old thing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wanna be a man, yeah, you're playing games.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you gotta kid act like your father, the baby ain't yours, then hey, why?
[SPEAKER_07]: We often wonder how some of those Bomani songs are chosen.
[SPEAKER_16]: We think we figured it out.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, the lovely karaoke stylings of me there in that little diddy one-hit wonder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I have your autograph?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Rob!
[SPEAKER_13]: It's Rob!
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show me your moves!
[SPEAKER_04]: I just showed him, now he's not going to talk for the next half hour.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we're really R-rated, you know, we've had nudity on here now.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was our little hippie... I don't know if anyone picked that up.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was our little hippie hoppy set there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our fresh set.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our booty fresh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our booty fresh set.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brought to you by... Cracker, starting it off from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then two songs from DDR, solo 2000s, a six panel version of DDR, Dream a Dream by Captain Jack, the booty mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who that is?
[SPEAKER_04]: My Baby Mama by Anna Kett, finishing that off DDR Solo 2000, most people really don't give a shit about Solo 2000 anymore Solo sucks anyway Exactly, ever since that infamous tournament, that's kind of become the catchphrase How did that happen anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: You probably know more about the story behind Solo sucks anyway than I do Because I'm sure a lot of people would like to know why, whenever they talk about Solo Somebody always jumps into the thread and goes, Solo sucks anyway I think it resulted from a failed routine
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know the entire story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so that's what this game is about.
[SPEAKER_04]: But DDR Solo, in the news around the community this week, this has everybody talking about something.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the point where I let my head into my hand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's talk about the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to read this article here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from the San Diego Union Tribune, and it's by Brian E. Clark from the San Diego Union Tribune here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: It talks about the Poway Bowling Alley Arcade replaces a game after used protests the images in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jennifer Stoethan couldn't believe her eyes.
[SPEAKER_04]: There on the Dance Dance Revolution machine, a video game immensely popular with preteens and teens were images of drugs, alcohol, and a scantily clad nurse riding up and down on a syringe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was appalled to see that stuff flashing on the screen, said the 17-year-old Stofan.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she first saw the pictures way back in March on the Dance Dance Revolution machine at the Poway Fun Ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: She says, I'm a teenager, but I've seen five-year-olds playing this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as I'm concerned, those images are totally unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do they need to have pictures with rows of pills, cocktails, ecstasy, and a syringe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'd like to know how that girl knew that the pills were ecstasy.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was appalled, yet excited.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's probably seen five-year-olds naked, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's talk about what she did.
[SPEAKER_04]: She basically documented pictures, contacted the company that placed the game in the bowling alley, and convinced the arcade owner to replace the machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know with what.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be really, really funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be really funny if it was Humpahorse.
[SPEAKER_06]: That Namco horsey game.
2002.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Furlong.
[SPEAKER_04]: So she basically got her way.
[SPEAKER_04]: She whined, bitched, and moaned.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we shouldn't just say her because obviously she got other people in on this too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Her little coalition.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which happens to share a name with a very big lesbian, gay, bisexual coalition group.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Youth Advocacy Coalition or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kind of a funny side note anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who probably lesbians and gays wouldn't really care about.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR, Solo 2000, they'd probably find it funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should also be noted that Solo 2000, just like that movie The Last Starfighter, recruits people for the Army of Satan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's widely known knowledge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I signed up just last week!
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think a lesbian would have a problem with looking at a nurse riding on a syringe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so they go on to gloat.
[SPEAKER_04]: We feel really good about what we were able to accomplish.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she graduated from high school.
[SPEAKER_04]: She is a high school graduate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for her.
[SPEAKER_04]: And she's going to study film at San Jose State University.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I imagine her next target will probably be in San Jose somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Little kids or even teens don't need to see that stuff, and we were happy the business people we dealt with agreed with us too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the moral of the story, if you bitch and moan and you threaten to sue, you'll get your way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch out, Sunnyvale.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's coming for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's protesting these images, yet she's going to be a film student.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that how, like, you know, independent filmmakers, like, win?
[SPEAKER_06]: By being provocative.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do we know she's not going...
[SPEAKER_04]: She's gonna get Sundance shut down for showing titties.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if the nudity is artistic, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Kate Winslet in Titanic, that was artistic nudity.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was ugly nudity also, but it was, you know, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was... That's the whole thing, is that, you know, this particular organization... See, I don't get, it's not just this organization, it's any organization who decides that there's something out there that they don't like.
[SPEAKER_06]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, you know, there's just so much positive about it and they have to focus on all the negativity so a lot of people have to lose out because something crawled up their ass and died.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait till Solo 2004 comes out with aborted fetuses and crack whores in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I be the devil's advocate?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come here, Irene, you want to be the devil's advocate?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come here and tie him to the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to hear this from the other perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have loved to have gotten an interview with this person but I was too lazy so we'll maybe get one next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, what was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, you said that just because a band of people got together and protested against something means that, you know, they get their way.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think it's kind of like if there was a group of murderers out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course that's going to be sickening to some people and they're going to band together and kind of complain about these murderers.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I can't say that I fully agree with
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about people that band together and complain about things?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, sometimes it's for good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, this particular instance, I don't feel so strongly about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she's wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: But let's not say everyone that does that is terrible.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hi there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, guess what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_06]: Eat my ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so, any comments?
[SPEAKER_19]: Am I talking?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm talking like Waylon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any comments?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very good point you're making.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're wrong!
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that part of it just has to do with the fact that people are generally closed-minded.
[SPEAKER_06]: People aren't willing to accept an idea that might be different than their own.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so they're going to stick to that one idea and think that everybody has to adhere to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where, you know, apparently we disagree.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's obvious because we like DVR.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I mean, not just with that situation, but with a ton of situations in the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's intolerance and just generally being closed-minded.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I'm going to be the devil's advocate for the devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I need to make another point.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to fill this damn show somehow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just make this the Irene show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, how about the people that were, you know, the kind of people that I can see being against is like the Nazis.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, at one time people thought the Nazis were cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if anybody here necessarily thought the Nazis were cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Jewish people ever thought the Nazis were very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's because people were shocked.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's another example of the sheep mentality I'm often fond of bringing up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and you know, I think Adolf Hitler just had some insecurities, because he only had one testicle.
[SPEAKER_06]: and he's just like, fuck you all, I'm just going to kill everyone because I have one testicle.
[SPEAKER_03]: How did you know he had one testicle?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wouldn't you like to know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's been reported from unknown sources because I just read a bunch of books and shut up.
[SPEAKER_20]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can read.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I'm not a geep like Paul.
[SPEAKER_06]: A geep?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, he has a geep on his shirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, so, I mean, I guess it just depends on the situation, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's circumstantial.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you have beliefs... Oh, that's my cue.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta go now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: You were saying, if you have beliefs, continue.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The giraffe noise threw me off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, if you have beliefs... Good point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, thanks, thanks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the general moral of that is even though there are people who do occasionally win to take away things, not necessarily take away things that we enjoy, but just to inflict their closed-minded opinion on the masses, there should always be the people who are willing to stand against that, who are willing to say something, you know, we don't think this is right.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have no right to censor our lives.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and I also, one last thing, like
[SPEAKER_05]: If they don't like it so much, why don't they just not go there?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my whole opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, why ruin the party for everybody else just because you have a problem with it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody is forcing you to play this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, everyone's so hip on, like, let's, you know, everyone puts disclaimers on things and stuff, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: And why is it that this particular incident, they have to take away our fun?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here's probably what the situation is for this one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, you said it's at a bowling alley.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm guessing it's probably someone that's part of a league or a bowling league or something like that that sees a stupid game playing in the background when they're waiting between frames to bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bowling for God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Christian bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Highway to pins to heaven.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so probably it's just someone with nothing better to do than complain about something if it wasn't, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Arguing against people killing whales or small animals or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Children.
[SPEAKER_02]: Abortion or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure they would have picked on something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like a starter to other things to debate about.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I just think it's probably no big deal, but like I've read on the responses for these, that not really anyone's worried about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't really think it's going to go too far, and I probably agree with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see why the bowling alley owner decided to get rid of the game in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: It must not have been making him any money or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: There must be other factors involved.
[SPEAKER_03]: The thing I see, let me be the extremist here for a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even on that one instance, that machine getting taken out is doing more damage to a larger amount of people than...
[SPEAKER_03]: The images on the machine are doing to the little kids, I believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: And let's be an extremist here and say that what if all the machines eventually do get taken out because this does go way too far, which I doubt it will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then that's definitely doing even more damage to a larger amount of people than the little images of syringes and naked women.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuckin' A!
[SPEAKER_03]: You see more of that kind of stuff on TV anyway than you do on the frickin' machines and arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: Inside at the bowling alleys, all the parents are drunk anyway, so who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, they don't want to watch their own kids, so they put something that has syringes and stuff to baby for their kids.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only other thing I can think of why the manager would agree with something is if it's supposed to be a family environment and enough families banded together and said this is not the type of environment we want our children around.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Mormon Bowl.
[SPEAKER_06]: Their protests might have actually had some credence with the manager.
[SPEAKER_06]: But even so, I mean, first of all, they stand to lose money because I know for a fact DVR machines make a ton of money.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, from having worked at three different arcades...
[SPEAKER_06]: I do know that they make those rating stickers.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how you have your ratings on your video games to have at home?
[SPEAKER_06]: They have those rating stickers for arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: Corporately owned arcades are actually required to have them.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I know Namco did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not too sure about Gotham, but I know that most of them do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I personally went through and put a lot of those stickers on machines.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that any parent who had their child with them could look at the machine, look at the rating, and see if that's really something they wanted their kid to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, parents don't want to watch their children themselves and do their job, so they let the arcades babysit their children for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the thing I notice at Golf Land all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Parents bring their kids there.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then just turn them loose.
[SPEAKER_04]: They run around everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're stomping on all sorts of machines and shooting things.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's worst of all is that when we're playing on DDR, they start coming and playing with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like eight people playing on the machine at once because all these little kids want to jump on the arrows because, oh, shiny thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're getting into my territory here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, why don't these parents watch the kids when they drop them off here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Then you would be able to take an active role in what they're playing, because if you just let your kids turn loose, there is way worse arcade games out there besides DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if this bowling alley, I would like to know if this bowling alley has like a police 911 machine, where you're shooting people and there's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Lost Drogas and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to say something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't we just band together and say, we're offended by these god people.
[SPEAKER_06]: We just need a derby owners club.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's not politically correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: And race horses all day and teach good horse raising values.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's unconstitutional.
[SPEAKER_04]: I say we just screw DDR and we all get a Neopet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want a Neopet.
[SPEAKER_03]: My Neopet wasn't fed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to throw it at you now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we're weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: Malnourished Neopet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, yes?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's about, we should, you know, definitely have my rant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we'll get to your rant after the next break.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I was going to make a point and I just forgot it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess I won't make a point.
[SPEAKER_04]: The points at Cal Expo.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think is going to happen after this?
[SPEAKER_04]: After what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that more machines are going to get taken out from other places?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this person said they're going to go on to DDR Freak, which is probably the most well-known DDR site that's out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go look at their machine locations page and start hitting every Solo 2000 machine out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you see how many were on there?
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, honestly, the owners of these places...
[SPEAKER_06]: They've had them long enough to know, you know, what's going on in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've had them long enough to know the kind of content is inside.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and there's, you know, I don't, I think they would have taken them out by now.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they really felt passionately about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here comes Brad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's Matt, he hasn't been here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I think what's going to happen is if people are going to call up these establishments with the Solo 2000 machines,
[SPEAKER_02]: and they're just going to get laughed at because these people are going to be like, yeah, I'm just going to take this machine that I paid a couple grand for and just get rid of it because you don't like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, go screw yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they're probably going to end up saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just ridiculous to even try to take these machines out because of a few images that flash in the background that you don't even notice anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I'm sure they'd be like, oh, it's subliminal then.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't notice it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It gets in their subconscious and they'll become murderers and rapists.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just one thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it may be a sad thing, I should say.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, unfortunately, greed ruins over morality in a lot of cases.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, are you going to throw away an income of well into the thousands because it offends somebody?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, true, there's some offensive material that I think should be removed on occasion.
[SPEAKER_06]: But on top of that, though, this is an instance where this small group is not really going to be able to make much of a difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, true, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: And in fact, also, let's just, you know, say for instance that they do get away with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Solo 2000 gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really, would you miss it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't miss it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was just, I don't miss the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even care if they get rid of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a better game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get a Max 2 machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, I mean... Well, okay, but, okay, say you go and upgrade the Solo 2000 to a fourth mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at the background of Kick the Can.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a bunch of flying heroin needles.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've still got the same thing going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still think Secret Rendezvous has the best video.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then they'll just want a Max 2 machine removed because there's lesbians all over the Secret Rendezvous video and it's a secret message that everybody should become a lesbian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lesbians.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Solo 2000 is a good machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: It attracts crowds.
[SPEAKER_06]: People actually go look for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have a new face to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glenn would like to contribute an opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: An appearance and an opinion.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's the thing about the whole... Because basically what it is, it's censorship.
[SPEAKER_19]: And censorship never stops.
[SPEAKER_19]: It just keeps going further and further and further.
[SPEAKER_19]: And nobody's going to be happy until there's nothing left.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because somebody will be offended by something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Either it's degradation of women...
[SPEAKER_19]: by the songs or images or whether it's subliminal messages that they think they hear or drug use or anything.
[SPEAKER_19]: It will never end.
[SPEAKER_19]: So if they keep... If it's a trend and they keep caving into these people, then DDR will be gone.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then there'll be something next after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a message to all you arcade owners out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grow some balls!
[SPEAKER_06]: Only in America.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wash your pussy!
[SPEAKER_04]: and a message out there also as well to the coalition there that's taking out all the machines out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: First, we would love to hear your opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: So please contact this station and we'll give you a fair interview and some equal time and let you present your side of the story because we're curious what your motivations are and maybe you can talk us out of playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Second off to the coalition, there's a place called Laser Force in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go take their machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you need a place to properly deposit this machine, I live at... Alright, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk more about Laser Force and other evil Bomani things when we come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, we're going to play something from Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to play something from... Well, it's actually Guitar Freaks also.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to play our namesake here, the lovely Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their little medley from the new guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back in about five minutes.
DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
A-flat, I believe, a little sharp.
Get this thing off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Kale kale kuta kuta kuta ee oh ee oh
[SPEAKER_01]: Cargale, cuta, cuta, cuta, eh oh, eh oh
[SPEAKER_04]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I would like to present to you the comic stylings of Irene, future comedian extraordinaire.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep clapping.
[SPEAKER_06]: So these two muffins were baking in the oven, and the first one says to the other one,
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's getting pretty hot in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the second one's like, holy shit, a talking muffin!
[SPEAKER_18]: Warning, Orange Lounge Radio's Monty Music and More program might be dangerous for you to listen to in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_18]: We have reported incidents where exposed listening to this program in the kitchen has caused people to bust out a sharpie pen, draw arrows on the tiles, and start stomping away.
[SPEAKER_18]: A friendly public service announcement from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're live for our very first show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're halfway through it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: We made it this far, so let's see if we can get to the other end.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think now would be a good time in the show for Jamie to be given space to do her little rant.
[SPEAKER_04]: How does that sound, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds delightful, Ron.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's hear your little rant of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is Jamie's big fuck you of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That goes to...
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have to say parents at Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who agrees with me here?
[SPEAKER_06]: Especially one delightful lady who I saw putting her three-year-old child on the keyboard mania machine to change a diaper.
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew a lot of people called that a shitty game, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: She was checking his diaper, but she put the child on the keyboard, and I couldn't help myself but go up there and go, Excuse me, ma'am, and mentally I was going, and I used the term loosely, would you mind moving your child off of this machine?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I could go get management and make them, you know, have you pay for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Walk off while their three-year-old, not three-year-old, more like a five-year-old was holding one of those big guitar controllers, which I have issues holding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mommy, it hurts.
[SPEAKER_06]: It feels like burning.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, and I actually, I was playing drumming at the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I called the parent back and said, you need to get your, you know, you need to help your child because if they drop this on their foot, they will likely break their toes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Attention to parents at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_04]: This goes for not just Roseville Golf Club, but any golf club.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie circulates a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: She gets around, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: At many different arcades.
[SPEAKER_13]: She gets around.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am such an arcade whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't mother your child, Jamie will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I will spank your child.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, like that prime example of the people we got kicked out of Golfland the other night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, they were getting up, bumming around the machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had management kick them out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, well, we actually got a restraining order that night.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a Golfland restraining order the other night.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: This guy was hopping up on the Parapara machine while I was playing, and I nearly whacked him in the face one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then he was making this act out of himself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did he almost get hit with your ass, Deluxe?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that was when I stuck my fist out to do the side.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you know how you have to stick your hand out to do... Well, I don't know how many power lists we have listening, but you stick out your hand side to side to do Deluxe, and I nearly palmed the guy in the face.
[SPEAKER_06]: And honestly, he deserved it because he was a moron.
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, you know, I can't go around hitting every stupid people I see or else my hand would fall off.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, but anyway, that's the rant, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we have any parents who are listening to the show where I seriously doubt it,
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, if you have younger siblings, you know, make sure that someone's got an eye on them, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look out for the little ones because we sure as hell aren't.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not our job.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the parents' job.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll step on your children.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we're going to step on them and then they'll learn.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I would not consciously step on a little child if I couldn't help it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, that's my rant.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you'd like to comment on Jamie's Fuck You of the Week, or you'd like to comment on anything else we talked about the past hour of the show, I encourage you to join our chat room, which is located on server irc.eggheads.org or karma.othersideirc.net and it's just channel...
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge, all one word so we look forward to seeing you in there and we'll take your comments and maybe talk about some of them on the show in future weeks on the Orange Lounge we are looking into getting the phone system here so we can take phone calls on the air but we're kind of doing some test runs to see what kind of reception the show gets because that's going to be a large investment to get the phones here so it might be a little while before we get those but we'd like to start taking phone calls, that would be cool
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you can initiate a national boycott at Laser Force.
[SPEAKER_04]: International.
[SPEAKER_06]: The one issue with that is that I don't want them to go targeting every place that has a Solo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Walmart and Lodi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the Walmart and Lodi rules.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any place you can buy Pringles and then go straight to play DDR just rules.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I win so many toys out of the crane machines there, it's not even funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's hear why Laser Force sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell your Laser Force story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this has to do with the day that Iguana Girl and I and a certain unnamed, well, cockspanker, cockspanker for bucks, who is no longer worthy of a name.
[SPEAKER_06]: We all went to Laser Force to check out the new solo machine right around the corner from my house.
[SPEAKER_06]: and people, please don't come to my house anyway we go in and we're all playing nobody's getting up and doing anything
[SPEAKER_06]: and, you know, this woman's asking questions, you know, we're answering, she's got her kids there and then this group of little girls gets up by the machine and we've all been taking our turns and using a coin line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyone with common sense can see what a coin line is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eventually the mother got up and was complaining that, oh, you know, my kid wanted to get up here and, you know, we explained the coin line and we're like, okay, well, you know, we're going to go ahead and let your kid go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll go ahead and, you know, trade this turn, just give us some tokens because we'd already had tokens in the machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she's like, no, I gotta go, and they left.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then management came up and just, like, tried to ream us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were being, they were being very... Oh my goodness!
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything's ruined!
[SPEAKER_05]: As many times as I can fit it in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, we had issues with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Basically, we just said we weren't going to come back, and I made sure to let everybody I knew.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so far, I think we've had a fairly successful boycott, haven't we?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I understand that their business isn't doing very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, it's just, though, nobody really plays the solo there anyway, so they should just give me the machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then we wouldn't have to boycott them anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is crime logic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but then that woman's gonna have to come to your house and remove the machine because she finds it offensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it's my house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, but the more furniture.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's offended.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Jamie has a guard cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Shermie would kill her.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shermie would roll around on the floor and out-cute her.
[SPEAKER_06]: But no, if somebody came to my house saying, you can't play this in your own home, that'd be the point.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd break out the katana and decapitate somebody, okay?
Whoa!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's evil, Jamie, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's in my house.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's self-defense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Jamie's on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie's on.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, all those steroids.
[SPEAKER_06]: Making me feel badly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Laser Force sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only official laser tag game that I can, you know, put my name behind is QZAR.
[SPEAKER_02]: QZAR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Played it for four years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spent...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh good, 15 grand there.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should say that Loki was a Cusar nerd long before he was a DDR nerd.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to hear it for Team Sack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, Cusar, it was my first love.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once Cusar left last year around May, I was very sad, still sad to this day.
[SPEAKER_02]: And anyways, DDR became my new addiction, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: I just have to say, QZR rules, Laser Force sucks ass, and they were almost out of business just when QZR went and left, and then they came back just like a festering sore, so they can die.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really does smell like pee in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they smell like pee.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad I'm not the only person that noticed how bad it stinks in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep in mind, though, we've also got LaserX at Country Club Lanes, and we still have whatever thing is at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, you're talking about LaserX?
[SPEAKER_06]: But there are local alternatives to LaserForce if you have to shoot the infrared beam at somebody.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, unfortunately, I do not have dramatic music to play when people are crying over their losses, but I do have Cam Laughter.
[SPEAKER_06]: We can play Flowers for Albion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I could load that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: House is so crazy right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's people in here playing... I banned... Didn't I ban that song from being played in the house?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid Crack Baby Oh my god, it's the evil Crack Baby I know, let's I see sitting in the corner over there, my roommates over there in the corner crying Let's bring them over here, I want to ask Brian a few questions Come here, come here Let Brian have the microphone here You gotta hold the mic far away from you because it's very sensitive It's like a penis, it's very sensitive Okay Don't get too close to the head or you're gonna get shot Anyway
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't want to hear about you and Glenn at night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, hey, hey, if you ever played, if you ever played DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I have, Ron.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what do you think?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's a penis envy contest at best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie doesn't have a penis, last time I checked.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can make one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can make one.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of this whole thing, this show, this house that you co-reside in being transformed?
[SPEAKER_20]: My house has a complete disaster area right now being overran by a bunch of geeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, wait a minute, that's me.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I'm stuck in the middle of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're now an honorary geek.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're the meat in the geek sandwich.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, that was just a bad image.
[SPEAKER_20]: That was just not somewhere I wanted to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brian and Meat at the same time, quotes Irene.
[SPEAKER_06]: And followed by a... Very descriptive.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any comments you want to add out there to the Bomani people listening?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we have quite a few people listening right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there anything you want to say to the addicts out there at Bomani?
[SPEAKER_20]: and besides the fact that they turn my house completely upside down when you throw these types of things and that I'm going, I have no house and no life right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, there's a pool.
[SPEAKER_20]: You could go swim.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's quite all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's a ball, Brian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you go bounce it?
[SPEAKER_20]: Thanks, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually want to thank you very much for the use of the... Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least someone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay, Brian.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll make an edit in your honor.
[SPEAKER_20]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_06]: To Pink Dinosaur.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for being on the show, Brian.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo, Brian!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm the only one happy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and you don't have a microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_04]: What now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get away from Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're right, we can't fill two hours with Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or what do you want to talk about then?
[SPEAKER_06]: Bomani.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else is Bomani?
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Our personal cross-dresser is not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Ryan was supposed to be here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where'd he go?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, our cross-dressing fellow admin is not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where is he at?
[SPEAKER_04]: I knew he had to work today.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's out cross-dressing playing Para somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew he had to work today, so maybe he didn't show up because of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's out working.
[SPEAKER_04]: What corner is he working today?
[SPEAKER_06]: That would probably be one of the corners of the power machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if my ototo-chan is listening tonight, dude, get here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's fill it with witty banter.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, you come on.
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_21]: Is there anything about Monty really you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about Matt say something?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to announce, for all those people that do play The Sims out there, for DWI, actually, Bimani Ruler, you might know him from DDR Mania X, he's having a blitz for the next two weeks, he's going to be releasing a new file every day, and if anyone hasn't played his stuff, do play it, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Today, in fact, his release was the Classic Party Triathlon, which I have to say was...
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so go try that, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Everyone watch the webcam, because every once in a while something crazy is going to pop up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Something out of control.
[SPEAKER_22]: Something you didn't expect, something crazy and wild.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Brad comes back from the webcam room with this weird grin on his face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Should we fear?
[SPEAKER_06]: Should we be scared?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe you should look at the, uh, cam.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully it got caught.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like somebody's parrying the deluxe.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's, um, that's Brian playing DDR after he just... Brian's playing DDR after he was just in here slamming the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, now he's going, see, it's more truth that Vamani just owns everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Paul goes to play DDR now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's my picture?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, so were we going to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Irene has an idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to... Okay, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: What were you going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, we could talk about Max 2, because that's what everybody talks about these days.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Burning Heat now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just unlocked Burning Heat yesterday, which is kind of a big deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really the only song anybody seems to care about in Max 2, is Burning Heat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Kakumei, but Kakumei kind of... It was the big deal in the beginning, but then as people started unlocking Burning Heat, it was just like, Oh my god, Burning Heat!
[SPEAKER_05]: Burning Heat makes me cum.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what do you guys think about Max 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: Max 2 was the first new DDR that I had a reason to get excited over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Max 2 is everything that Max should have been.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's kind of been the opinion across the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's got way more songs than Fifth Mix had.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's got about the same amount of songs as Fifth Mix had.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Max had like 40 songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It had nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Max had way more.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what's missing from Max 2 that you'd like to see in our next installment of DDR?
[SPEAKER_04]: In Max 3, if they should actually take it that far?
[SPEAKER_06]: I want the ability to have flat dark mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Flat dark mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because dark and flat run on the same modifier, so you can't use them both.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, you know, we should be able to have more songs and less, maybe not less Oni modes, but make Oni modes, make more Oni modes accessible at first and not unlocking a lot of Oni modes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I noticed we unlocked a lot of Oni modes and hardly any of them were songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they're even between Oni and extra.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or close.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think people want more songs to play because Oni mode is,
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess, in my opinion, a little bit harder for people because it's a perfect attack thing, you know, or a great attack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's really hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, remember in 4th Mix how they had the, you could come home and make your own non-stops on the home version of 3rd Mix and save it to the card and then take it to the arcade and play your own non-stop?
[SPEAKER_04]: They should do something like that for Oni.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can see why they hesitate doing it because then everybody would just make a 10 song non-stop of a bunch of basics and they'd be able to stay on the machine all day.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe limit the homemade non-stops to as many songs as you would have on the normal game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, or maybe a certain amount of sets you have to have in a song or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually think that it might work better to do something very similar to how 2DX has it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, have an expert course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of what Oni is, in a way.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then there's people out there that maybe want to play Oni that can't play Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that they maybe should have had an easy Oni course?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just plain devil's advocate.
[SPEAKER_02]: What I'd like to see would be to have actually more unlockable stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not necessarily more songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, more songs would obviously be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: But let's say, for instance, we could have different sets for a song being added in or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe even...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, just have like sort of a challenge mode where you play and you get more points, you know, to go towards, you know, unlocking songs, but have it be like a certain really hard, strange thing that you haven't seen before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or even, you know, bringing back solo via megamixes where you have three songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Megamixes are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something I'd like to see come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember how in Solo 2000, which is getting way too much talk time on the show tonight, you have the, like, one chorus had Afronova, Dropout, and I think Wild Rush.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the cool thing about it is it wasn't just a non-stop, the songs actually mixed together.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, well, go ahead, finish your talk, because I'm going to change the subject a little.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I was just about the different steps, like Matt was saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I kind of missed was, it was kind of cool, I think it was on one of the versions of Third Mix, there was alternate steps for some of the songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was like, down, down, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the club append steps, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had it for like, Brilliant to You, Keep On Moving.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd love to see some of that come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about new stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been talking about a lot of old stuff we'd like to see make a return.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you think Konami can keep...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Prevent themselves from releasing a DDR final.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can they do to keep... They can put a foot pedal.
[SPEAKER_04]: On DDR?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've often thought that they need to do partner solo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, have the six panel solo set up, but with two players.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, instead of having the linked machines like they work now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not if you put enough space in between the machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or set it up like the three player Parapara.
[SPEAKER_06]: where you have three panels with the large monitor in the front.
[SPEAKER_06]: DDR could be made to accommodate that and have it with Solo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to see DDR on a humongous screen like, I say pump it up, is on a huge screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't like, though, how... Go to Fry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like... Oh, I don't like the setup.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something that's worth talking about here if we want to change the subject a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk about that when we come back from break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's save that for later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's keep talking about mechs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Max is maximum.
[SPEAKER_04]: The thing I don't like about Pump is it's got a huge screen, but then it's got this humongous box that just kind of sits out there, and the screen goes back.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like looking at the end of a tunnel to see what you're looking at.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of odd.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'd like it to look more like 2DX, which is a giant freaking huge... I think you're too tall for Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm too tall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another thing you can add to it would be more modifiers to, like, say, for instance, stuff you can do with the arrows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, have them all mixed up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Some things I thought, even for doing some of my edits and stuff, maybe even have it where, like, stuff in the background kind of helps you, you know, not to be able to see the arrows just right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, have a bunch of arrows all of a sudden appear in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just crazy shit like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's kind of, a lot of people say Flash in the Night was like that on Macs, because when it would go Flash, the screen would do this seizure thing, like, amazing seizure robots, Flash!
[SPEAKER_14]: And then it was kind of hard to see your arrows, so... They also need to put in, like, super random mode, like they have in 7ix Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_14]: where like in normal shuffle mode like all the up arrows become something like left down or right but you can have them so all the arrows are completely random so they'd still appear in the same place but they'd all be completely random and not appear in any order and figure out some way to shuffle double steps because I'm just sick of being able to only play it on regular or play it on mirror and really that's just the same yeah yes
[SPEAKER_06]: I had a dumb idea once, because I'm terrible at freestyling, so I always thought it would be so cool if they put a screen on the back of DDR so that you could turn around and not fuck up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I remember when I first played Only You You're right, that is dumb Yeah, and I'm going to kick you Like, I turned around, and I tried to turn around again And I totally messed up because, you know, I don't know how to freestyle Well, that's part of freestyling, is learning how to turn around Now, I know you have issues with Mirror, but I fucking hate Mirror Mirror is the devil Okay, what I meant was, like, you know, just If you want to turn around and start doing steps or some shit like that, you know, like
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, I don't know, I can't look at a step chart and know what I'm doing because I am a complete retard.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're saying that they should make a freestyle for dummies machine?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, yes, exactly, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR autistic mix.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's freestyle DDR or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's a possibility.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be expensive.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the thing is, I don't know how they would be able to pull that off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, it would block the view of people who'd want to watch anyway, so that'd be kind of pointless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: And the bars would obviously pose a problem because some people need bars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody in the back of the room is yelling and you can't hear it over the microphone and suggesting that they just take the bars off the next DDR Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is going to be a tournament coming up in August.
[SPEAKER_04]: I happen to know there's going to be a tournament in Concord at Mountain Mike's that they are taking the bar off the machine for freestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: That should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have more details on that as they're announced.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got Joe Mama suggesting that they have each arrow go at a different speed.
[SPEAKER_04]: For like a modifier you can set each arrow to go at a random speed That would be crazy, I don't know, that's almost a little too weird Do you think there's any, besides adding new panels, adding new screens, bigger screens Is there anything Konami could do to the game itself to make it more interesting?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or do they pretty much just have to trash the whole damn thing and start over?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually I got another idea, kind of similar with ParaPara where you have set routines to do
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe set something up like have a freestyle mode or something where they actually have a set routine for a song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Freestyle for dummies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, basically, you know, kind of get ideas or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: White people dancing mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Teaching you how to do country line dancing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't imagine this would actually be a new DDR but, you know, they've got Parapara, they have DDR they should do something that combines the both together where you have like maybe a sensitive panel beneath you plus the sensors above so it's not just where you wave your hands or where you're stepping but you are doing everything and you memorize their dances or you just have to be in the right place at the right time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I was thinking this might sound kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if I had explained it right, but I was thinking maybe they'd add like mini panels.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe where you could do like little hand plants and stuff, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they could have like the floor, little moles would come up out of the floor and you could step on them with your feet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe my dead spider stomp.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you know, maybe that should be it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they should just make the whole thing like a... You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The hell with DDR, we want spider stomp 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about they just get rid of actual panels and they just make the whole pad pressure sensitive?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, pressure sensitive?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and then, like, the whole thing would be just one huge panel, and then, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: One huge panel.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you could kind of freestyle that way, and they can put arrows wherever they want.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be like Saturday Night Fever, where you got the light-up dance floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wouldn't that be cool?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can suggest, like, John Travolta.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_03]: More thoughts.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is my two cents.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking maybe Konami should just give us all free machines.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'd like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you hear us, Konami?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hook us up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Konami, if you're here listening, which I doubt you are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami, I love you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give me a machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: On that note, I think it's time to go into another break here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go listen to a request right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to listen to some Jerry Hallowell with It's Rainin' Men.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a request, by the way, from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: which you can visit us on irc.eggheads.org and visit our website as well as http://orangelounge.sky.cx In the meantime, this is for Dark Tetsuya in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some Jerry Halliwell from Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Waymen, Waymen, Waymen It's time to scream it!
[SPEAKER_10]: It's time to scream it!
DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and many more.
Thank you for watching!
But I guess that's the way to let you know I'm here
I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe, I believe
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye-bye, baby balloon.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bitch, get a new song.
[SPEAKER_17]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, get a new damn song, lady.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the very first show.
[SPEAKER_04]: About 8.36.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're taking this show two hours, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go to 9 o'clock with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We think if the show is successful in the future, we'll try three hours, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, this is kind of an interesting situation because my co-host Jamie, the lovely Jamie Summers, is going to be gone for the next two shows.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I'm going to be in San Diego next weekend and then I'm going to Anime Expo where I have enlisted aid to do interviews with several of the people there in cosplays and general views and crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's one thing we're going to bring you on future episodes of Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to do interviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately, we were going to be taking a trip yesterday over to Sunnyvale because we knew a lot of people were going to be convening there and we wanted to get some interviews with your favorite Bay Area personalities.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, we weren't able to get out there because I had a job to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got work, so we couldn't make it out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we're going to try in future weeks to get out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you have any event in NorCal that you'd like us to come cover...
[SPEAKER_04]: Drop us an email, orangeloungeradio, that's all one word, orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com and we'll try and make it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even SoCal events we'll consider, but pretty much anything further away than that, we don't really have a travel budget to accommodate yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to give us money, we'll definitely think about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Money is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Money is always wonderful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Money facilitates going places and doing things.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: We do have some new subject matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The last song we played just before coming out of that break was LED Light from Beatmania 5th Mix with Overblast, which is something brand new in the new USA DDR Max that's going to be released.
[SPEAKER_04]: You remember the release date on that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they said they were going to do it in October.
[SPEAKER_04]: November.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about you guys, I kind of had a hunch that this is what was going to happen at E3, is that they were kind of keeping it a secret that there was going to be a new DDR release in the USA, and it turned out to be that they are going to release Max in the USA, except it's not just the same song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be some old songs, like Brilliant to You, Orchestral Groove is in it, and AM3P I believe is returning as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of my friends who is not into Beimani, he was kind enough to videotape some of the game for me while he was at E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: The songs that I saw being played, I remember definitely that one of them was Insertion.
[SPEAKER_06]: He said that it looked very clean.
[SPEAKER_06]: He was very impressed with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: He got to hear a little bit of some talk about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And on the tape it sounded like everybody's favorite Konami rep, Jason Enos, in the background giving some information.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I can find the tape, I'll definitely make sure that I have the segment encoded so that everybody can see it or try to do something like that for everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's something we can put up on our website.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's kind of old stuff and there's going to be new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And something that is going to be new is 20 new tracks to the USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something that has not been on any Japanese release.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one of those songs right there we just played for you, Overblast, from Beatmania 5th Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a song in DDR Max with steps and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we've been promised that we're going to have some licensed songs in the new DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, hopefully no more crappy remixes of AM3P.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I like the remix of AM3P.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the one in Max 2 is okay, but... I like all of the remixes of AM3P.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like the Canomics one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like the remix of Superstar, but that's me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyways, Overblast.
[SPEAKER_02]: That song, eh, I could think that you picked a better one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody's entitled to an opinion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, my opinion on this is that that song sucks ass, and I wish that they had picked a better song.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, out of all the beat mania songs in the world, why the hell do you pick that song?
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, that song sucks ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pick, like, The Fall, I mean, pick, uh, Nopia, I mean, there's a bunch of songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, hell, why not 321 Stars or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just...
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, there's still 19 other songs that can be on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I still have my hopes up for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: So hopefully you'll be pleased.
[SPEAKER_04]: They say there's licensed songs that are going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that would be pretty cool if they went back and took some old school 80s songs or old 90s songs or even some current stuff and made it popular.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just as long as it's not Britney Spears or some of that new top 40 crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's be glad that Britney Spears is working with Metro and not Konami.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So no Britney Spears is likely in the new Max USA, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means no Jive Record artists will be on Max USA, which pretty much eliminates all the top 40.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was much rejoicing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no remixes of Let Them Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually has been promised on one of those message boards.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was promised that there's no Let Them Move in any way, shape, or form.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, Konami comes to a good decision, hooray for them So we'll keep bringing you news on Max USA as we hear it Because it's going to be a big freaking deal At least for us Because they all say that DDR is dying in Japan I don't know if there's any truth to that We're not in Japan, so we don't really know if it's dying or not But that's what people are saying So we'll see Maybe it's dying there, but it's going to be big here So maybe they'll start focusing their efforts on what's starting to become a fad here
[SPEAKER_06]: I would actually like, you know, in the whole respect that we're getting this Max USA, I would like to actually, I'm probably not listening, but I would still like to give a big kudos to Jason Enos of Konami of America for all of the hard work that's been put into us getting these games.
[SPEAKER_04]: and anybody that happened to contribute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know he's kind of the contact person.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's the one that lurks on all the DDR boards and stuff, letting us know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anybody that happens to be involved with that whole process deserves some thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoever woke up over there and said, let's bring DDR to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: and let's bring them something new, not just recycled crap that they've already imported.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you know Konami's got to know about all these import machines.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's one thing that's completely boggled me, is you've got all these Max 2 machines popping up everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the new thing, which is great, because Max 2's the best mix they've done in a long, long time, I would say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most people wouldn't argue with me there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yet Konami doesn't seem to be... They have that, you know, this message is illegal for use outside of Japan message that comes up on the screen, but yet they're not really doing anything about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All these Max 2 machines are still sitting there, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we're not seeing a new release, at least that I've heard of, or that, you know, as far as an arcade release, I haven't seen any new releases come through.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure exactly the reasoning behind that, but, you know, if they're not minding us getting those imports or they're not actively trying to stop it, let's not bring that up and not, you know... It's very interesting to see that we're actually getting a brand new, you know, actually it doesn't look like something recycled, as Rob was putting it,
[SPEAKER_02]: And actually, it's looking like they're putting time in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, adding features like, you know, the .5 speed and other things like that, it looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, .5's kind of a weak feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not really... How many people are going to... Outside of Max 300, which is, in my mind, it's kind of a crutch, if you're going to use .5 speed to beat Max 300.
[SPEAKER_04]: What...
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the use of 0.5?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it just to make things challenging, you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's to make things more challenging.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the other things I was looking at is hopefully this won't be as buggy as Chronomix was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, I have problems with the fact that you can't take the edits off there, put them on Japanese machines because, you know, they do have region coding inside the actual edits also, which kind of sucked ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully they'll fix that this time around.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, it's very interesting that...
[SPEAKER_02]: In Europe, they're getting Euromax, which is the brand new Euromix there, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish we could get some of their songs over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, maybe this is Konami's little trick, is that they're going to actually take those songs they put in Euromix and give them to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what's interesting, though, is Euromax, they're also getting a machine for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So maybe we can be looking forward to DDR USA Max also.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, something that's being suggested in the chat room, a use for .5, imagine my summer love maniac on .5 flat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so, stealth, that kind of eliminates, that eliminates, oh, okay, we'll stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's effectively stealth, what we're hearing from the back of the room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting suggestion there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know when we're going to hear more news on Max USA, but we'll give that to you as soon as we hear any more information on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: One thing we have been hearing little bits and pieces about, it's kind of a surprise to most people, was DDR PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not talking about the politically correct version of DDR with the heroin needles removed.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're talking about DDR for the personal computer on IBM.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you heard about this at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I have.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually exclusive to friesandoutposts.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can go buy it there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically like Forth Mix on a PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got 40 characters you can choose from.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have more that you can actually download off their website at some point or another.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now it's been kind of iffy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've been having it available, then coming soon, available, coming soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think they're having a little bit of trouble getting the actual product out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're falling short on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as the song list goes, you only have a few more that actually aren't available in any of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: But pretty much it's just a rehash of 4th Mix all over again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I was promised to be able to try this out pretty soon, so I'll be able to maybe give a review on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be nice, next week maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: But one of the features that was pretty interesting with this one was the fact that they're adding internet ranking, just like 4th Mix and all the other Japanese releases had.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know how well it's working out, though, because you have people playing on keyboards and you have people playing on pads.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, I'm sure there's a lot of...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, inflating of people's actual ability on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it looks pretty good if you haven't had any home versions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if there's some kind of switch that would be able to show, hey, this person played on the pad or this person played on the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: But even then, any hacker could probably wire a switch that would look like a pad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, no, they do have such a thing in Dance with Intensity.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have it where it actually detects whether it's keyboard or playing with controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no, still...
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they just did a port of the PlayStation version, they probably didn't bother to go that far with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one thing, I remember before the break, Dave was out here talking about Fry's.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know a lot of people on the West Coast probably haven't seen this because they don't have Fry's Electronics outside of California too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got this really interesting setup for DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have any of you guys been over to Fry's and seen their DDR setup?
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got the two BADs on the ground, and Fry's is on a concrete floor, at least the one we go to here in Sacramento has a concrete floor on it, so it makes it pretty good to dance on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of feels like the arcade BAD.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they've got like a big screen TV with DDR economics going on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every time I've gone into Fry's, I don't play DDR at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to be stared at by all those weird people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not the only one doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I constantly see little kids in there playing on the thing, and those things, the pads and games sell.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems like I always seem to look over, and there's one set of parents, at least one set of parents looking at the games, thinking about buying them.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Fry's has kind of been pushing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But people really, really, really want to go to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, and I'd like to respond to Joe Mama in the chatroom about editing images and posting them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they have passwords, and basically it's just a long string of letters and numbers that they give you when you, you know, finish your songs to post up for the internet rankings.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't have anything to do with screen captures or anything like that, so there's really no way to cheat as far as photoshopping goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, I'm sure there's ways you could probably find to, you know, crack the passwords and all that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like, it sounds like it was going to be just like the ranking for 4th Mix and 5th Mix and Max 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything had on it where you had the long passwords.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's pretty much a lifted system from that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if it matches any other game, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you were to play a song on another mix, it gives you the same code that... You know, that does remind me...
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone, I believe, we should make it a part to actually post somewhere the actual, there is internet ranking in Max, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people don't know about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you play three songs, certain songs in a row, you'll actually get a password and stuff that you can post on the internet ranking site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not many people know that that's actually out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps we might need to make this a future contest or something, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sure Japanese and people from the barrier are probably dominating that internet ranking list there, but we could give it a try.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also the Oni ranking.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know that there is, somewhere on Team Guilo's page, there has been a page for the Oni ranking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they went to the effort to translate the internet ranking page into English, so a big shout out to them for doing that, because that's a good favor to the whole community there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of the community, we'd like to make a mention that if ever, you know, whenever we're not hosting our show live, you can also check out a lot of the community action for the Sac Baymani forums located at www.sacbaymani.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's S-A-C-B-E-M-A-N-I.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to take a really quick break here and then we're going to come back and wrap things up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to do a set of a couple 2DX songs and then we'll come right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start it off with Rizlam here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's my fan when I need it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to do the Tran Dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Tran Dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Starmine Tran Dance.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's actually the way I freestyle in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a little break in Starmine and I'll do a little spinny arm thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, that was Ryu with Starmine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before that, Rick with Rizlam.
[SPEAKER_04]: from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: And right now, they've been playing 2DX all night here in the broadcast room.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're playing, what is this, Love Will?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great 2DX song.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll play that next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's old school 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: Old school 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting ready to wrap up the show here, our first show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to thank everybody here for listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you so much for listening to our first show.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're listening to a little piece of Bomani history, I'd like to thank.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Right before, right when we came back from the last segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Jamie, you're going to be gone for a couple weeks now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're the co-host of the show, yet you're already abandoning us, but with good reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: I go to AX every year, and I'm actually heading down a week early to go to San Diego to see some friends and to hunt down our little Youth Coalition friend with a chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, with a recorder so I can maybe get an interview if the door's not slammed in my face.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: But really, I'm going to be at Anime Expo.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to have recorders with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: So all of you people who are going to be there, watch out for the girl with the wings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I will be in costume.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen cosplay.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's cosplay costume is something else for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will be either in costume as Mad Hatter from Angel Sanctuary or Baiken from Guilty Gear X or Leona from King of Fighters.
[SPEAKER_06]: So watch out for the short girl in the costume with the big black wings and the face paint.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our website was finished today and your picture's on it so they can find it there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the issue is...
[SPEAKER_04]: We're still doing the show every week, so we're going to have an open seat.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what do you think I should do about this predicament we're in?
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I have them all fight over it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I make them all play 2DX to see who wins?
[SPEAKER_06]: You could do like the clown car thing and pile them all in.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You could do the clown car thing and pile them all in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could make them all sit in the big chair.
[SPEAKER_06]: The seat is really cushy, and I think that we should just put caution tape around it, and people have to caution drop to get in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do Trippie L.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could do elimination.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could trivia battle.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could do Bomani Survivor.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the seat will be filled by a random individual.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it will be temporarily filled because I don't let up my spot easily.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll do Bomani Pop Idol.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're awful.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be quiet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not coming to Hollywood, you little bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are the weakest link?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty much a cross between the weakest link and Star Search.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is why I don't watch TV anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we should do karaoke to see who stays on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think maybe what we'll do is we'll just come back next week and we'll kind of surprise everybody with who we're going to have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll talk about it during the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, unless you have any... We will have a lovely surprise waiting for the crowd next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you sure?
[SPEAKER_05]: No karaoke?
[SPEAKER_04]: And no karaoke?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll do karaoke.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you know, don't you know, I've been waiting for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Irene Moss, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, no I didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or we could just settle this the good old D&D way, where's my dice?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Somebody chatbot!
[SPEAKER_06]: I know all of you know what D&D means, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we're all a bunch of dorks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You sacrifice chickens by the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_02]: How about we pick a number between 1 and 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, everyone picks a number.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't say it on the air.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we'll have someone that's in our chatroom type a random number between 1 and 6.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that'll be who hosts, since we all have a dice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, I got an 18 strength.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to own you all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Six different numbers.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as we have a moment of silence to decide, since the microphone can't pick up the people in the background, I think that we will have a random guest next week, and we will surprise our beautiful, lovely listeners, who we all love very much and are trying not to bore to death.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if worse comes to worse, we'll just pass the headset around.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll let everybody sit in the chair for a segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that sound like a fair option?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, so now you're pimping out my chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we'll pimp out the chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the new co-host for next week will be the Bomani pimp.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll be the whore.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to be the pimp to pimp out the chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll be our whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, so they'll be the Bomani whores.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get ejected out of the chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say something stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bail!
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're out of the chair.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a button with a spring, and if you piss me off... It'd be like Russian Roulette.
[SPEAKER_04]: They'll fall through the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Russian Roulette.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be like that MTV show, Remote Control.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be like Remote Control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, see, there is a sign of being old when you remember when Remote Control was new.
[SPEAKER_06]: That mitten and you're old, if you remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the song they all sang when the person went through the wall?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_04]: Party!
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I think we're going to bring this show to a close now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you everybody for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please join us next week again at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to rebroadcast this show sometime through the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just haven't figured out a good time yet, so if there's a part you missed, you can hear it later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But do send us an email, orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com, all one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let us know what songs you want to hear through the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, all your suggestions and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: All your suggestions are belong to us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: For great justice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we're going to end the show now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you to everybody for listening and we will see you next week on the Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any final thoughts, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_06]: Be excellent to each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: Party on, dude!