[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, August 12, 2007, is the Xbox 360 Core on its way out?
[SPEAKER_00]: New details on Super Mario Galaxy, and is it really possible to now play NES games on your iPhone?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be here with you all night long as will my lovely co-host DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how are you doing, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Full of burrito.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mmm, yummy burrito.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shrimpy burritos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just shrimp?
[SPEAKER_05]: No red meat tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I'm not going to be eating red meat anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going on one of those funky diet things?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, out of necessity, every so often I get to where I can't actually eat it very safely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, because I was going to say you can't have diet without dye.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't diet.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have lifestyle adjustments.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a clever little workaround.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, also joining us, say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: So would a funky diet be like pizza and disco or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, would that be a funky diet?
[SPEAKER_02]: Would that be eating dirty food?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why, is that what your life is like right now, disco and pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, everything's all disco and pizza.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever happened to discos?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, my mom still calls clubs discos.
[SPEAKER_04]: The discotheque.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it good pizza?
[SPEAKER_04]: TheFunkyDiet.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because we don't have the air conditioning yet out there and it's too hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're in the little studio.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the good news is we're back on the normal computers and the normal network setup and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the sound of the show should be pretty much what you guys are used to, at least I hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Save some minor echo and probably things you probably can't even really hear on your iPods.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're happy to be back.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also we're happy to have you back, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I know a lot of folks were thinking about you last week, so I hope everything was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well, we'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's talk about games instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: And talk about your interesting experience at California Extreme you just got back from yesterday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, at, you know, two in the morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_05]: What exactly is California Extreme?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a pinball and classic gaming convention of sorts.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had an auction there, but as far as I know it wasn't actually part of California Extreme.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I did play a whole crap ton of games and finally beat Space Harrier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw your LJ post about beating Space Harrier, so... I sure did.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot that it just says the end.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, they just get a bunch of random games together and call it an expo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, some of them are for sale.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had Big Bang Bar, which was the first thing I went right to.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ran into... Well, actually, I met up with Mel and Melody.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the first thing that she and I did was go right up and play...
[SPEAKER_03]: Big Bang Bar which was one of the last machines Capcom made but they only had about 16 prototypes and now there's production models of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I should say reproduction models but the one that we played was a legitimate prototype and
[SPEAKER_03]: Then it was just mostly wandering around.
[SPEAKER_03]: She was playing Star Wars.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got to play Ultra Pin, which was kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Ultracade's answer to pinball.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I think you talked about this on the show once.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it like they use an LCD but laid flat instead?
[SPEAKER_05]: How does that work?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: The perspective kind of messed with my head a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I played Black Knight 2000 on it, which was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I was like, screw this and went to play a real Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Black Knight Pinball Pinbot
[SPEAKER_03]: or Jackbot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cry and Sadness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they have Bride of Pinbot?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have Bride of Pinbot in your house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Bride.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they didn't have that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bride of Pinbot is so badass, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Vortex, which is one of the mid-80s games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I remember Vortex.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's a cool one, but I played one of the best tables ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called Airborne.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of Capcom's.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's all ramps.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a bajillion ramps everywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it was fun, and they had it on like a bajillion buy-ins.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So did you play anything besides Space Harrier and Pinball?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, um, Words.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't play Journey.
[SPEAKER_03]: They got Journey working.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had Journey?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, I should have gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying to go, but I couldn't because I had other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, what I would give to play a Journey arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Mappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played, Julie played a bunch of Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time I ran into her, she's either playing Crystal Castles or Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a tapper, Rob, that someone had messed with the sprites, and it was all Simpsons characters.
[SPEAKER_03]: With Moe as the bartender.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played SVC Chaos, because I had to get my fighting game on.
[SPEAKER_03]: X-Men vs. Street Fighter
[SPEAKER_03]: Panic Park
[SPEAKER_03]: Panic Park is a great game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they have one at Milpitas Golf Land where there's a big one and then there's a small one.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had an actual Japanese one there, but they had the bad Ingress-y one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a game where one person's on one side and the other person's on another.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to play with another person.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have a big stick and it slides around.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you are competing with somebody in minigames and it's best however many out of however many and you push them aside or they push you aside using this big stick when you're grabbing hula hoops as they come from the ground or grabbing coins or jumping from thing to thing or avoiding hammers falling on you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have never heard of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've actually played with Dan's buddy, Will.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Will is really strong, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I had a hard time.
[SPEAKER_03]: We ended up, he won two matches, I won two matches, and we had a draw of three matches.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we actually had a perfect draw game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to read some comments from chat because, you know, your comments on old gaming is sparking a lot of discussion in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, since I haven't introduced them yet, say hello to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have GS68 says, I was at Milpitas Golf Land on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember seeing a game like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So maybe it wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it was at Sunnyvale or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kevin DDR says, Oh, my God, Panic Park.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: So somebody knows what you're talking about there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sakura Max says, He's confused.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the youngest guy, so he doesn't know about these old-ass games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's time to learn.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: XBOX LIVE ARCADE
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh cool, like the little like, what do they call it, Megatouch and that stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but they were actually the ones with the controllers and everything on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they had an actual Pong, and they had the small child-sized machines, the SNK machines.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Neo Geo ones, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: With like, you know, Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it sounds like you had a lot of fun, and it sounds like I really missed out getting to see a journey machine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did get to find, though, some of my favorite old tables were there, though, like Centaur.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a Hyperball, which I refused to ever play again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stupid fucking Hyperball.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they had... I'm sorry, I'm trying to watch my language.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Watch it fly out of your mouth and affect people.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go, language.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you play any, like, new games this week, or was it all pretty much retro gaming goodness?
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I played the Ultra Pin.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's technically new.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Max 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Cowgirl in Flip Flops.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was actually kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, dude, I'm going to fall over.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, next year, the dude with the journey machine needs to come back to California Extreme so I can play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or I'll be sad.
[SPEAKER_03]: But my World Cup soccer is almost fixed up nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, this is what pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not really an FU.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a...
[SPEAKER_03]: The one Theater of Magic they had, and the entire place was at the tournament area.
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless you pay to do the stupid tournament, and you can't play the Theater of Magic, and I'm like, I want to play Theater of Magic!
[SPEAKER_05]: Theater of Magic's pretty badass.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did play the Devil Madness, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knocked down the castle, it was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we gotta move on, but it sounds like you got a lot of good gaming in, even if most of it was pinball, not console games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pinball's pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before I get into my gaming week, though, I wanted to talk about, there was this game that I saw
[SPEAKER_04]: Neo Geo Battle Coliseum
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: from King of Monsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all kinds of rap.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then I also tried the Fatal Inertia demo which you know I've been really hyped up about the game ever since they first announced it because it reminded me of like you know kind of like F-Zero GX or something like that you know a combat racing game that was not the case with this this is crap and I thank god I played the demo because I'm not buying the game now it's just it's hard to control and it didn't seem that fast and I don't know I just didn't like the level layout it wasn't pretty enough for me so
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, let's see, I also played 300 on the PSP because I had just watched the Blu-ray for it, so that game sucked also.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what do you expect?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a hack and slash game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a movie tie-in game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, isn't that what the movie was?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't see the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the movie was a lot better than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm the one guy that didn't see 300.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, um, I've been playing, actually, strangely enough, uh, well, Overlord I've been playing, and that game's still really fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I've also been playing, uh, this is gonna be really weird, um, Settlers of Catan, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh, because I got hooked on this yesterday, actually, I was playing the actual board game, uh, with my sister and her boyfriend, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really fun, so I bought the Xbox Live Arcade game, and it's pretty much the same thing, except the AI is completely cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: But other than that, the only thing I really wish it had was local multiplayer instead of just over live.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be pretty cool, but they didn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this game has passed the wife test, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, the wife is probably playing it right now, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, she was playing it all afternoon, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Crimey River.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, somebody in chat earlier, and I apologize, I forgot who said it, somebody had said, what's more funny than watching Grand Theft Auto 4 get delayed is watching everything else back out of its way now that it's been delayed, everything else is getting delayed because of that, or, you know, the other games that all kind of moved out of way, like the ripple effect that Grand Theft Auto is having, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Looking at the chatroom and talking about some quotes there.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it the Rob D said that was really funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, about the Battle Coliseum game and how I said Mai could fight one of the King of the Monsters.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sky just wants to see Mai versus a tentacle monster, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That quote coming from the Rob D. Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently the Rob D didn't see 300 either.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess I'm not the only one ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see what else is there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: RossDLUT impersonates Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Durr, I'm going to play this movie game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it'll suck less than all the others.
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose saying that all movie games usually suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the most part, they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's some movie games that are okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember some of the NES Batman games weren't that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I actually liked the Friday the 13th game like it always ends up on like these worst NES games of all times list but that game actually scared me when I was a kid because it was kind of a scary game I don't know anyway but yeah movie games usually not not so much fun let's see
[SPEAKER_05]: Games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot of new stuff, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been on World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm really grinding like hell in World of Warcraft to try and get my character to level 70, so I'll be all ready by the time the next expansion comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also, the fact is that I know all these console games are coming out very soon, especially when we get into the end of August.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blue Dragon, Eternal Sonata, Halo, and then Metroid Prime 3 and all these games I'm going to want to be playing are all coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want to get as much grinding in as I can before I get distracted by the console games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So most of my week has been spent on the PC playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, though, I have been playing some other console games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was playing Kingdom Hearts 2 more, and I finally surpassed my first save game, so I guess that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Otherwise, I checked out probably like all the... because I was without internet for a little while, because, you know, if you listened to last week's show, you know Comcast finally didn't come out here until Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, let me say, Comcast said they were going to come here in a window between 12 and 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what time they finally got here?
[SPEAKER_05]: 7.30, 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, then I would... Don't you get some money or something off your bill?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a $20 credit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, whoopee!
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoopee-doo!
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoopee-doo, that's like... Then they installed all this shit we didn't ask for, like all the HBO and Showtime channels.
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't want that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it was cool for one night, because I got to watch Big Brother After Dark, which is kind of cheesy fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, we had to get rid of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just totally screwed up the order.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually surprised they remembered to put the HD in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, otherwise my gaming week's been pretty light in that regard, just mostly World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I will be kicking back into high gear when we get into the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did catch up on all those ones I missed while I was out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't really care for any of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played like four.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't like the Spyglass board games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Super, well, Super Contra was okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you know, and Track and Field is okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surprisingly, I actually think I played Track and Field more than any of the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was thinking about buying Track and Field.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's just back and forth with the analog stick, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that or you can use the buttons, because the actual arcade machine used buttons, like giant poppin' music style buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or you know what I suggest doing, since I think, aren't the controls completely configurable and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR pads, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get out the DDR pads and bust it out like track and field.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not the most thrilling game ever, but for some reason I like those old retro games, so it's fun to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I don't know if I'd actually recommend it to a lot of people, because it's certainly not one of the better Konami arcade ports that's on Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, let's move on and get into some housekeeping so we can get to tonight's news.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: and they highlighted us this week as kind of like they were mentioning all the podcasts they had that week and they had themselves because Joystick does their own podcast but they're a little bit irregular but I guess they did two weeks in a row so they were nominating themselves for having done two weeks in a row like saying hooray for us and then they followed up with us and saying well now we have these guys who've been doing it for years and years so that was just kind of funny so we appreciate the plug but it's hilarious that it happened the week that our show was like totally broken and like Jamie wasn't even here and
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we had all the sound issues we had last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was nuts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what the listeners couldn't see last week is I was also trying to read stories while keeping the spaghetti away from my cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I had a plate of spaghetti and she kept trying to attack the plate.
[SPEAKER_05]: The sound was so horrible last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then for some reason, there was little packet losses throughout the file.
[SPEAKER_05]: So suddenly you'd be... And then the words would drop out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost felt like I was gonna burst into flames, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we almost had a webcam tonight, but I just didn't get it set up in time.
[SPEAKER_05]: But speaking of Apple, my little Apple webcam and the laptop, so I can have it wherever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're going to wait until we move out to the garage to do that, so it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know who else likes that Seller is a Catan?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: My cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: She'll sit there in front of the TV and watch the dice move and the cards move and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's completely fascinated by it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: XBOX 360 Core Model
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of theorize that this might be happening, although I don't think it's anytime soon that it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the theory behind it is, other than the fact that it is showing discontinued in their system, is that they're replacing all of the current premium systems out there with the ones with HDMI, but they're not doing that with the core system.
[SPEAKER_04]: So people are thinking, okay, well, they're going to just sell out the core system and then discontinue it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did Microsoft maybe do something to Target?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I noticed Target also, aren't they phasing out HD DVDs?
[SPEAKER_05]: I seem to remember that was a previous report.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was Target that was doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they're phasing them out of their store, but if you've ever gone into Target looking for HD product anyways...
[SPEAKER_04]: Their shelving that they have is like, it's literally maybe 12 movies that they have there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blu-ray and HD DVD combined.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I wouldn't exactly consider Target my number one stop for HD DVD purchasing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's only in store.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they have them still on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little disheartening, though, to see HD DVDs be phased out when, you know, I spent as much money as I did on the HD player for the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if their Blu-ray product is selling and their HD is not, then...
[SPEAKER_04]: And then hopefully with season 2 or something they'll do it where you can download the episodes right after they air, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Target isn't the only place that's phasing out the Xbox 360 Core model, according to some rumors out there right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the other store that is phasing them out, Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best Buy, as apparently a little screenshot has come out of their system, shown that the status of the Xbox 360 Core hardware in their system was deleted on July 29, 2007.
[SPEAKER_05]: So Microsoft denies that there's any type of Core production being stocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: or it actually is something coming from Microsoft saying, hey, we're getting rid of the core model.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's actually been announced yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if that is going to happen, probably won't happen until after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow, lots and lots of comments from chat on this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Dark Knight says, Sears has never had the core models.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Raven's Dolphin says, when Walmart says no more Core 360s, then it's done.
[SPEAKER_05]: RawSteelUT says, of course Microsoft would deny.
[SPEAKER_05]: They probably also deny that the Core only counts for maybe 20% of their sales.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bandit says they should keep the Core for people who want to upgrade their memory later on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be more accessible to everyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't think they were going to announce the HDMI thing either until it leaked out, so, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to join our chat room and give your comments, if you're listening live here on this Sunday night when we tape live, chat.orangeloungeradio.com By the way, some other chatters following up on the whole Target HD DVD thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: GS191 says this, Target is not getting rid of HD DVD.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Blu-ray camp just inked a deal for their product to be displayed more through the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wonder Dog Harold follows that up with a web link that says that's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, myself, being that I've got a Blu-ray player, then... But you don't have an HD DVD player, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's one of the things you don't have in your house, amazingly enough.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amongst all the other crap you have.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't have an HD DVD player, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I actually know more people who have Blu-ray players myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because they're built into the PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't own PlayStation 3s.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: The new VIOs come built in with Blu-ray players.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, Sony just used... I mean, you know, if HD DVD loses, then it loses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine, I went with the wrong format, but... I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony is really pushing with all their... Because, you know, Sony is not just a gaming company.
[SPEAKER_05]: They are an electronics company and a major one at that, so it's kind of... They've been able to sneak Blu-ray into all these other little places, and it's worked for them, where, for whatever reason, Beta didn't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know, there is still some hope, though, for people who...
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it's not specifically HD related, but they are dropping the price of the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually said that it was scheduled to happen on August 8th, so the price reduction should already be in place.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we are seeing the Elite model go to $449, the Pro model to $349, and the Core at $279.
[SPEAKER_03]: So
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course the premium had the biggest drop, given that that's the best seller.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that price drop was totally a surprise to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: And everybody out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, the entire internet was shocked and awed at that price drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually curious though, well I guess I don't think we have any stories on this tonight, so I can say that, I think I want to say I read somewhere that Amazon, you know, the sales of the Xbox 360 went through the roof after the price drop.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm just kind of curious if the same thing happened to retail outlets or what happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you surprised they made the move at this time?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm actually kind of a little surprised they didn't wait until a little closer to Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I would have expected the price drop a little more October-ish.
[SPEAKER_05]: But maybe then again with Halo 3 coming out when it is, maybe they wanted to do it in advance of Halo 3, which would certainly make sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just going to mention there was another story I remember reading, I guess, that the NPD group did a survey with people saying, you know, kind of...
[SPEAKER_04]: Asking them whether they're aware of different features of their console.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I guess there was like almost like 60% of people didn't realize that the PlayStation 3 had a Blu-ray player in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or had never used it for like Blu-ray movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I thought that was a little bit funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anywho.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I want to know is what are they using it for then?
[SPEAKER_05]: Motorstorm?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: The basketball game that's on it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It must be all that wonderful download content that's online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wait, no, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, anyways, other countries are also getting a 360 price drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, Canadians are seeing a pretty big price drop.
[SPEAKER_04]: They will see a $100, um, of course that's in Canadian money, um, drop on the premium and core systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, um, yeah, so after that price drop, uh, the premium will be running, I guess, approximately $378 US.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, still, you know, of course with the exchange rates, uh,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: There wasn't really a whole lot else to that firmware update.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's kind of a bummer, too, because, you know, when you turn on your Xbox 360 and you see, ooh, a new firmware update is available, you kind of start to get a little bit excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, ooh, I wonder what new features they've added this week, you know, or what they're adding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is this the big seasonal update?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they do a big one in fall and I think spring.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, it's summer, so that wouldn't make sense for my brain to go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can still help but get a little bit excited when the thing comes up and says there's a firmware update.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, ooh, what cool new feature are they going to add?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then it turns out to be nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_03]: That poo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh well, I mean... That big stinky poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was unexpected, so it's, you know, can't really beg for a lot with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: For anybody who is actually excited about anything having to do with Halo, well, Halo 3, I should say, or likes having green Xbox 360s, the Halo-themed Xbox 360 will be out in September, priced for $399 with a wireless headset for $59.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really see anything all that special about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says it's Spartan green and gold.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really, it looks to me like it's baby poop green with orange.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least that's what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_03]: As far as your HDMI cables, that comes separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's exactly how they should market it, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have an HDMI port.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they all have the HDMI port now.
[SPEAKER_02]: But no cable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, the only thing that you get for the extra $50 is you get a plain charge kit that's also the, I guess, baby poop green.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you get the wonderful baby poop green paint job.
[SPEAKER_03]: It does look like baby poo.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that type of green.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you do want HDMI cables, those will cost you about $50.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're going to be sold separately, actually, now that all the 360s, the premiums with the HDMI are coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: You get the... There's no Halo 3 with it, even.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is kind of, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, why didn't they do that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know there's people that are going to go out and buy their Xbox 360 the day that Halo 3 comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to finally make that upgrade, because they've been playing Halo 2 this whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And in case you forgot, there are also two custom Halo 3...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: SonOfDad in our chatroom at chat.orangeloungeradio.com calls the new color Split Pea in Halo Chunky Style Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mmm, yummy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyways, speaking of Halo 3, apparently there are a lot of fans out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, who knew?
[SPEAKER_04]: Halo 3 has become the fastest-selling pre-ordered game in history.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, 1 million pre-orders have been taken in North America, a new record, apparently, for those keeping track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, this all ties in with their marketing campaign, including 7-Eleven, Burger King, Comcast, Mountain Dew, and Pontiac.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, Pontiac, how the fuck does that relate to Halo?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can understand the 7-Eleven, because you have that Halo Mountain Dew crap and stuff that you can sell that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, and then maybe Burger King, because it's on their cups and shit, and maybe there's some kids' toys or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Pontiac, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing to... Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you going to hop on the bandwagon?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you really that hard up in selling your cars?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're going to make tanks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Pontiac's getting into the war car building business.
[SPEAKER_04]: But really, would you want a war car made by Pontiac?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that's just like, you know, this is my Volkswagen killing machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, because remember, Volkswagen wouldn't lend their likenesses for that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd buy the Volkswagen one before I'd buy a Ford one, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Found on road dead.
[SPEAKER_03]: The fix-off and repair daily.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they release like a Covenant car and a Spartan car that you can have the fucking Halo fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to fucking kill you in my Spartan car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's better than your Covenant car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I'm driving a Pontiac.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're both losers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd buy a Pontiac if they put guns in the front of it so I can shoot people who get in my way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I wanted to say about this, how is Halo 3 tied into the Comcast thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we didn't get a baby shit green cable box.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's why.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to have videos on their Comcast on-demand service, the service that I never use ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to have that on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they even going to bother and do it next game?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it justifies them raising the rates on their cable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, thank you!
[SPEAKER_04]: I get Halo exclusive content!
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're raising my rates and they're $5!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, Comcast!
[SPEAKER_05]: Boof.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I could just imagine my roommate's reaction if, you know, because it was bad enough when they only offered him the $20 discount for wasting his whole day and then, like, fucking up his total order.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could just imagine if the thing had been, you know, oh, well, we're really sorry about the inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's some free Halo 3 trailers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_03]: Joy plus rapture equals no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm not surprised about the whole pre-order record-breaking thing, because like what you said, the whole 7-Eleven tie-ins, like we talked about last week, how you can pre-order Halo 3 at 7-Eleven now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then just the fact that, you know, many, many stores whore their pre-orderings now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've all taken a page from GameStop, and of course GameStop's still king of their game every time somebody comes in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you want to reserve Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I see you're buying Bratz for the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, hey, you want to buy Madden from us?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll give you a free mini poster.
[SPEAKER_04]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like Madden.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck off!
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I've been hearing about nothing but Madden lately.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just bought Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you want to pre-order Halo 3?
[SPEAKER_03]: Every time I call Dan's store, it's like, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, reserve Madden.
[SPEAKER_03]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: I can imagine walking into GameStop, yes, I'm here to reserve Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, great!
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you like to reserve Halo 4 while you're at it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if anyone, if they should have partnered up with a car dealership or a car company, it should have been, like, the fucking Hummer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because at least that's the size of the Warthog, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: A Humvee.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Humvee, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other thing I'm kind of curious about with all this is...
[SPEAKER_05]: I know what I wanted to say earlier that I couldn't think of.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think one of the worst trends in retail across the board that I've seen now is fake boxes to try to get you to pre-order the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll be walking down Best Buy and go, oh, I didn't know this game was out, and you reach for it and you grab it, and then it's like, oh, a little sticker.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pre-order.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, and it's a horrible, horrible trick that I always fall for.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last summer, they had Madden 08 already in GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kid you not.
[SPEAKER_04]: They made up their own box art so you can pre-order Madden 08.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was literally weeks after Madden 07 came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tigerclaw says, Sky, I went to GameStop on Saturday and one of the employees, for some bizarre reason, was wearing a cardboard box over his head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did it say pre-order Halo 3 on the top, maybe?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the other thing, do we really need press releases that go out when your game's put out?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the fastest selling game ever!
[SPEAKER_04]: Until the next game comes out and then it'll sell more.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Everyone knew Halo 3 was in existence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, let's move on off the Halo 3 talk, because there's plenty of other things on the Xbox 360 people are looking forward to, including the next round of Xbox Live Arcade games, and there's a lot of games slated to be coming out over the next couple months, including the much-anticipated Hexic 2, also Echo the Dolphin, War World, Geon Emotions, Puzzle Quest, yay, Space Giraffe,
[SPEAKER_05]: Streets of Rage 2, and of course Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo HD Remix
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually very much looking forward to that game
[SPEAKER_05]: Could be interesting, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of what I thought when I read that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, so they want you to make more power gems?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, okay, Drenami, you don't use Dan unless you think that you're like God's gift to Puzzle Fighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or if you want to have a really hilarious Dan versus Dan match.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because he does nothing but drop red blocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, the chat room is daring to correct me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hitstun says, there's an X dash mode with the new drop patterns, but there's also the original X mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a label of Penny Arcade Adventures Episode 1 on the Rainslick Precipice of Darkness to be out in the fall.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one surprised me at all because there's already Penny Arcade content on Xbox Live and has been for a long, long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you can get themes and little clip arts or the little gamer pictures and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope it's amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it's anything less than amazing, I'll be like, well, crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll probably download it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it wouldn't surprise me at all if there ended up being a Penny Arcade game on the marketplace because Microsoft's kind of like that lately is that they're really trying to get into those fan communities and the thing that the internet's all abuzz about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft wants a part of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's nothing actually confirmed yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: All they'd have to do is throw money at them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Money is what moves the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool!
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to get Madden on the Atari.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want it on the Turbo Duo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you seen the Simpsons game trailer?
[SPEAKER_04]: It actually has that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says, coming out for all game systems, and it shows the Coleco, Atari, Intellivision, Jaguar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, they should put it out on those systems.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so no, it is coming out on most everything, I think, except for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, if you're not into Madden, on PlayStation 2, Shin Megami Tensei Persona 3,
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I brought my copy for you so you can try it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, let's see, Metropolis Mania 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's also coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, Fatal Fury Battle Archives Volume 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: On PSP, Dungeons & Dragons Tactics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ghost Recon... Oh, no, that's next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, other than that... Oh, DS!
[SPEAKER_04]: DS, there's some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, Luminous Ark, that's supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rune Factory, a fantasy Harvest Moon.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many Harvest Moon games will come out this year?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heroes of Mana, that's supposed to be actually pretty good on the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Operation Vietnam, and High School Musical...
[SPEAKER_04]: Making the cut.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Madden or nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well I'm out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was Nerf or nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm heading over to the Japanese release dates, and I'm here to tell you there's not a goddamn thing worth noting coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely nothing coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, if you happen to live in Korea, you're getting some of the same things we are.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're also getting Persona 3 on the PlayStation 2, but otherwise, it's a very slow week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing of note.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I guess there's a couple small titles, but nothing worth mentioning, honestly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, slow week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, it's about the same.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm over in the UK right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Premier Manager 08, and Two Worlds.
[SPEAKER_05]: Slow times.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, lucky people getting Blue Dragon on the 24th.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we are, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hey, we get something at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're getting Blazing Angels later, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is just the calm before the storm right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: August is always the slow period, so we're going to start seeing things really pick up very soon here, like Blue Dragon, Metroid Prime 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we get into next month and the Halo, everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a mess.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a to-be-announced on here for Final Fantasy XII International Zodiac Job System.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need to get a date on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that already came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out in Japan, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was last week's releases in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's sating, pending for the UK, but nothing specific.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish it would come out over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't they put out a press release saying that's the crappiest title for a game, or a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheRobD would like to say August ain't slow this year because you're getting a Bioshock and Madden and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, I know, but I'm saying like, you know, that's all towards the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoa, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to play Blue Dragon and Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not Blue Dragon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, just because you guys are anti-Madden.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still a slow month, even though those games are coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so Bioshock, that's coming out next week, in the week of the 21st, and, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: So basically you're saying the problem with this month is that you just have these few A-list titles kind of tent-pulling us through the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not a lot of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bioshock's next week, and then the week after that you've got the Blue Dragon, Metroid Prime 3, Stuntman Ignition, Tiger Woods 08, and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's pretty much it for the rest of the month.
[SPEAKER_04]: September is crazy, and then beyond that it's just... I don't even want to... I fear November.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, Blue Dragon's the only one out of that list that I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not as looking forward to Metroid Prime 3 as you might think.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was very, very, very disappointed that Nintendo did not decide to go online multiplayer with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need a Metroid Metroid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like old school Metroid?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we get them on virtual console.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next week, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need an actual new Metroid game.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Metroid Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Metroid Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: We love Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's Metroid Prime 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want a 2D?
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to be specific.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want a 2D Metroid on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want a 2D Metroid on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or like, you know how the Sega Ages Fantasy Zone is with the 3D, 2D look?
[SPEAKER_03]: You need something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you heard, but there's rumors going around saying that Castlevania Aria of Sorrow is going to be shown at Let's Big on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so if it's on the PC, then it could ideally come to consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was the Game Boy Advance one, so... Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go ahead and move on and get back into some news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anywho, so we were talking a little bit earlier about firmware updates for the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the Wii couldn't be left out, so they decided to update to version 3, which you get some spiffy shit with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, nothing major like the Check Me Out channel or anything like that, but you get a wonderful digital clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the forecast channel now displays the current condition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yet it doesn't display the temperature.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the current condition is still, like, I'll boot up my Wii at like 4 o'clock in the evening and it shows a picture of a moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: The message board now has today's accomplishments message as a white message which will allow it to stand out from other messages.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still hate those today's accomplishment things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Address book can now be shifted around using A and B. Calendar no longer shows today's accomplishments.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scrolling messages in the Wii message board now use a different sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess in the Wii Shop channel, they've got some other stuff you can search by category, publisher, genre.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you still can't look at videos within the Wii Shop channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to go onto the internet to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, of course, you know, there's some settings, I guess, warning added to pre-system update detailing that technically modified consoles may cease to function.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we break your mod chips!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: GameCubeGames.com
[SPEAKER_05]: One other thing that should be said is the Wii system update also made the USB keyboards now start working.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually plug in a USB keyboard into the back of the Wii and you can use your keyboard for the message board messages.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can use it to type in some things.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can use it when you're writing questions for everybody votes or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can also do the internet channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, you can't use it in the shop channel to search.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I don't know what that's about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you use it in the internet channel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I thought you couldn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm pretty sure you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll have to try it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought a USB keyboard for Final Fantasy XI for the 360 and then I stopped playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I have one sitting out there that I don't really use.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it glows blue.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still had one from when I played Blue Burst.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or I should just say Fantasy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: At any rate, there's other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I screwed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually you can't use it to do any of that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can only use the keyboard for the message board messages.
[SPEAKER_05]: I screwed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a can't on the Internet channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's what I get for not testing it myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just not kind of interested in that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, why would I use the Wii to surf the Internet when I have a computer five steps away that can do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people, I guess, want everything to do everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like having one thing that does one thing and another thing that does another thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, anyway, for anyone who has actually been keeping up with Super Mario Galaxy, there has been a few screenshots put in Famitsu showing that there is a desert world and a haunted house.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we get our buddy Boo coming back.
[SPEAKER_04]: A desert world and a haunted house in a Mario game?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's completely new!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I lost interest in Mario Sunshine about halfway through it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Super Mario Galaxy will be coming out later this year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I want it to actually keep my attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, some other interesting stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a patent found online for a motion sensing portable, or at least something for a portable system to sense directional movements on all different axes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, a six-axis built into a Game Boy Advance type thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, maybe something in the future to be added to...
[SPEAKER_04]: The DS, new handheld console, who knows If I were to guess, I would say that maybe something to plug into the Game Boy Advance Or actually the DS, the Game Boy Advance slot To use that actually as a controller for different games Because the DS, it can connect to the Wii So might as well add some tilt sensing to it as well
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I hope they're not putting out another portable system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they will.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they'll call the Game Boy something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they'll be like, ha, you get to buy it again, bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Part of me kind of hopes that they're doing this so that nobody else will.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, maybe they're doing one of those, like, what is it, the company that keeps filing the patents on the... Immersion?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, like they're doing one of those type of patents where they're just doing it before anyone else can think of it because of the success of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hope not.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meanwhile, for the Nintendo consoles, as we mentioned earlier, Metroid and Super Metroid have been confirmed that they are on their way to the virtual console a little later this month, leading up to, of course, the release of Metroid Prime 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: All this can be found in the new Metroid Prime 3 preview channel, which you can download for the Wii, which I tried to do, but it wouldn't work.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got like three download arrows in a row, so I was like, forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you check out the Metroid Prime 3 preview channel?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drew Nami says, it's cool, but it's YouTube, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can't get an accurate portrayal of what the game looks like with something like YouTube graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for someone to modify that channel because I'm sure that whatever it's streaming is probably off the internet and not on your console.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that would be pretty cool to change the DNS in it or something to stream video off of other things so you could actually turn it into not really YouTube, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, tell the kids where they should be pointing their web browsers this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Today's website of the week is really a result of wishful thinking on my part.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's ferretsunlimited.org.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's basically a shelter for ferrets.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have adoption services.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're actually in Ohio.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the good thing about this site is it also has information about needs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has links to other shelters, how to shop.
[SPEAKER_03]: How to take care of your ferret and a bunch of links.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm working on trying to eventually have a ferret baby myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though they're still illegal to own in California, aren't they?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not if somebody brings them from out of state.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to smuggle in a ferret in California?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to smuggle in a ferret, hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You probably wouldn't be the first one to do it, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: And on top of that, there's a few other sites out there on the internet that tell you where in California has a list of vets who will take care of your ferrets and not turn you in.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I think that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or even better, that they still sell the crap for ferrets at, like, the store, but... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, even though they're not allowed over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ferrets are the best pets ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: As much as I love my cat, I really want a ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, what's going to happen when you have a cat and a ferret?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they going to chase each other around the house?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, well, I'd love for Shermie to get chased around the house, that big fat animal.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, my cat is intensely obese, and she's lazy, and I can't even chase her around the house.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's like, oh, it's just mom.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll just step on me, and then I'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dar Tetsuya says in chat room, chat.orangemonstrator.com, Rob Roberts reminding you to help control the ferret population.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have your ferret spayed or neutered.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: and RossDLUT asks a good question.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually don't know the answer to it, but I'm assuming you do, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why the fuck are ferrets illegal in California?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's... Okay, I don't know the entire thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually haven't seen anything legitimate about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're talking about some problem with certain breeds of them being endangered and with having this...
[SPEAKER_03]: Wild Ferret Population from Strays.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you why.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's because of Beastmaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they don't want another one of those crappy movies made in California, so... No ferrets, no Beastmaster sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: My friend... Before I moved out here, my friend was... At least not another sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: My friend was going to give me his ferrets, and their names were Koto and Poto.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm on Wikipedia, of course, to find the answer to this question.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm on ferretnews.org.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in the ferret article, it cites this reference, the Fish and Game Code of California, and what it says, quote, animals of the families Vivuridae, I'm sorry, I'm totally mispronouncing these, and Mustelidae, which I'm assuming the ferrets belong to, in the order Carnivora are restricted because such animals are undesirable and a menace to native wildlife, the agricultural interest of the state...
[SPEAKER_05]: or to the public health or safety.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but then you're going to get those stupid people that let the ferrets run loose outdoors like a fucking cat and it's going to kill things and screw up the ecosystem.
[SPEAKER_02]: A cat can take a ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know that ferrets shouldn't be outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally oblivious to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, you know, they ruin it for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why we're talking about ferrets on a video game show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have ferrets, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: A ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: The ferret's in the box somewhere right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't have a ferret in the studio yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But no, I really, really, really, really want a ferret.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm working on trying to get my significant other to agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I really, really want to get back into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to answer, son of dad ferrets live anywhere between 10 to 15 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I guess a decent game for the iPod.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw in chat has a great point.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no ferret video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's fix that!
[SPEAKER_05]: Has there ever been a ferret video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: In existence, has a ferret even been a character in a video game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Beastmaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: I cannot... Besides Beastmaster...
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't think of anything where a... This is a travesty!
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX16, Ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: No!
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to have a game... Okay, now that's... 2DX Troopers, that's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's put that up on the Orange Lounge Radio Xbox Live Arcade wish list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we have Laser Cats, the game, and now we have Ferret, the video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: What, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, there has been a ferret video game for the Game Boy Color created by Culture Brain.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Ferret Monogatari Watashi no Okini Iri.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, Ferret Story, My Dear Ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Japanese-only video game that's a simulation-style game where you take care of a ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the start of the game, choose one of three different colored ferrets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Colors are randomly chosen.
[SPEAKER_04]: The ferret is kept in the cage a bunch of the time, but you have to keep his water and food topped off and clean its litter box.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can take the ferret out for walks or to play with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also even play minigames.
[SPEAKER_04]: One is a race, one is putting together a picture, and the other is dancing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and just like Nintendogs, the game gets fucking boring after playing it for an hour.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting the ferret game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got a lot of comments in chat here on the ferret game.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100Matt says, There's a ferret-like creature in Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really a ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: TheRobD says, Was there a ferret in Bible Adventures or in Super 3D Noah's Ark?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably not because ferrets are unclean.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not God's animals.
So...
[SPEAKER_05]: They weren't allowed on the Ark.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like lice.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think Noah took lice on the Ark.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: The lice were in their hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't have rid back in the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's a bastard anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't vote for him.
[SPEAKER_05]: I voted for Gary Coleman.
[SPEAKER_05]: I voted for Mary Carey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bandit says there was a ferret in a video game called Penguin Wars for the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would a ferret be in a penguin game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please put the show back on track if you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's this news website that has a character that they talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a video game news site.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Toothpick the Ferret.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has a giant cloud sword.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Music Cuts, Parappa the Rapper
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's a game that's basically a musical music visualizer game more background I guess than anything and I guess when the game creates visuals based on the titles of your songs and then asks players to tap the center button in time with each letter of the name and you get points for doing that and build up your combo yada yada yada so if you were interested in buying it it's $4.99 on the iTunes store
[SPEAKER_05]: I might have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw, I hate to go back to the ferret thing, but the chat room just won't shut up about it, which is what I love about having a chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: HitStun says, Hotaru Fukuba from Garou Mark of the Wolves had a yellow ferret.
[SPEAKER_03]: I found the game online, but it's a Flash game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see what else is there.
[SPEAKER_05]: TigerClaw says, if Nintendo or Sega is listening, they have a potential franchise if they create Sonic the Hedgehog type game starring a ferret.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_05]: Beatmania 2DX
[SPEAKER_05]: Beatmania, now in 2DX, and it's 15th in creation, is now being location tested.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called DJ Troopers, is the new theme.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of a silly name, but of course, a lot of people thought Red and Happy Sky were dumb names too, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy Sky made sense, at least it was very, you know, English-y.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, DJ Troopers, I give it a chance, because it's kind of green, like camo colors are kind of green, so that's one color they haven't really done yet, so, I give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the cutest thing ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beatmania 2 DX has not really changed a whole lot over the past few games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, little subtle changes here and there, but the game itself hasn't changed a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it has been location tested, or is going through location tests in Tokyo right now, and some of the songs are sneaking out.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a new song from Chorus K called Evergreen, a new song from Akira Yamaoka called Shift.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a techno song, should be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another remix of A is in the game, which should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: New songs, of course, are green colored in the song list.
[SPEAKER_05]: The five keys modifier now uses keys three through seven instead of one through five when playing on the two player side, which is kind of a different type of change there for those that like to play five key mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a song called Deep Strikers.
[SPEAKER_05]: has 1,528 notes on Hyper and is a 12 rated song on Double Hyper.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: They got rid of a bunch of songs, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bag is finally no longer in 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But also sad, Diamond Jealousy is also gone finally.
[SPEAKER_01]: Boo!
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure we'll be hearing more about this on your favorite music gaming website as the week goes on and more stuff comes out of Location Test.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure YouTubes are coming far behind.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have some happy that I hope would be something that happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: There is actually a hint about there being a downloadable sequel on PSN for Parappa.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would just be so happy to have more Parappa.
[SPEAKER_03]: But right now it's in rumor phase.
[SPEAKER_03]: The creator of Parappa the Rapper just sort of talked about it, not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: He said, oh yeah, let's just do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck Parappa, I want Umjama Lammy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: How come we always hear about Parappa this, Parappa that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Parappa remake, Parappa going to be on the PlayStation Network maybe, but there ain't shit about Umjamalami.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need Umjam or Death Metal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or what was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: There was Umjamalami and then Rami was her friend, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rami was her opposite.
[SPEAKER_03]: I still think it sucks because I wanted the hell level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Instead they put him on an island.
[SPEAKER_05]: and RustyLUT theorizes maybe it's because Unjamalami sucked, but that would be a lie because Unjamalami was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I failed to see your logic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you have it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I suppose, though, if the Parappa thing did come out for the PlayStation Network and it sold like crazy, maybe we could convince them to do an Unjamalami song in-game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyhow, that's going to bring this segment of Orange Lounge Radio to a close, but we will be back with Part B right after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and is podcast to the world twice a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stay tuned to our podcast feed for the conclusion of this week's Orange Lounge Radio.