[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly To listen to the first half of this episode visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently the tokens that you can earn in the game are in four different tiers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red, blue, green, and gold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red tokens are gained by scanning enemies and items.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blue for scanning lore and completing side quests.
[SPEAKER_08]: Green ones you get from friends.
[SPEAKER_08]: And gold is achieved from defeating bosses on various difficulties.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is different from this and like the trophies that you earn in Burnout?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what is so noteworthy about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it the fact that it's the first time in a Metroid game?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess people are thinking, oh my god, achievements are coming!
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well one other thing that people would like to see coming to the Wii any day now is online play.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and on it are some different types of questions on it and they seem to point towards the all signs you could say point to the fact that they're at least exploring the possibility of doing downloadable demos of course to date all we've really seen come from them would be the Metroid Prime 3 preview channel
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the things here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Please indicate your level of interest in playable demo versions of Wii games.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is your preferred method of receiving Wii game demos?
[SPEAKER_10]: Would you be willing to pay more for your subscription in order to receive Wii game demos?
[SPEAKER_10]: So, kind of interesting there.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be kind of cool if Nintendo Power did have Wii game demos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the other big three consoles do for their magazines.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I would like to see the Wii actually able to download things other than virtual console titles.
[SPEAKER_08]: and a few crappy tales.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they're supposed to have original software.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least we know about that Mission Impossible thing, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, they're supposed to go online someday, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: The console's been out for almost a year now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Time to start following through with that shit you've been promising us for a while now.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or we're going to have to start calling you Sony.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, burn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, how about some happy Nintendo news?
[SPEAKER_11]: How does that sound?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, guess what is back for Super Mario Galaxy?
[SPEAKER_11]: We have fire flowers and superstars.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love the fire flowers so much because they're like burning things.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're just happy that Mario can set fire to things again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know, the fire flower was such a great weapon and then we just didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had him squirt shit with water.
[SPEAKER_10]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mario 64 Mario 64 Mario 64 Mario 64
[SPEAKER_11]: I liked it on Nintendo because they totally recreated the Super Nintendo graphics on the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to chat room for some comments at chat.orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: RossDLUT says, Loki, stop wishing and relying on Nintendo's word.
[SPEAKER_10]: ShadowCharlie says, Tanooki suit.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be a great thing to come back.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no, Hammer Brothers suit.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or the Kuriboh's boot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Kuriboh's shoe.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that was it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But in other news, we do have a release date for the UK on this.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will be November 16th.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not soon enough, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not soon enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do want to know who this new hoochie in the game is, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, interesting news, and we knew this was kind of coming, but finally the Wii has passed
[SPEAKER_08]: The Xbox 360 in worldwide sales.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, the last screenshot that we've seen of this was of course a few days ago with the Wii having approximately 10.57 million units worldwide and the Xbox 360 having 10.51 million units.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, the PS3 still trailing behind with 4.32 million units.
[SPEAKER_08]: It should be known though that still the 360 is outselling
[SPEAKER_08]: The Wii in the US, but apparently, you know, Japan is where they're making up for a lot of slack.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, what does this mean for Nintendo fanboys?
[SPEAKER_10]: Is this something additional for them to brag about, or is this really not the big deal, it seems like?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it's fuel for, you know, flame fodder, I guess, because the Wii has basically caught up to the 360 in half the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think if they could produce more units, it would be even higher.
[SPEAKER_08]: But hopefully that means more support.
[SPEAKER_08]: Better games!
[SPEAKER_10]: XBOX 360 XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_10]: That means it's not going to be on shelves for the day after Thanksgiving madness, so that's kind of too bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm sure those people that have been very good boys and girls this year as they put this on their Christmas list, I'm sure Santa will find a way, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, then again, if you believe in Santa, you probably should not be playing Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come to think of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why does Santa die in it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_11]: For anyone who is at Penny Arcade Expo, they did confirm that Penny Arcade Adventures on the Rainslick Precipice of Darkness is going to be on an Xbox Live Arcade in 2008.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was also announced for PC, Mac OS X, and Linux.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, hey, game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that the console you guys would have guessed that this was going to be released on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: I sort of thought so, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just because, you know, there's the... For a long time now, there's been the little picture icons and themes and all that stuff that you can download on Xbox Live, so why not this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not now their game on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: If there's more money to be done, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, putting arcade adventures isn't the only thing coming to Xbox Live soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a rumor, of course, with the fall update due out in November, that it's possibly going to include XFID support.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, some other plans from this leaked list.
[SPEAKER_08]: Supposedly a new Xbox Live Arcade Blade, IPTV support, integrated clan functionality, a picture-in-picture setting, and improved slideshow effects.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be pretty awesome if it had Xvid codec support.
[SPEAKER_08]: What exactly is Xvid?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of like DivX.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a video codec for encoding MPEG-4 video so that you can rip a DVD and have it be a decent file size.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty popular.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you would still have to stream it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm saying you still have to have it in WMV format, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would imagine you would, but who knows.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony is also not going to E for All
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also some other companies that have said they're not going, including Capcom and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some companies that are going, though, would be Nintendo and Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's not like it's going to be an empty show, but it is going to be a little bit of a bummer that you don't have two of the big three showing up at E!
[SPEAKER_10]: For All.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't know about you guys, but the fact that I'm actually kind of planning on going to E!
[SPEAKER_10]: For All, because, you know, I got an invite and everything, and I was planning the trip to go to L.A., I'm a little bit irritated that some of these companies are dropping out of E!
[SPEAKER_10]: For All.
[SPEAKER_10]: That news makes me a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_10]: and when we get angsty, people die.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, and the FUs of the week come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, DarkSakura, why don't you start us off with tonight's FUs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, FU to my broken head.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really, it still hurts.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, it happened, what, four hours ago?
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's not four.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why am I saying four?
[SPEAKER_11]: Three hours, two hours, whatever, ago, and it still hurts.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a secondary FU goes toward the art block, because I've been trying to draw, and it's just not working.
[SPEAKER_10]: So instead of writer's block, it's art block.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's art block.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I've been having a bit of writer's block, too, just in different capacities.
[SPEAKER_10]: So FU to blocks of all shapes and sizes.
[SPEAKER_11]: To the block of creativity.
[SPEAKER_11]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, your FU's of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: My F.U.s of the week go to my cat for constantly waking me up in the middle of the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's almost like having a goddamn baby, so... Fuck you to the cat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just imagine when you really have a baby.
[SPEAKER_10]: Imagine babies in your house.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's not really fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't really have a lot to say F.U.
[SPEAKER_10]: to this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've actually had a pretty good week, so F.U.
[SPEAKER_10]: to people who don't like caramel, because caramel ice cream is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then again, maybe I shouldn't say F.U.
[SPEAKER_10]: to that, because that just means more for me
[SPEAKER_10]: Right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mikotov, do you have any FUs of the week while you're staring off into space over there?
[SPEAKER_06]: FU to you for thinking about getting Popsicles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they are the worst.
[SPEAKER_10]: Popsicles are awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the thing though, Mikotov.
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't that I was going to buy Popsicles.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to buy Creamsicles.
[SPEAKER_10]: And those are awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's end this segment now, shall we?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are either of you guys, is anybody else in here thinking of going to E4ALL?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to go, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't excite me as much anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd rather go to PAX, but that's kind of late for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little bit over now.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's in it for you to see at E4ALL?
[SPEAKER_06]: I like Nintendo and Konami, and that's really all I remember that are actually going.
[SPEAKER_06]: But not having E3 to go to this year and going to Comic-Con made me realize that I kind of miss stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So going to E4ALL would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get back to some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now that the FUs of the week are over.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, you know, it was bound to happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: For our buddies overseas, the Xbox 360 is getting a price drop in Europe, occurring on the 24th of August.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will be decreasing by 20 pounds on the core unit and 30 on the 20 gigabyte 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it'll bring the price down respectively to $249.99.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, that's on the 20 gig and $179.99 on the core.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's again in British pounds.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the Elite will retail for $299.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, I just gotta say real quickly for the live folks, it looks like our stream is down, and I'm blaming Operator 11 for that, so at this time I'm gonna shut this off until we can work on this some other time, because this is probably taking a lot of bandwidth, so we're gonna have to get rid of this to get our stream back, so that's the end of the Op 11 simulcast for now, until we can work on that a little later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, but in the meantime, we will go back to... There was more news on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shizzle Games of Belgium was advertising by price from Elite down to Core in Euros as $449, $349, and $279 on their SKUs.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I should know my apologies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Their Core was being called the Arcade, and then they have the Pro.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very bizarre, but anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is kind of bizarre.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's even more bizarre that they're called Shizzle Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shizzle Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the rumor, of course, of that new arcade SKU for the core system is actually supposed to be coming to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: as well, and same details, no definite launch date or anything like that, but it is allegedly supposed to come out over here as well, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, hey, the core system's not bad, but I know a lot of people complain that they can't save their game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now that that's going to be coming with a memory unit, that might be something to actually look into if you're not into the whole live downloading thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I bet you can't spell Maneuver.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura likes to surf the internet up and down and all around every single week and she likes to find a website that works for all of you and it's her website of the week that she's going to share with you guys right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Website of the week is actually suggested to me by Loki, and it's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Cult of Rapture.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you go to 2kgames.com slash cultofrapture, all one word, it will take you to a Bioshock page for the fans, I guess, talking about the music that's out.
[SPEAKER_11]: It has downloads, articles, a forum, goodies for everybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's actually very, very pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I do believe that you have to be over 18 to view the page.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, go see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'll be posting the address into the chat room presently.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: something else that's pretty awesome fans of Geometry Wars will be quite happy because with Project Gotham Racing 4 they'll be getting a brand new Geometry Wars game and no info though on it's supposed to be not too different than Retro Evolved but it is going to be a little bit different it's called Geometry War Waves so no real details though on what exactly is different but apparently not that much
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't know what's going to change in the great amount of time it's going to take for this game to come out, because Spore is apparently finished.
[SPEAKER_10]: The game is not totally finished and ready to go, but apparently the game is complete.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is coming from reports of people who have had hands-on with Spore at Leipzig.
[SPEAKER_10]: EA is simply going to be spending the next few months listening to feedback from players, assuming the QA testers and beta testers, to tweak and polish Spore for its final release, which is still set for next spring.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, certainly you can look around the internet on some different blogs there and find some hands-on reports from Spore, which is definitely a game I am certainly looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, GS68 in our chatroom says, Spore forever?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think you can make those jokes anymore because it does look like this game is actually going to come out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_10]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, it's time for an old favorite segment of ours here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a segment we like to call Listless.
[SPEAKER_10]: Listless.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: The way Listless works is that we create a list here.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're trying to define the definitive top three of a certain category.
[SPEAKER_10]: And tonight's category is character we would most like to see in the upcoming track and field DS game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, the character does not have to be a Konami character, but it helps.
[SPEAKER_10]: So here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to go around, and myself, Loki, DarkSakura, and Miklatov will all give their top three.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's going to leave us with a list of 12.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then we will all go around the room and take one unworthy candidate off the list, leaving a list of eight.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we will post that list of eight to the chat room, and you'll vote for your number one and your number two picks.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll tally them up, and the winning votes will be revealed a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how Listless works.
[SPEAKER_10]: So who's going to start us off tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, you ready to go?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, what's your number three pick for character you would most like to see in Track and Field?
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess it'd be a little weird, but I would like to see... Actually, this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Babylon from DDR5thMix.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, Babylon from DDR5thMix.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Just so you can run as a baby?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's a baby running.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Babylon says Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Miklatov, do you have a number three pick?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll take Robbie the Rabbit from Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's cuter than a bunny with blood on its mouth running around throwing stuff like javelins and things?
[SPEAKER_11]: We're already picking just Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't have to pick Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: I said it doesn't have to be Konami, but it helps.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it should be Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: The real game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it could be Nintendo because it's DS5.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's leave it to Konami.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to rethink my list.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aitsu or Koitsu from Parodius.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're the little stickmen riding paper airplanes.
[SPEAKER_10]: How the crap do you spell that?
[SPEAKER_11]: A-I-T-S-U and then K-O-I-T-S-U.
[SPEAKER_10]: From Parodius.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, my number three pick would also come from DDR, and that would be Alice, the little raving character.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know what you would really call it, the dog from Silent Hill 2, from the dog ending.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love the dog.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the dog from the dog ending of Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mikotov, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to say Evil Rose from Rumble Roses.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because what little boy doesn't want to watch the girls with the big breasts run around on the track?
[SPEAKER_06]: Except for sane ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so one of the big tittied girls from Rumble Roses will hopefully appear in Track and Field.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, she can't run.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, DarkSakura, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_11]: My number two pick is going to be Pit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pit, for now a Nintendo character.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, Pit from Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except he can fly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Couldn't that be cheating?
[SPEAKER_11]: So can Aitsu and Koisu.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Number two pick for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: My number two pick I would like to see in the game would be Dracula.
[SPEAKER_10]: from, you know, the Castlevania games.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: And then somebody can come out and say... Not by my hand.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was once again given a gold medal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Die, monster.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't belong in this world.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except that was the other guy that said that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I still think it would be cool if Dracula was in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Dracula is my number two pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Number one pick, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Number one pick, I will say... Well, that doesn't really count because that's Hudson.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, no, that could work, because Konami has license over Hudson Games now, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can do Hudson.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if this would be my number one pick, but Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, because maybe Bomberman could just leave bombs on the track, yes?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: That'll work.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever you say, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Miklatov, what would be your number one pick?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Left DDR Arrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: My number one pick is the mascot from Guitar Freak.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's needed with the bag over his head?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember his name.
[SPEAKER_10]: My number one pick did not get a lot of coverage in a lot of the various Konami games that existed out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, my number one pick was really obscure because he was only in one game that Konami ever put out, and it was on the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'll tell you what, if you've been listening to this show for some amount of time, then you know the love that the people of this program have.
[SPEAKER_10]: My runner-up would be the Konami Code.
[SPEAKER_11]: Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A, start.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have the Konami code in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I should have said the little shit from Parodius because then you can have the Sound Blaster or Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what also amazes me about this list is that not a single damn Metal Gear character on the whole list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Change Baghead Guy to Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twinbee?
[SPEAKER_11]: To Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like the Baghead Guy better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, she changed it then.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_11]: SSJ100, Matt voted for the goalie from Blazer Steel.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, here's the list of stands right now, but remember we're going around and eliminating off the list here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Babylon, Robbie the Rabbit, Aitsu Kwaitsu, Alice, the dog from the dog ending of Silent Hill 2, Evil Rose, Pit, Dracula, Bomberman, the left DDR arrow, Twinbee, and Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why left and not right, just out of curiosity?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's just the first one I thought of.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, one of these is not worthy of being on the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is not worthy of being on the list?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to say Aitsu, Koitsu, because I have no idea what the hell that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very obscure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was a little too obscure for my taste.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they're awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Miklatov, one of these is not worthy of being on the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is not worthy of being on the list?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because it really looks out of place on that list, I'm going to...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to throw out Pit, even though I love Kid Icarus a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, DarkSakura, what is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to vote for Alice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alice is not worthy of being on the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Raver Kids Everywhere are crying.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that movie about?
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you seen Alice from Supernova 2 yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: She's all dressed up like an Indian.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: The one I deem worthy of not being on the list is... Oh, this is hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm also going to take out a DDR character and say Babylon is not worthy of being on the list.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: That leaves our list as Robbie the Rabbit, The Dog from the Dog Ending of Silent Hill 2, Evil Rose, Dracula, Bomberman, The Left DDR Arrow, Twinbee, and Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so I'm going to post that there in the chat room, and if you would, send a private message to Rob Roberts, not Sky tonight because I don't have my normal name.
[SPEAKER_10]: set a private message with your number one and number two pick it is important what you designate as one and two if you do not designate I will assume your first pick is your number one so there you have it
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you find anything else that you thought should have been on the list, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I saw you searching Wikipedia frantically.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was trying to think whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember what the boss was called in Contra.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like the giant heart.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was thinking the giant alien head thing would have been pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: What about the vomiting baby turtle thing or whatever that was from like...
[SPEAKER_10]: Aw, we should have more time to prepare.
[SPEAKER_10]: Violent, uh, vomiting baby turtle would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: An unsold copy of, what was it, Bomberman Act Zero.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was actually thinking, cause you know, I was thinking really obscure.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, if we were going Sega, I'd totally say the, uh, the Opa Opa.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we didn't go Sega.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, we didn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: We sure didn't.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the Opa Opa would kill everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the Opa Opa's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: We will announce the winners a wee bit later, but for now, we've got to get back into some news, and then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Your calls at Orange Lounge Radio, username on Skype, or our 800 number 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll get to those very shortly, but first, a little more news.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, and apparently people were not too happy with Bioshock's way they've handled widescreen.
[SPEAKER_08]: And apparently there are some fixes, though, if you want to correct that.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is a hack that you can download for the PC version, and it will allow you to not necessarily resize your screen, but resize the view on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you can do all sorts of fun things, including different resolution sizes like 16.9, you know, true 16.9.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because apparently the way this game worked before is they would just kind of do like a reverse pan and scan on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They would cut the top and bottom off on the widescreen.
[SPEAKER_08]: But apparently there's also, I guess, there's going to be a fix coming for Xbox 360 over Live at some point as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: At least that's the rumor.
[SPEAKER_08]: If that's really bothering you, you can go ahead and download the patch, which is available on dl.tokaedit.com slash bioshockdfov.zip
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, out of curiosity, what do you think about that whole fallout about how people were really pissed about all the issues the PC was having, not just the widescreen stuff, but the fact that you could only install so many copies on one machine, and kind of like how quick they've been to respond to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole widescreen thing was stupid, I think, because, I mean, personally...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think anyone noticed it during the demo until someone mentioned, oh hey, by the way, this is like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're all, oh my god, that's horrible!
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it doesn't detract anything from the game, so, big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you can fix it on the PC now, so, I don't know, it's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cop protection thing kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know a lot of people are installing on multiple computers, which I guess technically violates some sort of
[SPEAKER_08]: Writes or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's a fix coming for that as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't think that's a big worry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, little bitty things.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: SSJ100 Matt says, though, Pan and Scan ruins movies.
[SPEAKER_10]: It does.
[SPEAKER_11]: It absolutely does.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's open up our Skype line and hear from you guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to give us a call, the Skype line is now open.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our username is OrangeLoungeRadio on Skype, or you can always give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR is the number to call.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: And while we're waiting for those to come in, I'll just say that this is your last chance to submit your votes for Listless.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think most people in our chat room already voted, but just in case there's a couple stragglers, we'll take those.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Raven Stolfen, the guy that got... Damn, you get through first every time.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, what's on your mind, Raven Stolfen?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a fast finger and a new keyboard.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll leave the fast finger comment as is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Lame, mean finger.
[SPEAKER_00]: My comment tonight is you mentioned that Nintendo surpassed the 360?
[SPEAKER_00]: In terms of worldwide sales, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you know, I know this is going to turn into a flame world real fast and real quick, so I'll try to keep the flames to a minimum.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, I believe that people that buy in the Wii is not us hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like, we bought it, I bought it, you bought it, Loki bought it, DarkSakura bought it, but those soccer moms of the world.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I totally agree with you, but a sale's a sale, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: A sale's a sale.
[SPEAKER_10]: Money's money, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: The bottom line is a dollar.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, I will say this, what I would be curious to see...
[SPEAKER_10]: is how many games per system is out there, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like a 360 owner probably has a lot of games at this point, whereas a Wii owner maybe doesn't have so many games.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't know, that may not be true, because then again, you look at the games that are out on the Wii, there's not a lot for hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, there's some, you know, your Super Paper Mario, your Metroid, but there is a lot of crap out there on the Wii, like, you know, your Happy Feets, your, well, I haven't played Boogie, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that commercial really wants me to, I'm memorized about that commercial, Boogie.
[SPEAKER_00]: It almost wants me to buy it, but my mind goes like, don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's junk.
[SPEAKER_00]: Don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't fall for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never seen the commercial, but I don't watch TV.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's it like?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's, they're doing a disco one, and they're like doing the Wii mode.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has nothing to do with the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: No gameplay footage whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_00]: But the commercials, I think it was great.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, I'm like, wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: That looks like fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I smack myself going like, shit, it's not fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they do show you how to actually play the game in the commercial because they do have the Wiimote and the Nunchuck moving back and forth and what I assume is how you're supposed to play that piece of crap game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then I smack myself and then... I can rent it for free.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, renting might be a thing to do.
[SPEAKER_10]: RossDealUT says, Problem is that most people are just buying it as a Wii Sports machine and will never buy anything for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what about Wii Play, though?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because Wii Play's been selling a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: And how come the PlayStation 2 is still selling?
[SPEAKER_10]: Gold Banjo, I think same reason, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gold Banjo says, my little sister sings along during that commercial.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the PlayStation 2 continues to sell because they're A, cheap, and B, there's a shitload of games for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, just massive and massive amounts of games for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_10]: One more thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, one more thing, sir.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, the new release of Bioshock came out, and I was just wondering, do you think this game's going to be buried like Dead Rising when it came out, when the first...
[SPEAKER_00]: Dead Rising is one of those games that everyone loved, played, you know, Loki loved it, I loved it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is Bioshock going to fall under that, like, we love it and we leave it for, like, another game?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to take a very controversial stance here, and I'm going to say yes, it will fall off the radar.
[SPEAKER_10]: Death Rising
[SPEAKER_10]: I think the lack of multiplayer is really going to hurt the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time, I think Bioshock will trump Halo 3 on some end-of-year best list.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I think you may see a small resurgence come the end of the year during award times.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'm just saying that because, you know, this game has, you know, everyone loved it.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, it's like, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: DOOM DOOM DOOM
[SPEAKER_11]: My hand is raised because we were playing it recently.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, okay, so one person on the entire internet is playing it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm the most important person on the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if I look at my friends list, I do not see people playing a lot of the old arcade releases except for a few big, big biggies like Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pac-Man Championship Edition still comes up.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, a couple of those.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Ross Steel UT says lots of people play games and don't go on live.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's true, but I'm using the rationalization that you have to go on live to get the game in the first place unless it was on that arcade unplugged disc.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I truly think that's a minority.
[SPEAKER_00]: One more comment.
[SPEAKER_00]: You would think with a mall that's so big would have more bathrooms.
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Raven's off and we've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: But have a good one, buddy, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: You too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, if you want to give us a call, our number 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Orange Lounge Radio 1-877-GAME-OLR Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, do you have any last minute stories while I change this real quick here?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give us one real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some interesting things coming out about the brand new Brain Age 2 DS, the one that, you know, red and black, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, the LCD screen's a little bit dimmer than the normal DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sucks for people that bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Enter interesting things.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, there was a PSP petition for Resident Evil coming onto the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: It got the attention of Capcom, who says if you get over 10,000 signatures, that will draw significant attention.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now they're up to 17,000 signatures, so maybe we'll see a PSP version of Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on, I fixed Skype, so save the rest for a little later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can you do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: GS68 Game Boy Color Games
[SPEAKER_10]: Black and White Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the big screen TV?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it just wouldn't look good.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would actually like to see them port crappy Metroid 2 from Game Boy onto the virtual console because that game was a pain to play on the original Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think actually playing it on TV would make it a worthwhile experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or how about they do a Metroid All-Stars where they just redesign the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that would be good too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Upgrade the graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and Kid Icarus on Game Boy, even though I'm not sure if it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't really know a lot of good Game Boy games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, there are the games that I grew up with, and that's about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What got you thinking about this?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know, just randomly, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all good.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what would actually be really cool, though, would be, like, even though the DS doesn't play the old, old Game Boy games, it would be kind of cool if, like, there was that functionality between the DS and the Wii a little later on, which we all know there is some functionality there, where maybe you could download a virtual console game from the Game Boy and play it on your DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wouldn't that be kind of neat?
[SPEAKER_01]: If Mr. Spankin wins the list list, I'll make videos of myself killing patients in trauma center.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, so if Mr. Spanky wins Listless, you're going to kill patients in trauma centers and put it on the YouTubes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, we're going to find out very soon what won.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just out of curiosity, can you describe your hatred of Mr. Spanky to the listeners who may not be familiar with the character?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I heard his voice.
[SPEAKER_01]: on a large media presence ago, and, well, I didn't really like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although, you know that wasn't the official voice, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was just some idiot pretending, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am noticing there is no article on Mr. Spanky on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was hoping for some pictures or something, like an article I could refer people to, but there's nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you spell it with an E?
[SPEAKER_10]: I did it both ways.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did it once with an E and once with no E. Yeah, DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDRPC, let me see.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, there's no DDR PC article either.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's just a Dance Dance Revolution main article.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is there no Mr. Spanky article on Wikipedia?
[SPEAKER_10]: He's an important part of the culture.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he's a DDR character.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't really deserve their own Wikipedia articles.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sick of looking.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, no, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Windows PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there's no article for the Windows PC version of Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadness.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you want to share with us, GS68?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, have a good one, GS68.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll talk to you next time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks, you too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hoping one of our Wikipedia faithful will somehow create that Mr. Spanky article.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be all kinds of awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, guys, it's Insanist.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello, Insanist.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you guys know, but that Penny Arcade Expo thing went on, and if you can tell, I have absolutely no voice from being at it all weekend.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Penny Arcade Expo should happen more often.
[SPEAKER_10]: It kills your voice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, fuck you too, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: PENNY ARCADE EXPO
[SPEAKER_10]: I went to the wedding on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_10]: So congratulations, Amanda and Tom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wave, wave, wave, hug.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although I know they don't listen to this program.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they got married, so I had to go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how was Penny Arcade Expo?
[SPEAKER_10]: So you were there.
[SPEAKER_10]: You were our man on the street.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what was really disappointing was Sony really didn't bring much to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, it was something outside of Sony's boot that was for the PlayStation 3, which I gave the unofficial OLR seal of approval.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's this game called Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a collectible card game that works with the PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait a minute, you gave the OLR award to the Eye of Judgment?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: FIRED!
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you played it?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I haven't.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw the tech demo and I was like, why?
[SPEAKER_10]: We did kind of see it at E3, so I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're being completely serious.
[SPEAKER_10]: This game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I won't give it the OLR, I'll give it the STFU.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll leave that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, that's fine, but I'm just curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're absolutely serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game rocked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thoroughly enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a huge CCG fan and obviously I'm a huge video game fan and this was a very good combination of the two.
[SPEAKER_04]: It felt more interactive to me than just putting a piece of cardboard on a table.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could actually see what was going on and I thought the technology was good and it was something different, which I'm always welcome to seeing.
[SPEAKER_04]: The graphics were great.
[SPEAKER_04]: There weren't any glitches with reading the cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had no problem with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And really, Sony didn't bring much else to the table.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, so I get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you're giving the award to Eye of Judgment by default because there were no other games there.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was nothing new from Sony there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: But was Eye of Judgment the best thing you saw on any system?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be getting to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my Wii award goes to Metroid Prime 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game's amazing and you need to all pick it up next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: One, it has the best Wii remote controls I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: The looking is fantastic, the shooting is fantastic, the motion controls are very intuitive and a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I didn't like Prime 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of like Prime 2, the multiplayer mode, but I found first-person Metroid so hard to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: Am I going to suddenly get over it with number 3?
[SPEAKER_10]: Will it bring me back?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it will.
[SPEAKER_04]: The motion controls really make you feel like a part of the game and some of the boss battles are amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to demo the Ridley boss battle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to spoil too much, but it was one of the coolest boss battles I've ever fought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get a rise out of it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes I did, and not down there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did it make you feel excited in a special place?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you have to go back to your hotel room and take care of some business after playing the demo?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because I had to go run tournaments, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so how about your Xbox 360 award?
[SPEAKER_04]: and overall award, Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: No question, this game is amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, I know everybody in the chat room is like, hey, I've played this before.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Guitar Freaks Drum Mania.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you're right, it is Guitar Freaks Drum Mania and Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's with songs that the mainstream people are going to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's going to sell a lot of copies and make Harmonix a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_04]: The interface is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: The controllers are great.
[SPEAKER_04]: The guitars for Rock Band feel like real guitars.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fret buttons are colored on the top of the controller, rather, on the buttons themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's the same layout as guitar here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's my question for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think if Rock Band does well, there'll be a pop band that comes out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know, I like shitty music, and there's just not a lot... I mean, Rock Band actually has a lot of good music in it, but I like shitty music.
[SPEAKER_10]: So is there any hope for me in my love of pop music?
[SPEAKER_04]: If you would have brought me that question, I would have asked the Harmonix guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_04]: But with them releasing Guitar Hero 80s, anything can happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, actually, I honestly wouldn't rule that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, a lot of the songs in Guitar Hero 80s weren't that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I think pop band could very well be a viable idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to comments from the chat room here, Zaku says, Excuse me, sir, but Harmonix fucked up the drums.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nuff said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you used them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wait, you can't respond in time.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're great.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're very responsive.
[SPEAKER_04]: My only beef is the Xbox button is in the way of the rightmost two drums.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn that Xbox button.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that got annoying a couple of times.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw says, Rob, don't give them any ideas.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next thing you know, there will be a game called Boy Band.
[SPEAKER_10]: Miklatov got all excited over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's called SingStar, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it is probably called SingStar.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be so much fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Halo 3 is the final.
[SPEAKER_04]: They showed two new maps.
[SPEAKER_04]: One was called Narrows, which is a hallway with vehicles, and it was a hell of a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: The other one was called Guardian, which looked very base-like and showed off jump pads and elevators and was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some new weapons.
[SPEAKER_04]: A flamethrower will be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fire grenades will be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Spartan laser will be in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this item called the Gravity Hammer, which is the sword on steroids.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: How did Halo 3 look?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because a lot of people complained the beta didn't look that much better.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_04]: It looked very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I was most impressed with was the heads-up display.
[SPEAKER_04]: It got a big overhaul from Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: The shield meter is directly top-center on the screen, so you'll be seeing it at all times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have your weapons and ammo in the upper right corner, and it has icons and the button.
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of saying, press this button to pick up this now.
[SPEAKER_04]: They streamlined it a lot, and I really, really think this will get rid of the disappointment that, at least in my opinion, was Halo 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gold Banjo says, yay fire.
[SPEAKER_10]: GS68, though, asks, any word on the man cannon?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not see a man cannon, but there is a fire cannon that you could...
[SPEAKER_04]: It was mounted, but you could yank it out and run after people with it, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anything else you want to share from Penny Arcade Expo since you were lucky enough to go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Two things.
[SPEAKER_04]: One, the frag doll stole a flowchart about boobs that I made.
[SPEAKER_04]: And two, Wil Wheaton kicked my ass at Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: You poor thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a good sport about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Penny Arcade Expo is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish you guys were there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, how the hell did you end up playing Guitar Hero with Will Wheaton?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it just by chance?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Matt and he entered the tournament beforehand.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was in there warming up and asked if I could get a game with him because I'm probably not going to get a chance to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he's like, sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we played Let's Talk More Rock Expert and he kicked my ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Insanus, thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: And real quick plug for your show if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_04]: STFU every Thursday at 7 followed by the Insanest Hour if I'm up to it whenever STFU is over alright good to see that there is some weekday programming still happening on the station on Thursdays and occasionally on Tuesdays not so much on Wednesdays and if I have any spare swag left over I will either be giving it to you guys or away to listeners hoorah more on that on Thursday alright speaking of Tuesday I will be live this week
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay, I have something to do on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I won't be here on next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I will not be here on Wednesday because I'm in L.A.
[SPEAKER_10]: for four days.
[SPEAKER_11]: I won't be here next Sunday because of something very special.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Rob, can I have one more request?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let Jamie finish your thought and then you can have your turn.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the weekend of my second wedding anniversary.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yay, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will be making Dan buy me expensive food on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's taking me to Weird Al on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: It should be an interesting show Sunday because Labor Day weekend and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll be here if we do a drunk show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I don't have any plans for Monday.
[SPEAKER_10]: The plot thickens.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, DM, what was your one more thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: You haven't hung up on me in a while.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I should do that now.
[SPEAKER_10]: DMN goes by Insanus now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why did Prince change his name?
[SPEAKER_10]: He just did.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, he did because his name was copyrighted by the label he was on before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you always have to know everything?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: DMN slash Insanus slash whatever your name is going to be tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't sign on to WoW, I'm going to get somebody to kick you out of the guild because you're being too inactive and I don't like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well I'd like to go to another call now.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can use your WoW guild chat some other time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, you can't kick him from the guild because you don't have WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had to cancel WoW.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we've got to go back to the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's AZHP!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just don't play that much.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of people who leveled to level 5 and then quit.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I got to 8 with my team and then I started.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry, 8.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will play World of Warcraft on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, and DMN sent me a private message.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell me Glotov I quit WoW.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then I'm sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, sorry, AZHP has been waiting on the line very patiently.
[SPEAKER_10]: You poor bastard.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of WoW, you know, after I got off the phone last week with you guys, you said that I might have bought this budget computer for WoW, and no, I'm not a WoW player.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, because that's right, you emailed us, and we said something about you had the budget... You said something about buying a budget computer, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, well, I Skyped in last week, and I said that I bought a budget computer, and you thought that it was for WoW, and no, I've seen what WoW does to my friends, and I...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to become a recovering WoW addict.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ironic that we're yelling about WoW the minute you call in.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why you were snickering to yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that all you wanted to say?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I didn't catch the mailbag this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys read my email?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: We read a lot of emails, so I don't know if we  I think I heard your name come up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, you could always just download Part A, and then you'll find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played the Bioshock demo, and I was looking at picking it up because it's so awesome, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, we read this email, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and I just read a lot of controversy on the forums, like, oh, if you buy the game, you can only register it on two computers, and after that, your CD won't work anymore on any other computers that you have.
[SPEAKER_10]: That and your computer will be reported to the Motion Picture Association of America.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why they do that, I don't know, but it's just more negative stuff to happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: And little gnomes will come live inside your computer, and if you don't feed them before midnight, then your computer will grow legs and walk away.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the coffee protection on Bioshock is just that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, actually, people have said that root kits were installed, like Sony's old root kits that
[SPEAKER_05]: and pretty much just monitored everything on your computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm thinking of waiting until that stuff gets all settled down, people start throwing lawsuits at 2K and stuff, more lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, actually Big Brother is watching your computer and sending daily reports to Amber who's crying about them right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bad joke, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you get that, you need a life like I do.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, Miklatov's booing me.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know he needs it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you want to share, ACHP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably, but it all got lost in the randomness, so I guess that's about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's like the tagline of this show, it all gets lost in the randomness, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is pretty excellent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, actually, one more thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, about the Wii outselling the Xbox 360, and you guys are all wondering, oh, it's not the hardcore gamers who's buying all the stuff for it, it's just Wii Sports, Wii Play.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's a mix, it's a mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, keep in mind we were reading some chat comments there too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think you've got both the hardcore gamers and soccer moms buying it, and that's why it's doing so well.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I think for a lot of hardcore gamers, the magic is dying off.
[SPEAKER_10]: And hopefully Metroid is going to bring that back, and Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_10]: certainly will bring that back.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I feel like it's the DS launch all over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the DS launch all over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had a bunch of great games at the beginning, and then like a year of deadness with the occasional gem.
[SPEAKER_10]: and now we're going to get back into Overdrive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean like from next week until four months from now we got like great releases coming every month.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got Metroid Prime 3, Super Mario Galaxy, Super Smash Brothers, you got Battalion Wars, everything's just like coming out one after another.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's about freaking time, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't bought a new game for my Wii since Elevates.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the last one I bought was Super Paper Mario and I barely played it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel like a dummy for even buying it because I barely played it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, ACHP, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to go and wrap things up, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, then.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, later, sir.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you didn't get through, so sorry, but try again next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: We had some long calls tonight that kind of took up all our time.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you're mad we didn't get to your call, just blame Insanus because his call went on for about nine minutes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get to the listless results, shall we, before we get to the last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you still had some last-minute stories, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And maybe DarkSakura has a few as well?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's get to tonight's listless results.
[SPEAKER_10]: In third place for the character we would most like to see in the new track and field game, Dracula is the character that people would like to see third most in their DDR games.
[SPEAKER_10]: In second place for character that we most want to see in track and field, Mr. Spanky comes in second place.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what could possibly top Mr. Spanky?
[SPEAKER_10]: For the number one character you most want to see in track and field on the DS, the left DDR arrow is the number one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So make it happen, Konami.
[SPEAKER_06]: Heart, Hearts Make It Better
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't throw napkins at me.
[SPEAKER_10]: That will just make me meaner.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, Mikotov.
[SPEAKER_06]: I realized like 10 minutes ago that it would have been better to do the right DDR arrow because it's pointing in the direction of like the running on the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: The lefty arrow makes even less sense now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It makes you run away.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it makes it funnier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, Loki, last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there was some other stuff other than the Eye of Judgment announced for the PlayStation Eye.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of which is the Towers of Topok, which is apparently a game where you roll around this giant ball down this tower using your body.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds like a shitload of fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will use the eye of judgment to roll a giant ball down a hill is what you're saying something like that you know hooray that sounds like totem ball I love totem ball it's not exactly a totem ball and basically it's a top-down view and each of the little platforms that you're on is actually an image of your screen so you actually are on multiple platforms there I don't know it's weird not something I would buy though um
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, Gran Turismo 5 Prologue, which is rumored to be out this year, according to an interview with some people working the Sony booth at Leipzig, that actually, I guess, with the series creator, Kazunori Yamauchi,
[SPEAKER_08]: has confirmed himself.
[SPEAKER_08]: He said that, yes, it will be a free download on the PSN, and we're thinking of charging, but doubt it.
[SPEAKER_08]: For now, it's free.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I think it was actually supposed to contain quite a bit of stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were saying, I want to say it was like quite a few cars and about 16 tracks or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was like 50 cars.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that would be pretty sweet if it was free.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I wouldn't have to buy the actual game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Other than that, there was one other thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to say that they've partially cracked the Xbox 360 kernel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that allows you to download or downgrade from any kernel without using a computer key.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what that will allow you to do is drop your firmware, I guess, down to a level where you can...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think I have a choice
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm glad you have such enthusiasm with this program.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll lift my ban on drinking for myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we might have to do a drunk show after all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Migletov, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is they had some people, I guess, at Leipzig that were just completely naked, except they were painted on.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we need to see at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Painted chicks.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're topless.
[SPEAKER_10]: My final thought is Mike and Ike's are yummy and I just found one left in the bag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Delicious.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't like Mike and Ike's?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're one of the candies I can't eat because I'm allergic to one of the ingredients.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like the gelatin something something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Same with Starburst and gum makes me nauseous when I smell it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm trying to figure out what the name of the ingredient would be.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's some... Jamie Repellent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, look, it's right in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie Repellent number five.
[SPEAKER_10]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, thanks, you guys, so much for tuning in to and downloading our show or tuning in live.
[SPEAKER_10]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember, if you like what we do here, please, or even if you don't like what we do here, please help us spread the word of independent radio nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell two people about your show.
[SPEAKER_10]: They don't have to be your friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, because we'll take your enemies listening to the show, too, because we just like to get the word out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_02]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week!