George, Lounge, Radio
Here's your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loku
Tonight, June 5th, 2011, the E3 rumors start to roll in a day before the first press conference
The track listing for the Play for Japan benefit album is unveiled
And soon you can raise pets in The Sims 3
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
We're going to talk about video games over the next three hours or so
And you can join us if you're listening to us live at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
We do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you with my co-host, say hello to the one, the only, the lovely DarkSakura
Jamie Summers, how are you?
I'm recovering from my party
It's your party and you'll cry if you want to?
I cried when everyone left
I was like, they're gone
Now it wasn't your birthday, it wasn't a birthday party, so what was the party?
It was for me getting two associates degrees
After 15 years of going to college
You are a professional student
I've changed my major so many times it's the problem
So I got my art new media which is basically graphic design
I have liberal arts and then next spring I'll have social sciences
You just like to learn
Actually I really enjoy college, I do
If I could, if I could get paid to be a student like mystery shop teachers or something, that would be bliss
Mystery teachers
Seriously, I'd be mystery student
Mystery student
Yeah this teacher sucks
Rate my professor and all that stuff I guess
Put it in the student's hands
Are they hot or not?
Alright, the voice over there of course, the one and the only tech master, Loki
How you doing?
I'm doing good
Alright, by the way we were off last week so it's a little interesting to be back here after two weeks
But I hope you all had a good Memorial Day weekend
I don't know what you guys did
I went to Disneyland, it was fun
But what else is new here at Orange Lounge Radio?
I don't ever travel anywhere else
We're going again
I know and I'm going again this weekend and I'll get into more of that later on because it's kind of sick
Well, Loki what have you been up to?
What did you do with your days off?
Um, I don't remember
Probably not sleeping
Ah, it's that time huh?
We mean it's that time
It's been that time for ten months
I thought he was sleeping through the night, now he's not anymore?
Well, he sleeps through the night but he also wakes up about eight times during the night
I see, I see
Alright, well of course if you are new to Orange Lounge Radio, Loki and the Mrs. gave birth to Josh what about nine months ago?
Ten months ago
He didn't give birth to him
Well you know what I mean
He was there when it happened
But he did not go through labor
He contributed, he made a very important contribution to the whole process
Yeah, but the woman does all the work
Here we go
Okay
You and your women's lib
No
Stop burning your bra here on this show
I'm not even wearing one
Alright, alright
Moving on
I'm in my pajamas for tonight's show
The chatters in chat.orangelandradio.com are like oh yeah, prove it
Alright, anyhow
Here I will
Here comes Dan who's on mic
Shut up
What did he say? I didn't even catch it
I didn't hear what he said either
Something blah blah irrational psycho, that's all I picked up
He just needs to shut up forever
That was enough for me
Go back to watching your pinball thing
Let's go back to of course video games
It's a big week for video games, I'm not sure if you heard
The E3 convention is coming up this week
We're going to be covering E3
I'm going to start off the show actually by talking about this and we'll get into our gaming week
Our schedule is like so screwed up over the next couple weeks
Because we didn't do a show last week
We're doing a show tonight
We're not doing a show next Sunday
Because we're doing shows Tuesday and Wednesday
This next week
They are live E3 specials, different place
They're not going to be at AllGames.com because there's other stuff going on
And we also wanted to help you guys learn about our brand new Ustream channel
Is now up and running
Our username there is OrangeLounge
More information will be available at OrangeLoungeTrader.com later this week
And best of all, our good buddy Bobby Blackwolf
Who does the show before us here at AllGames Radio
Will be joining us over the Tuesday and Wednesday nights
To be talking about what he's observing at the show floor
What's going on behind the scenes at the press conferences
What Sony is filling five and a half hours with, pray tell, tomorrow night
And then Miklotov is also going to be joining us
They're both going to Nintendo's press thing
And will get to fill us in on what it was like to play
Whatever Nintendo's calling their new system
Without a three and a half hour wait
Or whatever long that line is going to be at E3
Which I am looking forward to not standing in
It's very strange because it's not like I haven't been to E3 before
I didn't go during the airport years
But it's going to be interesting doing coverage from this end of things
But I'm happy that we'll be able to produce something a lot more slick
Where we'll be able to take your calls
Have the live chat room which will still be in the same place
Chat.OrangeLoungeTrader.com
And let you guys interact with the E3 coverage
And of course, give your feedback
Because we are the show where every gamer has a voice
And there will be voices here in the studio
Voices on the E3 show floor
And your voices out there all over the internet
Aw man, I gotta wait until Tuesday
For Nintendo, yeah
Just so you guys know how it's all going down
Tomorrow there is no expo
The expo floor is not open
But the E3 show kinda starts
Because that's when the press conferences start
Microsoft kicks it off in the morning
Then Sony is going to be in the evening
Scrunched in there, Ubisoft and EA
Konami already happened
Which we'll be getting to a little later
We'll talk about what they talked about
They're not doing their own conference
Also I noticed left out Activision
Unless I just completely overlooked it
Which is possible, I'm sure somebody in the chat room
Will jump in with that if I may say
They also tend to usually have a lot of announcements
Like Call of Duty will usually be shown as Sony
Or Microsoft's conference
It's like, woah, I've never seen that before on these
Consoles, yeah
My thought too is that Activision kinda really blew their load
Last year with that whole Eminem, Rihanna
All those celebs they paraded out
On stage for DJ Hero 2
Which then, well you know
It didn't end up doing so hot
Although it was a fine game, I enjoyed DJ Hero 2
Yeah, here I was asking
Because my boss is going, actually my boss
And our vice president of sales
The guy
Doesn't know anything about gaming
So he's going to E3
Awesome, anyway
So they're going, now it's like so you guys going to any of the
Parties or anything while you're there
It's like, no, it's not anything like
You know, when they had the DJ Hero 2
Thing where they had like, you know, people DJing
And Eminem and stuff like that
They're having, I don't remember which
Publisher it is, but someone's having a
Bowling night
Nice, nice, Black Wolf
Our good pal is in our chat room saying
Activision has a booth, but they don't have a concert
So it is, yeah
Whatever their big announcement is might be at one
Of the other press conferences, I think you're right on with that
So we'll say
They don't have really any big announcements
They've got to be this year
They've got to give us more details on the Bungie thing
Because right now, all they've got coming out
Well, they've announced everything up through the third quarter
As of last week
So they haven't announced their fourth quarter stuff
Other than Call of Duty
But
There's not a lot that they can really cram in there
Usually there's a
Guitar Hero game around that time
But I mean, they've got
What, the X-Men game
They've got the new Spider-Man game
They have a
Crappy Spyro game that has
Some stupid little toy thing that you've got to
Scan your toy in order to play the character
In the game
And then of course they've also got
I think they're going to have a big
I think they might be blowing a big announcement
About Diablo before
Before Blizzcon
Blizzard's all their own thing
They're not going to announce any of that
Activision has been the one calling the shots
For a little while, which is why some of us
Wow advocates think the game's gone
A little bit south the past couple of years
They may announce a console port
Because there's already rumors that they hired people
To port over the Playstation 3
I actually think that's exactly what the announcement's going to be
But we'll get into that later
We'll get into E3 predictions a little later on
Woohoo!
I'm going to try
We're going to go
This is definitely live radio here
We actually have a man on the ground
Already in LA who's also going to be joining us
On the Tuesday and Wednesday shows
We're actually going to give him a call right now
Live, unscripted
He's actually at some type of event already
And I want to get more details on that
I know he's already been by the convention center
So we're going to give our old buddy Miklotov a call
And see what's up in LA right now
This may be botched a little bit
He's at some event
And I'll get some more details on what's going on
It could be very noisy
Two ringing dingies
Hey Miklotov
Hey what's up
Hey not much, it's Rob of course
You know that because I've been text messaging you
Where are you at? You're at an event
The E3 parties have already started
What's going on?
Yeah this is the
What is this I'm at?
What am I at right now?
It's for Major Nelson's
Twitter
And it's
A huge meetup where they're giving away
Food and drinks
And free bowling
And most importantly
Passes to the
Fresher event tomorrow
Wait are you at a bowling alley?
Yes
No that's not it
Major Nelson's doing the bowling alley thing too
There you go
Well what's going on at the event?
Are there any games that you can see?
Anything or is it just a bunch of
Bros getting together tossing balls around
Here at the bowling alley
It's just some colored balloons
But I actually went into the
E3 expo hall
today and looked up what they have on board
Hold on hold on hold on
Put that on Twitter everybody
Microsoft unveils colored balloons
At E3
It's a brand new thing for the connect colored
This is almost as good as
Space suits last year
They are green and white
And I guess that's purple for connect
Breaking
Orange Lawns Radio exclusive
This is an exclusive report
I don't know what you're saying but they're about to get more tickets away
So I'm going to hang up on you. Goodbye
Yep that's just
That's exactly what it's going to sound like Tuesday and Wednesday
As well is that we'll get the nice professional
Radio call from Bobby Blackwolf
And then when he decides he's got to hang up to go to a swanky party
Then Megalotov is going to call us
Yeah I don't know what really happened today
But I saw some balloons
Go and run that IGN
Colored balloons
I remember where the space suits were last year
Cosmic jumpsuits or something like that
Space ponchos
I was just talking about that last night
With Alan in the car
Let's move on and get into how is your gaming week
We always like to start off the show when it's not E3
With how is your gaming week
But tonight was a little special. Dark Soccer how is your gaming week
There was a crap load of rock band
Last night. We had rock band 3
And Beatles rock band going on last night
And I sang
A lot and my throat hurts
I haven't lost my voice
What did you sing? What are your specialties?
Well I don't have
The song that apparently everyone says I'm really good at
So I was
Singing um
Chemical romance
And uh
What else did I do?
9 in the afternoon. Panic at the Disco
Which is like one of my favorite songs
And um
I think I did some Kansas
And
Any chance we get you to hum a few bars?
No
And I also did
I sang just about everything that we did in Beatles
Rock band except for like 3 that
Drew Nami
Sang
He was at the party too
There was a blast from the past. Intern Drew. Good job
And um
I also played Wow
Which I did today
And yelled at the ship for not arriving on time
Or at least on time in my universe
Sorry I have to share this. Mikolatov just texted me
He's like you can call me back it was too loud
To hear the numbers. I'm like I will call when you have something
News besides colored balloons
Don't judge
Um
They're green and white
No shit
It's Xbox
And Dan's been playing LA Noire
And I've beat Portal 2 now
For like the 9th time
And I'm on my 10th playthrough
On single player mode
And I find something new every time
It's fun
But I finally got the Smash TV
Achievement Rob
Well all the other ones are easy
Except for the last one you have to get
Which is the room where
It's like you go in
And there's uh
Glass to your right
And then there's 3 turrets
And the button you need to press is in front of the turrets
On the other side of the glass
So you have to go across and send the
Little uh
Tube to send your blue goo across
But you have to throw the goo
And knock down 2 of the turrets
And then go in the hole
That's above the last turret
And manage to jump down with enough
momentum to where you land just behind the turret
Pick it up, carry it over
And set it down straight so that it does not fall over
And die to where it shoots bullets at Wheatley
And then
That's how you get the last one
That sounds complicated
It's super complicated and it took me something like
25 tries to do it because
I get motion sick
And after try number 15 I wanted to throw up
But I kept doing it
And I finally got it
And then I like saved the game and left the room
Hard work pays off
The other ones were super easy
Alright anything else for your gaming week?
Um
We had pie
Loki how was your gaming week?
Orange sickle cupcakes
My gaming week was alright I didn't play a whole lot
I played portal through a little bit again
Cheating all the way this time
Which is fun mainly just
Kill time
I didn't really want to play anything else
Um played more Grand Theft Auto as usual
And um
Let's see
Also a tiny little bit of
L.A. Noire didn't really get a whole lot of time
To play it
But I made it through you know like the first
Kind of case that you have there
Um it's interesting I mean
The game is really detailed but uh
I don't know I'd probably get into it
I just have to have some time to play it
That's pretty much it
Wow
Sounds like uh you had a pretty
Quick week for games
Yeah well I'm still working on
You know Grand Theft Auto mods
And a whole bunch
Of other garbage
Anything that you're kind of looking
Forward to with the next week? Any demos
That might hit the store that you're like ooh I gotta play that
No oh by the way my uh
Dev console got banned from
Partner net which is kind of disappointing
How'd that happen? How'd you get caught?
It's just they eventually ban all of them
You know after a while
But it doesn't matter there wasn't really
Anything on partner net that I wanted to play
It was all Xbox Live or arcade games
There's no like you know betas
For you know another Halo or something
Like that you're not gonna find anything juicy like that on there
Um and
It besides all those
Games that are on partner net
Other people aren't banned and those people
Leak out those games for everyone
Else with JTAG consoles so
Eh whatever I decided
To check to see if there's any E3 demos on there but
You're getting better about hiding that stuff
Eh whatever I
I don't really even care
Well if it's anything like last year like almost all the trailers
That will be at the press conference tomorrow
You will see then show up on E3 or
I'm sorry on Xbox to download so you know
You'll see it in glorious HD
I'm not even worried about playing demos
For stuff um you know there are
Are some games that look really awesome
Like you know Saints Row 3
I was pretty excited for
From the get go cause I love Saints Row
It's just kinda it kept
The fun aspect and just the
Really over the top part
Of Grand Theft Auto San Andreas
And they just keep building up on it and
You know the first game was sort of a Grand Theft Auto
Ripoff but it's really become kind of its own
Thing and I love
Just the whole game it's just
Really fun and the new
The new one that they have coming out this fall
It just looks amazing
I really I can't wait to play it
Even if they do announce a new
You know Grand Theft Auto game
I love both games both series I think can
Coexist because they're just kinda
Different I am very disappointed though
That the third um doesn't have
Online multiplayer
As far as like death matches and stuff goes
Because I mean I don't know
The first game was kinda
Eh it wasn't very good as far as
That they had online and the second game
They tried to mix it up a little bit but it was really
Wacky the way they had everything they really
Shoulda just stuck with you know
Kinda doing a Grand Theft Auto style where it's
Okay here's a portion of the map that you play
In and go you know something
Simple like that but uh they tried to
Do some funky stuff with it and it was alright
But it's the maps that they had are really
Kinda limited and you know
The fun is kinda limited too but at least they have
Online co-op for two players this time
Let me go um to our chatroom at chat.orangelandradio.com
Uh and I think
Breakman's pretty much echoing something you just said here
Saints Row 3 doesn't have any multiplayer versus
Though frown. Yeah just uh
Two player online co-op like the second game
Which is fun you know cause I
I'm Grand Theft Auto so
Co-op can be fun. Yeah co-op is fun and
It was actually a lot of fun playing a
System Link co-op with uh
The second Saints Row game so I'm
I'm looking forward to this new one
For sure and I mean
You know
And you know right now I'm still playing lots of
Grand Theft Auto but that's gonna
Interrupt or something's gonna interrupt that
Though come July cause July
July 5th to be exact
Is when we get
The new Earth Defense Force game
Oh that's gonna be awesome
Counting down the days. Oh yeah
Alright let me get to my gaming week um
Quite a bit actually this week we'll start with demos
You know I usually don't like to review
Games based on the demo but when a big big demo
Comes out I like to kinda get my first impressions
On it uh Dungeon Siege 3 is the demo
I downloaded which is available uh
I was surprised that they were even gonna make a Dungeon
Siege 3 because I kinda thought the first two games
You know they they made their point they had their
Relevance of course they were PC only titles
Uh but now Square Enix
Is behind the publishing of this third
Game uh that's happening uh now
On the consoles uh and I believe
PCs later on so the demo's available
On Xbox Live. It's all the same time. Huh?
Yeah all the same time uh so the
Demo's now available on Xbox Live and it's very
Diablo-esque if you've never played Dungeon Siege
It's very Diablo it was kinda Microsoft's answer to Diablo
In some ways uh and so the game's very
Diablo-esque and uh it was okay
You know I had a good time playing it but um
I thought like especially
Following up a game like Torchlight
Uh it was nice to kinda see the more
Robust graphics and that Square
Enix Cinema presentation
Presentation style excuse me
Um was it something I'm excited
To spend $60 on? No
Not based off the demo but will I like
Get it or get it in a bargain bin? Sure absolutely
You know it's a very challenging
Position we're in right now in the gaming industry
With this whole it's gonna be interesting to see
What develops with this E3 because you know
Some games you are expected to pay $60
For some games like
Angry Birds you're expected to pay a dollar for
Or even get free and it's really about
Trying to find that happy price point and you know
We're talking about a new Nintendo console coming out
At E3. What are the games gonna cost?
Is Nintendo now gonna up the bar to $60?
Although some would argue they have
Been already
Oh yeah I don't doubt but are
The games gonna be worth it? I mean there's a certain point
Where the consumer goes hmm do I really
Buy this at $60 or do I just
Wait till it comes down in price or
I don't know like it's a tricky
NGP games are $50
Wow really
But PSP games were $50
Well not a lot of PSP games
Were $50 but there were a few
But like $40 is kind of you know
The price point
For the PSP but they did have $50
Games
So that's all I really want to say about the demo
It was cool
Fable 3 I got to play which is a game
Like a year and a half old so I bet a lot of you that were
Interested in this have probably already played it but
I was a little late to the party. I played the game
It's neat. There's a lot of concepts
In Fable I really like
But I sometimes wonder if this game tries to do
Too much and at its core
It's really repetitive
And it's like a Facebook game
Repetitive like
I like the fact that you do these quests
To enhance relationship with villagers
And I like this whole way that the
Villager enhancement thing is built in but when you're doing
The same fetch quest or the same
Delivery quest multiple
Times you're like okay
So what am I doing
Here you know and this is I felt like
It's just very very repetitive
I cannot trust anything Peter Milano
Says anymore I mean seriously
All of his innovative stuff is
Such bullshit because it's just like
Look at all this innovative stuff I added a dog
To my game no other game has had
Dogs in it before this dog
You'll love no I didn't give a shit about the
Dog yeah the dog was cool but you know what
The dog was as cool as any other dog in
Any other game the dog was actually
Kind of stupid sometimes the biggest
Crime for me that Fable 3 made
I don't feel it took the series
Forward I feel it took it back yeah I think
Fable 2 was a much better game
And I think it had that whole good
And evil thing developed and like Fable 3
I don't even notice it it really doesn't even seem like
That exists in it it's more about this whole
Path to being a king more politics
Which is a very repetitive
Grind
And I kind of got like I was really into it
For about an hour and a half and then I got bored of it
I got really bored of it and I was like you know
What I'm done I don't really want to play
Any more Fable 3 and uh
Yeah I feel bad saying it because there's a lot
That I like about the Fable
Series and I really liked Fable 2
I think Fable 3 was rushed
To be honest I think they needed to wait
Another year to put this game out there was a lot that was really
Glitchy in it too and just I didn't like
The map system and good lord the
Loading and like
Just watching the screen draw
Like oh
No this did not come out
Like you should have Dan got rid of ours
Yeah and luckily
I just borrowed this one so
I'm giving it back
So sorry Fable 3 gets a
Pass from me but the second one's good
Third one's crap
Not as good
So if they are announcing a new Fable game at E3
Which some think or I guess a Fable
Side, wasn't Fable 3 supposed to have Kinect
Later on? I'm kind of glad they
Didn't to be honest but if they spun it off
Into a whole new game I hope it's
Interesting
No
Anyhow
Katsune in our chat room says I got really bored with it
Quickly as well
And the whole
I know you all love this term
Microtransactions for like outfits
And weapons and stuff
No that was an obvious
Bad that was just
Microtransactions gone bad
I would never drop a penny on any of it
Period. Sorry
The other game I played
This week I got to watch
Alan play the Duke Nukem
Forever demo which hit
Steam over the weekend and
I have to admit I like
It's very tongue in cheek
It does not make any
Pauses about where exactly this
Game comes from. Have you seen Loki
The opening sequence to Duke Nukem Forever
In the demo? Ah yes
And I love that it starts in the
Whole football scene which is very reminiscent
Of the end of the last game which was in the football stadium
But then it
This is a little bit spoilery but deal with it
It's the first five minutes of the game
It pans out of the
Football field or whatever
And you see that Duke is actually
Playing the video game
And it pans out
So far that you see these two girls are actually
Giving him a blowjob while he's playing the game
They are the Molson twins by the way
The Molson twins
And they're like oh was that good for you
Or wholesome twins or something like that
It's basically the olson twins
And they said something like
Oh was the game good Duke
And he goes yeah well after 12 fucking
Years it better be
So I like that it made
No pauses about that but then
When Alan got into
The actual game all I heard was
This is hard this is bullshit
This is hard this game is hard
This is hard I hate this game this is bullshit
So apparently it's really cheap
Why doesn't he just play it on an easier setting
He is playing it on like easiest
Why doesn't he just get better
At games then
Tell him he needs to go back and play Duke Nukem 3D
I wish I could go back and play Duke Nukem 3D
I can't really
Accurately judge Duke Nukem forever
Until I play multiplayer
Because that's where everything Duke Nukem
I mean fuck single player in that game
Seriously it was not
I mean after level 1
1 where you have the stripper
And everything like that it's forgettable
I actually really did like the single player
The single player levels were pretty awesome
I even like the atomic edition
With all the extra stuff that they added in there
Like I love the level that was basically
Disneyland which is pretty awesome
I love the one that was in a supermarket
They had one at like a post office and stuff like that
It was just those were kind of cool to me
I kind of feel like I should just go back and play Duke Nukem 3D
Yeah but see though
We tried that though on
Remember the 360 we all downloaded and got all excited
And it kind of sucked
Salacious Pop is yelling at me in the chat room
Lies and slander lies and slander
Lies and slander
That's what it sounded like to me my bad
I'm sleeping on the couch tonight
Alright um
Is he on Skype?
I could call him to defend himself
Do it
Hold on I'll look up his number
Isn't that sad I don't even know his number
Because we live in such a cell phone age
That I don't need it
I'm just going to call him and see what happens
I know my husband's number
Do do do do do do do do do do
This is just the night of random outbound phone calls
Is what it is
Let's call my mother next
We should have sent my mother to E3 wouldn't that have been fun
Yeah
Should be able to get in
Pick up the phone
gonna be all what's this number instead of the voicemail he's screaming no in
the chat room he's not answering I went to voicemail all right live radio he's
like my phone is in the other room oh he's running to fire out I'll try one
more time one more time everybody in the chat room is yelling at him this is the
best radio ever this is even funnier than sure me saying bless you in some
apparently he was playing it on medium and I misunderstood that hello okay lies
and slander I need to turn the radio down or else we're gonna have really bad
gecko okay we're fine sure okay hi hi hi tonight's the night of random phone
calls where I call people chatters you'll notice what so so then you tell me
about the Duke Nukem demo since I clearly misunderstood once you get to
the second part of the demo where you it shows you some vehicle play which is fun
and then you get out of your truck and the background is brown and the enemies
are brown so when they pop out I actually had a hard time seeing them and
because I was playing it on me and difficulty by the time I could get
behind cover I was dead already so I switched it too easy and then learned
where the spawns were and then switched back to medium and I was fine but yeah
it's it's I think there's some work that needs to be done on the clarity of the
the mobs especially since they don't they all kind of jump out from behind
things from out of nowhere so the game's gone gold now so whoops I don't know if
they're gonna fix that yeah I know right so yeah I didn't it feels like Duke they
definitely captured the humor and the attitude but as far as some amazing
first-person shooter like Bioshock which was a completely different experience
there's I don't think there's anything that remarkable about it it's pretty
much all fan service the fact that it exists it means that it's going to sell
but I don't think it's all that you know super amazing from the demo so do you
think you'll invest 50 bucks or whatever in the full version on Steam hell no I
don't care I don't care that badly that it's really kind of offensive and I mean
obviously it's a dude bro game with the you know blowjob in the opening scene
but I you know does the demo have multiplayer I don't think so hmm that's
too bad all right all right well thanks for letting me bug you don't be mad okay
but I want you I wanted you to be able to accurately represent and defend
yourself I would never want to get your opinions yes all right okay who should
we call next let's see okay no no we got a versus a show to do okay we got to get
into news that's it for our gaming weeks quick housekeeping again I just want to
clarify the schedule there will be no OLR next Sunday there will be two
episodes at well are on the feed this week Tuesday night Wednesday night join
us on our new you stream channel seven o'clock Pacific with special
correspondent Bobby black wolf here's the great news I don't think this really
affects anyone listening to this show but he's also gonna be posting the shows
on his feed which I think is really cool so that way if you I don't know why you
would be listening right now and you're not subscribed to our show but okay
let's say you're not you can also get them from Bobby's feed so they're gonna
be in both places for a maximum exposure I'm getting tweeted pictures by the way
right now from miklotov who I guess went to the convention center earlier and I
guess you know a couple days before the show you can just kind of walk right on
in there and walk around he's not in the actual exhibition halls but let's see
there's a giant ad for is Assassin's Creed revelations giant ad for that a
little picture of the lobby that shows nothing really notable can't really see
in the room there and they won't let him up the stairs I'm sure and then it looks
like what they're advertising on the entryway is rage which is supposed to
that big new shooter right which is gonna have a whole new engine that
people are going to adapt kind of like what unreal brought to the table and
there's these little gross little aliens crawling all over the entry plaza for
rage so you can expect that that game is going to have a big presence and three
so there you go
I know our next Sunday because dark soccer and I will be at Disneyland with
Bobby actually won't be there Sunday but we'll be driving back so and there will
be a damn there will be a damn there will be a damn Dan will be here for the
Tuesday Wednesday shows to us because Loki unfortunately will only be able to
join what I can do
he might try to pull some strings and join us live that would be amazing
we'll see what happens when may you can call me you know I can do it over Skype
or something like that
all right for at least like from eight o'clock on but we need at least the
Nintendo press conference feedback that's all that's yeah I agree Wednesday
maybe you know maybe not Wednesday but like Tuesday would be fun because then
that'd be after all the press conferences there you go
all right anyhow let's move on with gaming news because we got a lot to
cover tonight it's not just e3 but of course course e3 rumors are going to
start it come on so everybody's talking about let's start us off Loki
yes and I don't know I I think it's a dumb name but whatever
there's a rumor that the what's being you know codenamed NGP right now is
actually going to be officially revealed as the PlayStation Vita or the PS Vita
or vita vita could be either way
pens if they're going for vital or vitamin or vita pita
yes and so well here's here's what evidence they have for that one there
was a leaked or apparently leaked picture of a brochure showing the system
with the PS Vita image on there and you know where is most people might say oh
that may be photoshopped well there's least some other evidence to go along
with that
there's actually a few a few pictures of that so that's kind of interesting also
there's apparently there was like a domain for developers that actually had
a PS Vita for it's the Sony dev site they had that and then also there
apparently there's text for the PlayStation Vita hidden away in the code
for the e3 site for Sony so yeah I gotta say that that's probably true
you know if it's if it's hidden away in their code on their website and it's
also on their dev site and it's also in this brochure it's probably makes me
feel great about the security of Sony in the future by the way
um I also agree it's it's probably the right name it makes sense
I it's you know they're trying to go for that catchy thing
I also just the fact that do you guys remember last e3 everything got spoiled
every no or was it two years ago yes well by them
member with the end with the PSP go no not just that there was one year were
like every big announcement that they were going to make was spoiled and I
remember he got up on stage when he showed the trailer for Final Fantasy 14
it was been two years ago
he got up on stage to show the trailer for fantasy 14 everybody thought he was
he had fucked up and meant to say 13 to but no it was actually 14 and then he
goes
hey there's one we kept from you like I remember that vividly in my mind like
the rest of that press conference and spoiled
yeah I'm glad you kept that one from us
wish you'd kept it away from us forever you keep it a little bit longer
I'm some other cool information regarding the NGP or Vita
I guess we'll call the Vita it's going to be fully backwards compatible with
all PSP games that are on the PlayStation Network obviously it's not
gonna have a UMD drive
it will also offer a smoothing and dual analog support so for example you know
games like resistance retribution you know how they had the DualShock 3
controller support if you you played that with PlayStation or the PSP Go or
believe through your through the resistance like for the call that like
the infected mode or something like that it's basically where it linked up
with resistance to be playing through that you could also do DualShock 3
support but now it's going to support for all games because you know obviously
the new piece of hardware has tool you know dual analog sticks that's kind of
cool
I'm sorry I I'm late to the party and that's fine I'm actually waiting to hear
a lot of this from Sony's mouth tomorrow but on this thing doesn't have a UMD
drive
it doesn't have any that doesn't have any dry has it has to physical like SD
card proprietary some sort of storage card
ok ok so there's some I was like they didn't learn from the go that people
don't want to download no it's like a cartridge
ok but yeah the rule is that there is no onboard storage at all for this thing
you have to buy your own like memory cards or something like that but that
each game would have its own you know card and there be space on there for
download content with a tiger kalana term says they should have called it PS
vivo which is Spanish for live might be ok name I think I think it's just going
to be PSV is what's going to end up I think yeah PSV and I think it's vita for
this is vital in for you to have because it has everything you know and that's
that Sony's little tagline it only does everything and that's what you know and
to be fair it was the strength of the PSP is it online you've a clip it is
just like you know my own trees
yeah I I would believe vita it's gonna and I think it's vital this is a vital
it's vital for all gamers to have this I'm sticking with for clint that's how
anyone who buys will handle and apparently you know the they've been on
the record saying that they're gonna learn they've learned from the mistakes
with the PSP and they're going to make sure they don't make them again with the
the vita they're basically saying we wanted to our biggest mistake I would
say with the PSP was that we were just so happy to provide the ps2 gaming on
the go we kind of stop there is what we want to do with the NGP or fighter
besides the great graphics and CPU think on what the interface could put in to
make gameplay reality stand out I really stand out you know something that you
cannot even do on the ps3 and yeah that makes sense with the rear touch pin the
augmented reality stuff and touchscreen also but I think it's almost like too
much you know like they have like some games that are kind of showing off that
we're touching I don't know it's a little weird to me but we'll see and I
gotta be honest you know I was kind of you know I'm one to kind of buy every
console when it comes out and stuff but you know I'm probably actually not gonna
buy one of these and the reason why is they were shown off some of the games
that they have at launch or whatever they have a wipeout game and they have
course ridge racer they have uncharted no ridge racer and some others and some
other games like super stardust and stuff like that but I'm not a fan of
uncharted I don't really care about wipeout so it's to me it's almost like
hey look it's the 3ds lineup again no I'm not gonna do this you're not a fan
of uncharted bless from her alright I wouldn't look at the chat room here with
some of the comments about the name JV Mon in our charm says Vita equals life
PlayStation life like you live a PlayStation life actually isn't
PlayStation life the name of one of the channels like it's the one that no one
ever uses that had the well they used it at first it has the news and the folding
at home is that PlayStation life don't they call it that I don't know also
salacious pop in our charm says living la vida joca we knew that joke was
coming we knew that joke was coming moving on more rumors more things to
talk about this time about Microsoft and some of the things that apparently they
have coming and this news has to do with trademarks and other things that have
been spotted out in the wild
let's see fusion genesis is one of the trademarks that is shown up for
Microsoft and also fusion vault infusion sentiment they are specified in the
little trademark as entertainment services namely providing an online
computer game so there must be some type of fusion series coming out for either
xbox live arcade gotta be fusion frenzy I fucking hate no fusion frenzy that was
a Hudson thing anyway was never Microsoft centric and you know they
couldn't swap developers on you know Microsoft game okay but like if
Microsoft was gonna buy a franchise like fusion frenzy which I don't think I
mean I realize Hudson in the US kind of close but I believe they still have a
Japanese presence so well just because why would you buy the fusion frenzy
series that last game was awful and on top of that you know it's like Hudson
was responsible for the Mario Party games and those weren't terrible it's
just like for the 360 like or even the original xbox let's just not give a shit
on this problem with all due respect to people that work at Hudson the biggest
issue with Hudson is that they've had some really big hits and some huge
misses like just wow wow like bomber man zero was a Hudson game if I'm not
mistaken correct yeah yeah fusion frenzy too I think all bomber man games have
been Hudson because Hudson created bomber man correct but the arc now see
but when they hit they hit pretty well deca sports actually wasn't a bad game
it was pretty nice little expansion of Wii Sports I the bomber man xbox live
arcade thing was great for you know it was delivered exactly what people wanted
out of a bomber man game but anyway how did we get from fusion to bomber man
oh yeah that's because it's a fusion frenzy yeah you know the problem with
Hudson is their own by Tommy I wonder if it's not their answer to pixel junk
that's where my mind goes like it doesn't necessarily have to be like
they're gonna go why do they need to even answer that I mean seriously
because it's done well for so what so good a game is done well for Sony
why they need to answer that they have plenty of good games on xbox live
arcade hell there's good games coming out every week on xbox live arcade
versus the PlayStation Network which doesn't get everything you know each
week game guru in our chat says I think Microsoft owns the fusion frenzy license
ok fine but really I really don't think these games have any idea of fusion
crazy that last game killed the series let it let it die you know just I don't
think this is it I mean I I don't know they could be a connect thing with me I
think it's just gonna be minigame garbage unfortunately that's where my
mind goes but it's just a freaking name it could also be the best game we've
ever seen I mean we just don't know their names I'm gonna make the best game
ever and call freaking garbage and you play a garbage man that's what well no
ok case in point super meat boy hat I based on the name and the box art I was
like this game looks stupid this game looks so stupid and then I played it I'm
like oh my god schemes amazing so you know names do not mean everything anyway
let's get to some other speaking of names some other registrations domains
apparently some internet domain names that have been registered fabled the
journey new fable game or possible Xbox Live or possibly fable connect fable
connect this is what Milo turned into I'm thinking it's this all that whole
like you can have him set down in the stream and you can hold the pieces of
paper interacting with people fable the journey is what happened to Milo I know
I don't even think it's that far I think it's just fable with some connect you
know connectivity I guess I've abandoned no I've abandoned the whole fable series
anyway so the hell with I don't even care what it is
alright connect fun labs is another one that was already leaked though in an
earlier thing I dance central to which I mean really duh really connect sports
season two duh yeah also also pretty much a duh so the sequels to our two
most successful connect titles never exactly again it's it's really all about
okay what is the connect gonna give us that isn't part of the we I'm really
interested in what this whole connect Star Wars thing is that because remember
they if they had teased that last year and we got nothing well this is the year
we need to see what connects Star Wars is all about all LucasArts got you know
they have right now is just the Old Republic that's it they have nothing
else slated to come out that they have announced all right go going to our
chairman chat dot orange launch radio comm Randy and our charm says hold hands
and fable with connect what the hell was that hand-holding thing anyway like it
didn't make sense like just say follow me for well for escorting the girl and
stuff it made sense but did you really have to be able to hold hands and run
everybody through town it's just weird I go did it but I go she was I go all
right moving on what did the press conference has already happened right
dark soccer konami we had some announcements from konami we had the
Metal Gear Solid HD collection that has Metal Gear Solid 2 Metal Gear Solid 3
snake eater and Metal Gear Solid peace Walker but the original one is not in it
Twin Snakes though I mean that was that should have been in there they've
already remade it once so but anyway it's going to be available on the ps3
and Xbox and will support 1080p and on the ps3 there is a transferring feature
well I guess transferring I should say it must have been misspelled no I think
they are misspelling it on purpose they're little trans firing yeah yeah
where you can transfer your peace Walker game from your PSP to your ps3 I know
like how they pronounce million Marion you can trance you can transfer your
game from the ps3 to the PSP there's also a zone of the enders HD collection
so that has one of the enders and some of the enders too and not much else is
said about that except that they're thinking it'll be out in 2012 and it'll
be a ps3 and Xbox 360 and it will also have trans firing much better but there
wasn't a zone of the enders game on the PSP I well more importantly than all of
that there's going to be a Silent Hill collection which is silent hill two and
three and it's just basically touched up to look good in HD and doesn't say
what's going to be on although my assumption would be well ps3 and Xbox
360 no maybe you can transfer to there too I don't know I'm gonna call it
trans fart so that I can think of pooting noises whenever you do your
trans farting well here's the thing the trans firing stuff the psycho mantis
read my trans farted data it's not really a good feature anyways because
the only game you can use that for would be the PSP port and peace Walker is the
only game and I'm assuming you have to have the original game for that as well
so I don't know that's kind of weird it does feel like a lot of wasted resources
on something no one's going to use correct yeah and what I would think
would be cool is that for those of us who have older ps3s it would be cool if
there you know could be some way to transfer your save file but other than
that you know that would be a pipe dream yeah I don't know did you guys watch
Konami's press conference out of curiosity no here's the thing I I did
watch most of it and what I thought was interesting most people were looking
forward to Konami's press conference this year because the last couple years
have just been an absolute fucking train wreck like it has just been like Konami
it's just like like you know and I've used this reference before on the show
but it's so true it's like the old episodes of the Ricky Lake show where
she's just got her hand against her like uh and her jaw drop like I can't even
control what's going on this stage right now is the show a hot mess yeah there
was the year that they showed rock revolution and they failed the song on
stage and then they had what last year the whole lucha libre thing wasn't that
part of their thing and like it was just like what in the hell is going on in the
hole what was it the one Marion troops and I I oh my god it was just it was
just like what fucking train wreck thing is gonna happen now like it's Oprah's
gonna come out and do bees everybody we got a game about bees hopefully you've
all seen that gift from the Conan show this is the best thing ever made anyway
um somebody in chat quick find me the Oprah bees gift because everybody needs
to see it because that's what we were expecting at the Konami press conference
this year was bees but no the whole thing was pre-recorded and it was a
pre-recorded slickly produced video reel it was very reminiscent of for those
that have seen the Konami booth at e3 they always have a giant television elite
well last year they remodeled it I can't remember if they have the giant TV
anymore but at least for the last few years before that they had a giant
television that would cycle through all the trailers and people kind of sit and
watch it was very reminiscent of this is the video that's gonna play on the giant
TV all e3 which is which I found it you know what hey it was a interesting way
for them to do it and you know they got their message out there and didn't
really get made fun of and there's been a lot of hypes for the products I found
it very interesting that they did it that way in part probably so that it was
very scripted and would not fall apart alright here's my complaint and besides
what Jamie's gonna talk about here in a second really is this all you've got
you've got remakes of your old shit I is that it this is what you've worked hard
on is well is taking assets from an old game and sprucing up sprucing up and hey
you know you're not really playing a new game we're just taking the old game hold
on hold on it up a bit and pumping it back into your console Kojima did come
out to talk about a new about his new engine for a game they has no game for
you know well here's the thing this is tricky though because maybe it's a game
they're going to announce but did because of this whole pre three thing
they didn't please just like you know they would announce it anyways if they
were going to have something to announce because I mean seriously where's a you
know no you're rising oh they mentioned that it's still coming to you next year
even though they mentioned it two years ago last year I guess yay thank you to
the four chatters that all found that at once for me the Oprah bees gift have you
seen it Loki I'm afraid I have not seen my favorite fucking thing ever wait hold
on oh there's a YouTube Ziba bless your heart
ultimate Oprah's ultimate favorite things here we go
nope I made a full screen here we go this is for you too they're opening the
box and bees and they're playing them I'm a bee in the background and this is
what we were expecting Konami's press conference this year was great I love
having a live chat room more than anything because they can find shit like
that for us on a whim and I don't care if it's a radio show and you can't see
the video this is about my amusement and Oprah bees amuses me I have more Silent
Hill me all right what well there was another announcement for a new Silent
Hill title and it's called book of memories and it's gonna be for the
vitamin the ps vitamin which is what I'm gonna call it the vitamin and they say
that is going to be exclusive to the vitamin and it will be released quote
later down the road after Silent Hill collection later down the road didn't
even say what fuck if we know it's coming someday so you didn't even
mention Silent Hill downpour at all they talked a little bit about dance dance
revolution hey we got an arcade machine that's coming to Japan oh good oh you
wanted something for you guys oh sorry we don't have anything for you we're
telling you this because we know you'll import it anyway we don't even have Glee
for you which is fine you know we don't care revolution Glee but I mean did they
announce some of that stuff kind of just in written form only like a new DDR game
is coming out to like it wasn't really in the video but they did put out a
little paper on it well you know I didn't see a DDR game on there I didn't
all I saw was you know x3 the arcade machine and that's it and yeah it's
coming out in Japan so that that does not count I'm afraid I'm sorry so really
what they're spending their time on doing is taking old shit and making it
new again or not even making a new making it prettier great good job you
know who can get away with that Sony can get away that cuz you know why cuz they
put out new shit on top of that I again you said they put out I think you I I
think it's too early to really say that because next week you know we have a new
Nintendo console coming out you know Konami is working on something as oh I'm
shaking waiting for the new elephants game it's gonna come out maybe it's okay
and maybe another deck of sports game because you know there'll be another
deck of sports game I'm done with you it's like deca sports and Ella bits
maybe and what other crap did they put out whenever there's a new console hmm
let me think here they don't put out Ella bits every time there's a new
console that happened once on the Wii yeah but they're gonna totally bring it
over you know it I don't think they will yeah that's right you just made sure me
leave the room that's guys believe that's another Hudson title too anyway
she's probably gonna go take a shit in the hall because of your outburst I'm
just thank you for making my cat poop all right can we move on with another
story please I guess I'm just saying it's it was not disappointing because I
kind of expect this little out of them you know I was hoping they would
surprise me but they might still know they're not come on this is Konami we're
talking about here they are never gonna surprise us they're gonna just come out
like almost want to bet money on this I'm doing the pie almost want to bet
money on this but I'm not going to because I'm broke and I'm going to
Disneyland this week and I need my money fine well just let's talk about
something else all right there's a rumor that Microsoft's gonna be announcing a
TV service at e3 basically kind of this whole rumor you know IP TV thing well
now they're gonna kind of take it a step further and basically become their own
you know service so instead of having you know dish or something like that you
could have you know whatever we're gonna call this believe Xbox Live diamond
they're saying is what's gonna be which is funny because I remember back in the
day having the diamond card which gave me nothing but didn't it give you like
discounts at Quiznos for like a month of something like that you know like I
never used I never upgrade of a section sub to a footlong that was what PS
diamonds those little like you know fundraising cards entertainment books
not even that not even the entertainment book but you know it's a little like
fundraising cards that you get that it's like oh this is for all the local
businesses you know 10% off of a you know a Subway sandwich or four square
well no not four square predating all of that I know I know it's hard to think of
a time that I wore square didn't exist all I can think of is the entertainment
books honestly there was the thing they'd sell them for like 35 bucks and
all it was like buy one get one free yeah those are sold those and banned
it's like I'm never gonna use all this I don't know um so before there was
Groupon there was entertainment books uh yes so they're saying that it's gonna be
for an additional monthly fee it's basically gonna be like a virtual cable
operator and yeah so not really too much that we know or if it's even gonna be
announced it would be kind of neat because honestly you know cables fucking
expensive so if I can get something decent for you know cheaper okay but
correct me if I wrong if net neutrality this whole thing about that the
websites will soon be able to block whatever the I'm sorry internet
providers will soon be able to be able to block whatever they want goes through
um do you think Comcast is gonna have this they'll just be like a block
unless Microsoft is somehow bought in to the providers and they kind of have done
this with ESPN like when you connect to the ESPN it shows in the corner when I
connect it says brought to you by Comcast like it knows what you're
connecting to them through it's possible so either there's gonna be an agreement
or this little TV network that they're doing might be their own set of channels
like it's not gonna be tied to regular TV I mean do you remember about a year
ago it had come out that before Conan signed the deal with TBS he had
entertained the notion about doing a weekly show or a nightly show on Xbox
Live have been awesome and that's why I think there's a lot of truth to this
because I think Microsoft's been trying to build this for some time and they
they have a similar service in UK although granted it's not their own
channel so I don't know I don't know where it's gonna fall I think I think
there absolutely will will be at least one new Microsoft channel in this and of
course MSNBC this is what does MS stand for in MSNBC so at least those two
channels but yeah I mean I don't if you get your cable internet through a cable
provider your cable providers gonna be pissed that this whole thing is going on
they'll try to stop it yeah and maybe even through nefarious purposes it'll be
it'll be about bandwidth caps and all that garbage so we'll see anyhow other
news about other things going on at e3 Q games is going to be showing three
titles at e3 please note that they are this is not the same thing as Q
entertainment I had actually made that mistake a little earlier on I thought
this is about Q entertainment no Q games is the company that makes like pixel
junk shooter and pixel they make all those games they are apparently they
have like a preview online for one other pixel junk game and it was a little bit
weird that title it was a pixel junk lifelike they had done a little preview
of that apparently they are going to do two unannounced projects at e3 could
they be more pixel junk games seems to be a lot of what they do now I bet one
of them will be but one of them might be something a little new maybe for another
console or something like that IDK but not the same as Q entertainment who
makes luminous and and you know it's a rez and all that child of eden mizuguchi
studio yeah different so there you go well we would move on to another story
of dark soccer left the studio so let me just yell at Loki some more what are you
yelling about how right I am but I was getting some dinner okay it's Dan made
pasta Alfredo anyway well how about some sim stuff although this is not the
cool type of sims news I wanted this actually makes me kind of sad but I'll
go ahead and tell everybody there's going to be a new standalone game on
Xbox 360 ps3 and the 3ds that is sims 3 pets and they said that it's going to be
a standard expansion on the PC and Mac but I don't know if it's gonna be as
awesome as what I'm hoping basically you can control your pets and you can breed
them and share them the Xbox 360 version will have Kinect capabilities you can
control the sims and their pets with voice commands and then he's like make
out and then they'll make out that type of thing but pets will for the 3ds will
have a pedometer so you get more karma points the more that you walk and you
can use it to buy in-game items and then with the street pass you can get pets to
other pets owners so there you go I'm just hoping that it I would rather that
for the PC one that it works a lot more like the old pets expansion did know you
have you can build your dog house and you can have your cat and you have to
clean up your cat's poo and that type of thing I'd make a big fat shirmy sounds
like fun well sims is for people who don't want to pay second life but you
know it's a lot more fun I don't know maybe they want to play second life by
themselves but like now I have to get generations if I want to play this one
it's RPM it's roleplay masturbation it's self-serving I'm kidding me the
odds of the Sims is what the still the best-selling PC game ever right pretty
much I don't even think Wow beat it so there you go all right let's travel the
world and look at some release dates if you don't want to get the Sims maybe
there's something else coming out to a store near you very soon this week
there's actually quite a few things coming out it's just kind of nice well
certain things off infamous two on the PlayStation 3 that's gonna be coming out
this week red faction Armageddon coming out on PlayStation 3 Xbox 360 and PC
let's see also this week
operation flashpoint Red River that's gonna be coming out on PlayStation 3
Xbox 360 and PC as well see here I really wish these lists would load up
faster pretty much the big releases this week the rest is just crap leave it at
that well you got these games in a bunch of crap that's what's coming out this
yeah I mean I think they have like a fucking triple pack for Ben 10 or some
garbage like that if you know that's your thing then cool what other garbage
do they have here Duke Nukem critical mass but that's not actually coming out
at that time Oh Green Lantern of course there's a movie tie-in game for that
which I'm sure it'll be just wonderful that's on PlayStation 3 we and Xbox 360
oh and DS and 3ds because that's a good 3ds title right there
oh yeah and then I forgot because this is actually about a week from today we
play motion will be coming out for Nintendo this is the innovative content
they have
oh hey we play sold really well let's make another one of those so that'll be
coming out from Nintendo with a black Wii U remote plus awesome that's it all
right moving on to Japanese release dates what's coming out over there on
the Xbox 360 on June 9th the Gears of War twin pack it's a platinum collection
now so a little bit of a price reduction for those of you guys in Japan also
Phantom Breaker in a limited edition red faction Armageddon and riot act 2 goes
into the platinum collection so that is also getting a price reduction riot act
2 is crackdown
what's their version of crackdown moving on to other consoles such as the
PlayStation 3 red faction Armageddon there as well real got to cool comes out
of the end is what that's called that is coming out on the ninth from Sega this
is a Yakuza zombie game
yeah that looks pretty cool could be interesting
are they bringing that over here I don't know it's not been announced yet so Yakuza
zombies maybe that's something you'll see any three next week localized
version of that on the Nintendo Wii nothing on the 3ds though fish on comes
out this week you guessed it it's a fishing game and it's 3d yay I would
have never guess it's a fishing game and lastly on the Sony PSP really not a lot
this week there's another even galleon limited edition thing it's a patchy game
trashy so I'm thinking that is what another Pachinko Evangelion game looking
at the screenshots another yeah it's like a little slot machine little
gambling games little mini games gambling slots that because there's a
revamped Evangelion series out so of course it's been getting big side
product reboot so there you go that's it does it for your Japanese releases in the
UK we have a few things we have on the 7th Super Street Fighter 4 arcade
edition and it will be out in the arcade Xbox 360 and ps3 on the 8th we have
Beyond Good and Evil HD and then on the 10th we have Arcana Hearts 3 infamous 2
Red Faction Armageddon White Knight Chronicles 2 and Duke Nukem forever
that's it forever and ever and stuff and ever did Loki just break in the song I
think you did a little bit I said never this is suddenly playing out like an
episode of Glee all right Loki so I almost made me gag on my food Rob thank
you tell me Loki what's going on what's going on what's going on as we have
rumors about the Wii successor this is stuff that we've all kind of heard about
before this is coming from Nikkei and this is basically the same publication
that also predicted the DSI to DSI excel the 3ds now they're predicting stuff for
the new Wii console or new Nintendo console apparently they are saying that
it's coming out on the let the second half of 2012 obviously fourth quarter
makes sense and that it will also have you the six inch touchscreen on the
controller yeah they are basically repeating what everybody else has been
saying and also apparently there is supposed to be having some sort of
camera on the actual controller as well they're saying that the company
omnivision who's working with Apple on its iPhone I'm supplying them with
cameras is also apparently supplying a Nintendo with cameras as well so
interesting that they're gonna do that and there was one other rumor that
didn't make our show roll because it was very very very last-minute but the
rumor is that Nintendo's next console might be called Nintendo that's right
that's how much effort they're putting into their console they don't even want
to fucking name it I you know what I actually don't think it's that terrible
the name I think there was a rumor that the Wii was gonna be called that that
it's just the Nintendo that whole reboot idea I I actually don't think it's a
terrible idea because you know if you go back to when all we had was the Nintendo
it was like hey you want to come over to my house and play Nintendo it was just
it became like a verb you know what I mean like Xeroxing Kleenex one of those
types of things so calling it the Nintendo Nintendo I don't think it's a
terrible name I could see like Nintendo HD or something like that I think most
people's reaction will be oh okay but I don't think you can say that's a bad
name if to be fair the original Nintendo was really called the Nintendo
Entertainment System yeah so if they're calling this just the Nintendo it is a
new name but I don't I actually don't believe it I I think because to call the
system your company when you're trying to also launch a 3ds thing side-by-side
I actually don't buy it I would I would give more credit to like Nintendo HD or
Nintendo with a very small suffix to it mm-hmm so let's see Randy in our term
says not Nintendo the Nintendo Rama says the next console called Nintendo I
fucking called that two weeks ago dude you gotta wait till Tuesday for you get
to parade that salacious pop to play Nintendo is still relevant vernacular in
my opinion so if they want to make a play on that it's not that surprising
that's kind of where I'm at my mom still calls it all Nintendo when I showed her
Mortal Kombat she was like oh you're gonna fire up the Nintendo okay maybe
not like that but you know she saw the same to her so we'll see anyhow one of
the story I want to get to you before we get to the classic game of the week and
this is important this has to do with of course fundraising efforts that are
still going on for Japanese tsunami relief guys it doesn't fix itself
overnight this fundraising effort is going to go on for years and years you
know again not to bring up really bad memories of the past but when hurricane
Katrina happened that took years to clean up and some would argue there's
still cleanup efforts that go on to this day so you know Japan is still in need
of help for tsunami relief and I think this is a great I love this gamers doing
good stuff stories play for Japan is going to be an album that is going to be
coming out we've talked about it a few times on the show before the track list
was announced this week that's the new news just going over some of the cool
things that are going to be on here there's original songs here a kiriyama
oka has a song called X on emo let's see Koji Kondo has a Super Mario medley on
two piano pianos meets uso Suzuki play for you
Tommy Tallarico greater lights so it's not just folks in Japan but it's Western
composers as well it's it's gonna be a great lineup so watch the the thing that
a kiriyama mocha was talking I did not watch the video I do have it here but
did you watch it yes it is what you think really good I mean what was in it
just talking about you know working with people from all over the world that
worked in the the industry specifically related to music and getting some of the
best things out there and that everything was going towards Japan relief
I mean it was it was really just thanking people involved and thinking
people to buy it and saying hey for all of you following us we recognize we have
a rolled a world audience and that type of thing awesome oh also how could I
forget no boo-wee Matsu has a new song every new morning you know no boo-wee
Matsu anyhow 100% of the proceeds from the play for Japan the album will go
straight to the Japanese Red Cross more information available play for Japan
org but I think this is great too it will be released in early June on the
iTunes store so I mean you know argue if you will if you hate Apple or whatever
but it is a huge store gonna be very easy and what I like about it is that I
remember a time three years ago it was very hard to find video game music on
iTunes now it seems like it's really broken through and it's pretty easy to
find a lot of the newer soundtracks on there so uh props to iTunes who
hopefully will be featuring that so that'll be available for sale again a
hundred percent of the proceeds going to the Japanese Red Cross play for Japan
org let's get into the classic game of the week every week here on the show
we'd like to highlight a game from gaming's past dark soccer likes to jump
into the vault and say hey look while you're talking about your newfangled
Nintendo's of the present I remember Nintendo's back in my day back when we
played awesome games such as this one yes bionic commando for the NES and I
could have gone over bionic commando the arcade version but I didn't because it's
not as great in Japan it was known as Hitler no Fuka Fukatsu top secret which
means the resurrection of Hitler top secret and it's kind of based off of the
87 bionic commando this one came out in 88 you basically have to explore
different stages and you play as lad Spencer who is going to rescue the guy
from the first game who was called Super Joe who was captured by the Empire you've
got to go stop the Empire of the the the general of the Imperial forces and who
is completing the project himself so you have to go and rescue Super Joe and lead
the FF battalion or double force battalion who were all commandos who use
wired guns rescue him so you've got a stage select map and you move around the
map screen and you can choose to move to different areas but you have to go back
and go through these overhead areas to get to different places there's 19 areas
in the game 1 through 12 or combat and 13 and 19 are all neutral areas where
you can't fight at all the if you fire your weapon at all in those areas you'll
be attacked by key peacekeeping force and but these are places where that you
can get information and items there's also green enemy trucks on the map
selection that will try to block your helicopter and if you fly into one of
these while you're traveling you have to battle the troops and this is the
overhead part oh it's like you know it's kind of like commando so you can
actually kill certain enemies to get additional continues so you've got a
bionic arm so you can't jump you just use the arm and you latch on and can
swing yourself at 45 degrees or you can go up or exactly right so you've got
different ways that you can move but it's really just those three ways you
can also use the arm to deflect some bullets and grab different enemies and
items and then you also get to communicate with your forces to get
information and you can tap into the enemy communication although sometimes
they will send a squadron to attack you if they detect you and sometimes you get
bullets from killing people because whenever I shoot somebody I get bullets
so at any rate there were clearly changes that were made to the game as
you can probably tell from the Japanese title the whole thing was basically
about fighting Nazis the Empire was like a neo-nazi nation and they used a
swastika for their logo so of course when it came out over here they changed
the logo and everything and they changed you know things to the Imperial forces
and blah blah although the end boss still looks like Hitler but they call
him master D like hi we kind of know who that is except you do get to see his
head explode which is pretty cool because he was a fuckhead yeah and I got
to say Tiger Claw in the charm says this is this game is from an era before the
ESRB so they were able to get away with some gore on an NES game that was just
because the ESRB that was Nintendo's own policy to get rid of the gore but yeah
heads exploding you didn't see that in many games no and it was a gory ass
explosion I mean it was like everywhere so yeah there have been other remakes
there was a portable version of bionic commando on the Gameboy in 1992 that was
based off of the NES game but it was turned into a futuristic one because
this was actually set in the 80s when it was made in the 80s and then there was
of course bionic commando rearmed that was developed by grin and it came out in
night in 2008 for PlayStation 3 Xbox 360 and PC and the sequel that came out
February 2011 and then the original NES bionic commando was featured on a game
boy advanced compilation is club Capcom classics mini mix which also included
Strider and mighty final fight two really good games well maybe not in a
strider but still so uh there's also a book a novel ization that was based off
of an S version so the main characters called Jack Marx and he lost his arm
when ninjas attacked his hotel room and kidnapped Super Joe so they replaced it
sounds like a Michael Bay movie no they replaced it with a bionic limb with a
grappling hook and other neato things so there's different things you know the
book was super toned down and they didn't kill anybody although certain
things like some of the deaths of Hal and kilt are kept in and they just sort
of skim over most of the stuff that goes on so they can fit the book and there's
an illustrated bionic commando story actually on a website that I will be
linking in the chat room and if you're not in a chat room oh well too bad so
here you can find out about Super Joe and about spencer alright there it is
your classic game of the week bionic commando for the NES not to be confused
with the arcade version or a Ziba keeps asking about in the chat room the
Commodore 64 version which I don't even remember playing but I'm pretty sure it
was based off the arcade more than was the NES speaking of which you did see
the magazine that I linked you right retro gamer oh yeah is doing a Commodore
64 special oh it's hot that's hot as well as the anniversary of Street
Fighter we need more Commodore 64 games in our classic game of the week well
guess who didn't play no I know I every week that you're not here I end up doing
something for comfort she picked the week after huh we'll see we'll see okay
good all right do you want to do the segment or me no it's your it's dark
soccer is game of the week maybe I'll pick something all right I've covered
stuff that have imported to the six to maybe I'll pick a spectrum game okay
that works or a vet track or just specter was a great PC game back in the
day I'll pick a vet Rex game all right maybe anyhow that's gonna do it for part
a of orange launch radio but don't go anywhere we got a busy part B tonight
your Twitter topics as you send those in hurry up get a minute twitter.com slash
olr and we got rapid-fire news news about Call of Duty's elite system
that's been catching a lot of press this week also news about 3ds shop we're
gonna get into and our e3 predictions we're gonna get into those as well in
just a little bit when we come back with more of orange lounge radio
welcome back everybody to orange lounge radio we are live here on June the 5th
2011 at all games calm for the 415th episode if you can believe it of orange
lounge radio you know there's this cool little thing that the fans created I'm
out there on the internet it's orange lounge dot wick it's either orange house
radio or orange lounge dot wiki a dot-com it's the olr wiki and you can
actually go in there and there's actually a compiled list of every
episode we ever did and it's like keep scrolling keep scrolling keep scrolling
it's pretty impressive yeah we're gonna be going on ten years next year so all
right anyhow we don't want to toot our own horn unless it is talking about I
can toot our horn if we want unless it's talking about the e3 coverage we're
gonna bring you next week Tuesday and Wednesday night 7 p.m. Pacific 10 o'clock
Eastern at you stream a little something new for us but it'll be cool because we
can play around with video and visuals a little bit so that'll be available to my
god you all right over there I'll be available on you stream and if you're
really good because you can do you stream broadcasting from your phone now
maybe I'll do a you stream broadcast of us getting Bobby on California screaming
I have to explain what just happened oh what happened I ran over the cord for my
headphones and then when I moved my chair it ran over the cord of the
microphone and yanked it out of my hand huh and then I had it all the way
wrapped around my legs and then I rolled over my foot ouch sorry everybody here
at klutz no no all right just accident prone all right let's uh let's get to
plugs for the spin-off shows then we'll get to rapid-fire news so quickly the
spin-off shows the other shows that we do when we're not doing olr comic
insanity and we're at infamous net and a new episode will be up on Tuesday so go
there and listen to us to do it with Mar and Marvel and Dan Jeddah comics best
little horde house in Azeroth or horde house for short available at horde house
calm we just taped an episode today we're usually on Thursdays but Thursday
didn't work this week so we kind of have a bridge episode because there's not
going to be one next week but it was a good episode tonight I mean they're all
good right but it was a good discussion and I especially consider we had a lot
of it done last minute some good old Warcraft talk so if you're into Wow at
all or you're just Wow curious come on by to horde house calm okay let's move
on with some rapid-fire news and there's a lot this week and then of course your
tweets so you better get those in because we're almost done twitter.com
slash olr by the way speaking of Twitter I want to get a plug out for this
because Bobby is helping us with those e3 wrap-up shows he's gonna be telling
us he's gonna be helping us get interviews he's gonna be I mean they're
like mostly his shows probably think about it but no we'll be here given our
smart ass commentary but I do want to say about Bobby speaking of Twitter if
you're not following Bobby on Twitter you should be because he's kind of doing
he's he's biting an idea we did a couple years ago but with permission we told
me good that is you drive him on the show floor he is very minimal
appointments so if you're like Bobby I heard this game might be on the show
floor and nobody's covering it he'll go find out for you so all that stuff that
used to be in Kensha Hall that's now kind of sprinkled throughout the East
Halls and West Halls he'll go find that stuff for you I need to know what not to
miss putting out so there right now there's the first moon game but there's
seriously Twin Cities or Twin Town yes we we demand that Bobby goes to Natsume's
booth finds the largest chibi thing that they have on display in the booth and
get a picture with it it's harvest moon come on it's always harvest moon no one
year they had the the tulip game they were showing the game was great and it
always come out you run up and kiss people it did come out as a GameStop
exclusive but um I want I don't want a cow I want cow swag from the harvest moon
people I have like a pig from them I have a sheep somewhere have their pig
but I want a handsome I don't want a pig it's not kosher should I get on to rapid
fire news yes please sir okay resistance tool pack is coming out July 5th it is
basically resistance one and two for one low price plus you get a few extra skins
and why not you get a multiplayer skin that's the Capelli skin and also you're
also getting some maps as well the aftermath map pack in skin bundle with
the race skin multiplayer skin for resistance to offer 40 bucks you know I
actually may pick this up because I sold back resistance one a while ago and I
never really finished resistance to before I sold back and I'm really
looking forward to number three so I have to pick it up again pretty cool so
also this is kind of interesting because usually you hear about these type of
things when people are doing their own kind of portable console mods but they're
actually selling portable Dreamcast now these are not necessarily I think
official you know Dreamcast items actually sanctioned by Sega or something
but it's actually a portable system it's gonna go for 38,000 yen or you're
roughly four hundred and seventy dollars u.s. and that's kind of crazy it does
look something looks like something like Ben Heck would put out I mean very
vacuum formed shell and whatnot but uh yeah if you're really interested in
portable Dreamcast seriously you're better off building your own because it
be way cheaper way cheaper and then finally if you wanted to pick up the you
draw and you don't own a Wii you can now do that because it'll be coming on 360
and PlayStation 3 HD you draw HD you draw it's getting it's kind of some
enhancements it's going to be a multi-touch tablet it's going to have a
high-definition input 2,000 by 1600 resolution and you know you'll be able
to do the pinch and stretch rotation area HD it's a built-in tilt sensors now
you can draw penises in HD and what I of course will be coming with you draw
studio or it's in this case is going to be kind of a souped-up you draw studio
you draw studio instant artists with tutorials and a new interface and stuff
like that of course there's gonna be supporting the different you draw titles
like Pictionary and that kind of thing I don't know it's kind of interesting just
from what I've seen with you draw on the Wii the support ports kind of a because
it's only teach cute and stuff out and now I know that we heard rumors that
maybe Nintendo might put something out for you know everyone's hoping for Mario
Paint but I don't know that's that's a stretch I think but at least teach who's
supporting it they've got you know the Wii I want to say there's about five
games out for now so it's not bad Frisbee in our term says get a real tablet dark
Tetsuya says hey look at it this way the Bob Ross game lives on you can paint
happy little trees but let's be real they're all drawing penises with it by
the way one thing I forgot to mention about that Duke Nukem forever demo
there's a whiteboard in it that seems to exist for no other reason than for
twelve-year-olds to draw penises on it yep and then the the onlookers will
commentate oh that sounds like a good plan Duke you can draw a wiener on it
and I'm not talking about that was done in a video for the demo I guess it was
time to penis we have not asked that question in a very long time but
whenever there is a new peripheral announced you always have to ask the
question how long before someone either draws a dick on it or puts their dick
in it real you draw time to replace five seconds it'll be the first thing many
people draw that wiener I think it'd be cool though if they did you know but
they really need a new magic pen Jo game seriously that would be awesome break
man in our chat room says 3d vaginas are ugly yeah I saw Cloverfield to anything
else that's it oh hey then let's get to more news Michael J Fox is going to be
in the back to the future games yeah that's pretty cool because he wasn't in
the first few but they are going to bring him back for the fifth and I guess
the last game in the back to the future of course these are the telltale games
episodic now here's the thing they are not going to just simply replace AJ
Laskio who's been doing the voice and apparently doing a very good job Michael
J Fox is going to be in the conclusion the rumor is that he's one of McFly's
ancestors so yeah it's not a rumor that's actually they have video of it
okay so I guess the video came out between the story I'm reading and now so
yeah that's cool though that they've been able to work him in like that I
think that's really cool you know a lot of people been talking about that new
x-men movie and apparently it's really good it is I haven't seen it yet it's
really good it's way better than three three is poop three didn't happen this
movie is really good are there any good one-liners like do you know what
lightning what happens when lightning hits a toad no but my favorite line in
the whole movie is fuck off and you'll know what I'm talking about when you see
it all right you got it but here's the thing uh as far as the x-men goes the
reason why I bring it up and I forget why I bring it up why did I bring it up
oh yeah we were talking about Patrick Stewart and Ian McKellen were originally
supposed to have a cameo in it as I guess playing and you know the older
versions kind of like they did in the original x-men movie but they cut it or
they didn't film it and nixed it because they didn't want the new x-men movie
tied to the original at all but I thought that was kind of sad because
Patrick Stewart and Ian McKellen like oh my god they could read the phone book
and I would just be like yes tell me more and they kind of epitomize the
characters that they played I mean they really did is professor Xavier of course
Patrick Stewart can play anybody and he would but I that person I hear the new
kids are really good too like just as younger versions they do a good job I
think they did a good job but but it's just like oh my god if somebody tried to
play a young captain Jean-Luc Picard like I don't think I'd ever be able to
believe it I tried to do that seriously he's right they did oh that's right
they did yeah seriously how fucking annoying is it that he picked Arnold
Schwarzenegger be mr. freeze over Patrick Stewart it would have been perfect oh
perfect give me started but no you know what it's a good thing Patrick Stewart
stayed away yeah you know what it would have killed him I mean seriously it
would've been real Julia all over again all right hey la noir which is a game
that Loki's loaning me I'm very excited I can take it out of my queue la noir
has got some download content that's gonna be coming out DLC is gonna come
what may 17th all the way through July 12th and there's DLC cases that you can
download one of them's called reefer madness I don't think it plays into the
movie but hey the naked city let's hope we see some more nude people yeah that's
coming out of May 31st for four bucks anyway if you want to buy all this stuff
a la carte you can pay $20 for it but you can also pre buy all of it for ten
bucks with what's called the rock star pass but you have until June 14th to
take advantage of that otherwise it's going up to twelve dollars after that so
there you go lots of stuff coming out that there's even I guess challenges a
new suits and guns and whatever horse armor but also some the social social
club things may 17th interesting stuff so la noir DLC speaking of download
stuff and all this stuff Capcom has reversed a decision we reported on no
actually we didn't report on this last week because I think we weren't here so
Capcom did take that DRM maybe this what I've seen you remember talking about it
so it was a couple weeks ago that this annoying DRM was going to be in Super
Street Fighter 4 on the PC that if you are not connected to the internet it
won't bork the game but you'll be limited to 15 fighters and of course
people raised hell on the forums and Capcom said okay okay we're back and
down yeah you we will be able to play as everybody even if not connected to the
internet however as one would logically as expect you won't have online
multiplayer replay sharing or watching and achievements unless you're online
and logged in which yeah that does make sense I think so there you go the
consumers win I think moving on we do have other news there is a Final Fantasy
5 rated by the ESRB for a PSN release in North America which is pretty good so
we'll be getting lots of classic games and hopefully it's going to have the
same treatment that uh that three in those had you know then we have Duke
Nukem forever download content details we have the first download pack that has
four weapons a minigun a new tube a sticky grenade and a BFG which we all
know what BFG stands for DLC number two is a deathmatch maps there's EDF base
LKR and map three it's just called map three and then the third pack is 15 new
single-player maps arm wrestling and the impregnator weapon and a karaoke machine
so hey also if you've pre-ordered the game you get the first DLC for free and
then the last news is in Batman Arkham City you can play as Catwoman and she
gets her own storyline she better not be played by Halle Berry she looks pretty
hot don't get me wrong Halle Berry is hot but that movie not hot no but she
looks pretty hot that's it nice all right let's get into what some Twitter
topics now yeah that's right twitter.com slash olr and every week you guys can
send us your tweets show us your tweets as we like to say and we read them as
long as they don't suck well let's start off Twitter this week with Oh Fiedelt61
tweeted us this and I don't think we actually covered this elsewhere on the
show trek movie.com reports that a video game set in the Star Trek movie universe
is coming in 2012 our soccer did you hear about this it seems right up your
alley Star Trek online it's gonna be set in the Abrams Trek universe I'm
assuming to maybe bridge the new movie because the new movies out next year too
right it is I thought they were targeting 2012 anyway well anyway it's
gonna be an original story an unprecedented co-op experience players
can play as Kirk and Spock so now you can be ZQ it's gonna be its own story
continues the adventure of the Star Trek movie the press release that was
released says that the game is filled with action-packed combat as Kirk and
Spock must work together to stop a legendary enemy race bent on conquering
the galaxy the story is being written by Mary Ann Kraswick she wrote for God of
War and she's a BAFTA Award winner and the writer producers of the new Star
Trek films so I imagine this will bridge things this is also the first full Star
Trek video game since 2007 they are not counting Star Trek online but they would
say that Star Trek conquest the game that came out from Bethesda because
that's what most people said about it it will be coming out in 2012 I I'll check
it out heck yeah I like Star Wars enough or Star Trek well I have an all tab open
with the Star Wars story that's coming later my bad Essex 22 tweeted us and
said just curious what you guys might consider the best downloadable co-op ps3
title want to find something a friend and I can play online any suggestions
best co-op downloadable title I would suggest on review I miss what's that
portal to you PC yeah I don't think you can download that though PC download it
for ps3 I would say Laura Croft and the Guardian of Light is a heck of a lot of
fun it's kind of like an arcade game but you could do the co-op mode that was fun
I had a lot of fun playing co-op in that that would be my suggestion assuming you
don't like already have it on 360 or steam I would definitely check out at
least the demo for the Laura Croft and the Guardian of Light I'm actually
really looking forward to that new Tomb Raider game I gotta say because you know
the the download title made me interested in Tomb Raider again and I
kind of like the direction they're going in with a new one the new trailers pretty
hot Loki I don't know if you mess around too much with co-op games online but
anything you can think of that might downloadable it's hard because I'm not
sure what type of games you really like and ps3 is also kind of limited with I
mean not as much stuff jumps to mind like they don't have quake 3 arena they
don't have in the kind of the same selection have perfect dark and some of
the same stuff that the Xbox does the pixel junk games are insanely popular I
would check those out too so things to think about more tweets coming to us
from the bacon bits tweeted us with something the Nintendo controller
spotted at e3 but then when I bring this up in a new window I'm like this is
somebody trying to be lolsy I think because what this is a picture of is I
think it's just an N 64 controller all taped up yeah somebody just posted an N
64 controller I think we'll see there although that would be kind of funny if
they just use the 64 controller all over again but I kind of doubt it
spasminator tweets us usual drill free TV shows on the PSN store also there's
free movie rentals too I gotta email him offline he's something about he set us
up an account that has like movies for me to watch like shit tons of anime
that's like what they have on the PlayStation Network store so that I've
been kinda inundated ever since PlayStation Network came back up which
by the way happened this week and has anyone tried to download the free games
because yeah I don't forget what did you download I downloaded Super Stardust HD
and I have infamous in my queue as well yes you get to p.s. 3 and 2 p.s. be nice
huh download some anyways yes you should take up the opportunity going to some
tweets from a blue swim her to LR play the opening song to Katamari Damacy on
the break and thought of retro force go orange on foodie a question what will
you be snacking on during the e3 pressers I'm gonna nom a bag of spicy
sweet chili Doritos popcorn yet me to kettle corn vegetables because we have a
bunch of them kettle corn specifically doing the Michael Jackson doing the
Michael Jackson thriller gift especially during a Sony suppressor and I will be
tweeting as well I can't wait to read your tweets I need that we need to look
into that cover it live software I don't even know if you could use that I know
you don't think it's a big deal but people people people love their Loki
rage it's just gonna be the problem is I have to watch them at work I have no
problem doing that because my boss is gone and his boss is gone so it's not
like it's not related to your job these are the games you're gonna be selling at
Christmas time I think you do have a right to watch this at work problem is
they let go so many people it's like I stupid Nazis don't let me know I'll just
lock the door what they're gonna do lock the door I'll lock the door to the
conference room we're gonna be watching on nice HGTV there you go
act deft tweets us what game or gaming related news would truly surprise you if
it happened on e3 this week now we are gonna get into e3 predictions a little
later but I'm gonna allow this question because it's not talking about what do
you think will happen this is talking about what would surprise you if it
happened is there anything that would truly surprise you if it happened Sony
doesn't fuck up that surprised me the f-zero game on the Nintendo console I
don't think it's gonna happen so I would say it would genuinely surprise me I
would be tickled pink when I go down there on Thursday to pick up Bobby I
might just have to rush the doors if the f-zero game happens there's not really
much that could be surprising to me I like so I'm going in the route to this
with really low expectations it's so hard to call things like that too
because when I think of like surprises I think of things that literally come the
fuck out of nowhere like I would say Gabe Newell getting up on stage at the
Sony press conference and saying hey by the way I don't hate Sony anymore and
we're gonna integrate steam in the PlayStation that was a fucking surprise
like and that I I couldn't have called that I don't think anyone could have and
Final Fantasy 14 as lolsy as that came up as that was two years ago let us not
forget when Jack Trenton was on stage and said we're gonna be delivering Final
Fantasy 14 everybody was like oh he just fucked up he meant 13 too and no it was
fucking 14 was coming out already even though really was 11 but you know yeah
11 HD surprises are so hard to foresee um I would say like a very strange
partnership especially from Microsoft and I know that's so vague I know the
return of Xbox live experience is like 1 versus 100 I sadly think that shit is
gone which pisses me off I think it was a great thing that they had but if if
they were to say hey we're bringing back the multiplayer game show type events
the live events on Xbox that would truly surprise me
where the fuck are my Burger King Kinect games Burger King Kinect part 2 that
would be your no they Burger King Kinect part 1 where the hell are they they
were they promised me that they're gonna have some exclusive Burger King King
Kinect games and I have yet to see these I was already the Bible because they
were gonna be terrible I know the Nintendo console projects imagery any
type of projector built into the Nintendo that would fucking surprise me
because that is not happening the holodeck the holidays holodeck announced
and it's coming to you from on live because nobody believed that shit would
work either and look there it is on life presents the holodeck alright I don't
want to miss these tweets from Tiger claw let me get to these top gun in days
of thunder to get blu-ray game slash movie combos did you hear about that
they're selling yeah I know packs I've been selling those have you really
known about that for a while and they sound lame it's no it's seriously it's
lame here's here's what they're doing they're doing basically what they did
with the Watchmen where they take the really shitty shitty PlayStation Network
games that sold like garbage and then they throw it in with the movie so
that's what you're gonna get you're gonna get the really shitty garbage top
gun game and the really terrible you know days of Thunder game awesome hey at
least you get a movie I gotta read this comment in chat guys you don't our
term says big brother on Xbox live arcade would be awesome if they don't
make it I will I've got to say this I was walking through Target and I saw
their Wii section of games and excuse me strawberry part um I saw for sale on the
Wii the survivor game that's now available on the Wii and look I'm a fan
of reality trash TV and I do watch almost every episode survivor stuff and
I picked up this box I just started laughing at how horrible this game
looked now have you seen the amazing race for the week I've heard that's
garbage too oh I'm sure it is but I mean like actually a survivor game or
something like that on Xbox live arcade in the party thing or whatever might not
suck if they do it right it could actually be really fucking interesting
but I just don't trust anyone to get it right because I look at this stuff
that's on the Wii and I'm like oh the Wii game shows that work best are the
minimalist ones like Wheel of Fortune that's pretty hard to fuck up jeopardy
again pretty hard to fuck up pressure luck no whammies no whammies stop I mean
somehow game show network fucked it up when they revived it but you know what I
mean classic pressure luck is still gold anyhow also from Tiger Claw penny arcade
comic to be adapted into a movie I had not heard about this have you heard
anything about this yeah it's a spin-off it's just basically what else is the
games didn't work out so well no it's not even a spin it's it's like a little
three panel comic that they did the story of the Divx player no it's not
even it's none of the penny arcade characters it's basically this kid who
is the new kid the new kid yeah he's moving it you know normally it's moving
to a new town well it's moving to a new planet and the planet has three-quarters
of the gravity that you know they had on earth or whatever and so I'm guessing
he's kind of like you know super strong and fast or whatever because you know
you would be if you went to a planet with less gravity well the guys but
everyone else would too you know no no if they grew up on that planet though
it'd be they wouldn't be super strong or fast or whatever they would be adapted
to that gravity where it's like it'd be just like you know for example if you
had leg weights and you're running with leg weights all the time you take them
off and they'll sudden you know you feel your logic there yeah I would question
how much are the penny arcade people gonna actually be involved in this
because they are pretty good writers and they write some really funny hilarious
insightful comments and they their commentary on gaming culture has always
been really good but then I read in this story here Paramount has tapped Gary
Witte a former PC gamer editor-in-chief and book of Eli screenwriter to pen the
new kid and I roll my eyes this has nothing to do with the penny arcade
comic it just it happens to be this is a comic that they also made okay none of
the characters are in it now the funny stuffs in I get that but I'm saying the
penny arcade comic proves that they're good writers and I would like to see
what they it's just like okay the South Park you know Trey and Matt are fucking
hilarious I want to see the Book of Mormon play on that alone like it has
nothing to do and I realized that that universe the South Park have nothing in
common except recurring Mormon jokes over and over but I want to see that
play based on the fact that I appreciate their work on the show and I think
they're very good satirists that's what I'm getting at does that make sense
oh all right and how that does it for tweets tonight twitter.com slash olr
send us more tweets for next week or send your tweets over to Bobby because
he's gonna be roaming the halls of e3 and he is your little eyebo that you can
command to go look at things and by the way he did accept the challenge of going
to find the giant stuffed animal at the Natsume booth and he will get chibi
wolf and a cow by the way you're not getting in the car to Disneyland without
swag for dark Sakura and sky probably Dan too no just for me all right let's
I'm giving him such a hard time all right let's move on more news plenty
more news and the mailbag and our e3 predictions just around the corner yes
so Activision not to lose out on a money-making opportunity they have
decided to create Call of Duty elite it is a paid digital platform being created
by beachhead studios built around right now modern warfare 3 and now the service
does have free aspects to it and this would include also like you know you
know guild making and you know you know sharing videos and that kind of stuff it
also you know tracks your stats you know very think of it like the halo waypoint
almost a little bit they have of course I guess they're saying part of the fee
will go towards a customer service operation that needs I guess that their
supporting the back and forth so they're saying you know it's gonna have a small
monthly fee and maybe like eight bucks or something and I don't know it just it
sounds interesting I guess you know especially since you know a lot of the
players for Call of Duty are really just online heavy it's really community
driven so it makes sense that they would be doing something like this also it's a
way for them to sell more you know subscriptions and make money and what
not make every month off of World of Warcraft from Blizzard how could we make
money every month offer other big games yeah why bother having them you know
share videos on YouTube for free when they can do it on our service and we
could just take down all the videos on YouTube well I don't think they would do
that but and I think a lot of its you know still free but they have like a
video out there that you can check out that has kind of some of the you know
features of it and stuff it sounds a little bit also I don't know if anyone
remembers because it's been around for at least a few months now since Medal of
Honor but remember there's also the EA's gun club or whatever so they've got you
know that kind of thing as well going on on the EA side so yeah I guess I don't
know it makes sense that they're kind of doing this sort of stuff and I'm sure
they're gonna have like you know betas for you know paid members and stuff like
that just a way to get people it kind of think of it like the PlayStation Plus
program or something like that I don't know if you're hardcore that it's worth
it to you well even for those of us that don't get it quote unquote we just go
lol more money well even if you don't like for example if you're not that
hardcore into it though you know you can at least get some stuff out of the you
know the free free portion of it like they haven't you like your career stats
or all that stuff if you like the stat tracking and I think they even have the
the hot points on the map and stuff where most of the players are you know
converging on and stuff like that so I don't know it check out the free portion
if you if it's not for you then you don't have to do it it's simple as that
you know we were talking a lot on Horde house today about $25 amounts and Wow
and why people buy them and you know it some of us look at it and go why in the
hell would you spend that money on them out but for some people it's like pretty
Barbie you know so you can't it's your money spending on whatever you want hey
some details on the 3ds shop launch excite bike 3d is gonna be the free game
that is on the 3ds shop when it launches June 6th tomorrow right holy crap that's
coming out of nowhere mmm what you're shaking your finger no my my finger that
means whoop these shit okay oh you're twirling your finger my bad all right
the eShop launches this week and it's gonna be giving you excite bike 3d free
for 30 days I'm sure that will be fantastic in 3d I'm sure it will fully
utilize the power of the 3ds goddamn NES game which is the the layers that's what
those layers NES games are gonna do it this like the background is one layer
and the sprites are a front layer and it's all in effect that's it but you
know there are a lot of people will pick it up and play it and go oh but I will
download it because it's free yeah it's free but I think I'm buying any of your
other fucking games other NES games and you know spinning unfortunately it
doesn't have internet play plus how are they gonna work that out did wasn't the
original excite bike kind of borked because there was a load save mode they
could fix that we get the original excite bike was a disc game and then
when they put it on the cartridge like it just flat-out didn't work when they
really fix that I thought when they even came the virtual console though maybe I
can't remember maybe somebody in chat this is why we have a live chat room
somebody will jump in here in a moment but anyway let me give you some more
details excite bike 3d classic will be free you want after 30 days you know how
much that was such a back six bucks that's retard well that's a bunch of
tacos well it's the five dollar NES game plus a dollar premium which is
interesting that's not we points that's 599 it sounds like they're walking away
from we points that that's that's right because it was so hard to calculate we
points based on the one-to-one ratio that they had their 500 we points that's
five dollars also Game Boy ports Super Mario Land alleyway and radar mission
will all be out on day one DSI and DSI XL owners will be able to transfer most
of the DSI where purchases to the system there are some things that are not going
to be transferable I believe all of it has to do with like license things like
the Domo Coon games don't transfer over because they probably weren't licensed
for more than they came out over here I I didn't know they did either it might
only be a Japanese thing IDK well DSI where I obviously I'd never really
downloaded any DSI were so hold on though this is huge
pokey decks 3d a virtual compendium of Pokemon from black and white it is a
free download it will allow you to just look up all the information in the world
on the Pokemon 3d models StreetPass functionality you unlock random Pokemon
by exchanging data I don't know if that ties in the black why I don't think it
does it's something to do with the pokey decks and QR code support you take a
picture of your friend set it as a background layer snap a picture of a QR
code to introduce a Pokemon like what whatever I think it's also got the AR
cards or whatever support so you can do the 3d models whatever I got to admit it
sounds I just can't wait for all the fucking mudkips because you know it's
just a matter of time before we get you know Oprah introducing mudkips uh let's
see do they have that I has your mudkips also Japan and Europe you are also
getting stuff on launch day for some reason it's always got to be different
you will in Japan get mega man dr. Wiley's revenge kirby's dreamland
baseball and phantasm which was called avenging spirit over here downtown
special kuni kun no G guy geeky dio Zenon Shugo it's a
River City ransom spin-off with samurais also in the magic word Kunio also in
Japan on June 7th excite bike 3d mystery pi 3d block breaking and Xevious will be
announced or released as well which I played at last year's e3 and it was the
background on one layer and the sprites on the front layer Europe gets excite
bike alleyway Mario Land and tennis every Thursday will Europe see more
games on the 3ds so there you go all those announcements out now so they
don't have to talk about it at the press conference because they will be spending
all of their time undoubtedly talking about not just the new console but I'm
sure they will first parade out skyward sword for an update they'll parade out
3ds titles including the Mario title and maybe some surprises there on the 3ds
and then easily half to two-thirds will be about whatever this cafe thing is
slashes pop in our chat room says look under your seat it's a mudkip you get a
mudkip and you get a mudkip everyone's getting a mudkip yeah is there a be
Pokemon all right forget it well how about some other news for
Nintendo the the DS light actually will have actually today has a price
reduction it's gone down to $99 sucks for all you the bought one yesterday
yep but I guess they're just trying to clear out inventory who knows but the
games are still the games there's not getting a price reduction pro tip I saw
them foursquare I know you stopped using foursquare but there is a pretty good
deal on it still check into Toys R Us and you get buy one get one half off on
DS and 3ds titles pro tip okay I'm which I don't think I got into it on this show
I was talking about it more on the Bobby call at the end of his show but I'm
convinced whatever this Nintendo controller is their little touch screen
thing I was saying on Bobby show you know Nintendo has been making touch
screens controllers for about five six years now it's called the DS and the
bottom half of that that's gonna be your controller it's a touchscreen with
buttons you've had one all along it would be amazing if the DS would just
work as a controller but let's not let's there'll be a special new button or
there'll be something extra on this thing Rob
all right moving on Loki freestyle games I may remember them from such series as
DJ hero well thankfully they are not dead which is good apparently though I
guess they have confirmed 35 positions will be lost but they still have a
strong partnership with Activision and they're currently working on a new
innovative unannounced project and it says of course they plan to share
details about those project or the said project in the next coming months it's
good to see that they're still around hopefully we'll get Lisa DJ hero 3 out
of them yeah that would be cool I would appreciate that Rama's correcting me on
something in the chat room nope you get your money back if there's a price drop
within two weeks of purchase you get the difference back well now that really
depends on what story you buy it at but okay fine I'll play your game here and
say sucks for those that bought it 15 days ago why are you buying a DS now I
mean seriously buy something else the 3ds will slowly add value before
Christmas before Christmas you're gonna see and there will be time like you're
gonna probably see the Netflix on 3ds in action and some of this at the
conference and all this so I think the 3ds is gonna see a lot more added value
before Christmas time it's just us early adopters we got Street Fighter pilot
wings Ridge Racer IDK steel diver that's Zelda oh yeah Zelda yeah a game we
played 10 years ago it was overrated then alright love of God publisher stop
making your old games making an old game HD is not a fucking new game okay who
remembers a company called origin do you remember this company origin I believe
they didn't have the ultimate games back in the day yes the only origin I know of
is the ones that as the cosmetic company yeah well origin yeah they did the
ultimate games which is huge get this EA but origin system some time ago it was
like 20 years ago they bought it was a long time ago they're bringing back the
brand so to speak or at least the name with a direct to consumer gaming
platform here it is it's an EA store it's basically a competitor to steam EA
has launched the service and more than 150 games are already available on the
service it's also gonna have exclusive limited edition stuff like battle
field 3 Alice madness returns kingdoms of Amalur Star Wars the Old Republic is
supposedly going to be downloadable only on origin origin will have its own
application which you can find connect with friends blah blah blah download
play PC games basically they're doing everything that seems doing trying to
get a little more competition in space because let's face it the games for
Windows live thing really hasn't you know just broke through like I think
Microsoft is hoping it would apparently the service is also going to work on
mobile devices Scrabble mobile versions of battlefield 3 all of that will be on
the origin store as well speaking of Ultima randomly I did read an article
that Ultima 4 is now like free-to-play online so if you want to go back and
play like a classic RPG that will just it's as hard to it's it's just really a
difficult title the NES version really dumped it up and it still was really
hard I would check out Ultima 4 that's what RPGs were when I was a kid and we
liked it more information I'm sure at EA's press
conference which is at 1230 Pacific 330 Eastern on Monday on right now is the
orange lounge radio mailbag every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at
orange lounge radio.com and dark soccer will dive in pick a few of her favorites
and read them right now on the air well we got a bunch so I'm only gonna read
four and I picked them at random and I didn't pick any that were by the same
person okay so that was my criteria so if you're not getting read don't worry
I probably and you shouldn't get butthurt if you're not getting read I
mean I don't want to sound like we have ego here but we do have a nice
listenership we appreciate everybody that listens but when you all email us
at once we can't read it all or it would be a seven-hour show it's nothing
personal yes I would like to say that if you've got something to send us just do
it in one email I don't care if it's really long I would prefer the one email
so this one comes from Holly exactly how stupid is this guy who complained about
it and it's actually about the portal to being offended offending seriously
GLaDOS is the villain Wheatley is the villain they're supposed to make you
feel bad and insult you my husband is 200 pounds overweight and he found the
fat jokes absolutely hilarious why because they are villains how thick in
the head do you have to be to think that the game is offensive because the villain
insults people more to the point she does it in the first game so you're
telling me that the moron bought the first game heard it ignored it and then
decided to be offended the second game you know I I know why okay you know I
know why there wasn't a rapture on Saturday God look down at the world and
facepalmed I think to a god this was a ugly story last week but yeah I mean
GLaDOS was very you couldn't take GLaDOS seriously you know what I mean
like the way the character was built and Wheatley was designed to be the dumbest
moron that ever lived end quote to me that whole thing was just sensationalist
media and it's just unfortunate like yeah people are gonna get offended but
you know what we all get offended they were completely the the news quote
professionals did they ever respond to you by the way no of course not highly
unprofessional mm-hmm don't believe anything that they say more emails this
one comes through the website just wanted to get your opinions on some
things what did you think of the original gold my double-oh-seven and
perfect dark I myself enjoy these games quite a bit because I'm a big fan of
first-person shooters keep up the good work sincerely CD Thunder well um they
both made me throw up not because they were bad they were bad at all golden I
was really great but I've told the story before when I first moved out here and
lived with Dan he had a Nintendo 64 play golden I mm-hmm and I would end up
rolling over on the couch and staring at the back of the couch because I was so
nauseous that I could not watch him play so I would listen to him play golden I
was simply a landmark title like it just it did so much for first-person shooters
that's what that's why they tried to imitate it on the Wii and try to hit
gold twice but it kind of you know it just wasn't the same you know and that's
the unfortunate thing with a lot of these retro updates it's just not the
same well the first golden I came at what 15 years ago no not that long well
whenever the movie was out it was late night well yeah so I guess it's the
difference between you know trying to capture that same it's like movie remakes
now you just can't capture the same joy now perfect dark perfect dark the 361
that was a launch title I didn't care for it all but the original perfect dark
was pretty awesome and it's fun to play on Xbox Live now just just saying well
we got another one through the website this is from Cal Roo I understand that
the news is trying to blame the game okay this is probably more about the
portal thing I understand that the news is trying to blame the game for poor
dialogue and dark soccer was blaming the news channel for their poor
investigation but neither of you guys really looked at the real issue and that
is the rating the this person is using such a horrible gram there's no
punctuation in here there's none but one ellipse okay anyway so the game was
rated e 10 plus and should have been rated T so a lot of the concepts in the
game seemed to be a little over the head of the ten-year-old so let's stop
blaming games and blame the rating system well yeah the rating system is
shit anyway but I knew what adoption was when I was 10 I didn't you know it
doesn't matter I actually think the emailer has a wee bit of a point but at
the same time it's no rating boards responsibility to fill the role of a
parent and I don't know it's it's it's it's a really tough call like I get this
perspective a lot like even though you might have known what it was when you
were 10 I can see where maybe there wasn't enough warning that hey there
might be some jokes that are gonna go over a 10 years old 10 year olds head
and maybe this game really should be only played by teens and up like I gotta
be honest would I let my kid play portal I would yeah I don't think it's really
dangerous but that's but then again I don't have these sensitivities to watch
out for I got a baby to stop crying by playing portal to seriously dance cousin
was over here and her baby was crying in her lap so I asked if I could hold him
and then I held him while I was playing portal to in my lap and he thought it
was amazing let me put it this way as far as his email goes it's a fair
argument I'm just not sure I agree but I think this is a it's a valid counter
point I'll give you that I can see it I mean I honestly think that they should
just rate them the way they do movies mm-hmm then people would get it because
apparently I honestly think that a lot of people especially ones who are not
gamers and that our parents now don't want to understand it they want other
people to do their thinking for them and that's not acceptable so honestly if
you've got to answer a difficult question because you didn't do any
research into the game guess what that's on you
tricky-tricky is there more to the email or is that okay one more yeah one more
another one through the website I was picking the short ones okay a few shows
ago you picked you picked this this is towards me all a few shows ago you
picked up this old game called phantasmagoria I remember playing it when
I was 15 and absolutely loved it soon after that I played Gabriel Knight the
beast within after thinking back of those games I started to wonder if there
are any recent games out there that are point-click horrors all I've seen so far
are mysteries and unfortunately it's more aimed at children I want my horror
and gore sad face toodles sill I love sill yeah
stills still lived in amps they I don't know if she was in the capital of Holland
but she was in Dutch country and then she moved to Britain not that long ago
she's not in London but she's you know in another part of the country and yeah
we had her own a hoard house couple weeks ago she hosts the girls gone Wow
podcast which is a lot of fun you should go on that show except at the time they
tape it's probably like 3 a.m. if they do it on a weekend and I don't have
school the next day but anyway back to the question itself phantasmagoria yeah
there really hasn't been a game like that a long time there was the Silent
Hill game only was kind of point-and-click II but not quite yeah I
mean there's there's one extreme of the other I know what she's talking which
talk about the Nancy Drew games are kind of like those mystery games that they're
kind of kitty they still have those coming on we oh yeah those well and they
still come out on PC as well those things still sell pretty well um as well
for what they are I'm gonna do a quick bit of research on uh but yeah I mean if
you want to go to the console side I mean Silent Hill games still have you
know the gore and the fun stuff and not just Silent Hill but Resident Evil what
are some of the other big horror franchise series we have and click games
scary games we have monster basement 2 we have abandoned to dead-end hotel
haunted trap soul orchestrated death inculation x mortis 3 which looks pretty
gory the holes crime evidence to you know what actually game was kind of
scary this is space this is actually a point-and-click games calm you know what
else actually remember the room thank you so salacious pop is jumping up and
down in chat I have to say this amnesia because I was thinking of that game too
I'm like what's that game that was on steam amnesia yeah amnesia is supposed
to be a scary as hell title on that's on PCs I would check out amnesia for sure
and that's a point-and-click well but do you remember the little flash game
that's called the room or crimson room or something like that Rob do you
remember that I'm sorry one more time sorry I was catching up on chat do you
remember a game called like it was like crimson room or scarlet room where it
was this one where you are in a room on a bed and it's just a little flash game
but you have to figure out how to get out of the room and different stuff
happens in the room you like you find a lighter and you have to like light some
water and make steam to set off something and then you get a string
that falls out of somewhere and the whole point is trying to get out of the
room is that like don't shit your pants
no that's a whole other type of I'll see if I can find it link the chat room but
that one it wasn't really so much of a scary game per se but it was sort of
like kind of imagining yourself in that situation made it frightening that's
what I thought was interesting about it I love that game by the way don't shit
your pants it's great game is that it for emails okay I think I actually found
it the scarlet room mailbag out orange lounge reader calm if you want to send
us emails don't be butthurt if you don't get through though it happens there's
also the forms nobody freaking posts on the orange laundry forms and I think we
need to fix that we need to make that our mission this year to have some hop
and forums so we need to encourage more discussion on the forums we're gonna
work on that anyhow that's it for the mailbag yes all right we're gonna get
into a game tonight and we're gonna do this with predictions and we're gonna do
this in the style of an old board game called taboo remember the game taboo in
taboo there were certain phrases that you wanted to say but there were
certain things that you didn't want to say so the oil our hosts we're gonna go
around right now and give our predictions five things you will see at
e3 and five things you won't see at e3 so for everything that you will see at
e3 that is in indeed announced that host will earn a point now see we can't tally
this up till later in the week but for everything that you won't see that they
do say there's gonna be a buzz and that host will lose the point and the host
with the most points by whenever we have another show next Sunday after next will
win tacos yay so they'll have to buy themselves yes no I if it's not me I
will buy tacos if I win then Jamie has to make me tacos all right so here we go
five things we think will happen and five things that won't happen let's
start with the wills and we'll start with dark Sakura something you will see
at e3 this year Microsoft will announce a halo game for connect Microsoft will
announce a halo game for connect we're going on kind of a kind of a safe bet I
think going off the rumors there right but and actually I blame Dan for my
entire list so really he has to buy you tacos if I lose all right fair enough
all right so Dan Dan wants the tacos if you win and we'll see what happens all
right Loki you got one for us new Super Mario Brothers sequel announced well
that's a real safe bet you guys are playing a super easy here you should get
a half point for that one all right fine a new Super Mario Bros now I'm gonna I'm
gonna go all in I'm gonna make a crazy-ass prediction here I'm gonna say
well this isn't that crazy but I think it will be announced at e3 Diablo 3 gets
announced for console especially after having played the dungeon siege 3 demo
earlier this week I think it can be done and I think Activision is gonna really
push blizzard to put that out on the console just to test the waters we'll
see I could be full of garbage but this is just for fun right dark Sakura Sony
will talk about network security Sony will talk about network security yes
they'll talk about how great their online is now know that they're gonna
toot their own horn some more and talk about how they're the safest it's gonna
be Sony auto fellatio all right fair enough
Loki something you will see a new Grand Theft Auto sequel be announced once
again playing it very safe that's right a new Grand Theft Auto sequel announced
fair enough I'm gonna go out on limb see I'm going crazy I'm gonna say that the
hardcore we title that is going to get you back to playing Nintendo III think
it's gonna be Star Fox I think it's new Star Fox game will be announced for the
cons the new whatever console it is I think if the whole touchscreen thing is
true I could definitely see there being mapping and plotting and communications
popping up from your little cohorts but most telling of all the fact that there
is a Star Fox game in the works being ported for 3ds blast from the past to
kind of raise awareness of the franchise again I think Star Fox is gonna be the
franchise that gets announced for Nintendo its new console dark soccer
they're gonna verify the name of the new PSP the what of the new handheld
PlayStation they're gonna verify the name yes it's already leaked I said they were
going to announce it uh-huh and before I realized that it had been put out mm-hmm
so I said they're going to verify it all right and I'm gonna have to send you the
list so you can yeah you'll have to send it to me so you can pile it and look
you'll have to do that to IDK and if you guys want to throw out your ideas in
chat room chat.org laundry.com things you think will happen at e3 Loki I think
that there will be a minor price drop on the Xbox 360 console and connect
hardware announced so like a bundle thing no I'm saying they're gonna drop
the price of the system and they're also gonna drop the price of the Kinect
interesting okay try to get more people on board yeah exactly because that's
what they're pushing so you know makes sense that they would try to drop to the
price of the console down all right the last drop was back in I don't you know
when the last drop was actually um I'm gonna say that these because Soul
Calibur 5 we know it's gonna be there the Soul Calibur 5 bonus characters are
Capcom inspired this time around they're not gonna be Star Wars absolutely not
Star Wars because we've already had that and I think this time they've already
done like some of the other big franchises so I think this time Soul
Calibur 5 will have Capcom and I'm saying this because of the whole kind of
we see them working together in Tekken cross Street Fighter and Street Fighter
cross Tekken the one that comes to mind right away Dante I think Dante will be a
character in Soul Calibur 5 that's my prediction okay two more Star
Sakura um mine was more portal to download content more portal to download
content all right like oh like the valve will show off like the user creator
stuff yeah there'd be that maybe new maps that they did and more more fun all
right Loki this is kind of retarded but new
Animal Crossing game announced oh so you think that's gonna be the Nintendo title
that comes out the gate I'll be a 3ds hell for sure oh you think it'll be a
3ds thing yeah all right um let's see I'm gonna say that valve will show
defense of the ancients 2 which I think is a risky pick for me because I think
valve is pretty much said they're not showing anything already but I kind of
think this game is ready to be shown more of because it's kind of their next
big thing they've got in the pipeline so I think defense of the ancients 2 is
gonna show up at e3 and one more prediction to round out the five Dark
Sakura oh I broke from IRC darn it Dark Sakura um there was well Loki already
said it but it was on my list I'm gonna say it anyway an Xbox 360 price drop
that's fine if somebody's list is duplicated that's fine in fact I will
say one of the things that you said will show at e3 I have in my will not so this
is going to be good interesting all right um my oh sorry Loki your fifth and
final DS titles on the new Nintendo system will be on their virtual console
or download service where the hell they're gonna call it say it virtual
console so DS titles on new Nintendo system virtual console sorry black wolf
posted in chat the picture from e3 and those that I saw those same creatures in
what miklotov sent me those are the rage creatures yeah I saw there was a thing I
could talk to where they're all boxed up or whatever they're having they're
setting them up okay my last one on my list is I'm gonna go for kind of an easy
one Nintendo will demo 3d Netflix I think this is a big thing that they're
gonna be showing at e3 and they're gonna be showing 3d Netflix did we disconnect
I think we did my win app is crashed I'm still on IRC hold on we're gonna
keep recording for the sake of the podcast we are not broadcasting right
now hold on just keep up keep going no I know you guys are connected the the win
amp crashed over here that's what's wrong okay good old live radio and the
pitfalls of it okay we should be connected again so to recap I don't do
you have all your five written down let's recap the five things we think
will happen so dark soccer your list again a halo game for Kinect network
security from Sony verifying the name of the PSP or whatever in GP vitamin more
portal to download content and Xbox 360 price drop okay Loki the five things you
said will happen and no particular order minor press drop on the Xbox 360 console
and Kinect hardware new Animal Crossing game announced a new Grand Theft Auto
game announced and new Super Mario game announced and I mean like a new new
Super Mario Brothers because that's kind of confusing and redundant and then DS
DS titles on the Nintendo new Nintendo system virtual console okay and then my
list of five things you will see Diablo 3 announced for a console Star Fox
announced as the hardcore Wii title the Soulcalibur 5 bonus characters are
Capcom inspired think Dante valve will show defense of the ancients 2 and
Nintendo will demo 3d Netflix ok so let's go to the five things you won't
see so if these things are said the host loses a point they get buzzed like in
tab oops so let's see what the five things that were putting on the card
that they won't say stark soccer what's your first one no Final Fantasy 7
remake I think that's a very safe bet everyone puts that on the I want to see
it list every year and it's not gonna happen yep that's a good one
alright so I have no Final Fantasy 7 Loki this would make me sad but no
excite truck sequel probably not gonna happen I I actually put on my list Sony
will not acknowledge the PlayStation outlet outage directly there I'm gonna
say that they will not say something about we apologize for the downtime
they're gonna try to look forward not backward that's not to say they won't
say secure security and they will emphasize existing security but I don't
think you're gonna hear an apology for what happened you already got that
supposedly so I don't think they're gonna announce the outage directly we'll
see though dark soccer your next one my next one is and this makes me sad
Half-Life 2 episode 3 will not be announced nothing Loki I was gonna say
the new Nintendo I don't even know see this is the problem I don't even know if
they're gonna announce the price but the new Nintendo system will not be under
$250 now that's a that's a good guess what do you think it will cost $2.99 I
think it's gonna be $2.99 the controllers are gonna be a lot more
expensive that's it price is gonna be difficult but they're gonna have to
justify it somehow I think the controllers will be $79 $79 99 79 99 and
they're gonna be half a DS my list my number two thing on things you won't see
killer instinct sorry file that in the fanboy went category too and there's
been rumblings this year that it's supposed to come back now no enjoy your
Mortal Kombat and Street Fighter remakes and all this because that's as good as
it's gonna get dark soccer no new Microsoft or Sega system well you know
people there is rumors every year about a Microsoft portable so dark soccer
saying nope not happening Loki I would have to say probably that there there's
not going to be like I don't even know what you'd call it like the one versus 100 type
thing anymore they're not gonna announce you know some sort of community gaming
type thing no more community games yeah okay fair enough I'm gonna say that one
thing you won't see a Final Fantasy 14 release date for PlayStation 3 you will
see big pushes on 13 to instead they're gonna just it's not that they're gonna
try to erase that 14 ever happened but they're gonna push 13 to before they try
to revisit 14 I think dark soccer Sega will make a good Sonic game that's
something you won't see that's a good one that's gonna be hard to see we'll
have to see what the feedback is in the show floor I suppose all right Loki you
will not see a new dance masters game
probably not I would you go so far as to say you will not see a
non-ddr konami dance game a non-ddr konami dance game yes I would go that
far okay funny enough my number four is about a music game as well I don't think
you're gonna see a DJ game from harmonix and when I say DJ game from harmonix I
mean one that involves a turntable controller because it could be that the
new are obviously whatever harmonix makes is gonna be music based but I
don't want that interpretation to be too loose I'm talking turntable and keys not
happening I think harmonix is gonna go somewhere new with something you haven't
thought of and let's see dark soccer let's wrap up the lesson number five
Duke Nukem booth dudes as in like you know scantily clad men what if there is
a Duke Nukem with that that doesn't count all right I said like you know
like scantily clad dudes okay fair enough
logi this is gonna be kind of a risky one but and not including because I know
that these are coming out because you know I look at this kind of stuff not
including these like greatest hits re-releases or third-party games you
will not see any new first-party PSP games no new first-party PSP games that's
a and I'm talking about actual UMD discs I'm not talking about some stupid like
download content I'm talking first-party UMD PSP games black wolf in our chat is
calling shenanigans on the fact that you have a Konami thing on your list when
they already did a press conference however I'm actually gonna back you up
because that doesn't mean it was everything because we don't know what
Nintendo's got and anything that Konami is making for the new Nintendo system is
under wraps and I I would stand by the fact that just because they didn't say
it in their little pre thing doesn't mean it doesn't exist like glee karaoke
revolution wasn't in their thing guarantee you there's another one of
those coming so I'm gonna allow it even though it's probably a safe bet it will
still count for tacos all right and my last answer this is a duplicate and it's
it's a painful one but I also put you will not see half-life anything sorry
Alan I actually wrote it just like that half-life anything sorry Alan yeah I
thought of Alan when I put that but I will keep him when I was at work I would
plug in my my little iPhone and listen to all the dialogue through half-life 2
well the episodes mm-hmm and that's how I got through half nice because I
couldn't you know didn't play much at home so I got to hear the entire game so
I was like what more what happens all right let's recap the five buzz things
the things that will cause a host to lose a point if it happens dark Sakura
my list dun dun dun is no Final Fantasy 7 remake half-life 2 episode 3 will not
be announced no new Microsoft or Sega systems Sega will make a good Sonic game
and Duke Nukem booth dudes Loki the excite truck sequels not happening the
Nintendo system will not be under $250 no community games on you know no off
like one versus 100 stuff no dance masters game or non DDR dancing game
from Konami and no first-party PSP UMD games all right and on my list of five
things you won't see Sony will not acknowledge the PlayStation outage
directly killer instinct Final Fantasy 14 release date for PlayStation 3 you'll
see big pushes on 13-2 instead you will not see a DJ game from harmonix meaning
one with a turntable and buttons and you will not see half-life anything sorry
Alan alright so we'll see what develops next week I've got to bring in the
actual buzzer when we do the recaps oh we've got one sounds of failure has the
family feud buzzer oh yeah there's the sound effects thing the tire clogged
maybe like a year ago with all the you know you said I use that on it for Dan
shadow every time he makes a joke we play sad trombone oh yeah there it is
it's bookmarked right here sound effects of failure so here you go sorry so when
they say hey it's a sonic game that doesn't suck Oh dark Sakura I like that
when you click it then it does the X that's funny I like the toilet flush too
all right anyhow let's move on we gotta get the F use the week done because if
we don't get our angst out then I don't know what happens with something bad I
accidentally kicked Loki oops I tried to voice him and kicked him instead fuck
you to Sally Hansen's miracle nail thickener it doesn't work and it bubbles
and it stinks really bad too so thank you Sally Hansen company for taking five
dollars of my money fuckers and also fuck you to feeling like crap in my
intestines all day eating all those delicious cupcakes last night damn it
Rob why'd you have to bring this delicious orange cupcakes they were
orange creamsicle I knew you would love that because they tasted like the blood
orange pinkberry by the way I'm riding a high this week because pinkberry tweeted
me this week and they could they did tell me the blood they told me
personally on Twitter the blood orange will be back this makes me happy but
salted caramel is fucking good oh my god chocolate no I just had it with a little
shavings oh lord have it swirled with chocolate trust me this episode was
brought to you by amazing I'm sitting here with two pinkberry gift cards on
here god I wish I didn't close at 10 on Sundays all right my F you the week goes
to a lack of pinkberry my F you the week goes to the thing freezing up and
dumping the listeners for like 10 minutes and I didn't even realize it
because we weren't connected in chat still and my F you the week goes to me
for not trying harder to do III this year I think I think in retrospect I
probably should have done it I'm really looking forward to this whole coverage
and kind of trying something different but I don't know it's it's gonna be sad
kind of missing all the atmosphere of e3 but at the same time my wallet says
thank you but I know there's Disneyland that's gonna rock it's a small world
okay you're not gonna subject Bobby that's a small world yes I am no I am
gonna take Bobby on it's a small world if you won't go in California screaming
he has to go and it's a small world that's the compromise three times in a
row I'm not that mean but Bobby you get to pick you you're either gonna go on
California screaming or it's a small world and when you ride it's a small
world dark soccer and I will be singing I will warn you it's a small world last
longer than California scream in 15 minutes and me who gets bad vertigo and
hates roller coasters can do California screaming just fine and then or Tower of
Terror I cannot now I can't do Tower of Terror I tried to take Bobby on Tower of
Terror Daniel go on Tower of Terror I love to I love Tower dance in the other
I'm saying I'm gonna tell her Janice Dan I scream like a girl on Tower of Terror
now when I came off of Tower of Terror I was so dizzy that I could not walk
straight okay all right back to F use the week sorry Loki F you to Disneyland
talk I guess happy not being able to go to E3 really like to have gone to E3 not
necessarily to be able to see all the wonderful boots and stuff because I'd
be in my own hotel room being able to sleep all night long oh how I wish I
could sleep all night long my baby doesn't understand that he needs to
sleep at least when your baby is 13 he can mow the lawn oh this is what I have
to say parents have no right to complain because they picked this I didn't pick
for the child not to sleep through the night you picked to have one yeah I
understand that goes with it is it your fault if you buy a car and explodes on
you but it's a given that babies wake up at 3 in the morning hungry or poopy or
have to pee or that they want mommy all the time it's not really actually all of
our friends don't have a problem with that it's just baby nature it's just that
our child decides hey you know what I need to be swaddled still at 10 my I
wake up that morning some past me whatever you know he just we moved him
into his own room so that's also an additional bit of fun I'm just used to
it now I wake up at 4 in the morning every day so all right let's move on to
a couple more news stories for you guys and then the Skype line 1 8 7 7 game olr
yippie yippie or our username on Skype orange launch radio please if you are
going to use Skype please take this opportunity now to call echo 1 2 3 and
make sure your connection works even if you've called us before orange launch
video on Skype or 1 8 7 7 game olr after two more stories Loki yes so this is
kind of cool you know there's been a lot of rumors that there's going to be
gaming coming to the Apple TV device but everyone seems to forget hey you know
what there's other things out there that you can stream movies on to and now
Rovio is actually negotiating with developers to create games specifically
for their Roku box and it will I guess be TV based games you know casual stuff
and they've really said how the controller gonna work I guess it may be
the you know new boxes or whatever can come with a controller but it's kind of
neat though to see the gaming is coming to everything I mean I sure won't be
long before we're just you know having internet able the TVs that you're
playing games off of without any sort of additional software yeah on live
without any additional software well I well the boxes that I understand that
I'm talking about in internet enabled TV alright alright whatever alright so
would you be interested in a Roku box now I had a feeling there's no reason
alright let's move on you poor guys are bullying Bobby into writing no no I'm
just being honest because keep in mind the first time I read California
Screamin I wrote it in the middle and got sick as fuck at least we'll go on
Toy Story Midway Mania and that right is amazing it is but no when I when I
started writing California Screamin in the front car never got sick again
it's the same like being in the front seat of the car I get motion sick in the
backseat in the front seat of mine alright one more story for you guys
before we get to the Skype line this story is about Animal Crossing but it
might not be what you're expecting it's a story that Kotaku ran earlier this
week and I guess it was kind of from another site called anti pixelante.com
here's the deal it's a story about I don't even know where to go here with
Animal Crossing the tie the story is titled if you could bone one Animal
Crossing character who would it be and the site anti pixelante.com has actually
combed the depths of I guess what is this site called like rule 34 which I
guess rule 34 is an internet rule about if it exists there's porn full of it so
these people anti pixelante.com actually combed the website to find what Animal
Crossing characters were most popular on rule 34 and believe it or not there were
59 pornographic images of the stitch lady that helps you to the crop make
your own patterns Hazel yeah Hazel so Hazel was the most popular character
with 59 pornographic images next up and I'm surprised he wasn't number one Tom
Nook was second place with 30 and then the other well it's Abel and Mabel or
something like that isn't it the Abel sisters the Abel sisters the other Abel
sister had Mabel and Mabel and then KK whatever he is
okay KK was 13 and then I don't even know who that last chick is that's the
hair the hair style it's the hair lady all right now if you want to know what
animal showed up the most that raccoon cock that actually gives me a whole new
incentive to play Animal Crossing again I want to make the most offensive
village possible we almost did that with mine remember I had the town I had the
town lesbian and we had people running around saying cocksucker yes they show
this posting of a board where somebody is written you know how you can write
your own messages on the board in town Nook special we've got a very special
item in today yes it's Nook's fat raccoon cock come check it out at
Nookington's anyhow what villagers were most shown in compromising positions
believe it or not 15 different cats compromising 138 tabby was number one at
36 porno images am I really reporting on this of tabby think you are six
different wolves 111 humans four or what four different elephants ten bunnies
nine squirrels and seven dogs dogs only shown 20 times the mummy dog was in seven
different pornographic images people like you know the bandaged up people I
don't know what to say about that anymore the fact I'm looking god bless
the internet that's the only thing I can think of where worse I'm trying to find
with pictures are the actual pictures are not there you have to go to that
rule 34 and I'm a little afraid to go to that site all right fine you know what
fine I will fucking go to rule 34 only because I'm on Jamie's computer my
computer that's the orange lounge computer that's the one that our
listeners built us okay then I'm going on the listener computer let's see what
is this website here doo doo doo doo doo rule 34 other real and I'm gonna copy
I'm just really afraid of what I'm about to see when I go to this website this
could be worse than two girls one cup and I'm waiting for it to load there's
an animal crossing movie and let's see okay I'm gonna search oh yeah I have
that already do they have it subtitled I think I've got it subtitled somewhere
tiger client chatroom says sky you do realize what you're getting yourself
into furry porn look I it's my job to be an objective reporter and if there's
news I want to post to that link what did you want to say about it what I want
to say about it typical internet I mean come on seriously if it's gonna be a
character they're gonna have sex with somebody this stupid website's timing
out I think cuz we're trying to do a show like I'm searching for Animal
Crossing and nothing's happening there's images though someone on Yahoo answers
said uh what was it actually asked to see if it had been done yet this website
kind of sucks well on India though there's a rule 34 with two ad at to
doing it this is great all right forget it the segments going nowhere one eight
seven seven game olr our username on skype is orange lounge radio if you
want to give us a call we will chat about whatever please not rule 34 for
the love of God again eight seven seven game olr our username on skype orange
lounge radio meanwhile how about last minute stories apparently there's you
know of course the connect Star Wars game is being shown by the way these
connects Star Wars game based on the video footage that we've seen so far
looks very terrible lag-tastic fun also apparently there is going to be a
Disneyland adventures game for connect where you run around Disneyland and ride
rides and stuff like that sounds like a game that you two would be picking up
yeah well some this is kind of awful there is a a modder for a Super Smash
Brothers brawl that made a mod for that replacing solid snake with Conan O'Brien
and he in fact even does his string dance at the end of the round it's
awesome so I don't think I don't know if there's a place you can download that
forms dot kc dash m i m dot com slash gallery slash brawl or slash brawl view dot php question mark number one thousand sure people are writing this down
furiously well thank you know what they download the podcast and they can go
back and rewind it and stuff like that and get everything number equals 19,000
277 alright or just go search on Kotaku you can find it interesting also the
Melger's and zone of vendors collection those collections will actually be
downloadable as well so if you don't want to purchase the box sets and maybe
you only want one title in HD you can download those I believe separately so
that's gonna be kind of neat I found you subtitled animal crossing on YouTube and
link to you I will share with everybody and then let's see if that's just the
trailer is that the whole movie movie very cool let's see also I was gonna
talk about here apparently mad cats you know following the footsteps of red
octane are actually becoming game publishers themselves they have launched
thunderhawk studios and they are developing a flight sim game neat
ok I did it I did a search on the whole animal crossing and Tom Nook and nothing
came up I found one in this website blows of Tom Nook and Tom Nook right we
go to 4chan I'm definitely not going there on dark soccer's computer the show
computers I don't know what will affect it with we have a call we have a call
have fun digging to that we have a call hi you're on orange launch radio who's
this I'm just trying to stop all the Animal Crossing talk that's all hi Bobby
how are you I'm doing good are you excited for e3 I don't know if I'm
excited more for e3 or not going on California screaming yeah I'm trying to
get them to stop picking on you but you know you should be glad my friend
Victoria isn't going because she says I have a rule you go on every ride once
and if you don't like you never have to go on it again but I'm a little more
forgiving if somebody says no Rob I'm really not going on I'm like okay
whatever I did that I'm not gonna bully I went on I went on a Tower of Terror
and it sucks but if Bobby's like I don't want Bobby to barf so if he's gonna barf
he's not going on it anyway yes yeah I wouldn't barf what it is is I do have a
medical condition and I will pass out and I don't want to pass out if Disney
doesn't want me to pass out because then they escort you out of the park yes you
will have to you will have to hydrate him and watch over him if he passes out
because you forced me to go on that right all right Dan's like then we get
to go backstage all right look we're playing the little game tonight about
things you will see and things you won't see at e3 and you're calling shenanigans
on Loki's list I know but so Bobby I'm gonna put you on the spot I won't make
you name five but tell me something you think we will see maybe that we missed
something we will see is something we won't see well I mean the won't see is
actually I had a call on my show tonight that asked me you know what what would
you not see there and I said a new Space Quest or really any new Sierra adventure
titles I think that's a pretty fair guess yeah because I mean I can't see
Activision re resurrecting King's Quest or anything like that well have we had
the telltale King's Quest games were announced didn't that come out a few
months ago yeah but we won't see it at e3 I'm gonna get my buzzer ready I'm not
playing all right fine we'll see we'll see all right what about something that
will happen something that will I'm you know it's kind of hard because like I've
seen a lot of the stuff that you know kind of is going in and stuff what we
will see I I think we will I think we will get a price on the Nintendo I think
they will say the price interest even though it's end of 2012 I think they're
gonna go ahead and announce a price or at least something they're aiming for
yes hmm okay that's a pretty fair really it's end of 2012 I thought it would be
the same launch frame as 3ds Wow I didn't realize that boy that's a long
tease now what I want to see is I want to see them do pac-man versus is one of
the demo games they could they could re-release all that stuff that they did
for the Game Boy Advance connect cable that nobody ever played can they will
because that's Nintendo oh well that's easy let's do it that way the only one
that probably wouldn't happen is Crystal Chronicles because that wasn't first
party that was a weird game I liked it but it was weird it wasn't really
fantasy it was just kind of in that storyline I guess all right well any
other thoughts for us Bobby before we talk to you again on Tuesday live from
Los Angeles okay so I'm supposed to look for large chibis mm-hmm and I'm supposed
to look for Duke Nukem booth dudes yes okay okay so weak so I could can I
provide the buzzer if I find the booth dudes yes you can because I have found
they hate they usually do have somewhere the scantily clad muscular guys right
now the question is are they going to be advertising Duke Nukem we'll find out so
get that buzzer ready and yes you I give you full permission to buzz dark soccer
if that happens although really like I'm gonna buzz me I'm sure all right yes
did you go by telltale smooth all right no it's fine I don't I don't think they
have a booth II they I don't think they do it either they do that was they do it
packs yeah they do packs but they don't get a booth at e3 and I mean and if
there is a king quest thing they'd be should probably shown in Activision's
group booth because they own the IP oh that's right it's like a joint thingy so
okay well Bobby I will talk to you more on Tuesday have a safe flight tomorrow
thank you and no more rule 34 talk come on guys all right we'll try be
professional how long have you been let's see this show about seven years
all right take care Bobby see ya bye 1 8 7 7 game olr a username on skype is
orange lounge radio if you want to call and talk more porn time I'm kidding what
about more last-minute stories I want them to do an Animal Crossing that
actually has a huge world like in the anime because I started watching on a
minute so she pretty good Ubisoft not what I'm sorry I see this type of thing
I'd usually expect from Ubisoft but here's one of Activision's big
announcements that they're gonna be making Activision Publishing and Sega
toys they have created wappy dog wappy dog is basically an eyebo ripoff for the
Nintendo DS and it will allow you to interact with the robot dog in the game
and you will to does wappy dog come with Jack a cat I don't think that's what it
sounds like to me wappy dog wappy dog wappy dog and Jackie cat I'm 12 I have
problems other ocean interactive they have announced that they're gonna be
working on a new project for Xbox Live arcade and PlayStation Network based on
the HG Wells novel war of the worlds and of course it's gonna be you know
following the events of the 1953 film and include a new story arc characters
locations and subplots you know I'd actually be kind of cool to see like
something like this like resistance style or something like that
it's not as Tom Cruise isn't involved let's go to the let's go to the phones
for another call higher on Orange launch radio who's this
legends off of here legend of Zaku what's up my friend nothing much just
getting ready to know for tomorrow's a case of the Mondays you sit back and
watch the press conferences you can have your popcorn yeah I'm gonna be trying to
you know browse it from my desk there you go I mean I have two monitors so I
could probably pull it off on one of them but going on going on what I was
trying to bring up tonight was the whole Call of Duty elite thing which is
basically activisions next you know shameless attempted and money-grabbing
mmm I'm sensing you're not a fan no I mean I don't understand when other other
like when other developers other companies you know like like Bungie and
EA have offered these services for free and activisions mostly paywalling the
the good stuff like videos I mean it's what I'm sensing is that they are
probably going to herald the the next video game crash you think about it and
I bring this up because you think about how the first one happened and how this
one might might draw parallels to the one half the one in 83 where you have
like one we have one particular company just trying to hash out you know
multiple just trying to just trying to rehash franchises to the point where
quality degrades and you know fans get turned off you know I I don't think
another video game crash across the board is possible I think there is
possible company failures I don't think forever you're going to have Nintendo
Sony Microsoft one of them will fail where you're getting to the point where
activisions literally watering down diluting the entire first-person shooter
genre like if people for the most you know if for the most part consumers I'm
not talking about the hardcore gamers the ones that consistently by Call of
Duty you know the ones that basically don't have other first-person shooters
lined up aside from aside from like the second Call of Duty Halo gears you know
like the small really I'm trying to like put my finger on the demographic but
it's the type of person that wouldn't care less about what the scene things in
more important you know it's just like instantly gratified by by just
explosions so what about what about just like voting with your dollars you know
it's a concept we were talking about a lot I understand that it's possible but
when you have when you have one company just giving negative connotations to one
genre but just like trying to nickel and dime people every step of the way and
just trying to like not really innovate then it's gonna be harder for other
titles to really stand out unless battlefield 3 manages to pull an upset
which I know it will because it has a lot to offer on the table and I think
that yeah I don't think it's gonna lead to a crash I think it would just be yeah
battlefield 3 might become the new champion you know or maybe I get to the
point where video gamers are gonna get sick and tired of actually of having to
deal with just mediocrity okay well let me throw this question at you kind of
out of left field here because you mentioned Halo is one of the games that
you think has done it very well but we know that activism bungee every party
for every bunch he was the first was first really to pioneer such a thing
where they integrated you know the ability to look up your stats online and
post the video straight from the console but I know it has the bungee and
Activision are partnering up for whatever this next game at least
Activision is publishing it so do you think that the same you know nickel and
dime extra stuff I don't really need the thing is gonna continue and now it's
under Activision I mean Microsoft didn't do that much didn't even do any of that
like I know when you know when bungee was working with Microsoft that never
happened because they were trying new ways to engage people into the into that
genre and into that game and what better way and then to launch all you know the
the whole halo waypoint thing I believe where it allows you to interact you know
look up your scores post it on Facebook and so forth but then you know when
Activision is thrown into the mix you have a company that's helping on just
trying to like monetize and maximize every single every single dollar out of
all their their IP to the point where just like they're willing to cut
corners and sacrifice quality in the name of the almighty dollar let me ask
this question we gotta wrap up and get more calls let me ask this question in
on this what do you think they could do to make more money on the franchise that
doesn't seem so nickel-and-dime well first of all you shouldn't try to like
you shouldn't try to nickel and dime for things that are have been offered for
free in the past like that whole call of duty elite that it looks many people
just like shrugged it off so far because from what I heard for example on the
other sites like a taco for example they basically you know they basically shut
they basically wrote it off as just another money grab so they basically
they have they really have no hopes for this um for this endeavor they really
don't they just like it doesn't faze them it doesn't engage them that well
and that's getting a really lukewarm reception right and you know more
importantly trying to create innovative ways to re-engage your customers like
try not to be hacked the same you know the same boring old five-hour campaign
and instead offering new ways to offer balanced gameplay like if they fix up
the game playing in multiplayer where it's not a camp fest then they could
then they have a better shot we at least have one person agreeing with you in the
chat room dark toa gak says Activision is one shit of a company for something
for lack of something less constructive to say all right buddy we're gonna let
you go so we try to get at least one more call tonight but have a good one
all right have a good one later one eight seven seven game olr or a
username on skype is orange launch radio we'll try to squeeze in at least one
more call if anyone wants to call it's e3 prediction time surely you've got
something you want to predict one eight seven seven game olr or a username on
skype orange lounge radio anything else you want to get out here low-key with
last-minute stories yes Microsoft is officially announced what games they're
going to be showing at e3 oh this would be in their booth including the third
party stuff some of it sounds interesting let's see starting off some
of these you probably heard before a Tomb Raider fours of four Star Wars
connect Gears of War 3 a halo related title I'm sure that's halo connect
codename kingdoms sesame street once upon a monster that's the new fuck was
it the new double fine game over they oh yeah
Elder Scrolls 5 Skyrim steel battalion well well Elder Scrolls 5 Skyrim is not
supposed to be playable they're gonna show I wonder if maybe it's just a
trailer if that would be hot if they're showing that playable on the floor I
think it's playable uh let's see here a steel battalion heavy armor Alan Wake
night springs which is connect compatible xcom hitman absolution
modern warfare 3 spelunky HD ghost recon it's a rail shooter for connect dance
central to connect fun labs x commerce connect sports season 2 toys soldier
cold war fabled the journey Raving Rabbids for connect another unspecified
double fine game hybrid which is an Xbox live arcade shooter roller coaster
connect and rise of nightmares for connect hmm so there's some of your
announcements for e3 all right let's go to the phone so we got another call
coming in here hello you're on orange lounge radio who's this
30 DC DT dark Tetsuya what's on your mind buddy finally coming out hmm what's
that Llamulana finally has a Japanese release day of course I should have
guessed Llamulana you are in love with this game and what's the Japanese
release date Oh God June 21st June 21st hey that's pretty close to my
birthday do you think this means we might get a US release around the same
time or don't bet on it after e3 yes hopefully maybe it'll be one of the few
we titles tucked away on the show floor actually the Nintendo's booth will
probably actually have a lot of we title still showing at least whatever they can
mostly 3ds though probably oh yeah so we'll see what is it about Llamulana
that you just love so damn much it's like well it's like Super Metroid or
Symphony of the night you've got this huge world you get to explore and you're
running around killing monsters and all that flying hmm like those other games
so great you like that whole Metroidvania stuff now there might you
might have a hater in chat because Bobby Blackwell is like is that that if this is
that Llamulana shit Oh God why do you think people are hating on Llamulana I
don't know I mean I know the PC version is kind of kind of hard but I hear
they'll be they'll be adjusting that from the PCWare version yes it's got to
be a little easier for all those we kiddies it does yeah so e3 is this week
besides Llamulana is there anything you're looking forward to hearing about
at the show oh Nintendo's new console I'm kind of
sure they got going on with that yeah I'm really hoping that they'll announce
something that actually will make Loki say wow that looks cool like if that
were to actually happen like I just I'd die the show would be done because I
would have died I think he just got chased out he didn't know he's talking
with Dan they're having boy talk about something Oh boys all right um let's see
so what would make you insanely happy if Nintendo announced on their new console
like I've talked about I want an f-zero game what game do you want you're
excited oh man you don't even know all of it I want them all I want an
Animal Crossing porn game on the new cafe that's what I want I'm kidding I'm
kidding there you go what an Animal Crossing Llamulana HD an Animal Crossing
game with the Nintendo games intact would be awesome and I'm not talking
about a new like I'm talking about like a new Animal Crossing game not this like
hey look we poured the same damn game over all right all right DT I'm gonna
let you go so you can go slap black wolf with the trout in the chat room but
thanks for calling and I hope Llamulana comes out soon all right take care
actually I'm a little worried because if Llamulana comes out too soon then
dar Tetsuya will never finish his series on where are they now that he's doing
for the website I don't even know who he's interviewing it's like a secret so
he's fine he's found blasts from olr's past to interview on our website
throughout the next month could be interesting so there you go that's going
to do it for the skype line tonight one eight seven seven game olr if you I
don't know want to leave us voicemail or whatever but of course mailbag orange
launch rated calm is the place to send us emails every week any other last
minute stories I missed low-key that you want to get to yeah Carmageddon come as
a download title yeah that's all I want to talk about for now we may have
something a little later though hmm maybe something to stay tuned for this
after the show for yes maybe mm-hmm all right well anyhow that's going to do it
for another week of orange launch radio we'll go around to get everybody's final
thoughts in just a moment but first I just want to say again thank you guys so
much for downloading our show and supporting our show you know even though
I'm a little bit sad panda I'm not going to e3 this year the only reason I have
been able to go to e3 in the years past is because of this show and you guys you
know really kind of fueling that fire so um thank you guys so much I'm looking
forward to the coverage this week and just having fun with the news and giving
it its proper skewering or fanboy wank whatever it deserves we will see so um
if you like what you hear here at orange launch radio please tell friends about
the show tell folks on iTunes leave us a nice five-star review by the way there
was an awesome five-star review left this week about somebody saying that he
listened to the show when he was like younger and he feels like he's kind of
growing up with the show and I'm like oh we're buzzies so yeah leave us a nice
review on iTunes you don't have to be warm fuzzy so if you don't know or tell
a friend that's what we really want to tell word of mouth is all we got we do
not have a giant booth at e3 to spread the word of olr we will be lucky if we're
were they able to get within 50 feet of the building and you know we don't have
any of the advertising dollars or whatever word of mouth is all we got so
tell a friend about the show all right let's go around and get everybody's
final thoughts dark soccer your final thoughts I have to help someone move
tomorrow my final thought is I'm gonna be making the popcorn and making Alan
get up early to watch Microsoft's conference tomorrow good times Loki just
looking forward to tomorrow and watching the conferences I've really disappointed
that when Nintendo isn't tomorrow but whatever good things come to those who
wait which by the way I think our win amp might have crashed again here that's
just lovely is people in chats complaining about the stream because my
win app has locked up yet again I'm just not having good luck today yep
we're locked we're down again live radio I wouldn't have it any other way so
let's try to reconnect yeah I don't I think I'm about to get kicked I think we
all I don't know there's some type of hiccup in the line or something ooh I
think your internet might just be down I can't even connect so connected
I'm still connected I'm let's go to a random website here I cannot get through
on the server yep mine's working just fine all right so we're gonna want
actually what we're gonna do we're gonna just for the podcast sake of the podcast
will play the credits since we're pretty much done with the show anyway and then
we'll figure out what to do about our live listeners when we come back so
that's gonna do it thank you guys for listening to us on the podcast feed and
sorry it was a little bit of a mess tonight but you can't really plan for
things like random internet outages good night everybody kept calm see you
Tuesday Tuesday at seven o'clock bye you've been listening to orange lounge
radio orange lounge radio is an orange lounge production to join us for a live
show visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific Time the views
and opinions expressed on orange lounge radio do not necessarily reflect those
of the entire staff of orange lounge radio or all games calm but we're
probably right anyway see you next week