[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight, June 6, 2010, a lawsuit is filed against Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rumors say a new dance game is coming to Project Atal, and could you soon pay a new tax on your consumer electronics?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello my friends and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are that podcast where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is episode number 369 for this June the 6th of 2010.
69.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, the one, the only, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see, needing a good oiling, apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the first day I've actually felt somewhat decent, so I've been sick, but I am mostly over it, a little leftover.
[SPEAKER_03]: My voice may go out during the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what you need?
[SPEAKER_03]: A lozenge.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need, well that, and you need salad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Fresh Choice, just like Jamie.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw your picture.
[SPEAKER_03]: I sent you a tweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I have been eating salad all weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had an epic salad yesterday, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get this.
[SPEAKER_03]: and so there's different levels of salad there's like you know there's there's level one salads you're like basic house salad then there's epic salad of awesomeness my salad had used red vein chard which hard is delicious and raw squash and Roma tomatoes and dehydrated apples and
[SPEAKER_03]: and Chives and what else did I put in that thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, Pea Sprouts.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pea Shoots.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, Pea Shoots.
[SPEAKER_03]: And broccoli.
[SPEAKER_05]: And occasionally we do talk about video games here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: With a raspberry vinaigrette.
[SPEAKER_05]: But don't put your video games in raspberry vinaigrette.
[SPEAKER_03]: It won't work anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that not epic?
[SPEAKER_03]: It sounds pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to have gelato today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got to introduce the one and the only tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm full.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're full?
[SPEAKER_05]: What have you been eating?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a salad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Breadsticks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: This should be like a food MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to Sizzler, the MMO.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't need that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, of course, we do tape live every Sunday night at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.allgames.com 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_05]: So do pull up a chair and join us in our chat room if you are listening live.
[SPEAKER_05]: chat.orangeloungeradio.com We're going to be talking video games over the next few hours tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots of E3 rumors and kind of things...
[SPEAKER_05]: We're in that period where E3 is right around the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously, we're, what, eight days away from the first?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually, we're one week away from the first press conference, if you count the Cirque du Soleil Project Natal thing, where they're going to announce the real name of it, which I heard a little rumor, take it with a grain of salt, Xbox Wave.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: How would you feel about that as the name?
[SPEAKER_05]: You think that's a good name for a peripheral?
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox Wave?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see them doing little title waves.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie's waving her hand.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least it's not the Xbox flail.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's, I guess, a little better.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would be if they put Parapara on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take that with a gigantic grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just had a thought about the Natal thing and Parapara.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Could you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: But otherwise, the show was just kind of like a lot of it was behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of it was more conceptual because you had Natal and Move being announced, and I guess the vitality sensor to some extent, but nothing really being shown.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think this year, we're really going to see what is going to be out on the shelves this Christmas, and there's going to be a lot fighting for your attention this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, as I was playing just a moment ago, I was playing some Portal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I really have to owe it to a lot of Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I realized that I had three more ranks to go before I hit Commander.
[SPEAKER_03]: And damn it, I'm almost there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I want that extra pip.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, other than that, I also, uh, canned two of my crewmen and now have this weird purple dude, or purple chick, who just is bizarre looking, but she's got good stats, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, and, um, I have to say, the crystalline entity is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: What is, what is the crystal, I don't, I'm not a big enough nerd.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a next generation foe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it's this big crystal thing, spiky crystal thing floating in space.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in the show, they used a high-pitched noise thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they eject the warp core to fix it?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's always how you fix the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: They pretty much screamed at it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You eject the warp core.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty much screamed at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: They used a high-pitched harmonic or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you're saying that the purple chick is a butterface?
What?
[SPEAKER_06]: She looks strange, but she has good stats.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay She has a nice body but her face, is that what it is?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes Okay Whatever Anyway Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait Do you want me to find a picture of her?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, no I want to ask you something Star Trek related Have you heard the commercials on the radio?
[SPEAKER_05]: There is the Star Trek tour Is apparently like right around the corner from my house McClellan
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, not giving away where I live on the show, but that's right around the corner of my house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's like one exit up the freeway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the entire internet knows where I live.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you lived in the butt end, the other way.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan's in the other room singing Knowing is Half the Battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to get Dan a mic in the living room.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to get like a really long cord just so Dan can give his MST3K commentary during the show from the living room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um.
[SPEAKER_05]: and BurgerTime.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we'll have some fava beans and a nice canteen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, this is an open letter of annoyance to people who play Star Trek online.
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, the crystalline entity thing is an open instance.
[SPEAKER_03]: That means anyone can join it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Even the most retarded of the retarded, the butt-tarded, can join this instance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not use mine!
[SPEAKER_03]: Do not use mines.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way that you beat the stupid thing is you eject the warp core breach.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how you kill it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: The way that you kill the thing is that when you get it down to 30%, it's going to shoot out these large crystals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't shoot the fragments.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shoot the big crystals because the big crystals go back and regenerate the damn thing and then it shoots out everything and kills you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can't do it, Captain.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have the power.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just people think strategy, please.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does anybody ever yell that in Star Trek Online?
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have the power!
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure somewhere somebody has.
[SPEAKER_03]: They keep mentioning Worf.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually enjoy all the instances that involve the Klingons because they're so much fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really enjoying the game, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: And Rob, you were supposed to play with me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will use the pass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, you know, World of Warcraft, Addict, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, look.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com And SSJ100Matt is saying that Tigerclaw has already found my house, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki's house.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or was it my house?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, because Tigerclaw is the expert in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, if we mention something, he'll have a link in five seconds.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: His Google Foo is unmatched.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, SSJ100Matt also commenting on the date between DarkSakura and myself Rob better put out Yeah Rob
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, put out the credit card to pay the bill.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I'll be putting out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, where was there?
[SPEAKER_05]: There was another one I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby Blackwolf, our old pal, buddy, friend who does the show before us here at All Games Radio, he is hatin' on split second.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, if you listen to his show tonight, it's just an hour of split second bashing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really, but it might as well have been.
[SPEAKER_05]: He says in his gaming week, he ejected the warp core breach that is split second.
[SPEAKER_05]: because he is not a fan, apparently, of Split Second.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have not played Split Second outside the demo, but maybe next week I'll have more of an opinion and I'll either eject Bobby's opinion from the Warp Core or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I also have to say the thing that Dan's been playing because I have totally just gotten a kick out of watching him play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We don't have the other controller hooked up where I'd play it because you can play simultaneous on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: X...
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of pals from All Games Radio, I noticed Derek H. from Dead Pixel Live is in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you don't listen to Dead Pixel Live, you're an idiot!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's on, what, Monday through Thursday at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they do lots of shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's asking a good question I want to pose to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is Star Trek Online anything like you're in the show?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did tell him that it's pretty episode-like and that I love it, but I will give a little bit more of an apt description.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have... You basically talk to your commanders.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can talk to them via subspace, and you get your missions.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you go to whatever system.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes it's just a patrol.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes you think you're going to some abandoned place to look on some research that you don't know why it killed everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, oh, the Romulans are there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: and, you know, they do new episodes with new missions and everything and I think that that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But really, it's like you're playing through seasons of the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: For me, that is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, and the other times where I'll scream at the stupid, you know, the Romulan medics are the worst because, like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Shoot, shoot, shoot, regenerate!
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, but they really do, you know, pay a lot of attention to canon in this, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, now, I've been reading the books.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep in mind, this is a different universe than the books.
[SPEAKER_03]: The books were written before the new movie came out, and this is incorporating the new movie into the storyline.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, basically, Romulus, go boom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Warf gets pissed off at everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pissed off.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really is a good continuation, but it says something like 20 years later.
[SPEAKER_03]: You actually run into people who were children in the series.
[SPEAKER_03]: You run into Meral Paris, and you run into Kiriyoshi O'Brien, and
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really is like being in that universe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nerd, nerd, nerd, nerd, nerd, nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to play a little more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I only played during the beta and I wasn't totally absorbed with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the space combat turned me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the away team mode, but I didn't like the space combat at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Rob, they've really, really addressed a lot of the problems with space combat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lot smoother now.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other thing, too, is that once you get a little bit more used to the controls...
[SPEAKER_03]: It actually is really fluid.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, you and I may have had the same problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: My graphics card was crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fixed that, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now I can run WoW at highest settings and it's purdy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then you should have no problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I upgraded my graphics card, a lot of my problems with control stopped because I wasn't lagging.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because it would literally, now the difference between graphics card lag is that it would be stutter, stutter, stutter, stutter, stutter, and internet lag is that you'll go forward, you'll row back a few steps and you'll go forward again.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's very few and far between.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a little lag and it looks like you've gone back like a millimeter on the screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow lag can suck when it's like seconds and seconds of lag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, just everything kind of freezes in place and then everything happens in like half a second.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it was bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, usually the game doesn't get too laggy, but when you get those lag spikes, oh man, world of hurt.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I hated it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, that was one of the reasons that was, I like the lag in Star Trek Online a lot better than the lag in World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I actually don't like World of Warcraft, so that helps.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got a character to 20, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got one to 20.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, if anyone wants to play with me, just saying, my whole account name is DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: Duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: My character's name is Idarin, E-D-A-R-Y-N.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'm playing a Trill, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Trills are cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, yeah, we need a fleet.
[SPEAKER_03]: We need the O'Larmy fleet.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's basically this guy's made different, you know, Mario, Super Mario games that'll have elements from Super Mario World, Super Mario 3, even the flurries from Super Mario 2 are in the level.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was a very good looking game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it just looked like Super Mario World, at least the little bit I saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't, you know, Dan tried to show it to me in about 10 seconds, like, you gotta check this out.
[SPEAKER_03]: He was playing levels last night that are really reminiscent of Super Mario 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the part that made me go, oh, neat, is that it was two players simultaneous, kind of like the new Wii game is all simultaneous.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we and I haven't played it together yet, but I have to say that it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude who made that game, well done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very much well done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy it while it lasts before Nintendo sues the pants off those people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although there is a big splash screen that's basically the equivalent of, please don't sue me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Has it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's been around for a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the games he has on there is the first one he ever did, which is really annoying because all you ever get is mushrooms in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's really, he did a great job.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's this one level that Dan was going through where you get the buzzy beetle shells and you have to break purple blocks with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you have to get to the purple blocks and everything to unlock a door.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got some definitely creative elements in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I have some time that I'm not feeling like crap, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's move on with our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're almost 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, you played a lot tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, most of that was Star Trek babble.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also still had to do a plug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's do it during housekeeping because I do want to give that plug as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what did you... Oh, you're chowing down over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you ready to talk about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm almost done eating.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bad time.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want me to go my gaming week then?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm ready.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, so this week I played really only three things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Red Dead Redemption, played a lot more System Link co-op, and the game, surprisingly, I don't know how to really put it, the System Link games, we have trouble staying in the same game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, it will...
[SPEAKER_06]: have trouble joining a System Link game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have never seen a game that has trouble joining a System Link game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a System Link game means your Xbox are connected.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not even on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: You are literally connected cable to cable.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just like... And you can't find the other Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, oh, you're in your own game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I have to find a new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you're in your own game again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Find a new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there he is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're like, we finished the mission or whatever, co-op mission, and it split us off into two different games again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, what the hell is wrong with this thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's very buggy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had issues with where we were playing and we got dynamite and the Molotovs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it stopped showing us the explosions and the blood splurts and also the fire.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then my friend had trouble going through a gate because on our screen, the gate was open.
[SPEAKER_06]: On his screen, the gate was shut and locked.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it was interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, it's still really fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't gotten to play a lot of online, because trying to join games online, at least at our work where our connection's not so great, it's near impossible to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we just basically stick to System Link games, because at least that way, if live drops, which it does all the time on our connection there at work, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also this week I went and played some Grand Theft Auto, Battle of the Gay Tony, more of the Episodes of Liberty City stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still playing through that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm actually still moving up the ranks because I haven't lost a game in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm 63 now, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And really frustrating the hell out of my coworkers because they're getting pissed off now that I don't lose any games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying... Because there was a guy that used to play with us named Chris Marsh and they're saying he... What I'm doing is very Marshian because he would, you know, pull off these just crazy ass kills and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, for example, in the old PSP game, Liberty City Stories...
[SPEAKER_06]: It was very glitched out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we had problems with teleporting grenades and whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he actually got one kill one time.
[SPEAKER_06]: He actually got two kills out of one death.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just ridiculous because he killed somebody and somehow they had just driven over health or something and then they got a second death.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he got two points for where he should have only gotten one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've actually gotten assists off of my own death, so I actually got points for me dying, which makes zero sense whatsoever, because you're not supposed to be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's not my fault, it's just the game is really glitchy, and that's just the way things are.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of glitchy games, I've gone back to Earth Defense Force 2017 and I am going to beat it this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We actually were playing some more and just going through the game and almost finished the game now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I will be finishing that game hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of had to dust it off again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually cracked my copy, but thankfully a while back, I bought the last three copies we had for $5 each.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have spares.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should, I don't know, give one of those away as a prize.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was planning on it someday, but I cracked the copy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Endorsed by Loki Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet the developers would love that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything else for your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty much it as far as stuff I've played.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm kind of working on something right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'm working on a lot of things because that's just the way things work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm working on painting the baby's room, which is game-related because it's New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: themed.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should put pictures on the LR feed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, there will be tons of pictures.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be pimped out.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got some of the wall decals, but we're going to paint a lot of it, but we want the wall decals for the characters and some of the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're doing Mario, you said?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: theme.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a plan I can give you to make hampers look like the pipes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll have to look at that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I was just going to get giant PVC and make it into a pipe, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: That was, well, it's something that I had planned because that's what Dan and I were going to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I got some other stuff from ThinkGeek.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I got a, it was an open source music box.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have it so that you can make the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: theme on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then some Mario figurines.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we're planning on doing some question block.
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, a lot of it's just going to be handmade and will be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, there'll be tons of pictures for it once it does get finished.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other thing I'm working on right now, and this is just kind of an on a whim thing that I decided to do the other day is what...
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the phrasing Project $10 that EA's been using, you know, because they're charging people lots of money for stuff that should be in the games in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I decided to come up with Project Under $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what Project Under $100 is, is building a working main cabinet under $100.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that's including everything including shipping now although I'm pricing stuff out now I don't know if I can include shipping in there because it's I want to do a two-player cocktail but it might be a little difficult but basically though you know involving actually getting like an LCD monitor computer all the arcade parts and that kind of stuff under $100 it might end up being 120 we'll see
[SPEAKER_06]: After all that stuff because, like I said, I don't want the extra buttons and joystick and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But so far I have the computer and the monitor for under $70.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm off to a good start.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the cabinet itself will be funny because it will be made out of cardboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Postal Service because you can get a ton of boxes from them for absolutely free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: And they will ship them to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: comments from our chat room chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you are listening to us at All Games Radio live on this Sunday night please join us if you're listening to us on the podcast remember you can always send us your comments via Twitter or mailbag mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com some comments from chat SSJ100Matt talking about the baby room says diapers go in the chomp chomp bin
[SPEAKER_05]: Derek H says, if he does that, I'm assuming talking about the MAME cabinet, I'm doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: My MAME cabinet is an old laptop, a monitor, and an Xbox 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, I could have done a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I've got some spare parts.
[SPEAKER_06]: This doesn't cost me anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I wanted it so that it can be somewhat reproducible because the problem is, though, shopping on eBay and buying used stuff, you never know what you're going to get for what price.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ideally, you get one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not ideal.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're going to get another day.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I got lucky with some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, I got a monitor for $32, an LCD monitor, 15-inch LCD monitor that has one dead pixel, but I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going in a cardboard cabinet, so who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: And I got a computer for $35 that's basically a 1.6 gigahertz processor, which is fine for MAME, and I think a half gig of RAM, which is perfect for MAME.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So I may have to supplement it with some other stuff, but I'm just kind of throwing around the idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got this gift card from work for, ironically enough, selling Split Second, and so I'm using it for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bet Bobby would be proud to know that you got rewarded for selling extra copies of Split Second to people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a decent game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, anything else, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess, actually, one thing I didn't realize, it's one of those arcades that's also participating in the Save the Arcades 2 campaign.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had a story on that a couple weeks ago, because Arcade Infinity is also competing with this place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I gotta tell you, this place was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a good time, and, you know, I didn't try to talk to anybody, or I wasn't like, you know, oh, yeah, I'm from Orange Lounge Radio, I want to talk...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they have a black rose?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember seeing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had more pinball machines than I've ever seen in an arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody asked me if they had Space Jam.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't see Space Jam.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did see Doctor Who.
[SPEAKER_05]: That made me think of you.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a Doctor Who table.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only complaint I have about the place is that the games are packed in so tight because the real estate there, there's not a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of brushing up against strangers and not a lot of elbow room.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta say, I was there on a...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dave & Buster's got it, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: They do all sorts of theme nights.
[SPEAKER_05]: apparently throughout the month too and they have bands that perform there and everything so yeah I had a good time so I'm surprised and one thing and Alan said the same thing and I commented on this too is that why in the hell don't they have this in San Francisco like there's nothing like it in San Francisco and you would think of all places kind of tech central you know NorCal would have something like it but sadly it does not SSJ100Matt says that there is a barcade in New York City Brooklyn to be exact you know I think I'd heard about that
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had not been there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bond006 in chat says, Did you have a geek moment?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did have a geek moment when I went in there and squeed.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I watched my friend, get this guys, I know long time OLR fans will appreciate this, they had a DDR Extreme machine that I watched my friend play for only 50 cents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: And no tokens.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was another refreshing thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everything actually ran on quarters.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they had to have signs on the machines that say, Don't use this for your laundry, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's old school.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yes, A++ for ground control, and I hope there's more places that spring up like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as other games that I play that you don't have to be in Portland in order to access, I did play a couple of new games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Since I was in Oregon, Oregon is infamous for not having sales tax, at least to those of us in California, so I loaded up on games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought four new games this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought Blur, Split Second, Red Dead Redemption, and Alan Awake.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought all of those games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that I could save a little bit on sales tax because I'm cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I bought four new video games, it wasn't that cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played two of them this week because I didn't have time to do everything and I was kind of focusing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I probably played Blur more than any other game that I got this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Blur is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is exactly what they are marketing it as in the commercials.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Mario Kart meets Burnout.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Mario Kart for grown-ups.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Things they could do better in the sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm pretty sure there will be a blur too.
[SPEAKER_05]: There deserves to be a blur too.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there are some things I would like to see them do better in the sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, my number one complaint about the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The soundtrack blows.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's non-existent in some parts, and I don't really know what the music score is.
[SPEAKER_05]: In some parts, there's a movie in the beginning that kind of had a cool song I recognized in it that was neat, and in the opening menus, there's some cool techno songs, but you would think something with that look of blur, like the neon, the kind of like...
[SPEAKER_05]: F-Zero but not in the future look that Blur sort of has, the Burnout meets F-Zero look, you would think has some type of techno thumping soundtrack to it, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what Burnout had, the Burnout tracks, EA tracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, granted, Blur is by Activision, but you would still expect there to be somewhat of a soundtrack, but it
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't notable for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And from what I understand, they had this agreement apparently signed where I guess Crystal Method produced a soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just expecting something a lot more.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was tempted just to really use custom soundtracks the whole time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was very disappointed in what should have been a better soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_05]: My other complaint is, believe it or not, the graphics are not...
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, like, they're good.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're definitely next gen.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're a step above what you're gonna see on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I wasn't, like, blown away by the graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Blur has this neon thing going for it, but that neon is often mixed in many stages with Highway 50 going through Nevada, like that very brown, blah, dusty kind of theme, which I don't know what they were trying to go for with it, but it didn't make the graphics look that notable.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, the graphics were kind of comparable to Fuel, which didn't really have...
[SPEAKER_05]: A++ graphics either so I was a little bit disappointed but in the end graphics and sound are not the only important things in a video game and the game itself is still a lot of fun and I am having fun making my way through it it is a game deserving of a sequel I'm
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope they just put a little more polish on it next time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is what I would hope for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Comments from our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Bond006 says, Has anyone seen the underhand slap at Ninty, Nintendo, in the Blur ad at the end?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I think the Blur ad is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's really perfect for what Blur is trying to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deathwishing says, The graphics are better than Fuel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved Fuel.
Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked Fuel a lot too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought Fuel was severely underrated.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Fuel was also... The biggest problem with Fuel is that it was too ambitious.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there wasn't enough polish because the world was too big in Fuel.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was its biggest problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Its ambition was its own worst enemy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And to some extent, maybe that was the biggest problem with Blur is that they spent so much time on the game itself, which is...
[SPEAKER_05]: Where you should spend the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think some of the graphics and sound I think suffered a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But let me say this too because this is important.
[SPEAKER_05]: One feature that's in Blur that I think a lot of people overlook that does make it pretty awesome and may explain why the graphics take a hit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It does have split screen multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you don't just have to play this game on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can play, like Mario Kart, two people on one screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, take it with a grain of salt, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's why they had to make some concessions with the graphics and sound.
[SPEAKER_05]: The other game I played this week, Red Dead Redemption, which might surprise some of you guys who listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not usually the type of game I would play, but the reviews on it have been so stellar, and I've read such good things on it, I'm like, I have to pick this up and know what I'm missing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to be honest, I haven't played a whole lot of this story, because I can't stop shooting random people.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, the minute they gave me a gun...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody tells me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan just said the same damn thing when I walked in here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, my sister came over.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's been playing Red Dead Redemption as well because I got her a copy.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she just comes over and just can't stop laughing at what she's been doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: She says one of the things that she likes doing is lassoing a coyote and dragging it into the middle of town and then letting it go because it will attack whatever it sees.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then you can tie people up, throw them on the train tracks.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, here it is with Red Dead Redemption.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's sandbox gaming at its finest.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've ever wanted that Wild West sandbox, there you go.
[SPEAKER_00]: Grand Theft Horse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Horse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's that Rockstar engine.
[SPEAKER_00]: Rage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Rage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Their proprietary engine.
[SPEAKER_05]: And their euphoria.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tigerclaw says, wow, Sky is sadistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very uncharacteristic of you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, I just...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't play these games an awful lot, but when I do, it's really funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't take it seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you guys know how I feel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of you guys must be kind of like, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't Rob the same guy who went off on the Saw movies and how he doesn't like them because they're too violent?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah, but Saw's kind of, like, realistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, like, Red Dead Redemption, like, the graphics are good and all, but it's not realistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a difference.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a huge difference.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if it makes me a hypocrite, well, screw you.
[SPEAKER_05]: SSJ100 Matt says, Rob, what would your mother say about this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just gross, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: My mom said we could call her, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if we should do it tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to say next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do it after E3 because I think the next week is the Microsoft thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: But definitely in the near future.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will make that work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kitsune says, Red Dead Redemption feels so much more fun than Grand Theft Auto 4 though.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I kind of agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what it is, Kitsune.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's something about it where I don't know if it's just the environment or it's just the story or I just get drawn into Red Dead Redemption a lot more than I do Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deathwishing in chat says, Rob, I got mauled by 13 cougars at once.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was instantly thinking of...
[SPEAKER_05]: I was instantly thinking of Courtney Cox and Cougar Town.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it just me?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was thinking of Blanche.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rest in peace, Blanche.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss those old broads.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Betty White has outlasted them all.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: There can be only one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Betty White has proved she's the HBIC.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's pretty much it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are literally 40 minutes into the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't touched a damn bit of news.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let me do some quick housekeeping, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some new articles at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's been some great, great retro reviews.
[SPEAKER_05]: Retro rear views written in the past couple weeks RBI Baseball's got some gameplay there's a story on Metal Gear a new segment that's being done by Actdeft called Video Stumble which is kind of neat so check that out guys our website is expanding with all this kind of retro-ish content and I thought that was really cool I also uploaded some pics from my Portland trip if you want to see the picture of the Burger Time machine and the OLR initials I put those up at OrangeLandry.com so check those out
[SPEAKER_05]: I also want to give a plug maybe I'll let Jamie plug this but she wrote a great article on our friend website I don't want to say our sister website but our BFF website we'll say that our BFF at geek-life.com tell them a little bit about what you did DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I have... Actually, I have a regular panel on there every week on Tuesday that's called Geek Cube.
[SPEAKER_03]: Talking about, you know, how to incorporate your geeky life with your work life.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I also write other articles.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I did a review of this place called Fairytale Town for little kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I also did a write-up for Orange Sounds Radio since we get a nice big plug on the website.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I just basically kind of did the not-so-secret origin of Orange Dolls Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it was a historical type of thing and kind of went through how we evolved from the show that was on the living room floor about DDR and 2DX to the show we are today.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, and really it's the question, you know, we get asked it fairly often, like, how'd you come up with that name?
[SPEAKER_03]: And how'd you come up with this?
[SPEAKER_03]: And how long have you been doing this?
[SPEAKER_03]: And what was it like?
[SPEAKER_03]: And blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's a few of you who've been here since, you know, episode one, which I think are all in this room and two people in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, but, you know, I really just wanted to go through and sort of give, you know, the little origin story, how we evolved, how we've gotten to where we are now.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, I hear DarkSakura might not be the only OLR host writing something for Geek Life.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, just to go ahead and do the call out, we are looking for people to contribute content.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just basically go to geek-life.com and we have a little link on there for submissions so you can submit to our will.
[SPEAKER_05]: All of those kids.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, keep a look out because, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, you may see a few things cross-posted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually going to have an interview up on the site next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next week, I hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interview, interview.
[SPEAKER_03]: With Jim McCann, who wrote New Avengers The Reunion and is writing the current Hawkeye Mockingbird and the Dazzler one-shot that was fabulous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Geek Life Indeed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Emphasis on geek.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's just a really, really cool person.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Geek-life.com The dash is important.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happens if they don't put the dash in?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they get porn?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_03]: Geek porn, could you imagine?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, hey, I want to mention this too, because I got asked about this earlier tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have a lot to say on this yet, but we were asked, apparently All Games Radio is putting together this thing called The Big Battle.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I was asked if we are participating.
[SPEAKER_05]: I literally found out about this today, but from what I understand in a nutshell, it is a bunch of the shows at All Games Radio kind of getting together.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's kind of one of those things, like when you hear the idea, you're kind of like, this should have been done like two years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, how obvious is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: And why haven't we done something like this a while ago?
[SPEAKER_05]: but props, I don't know who is spearheading this, I think it might be DeadPixelLive, I don't know, but props to them for putting it on it's going to kind of bring the all games community together in big battles on games I can't 100% for sure confirm our participation yet, because I have to talk to DarkSakura and Loki after the show, see what we can do but
[SPEAKER_05]: Why wouldn't we?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all about trying to promote the All Games Network and other shows, and I think a lot of our greatest listeners come from the cross-pollination of the shows.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've always said, I realize Orange Lounge Radio is not for everybody.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some games we just don't really talk about here on this show, like Madden.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, we have a Madden story tonight, funny enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Usually we don't talk a lot about the sports games like Madden.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there's other shows on the network...
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, talk about that a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they probably would go, DDR, what are those guys doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you don't like us, surely there's another show on the network that caters to your interest.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm definitely all about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So sure, I'm sure we're going to participate.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a matter of figuring out what games we'll actually be able to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, as I understand it,
[SPEAKER_05]: This is not just a host versus host thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a listener versus listener thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're gonna need you, OL Army, to sign up and represent us in some of these games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I will hopefully have more details for you on that next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, I'm not confirming our participation, but I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's probably going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, hopefully I didn't say too much on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But somebody asked in chat earlier, and I think the All Games folks know what's going on, so whatevs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, the other thing I want to plug, E3 is coming up next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: E3 is kind of starting on a Sunday this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, not officially.
[SPEAKER_05]: The show itself does not start on a Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: But while our show is going on, did you guys know, at I think about 8 o'clock Pacific, I could have the time wrong, but that is Xbox, Microsoft's
[SPEAKER_05]: Project Natal Cirque du Soleil show is a week from right now so we're actually going to be here we will be doing a show we may cut live to the press conference if we can get some coverage we will figure out how we can do that I don't know if it's going to be much besides a show I don't know what's all involved with that but we will try to figure that out and bring you that live next week also here live next week speaking of old school OLR an old familiar guest of the show Miklatov is going to be here because he's going to E3 with me
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't leave until Monday night, so we will be here Sunday.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are not going to miss any OLR because of E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, there might be bonus OLR on the feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wouldn't see why myself and Miklatov and maybe Loki and DarkSakura via phone, depending on what we can do, or at least Bobby Blackwolf, I'm sure, if he's not too busy with all his appointments, will do some little mini-podcasts that will go to the feed during E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, I know you'll be hitting refresh on the sites non-stop Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now here's what I'm going to be doing during the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is sad because I'm not very productive during E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I watch the live conferences at my desk.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I refresh on four different live feeds at once.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd like to be able to stream it on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_06]: You might be able to.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our internet's that crappy at work, so why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, lots of housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now we can finally get to gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: Gaming news.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, and Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Add us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have I named everything?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's get into the freaking show already.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what is going on in gaming news?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I guess I could take time off during E3, too, because I do have a lot of time off.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should have just gone to the... Well, you got your wife and the baby.
[SPEAKER_05]: She would not let me go to E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's having nightmares about me going to E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not nightmares, but dreams of which she is mad at me afterwards.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, next... Well... Maybe not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe in three years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyways, there's a rumor going around that Harmonix is working on a dancing game for Natal And this is becoming, I guess, obvious due to some licenses that they are acquiring for different danceable tracks Including Cascadas, Evacuate the Dance Floor, Timberlands, The Way I Are Wait a minute, this came up a couple weeks ago, I think, some of these licensing things So now we've got clarity to what it's being used for?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they're just guessing, I think, based on the fact that it's danceable music.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hoping for a DJ game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that Timbaland thing coming up before.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think some of this is just... But I don't remember Cascada.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would have remembered something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and they're not really saying... This is coming also from Game Informer, the rumor that they're working on a dancing game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what, it makes sense if you think about it, because what game...
[SPEAKER_06]: Last Fall was just incredibly popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, I think it's still popular now that I would have never pegged to be at the top of some of these selling lists.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that would be Just Dance from Ubisoft, which is basically a game where you dance around to cues on the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it makes sense that you would use this for Natal or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's not a big surprise to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure with Natal and probably the same with the move, you're going to see lots of these really gimmicky things that we have had forever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but I mean, Loki, to be fair, that gimmicky game is kind of the roots of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, DDR was a bit of a gimmicky game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: I get that, Loki, but here's the place where I have a little more hope than I do with all the rest of that, is the fact that Harmonix is rumored to be tied into this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Harmonix...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm trying to think here, have they ever made a bad music game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a straight up bad music game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't think of one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe the chatters will jump in, but Harmonix makes pretty good games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the first Guitar Hero was revolutionary, and so the second one was good too, and then they jumped ship and made Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't have anything to do with the third thereafter, remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, Harmonix...
[SPEAKER_05]: The fact that they're involved gives me a little more hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if you think about it, Rock Band 3, I mean, how much more programming is Rock Band 3 going to take?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's probably just the Beatles and Green Day Engine souped up a little more with the keyboard, whatever's put in, a little more something, something there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's probably something else being cooked up over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: This makes perfect sense that this would be it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's to say that it's not necessarily a game like DDR?
[SPEAKER_05]: If Natal is supposed to be this magic thing that knows where you are in the room, it could work just like DDR with no dance pad.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to look weird if it works like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just going to be just like Just Dance.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's probably not going to be any more elaborate than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll just be interesting because you'll be able to do multiplayer and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it'll be more accurate because it's using a camera instead of just sensors and a close approximation of whatever you're doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe the joke is that these are actually tracks for Rock Band 3 because Rock Band 3 will also be incorporating dancers.
[SPEAKER_06]: or maybe they're working on a DJ game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because they never said anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just saying, oh, it's going to be a Natal-based dance game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I don't know if they're just guessing because, you know, Natal coming out soon and the fact that those types of games have done well in the past and also because these are danceable tracks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's a lot of speculation going on unless they know something that we don't, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: Being the expert analyst that I am, I'm sure it'll be something gimmicky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Miklatov is actually in our chatroom tonight, and he says, Rock Band Unplugged sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, opinion is relative or whatever, but I actually disagree.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Rock Band Unplugged, it wasn't Rock Band, it was Frequency Amplitude PSP with rock songs, but I didn't think it was bad at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: And actually, the really cool thing about that game, remember, it was totally free.
[SPEAKER_05]: The demo would work with the download songs, remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think he's thinking Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to be honest, I hope not.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, don't get me wrong, I like Dance Maniacs for what it was, but it's a little bit gimmicky, and I think it's a $60 game.
[SPEAKER_05]: The technology's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the technology's old and they're not going to do anything like that anymore because now you can do full dancing games because they have all these fun sensors that they can use.
[SPEAKER_05]: Couldn't they do better things with a Dance Maniacs style soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's what we should be looking for.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think we, especially as music game fans, I mean, OLR's been on for, what, eight years?
[SPEAKER_05]: And DDR was started in 1998?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, we've really got to start looking forward, not trying to emulate what's happened in the past.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is where Konami is failing miserably, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: what happened to DDR out of Konami I mean I don't want to spoil a story that's coming up later in the show but we're going to be talking about the games that are going to be shown at E3 this year I noticed DDR was not on the list from Konami I'm starting to wonder if that project was cancelled enter Harmonix just like they did with Guitar Hero
[SPEAKER_05]: Time to start looking forward with our music game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't understand how they can screw that up so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the problem, I think, with DDR is they need new blood in the game, basically.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need someone like myself to come in and just completely overhaul the damn game because what they're doing now, it's just not working.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, they need...
[SPEAKER_06]: Go back to square one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe game companies, and maybe I'm giving this with too few examples, but maybe game companies are finally kind of starting to listen to what the fans want a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so Harmonix is like, gosh, the DDR fans kind of want something new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like the Blur people were like, gee...
[SPEAKER_05]: People want a burnout Mario Kart game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's just me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It seems like there seems to be a lot more fan service.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're hearing a lot more, too, about like old ass games coming back from the dead on the iPhone or on DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you've seen that a lot lately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless it's Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_05]: Happy birthday, by the way, Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's smart that they do listen to their fans, the people that are buying their games, to make stuff that they intend on purchasing instead of, you know, oh, I don't know, let's recreate Karaoke Revolution again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that because now instead of calling it Karaoke Revolution 4 or whatever the hell number they were up to, oh, they're just going to re-release this or release a new game called Karaoke Revolution and it's not going to be very different.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's supposed to have had all this support with download content, but that never happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just can't buy what Konami's selling nowadays.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, E3 could surprise us.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take the Castlevania because apparently that Castlevania game, the multiplayer one, you know, is really legit and it should be super awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I mean, the Silent Hill game got some good feedback on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: Konami's got some hype points, but there's just, unfortunately, for those of us that liked a certain aspect of what they were doing many years ago, that is no longer one of their hype points.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to bring the Silent Hill and the Metal Gear Solid arcade games to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, actually, now you can bring them out to the PS3 and the Xbox 360, because...
[SPEAKER_06]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take a cue from Sega.
[SPEAKER_06]: Look at House of Dead 2 and 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome games, sold well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take a cue from that company who's doing The Rock of the Dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's even cooler.
[SPEAKER_06]: I take offense to Capcom making Marvel vs. Capcom 3 I enjoyed 10 years of utter arrogance in telling my friends there will never be Marvel vs. Capcom 3
[SPEAKER_05]: Four words, never say never ever
[SPEAKER_05]: If DC and Marvel can hook up, anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bionic Commando Rearmed.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sin and Punishment Sky Successor from Rei Ayanami in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: That Sin and Punishment game's all... And you know what's sad about that is it's not going to sell well and it's going to be considered probably a failure on Nintendo's part and you won't see that many games like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big words, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's to say that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why you say that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because every single mature or niche game on the Wii has not sold well.
[SPEAKER_05]: all of them think about this topic for next week I don't want to get into it tonight because we're running a little long anyway but just think about this topic for next week and write it down mentally in case I forget because I want to go through the different three press conferences and I want to kind of ask this question and maybe this is a good email topic too if those of you guys want to email us this week mailbagorangeandre.com because we're going to talk a lot pre E3 next week what could the big three do Sony, Nintendo, Microsoft at their press conferences to make you a rabid fanboy all over again
[SPEAKER_05]: Silly answers are fine, but give me some serious ones too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to tell you right now what Sony's got to do, and it's so simple, it's so obvious.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, alright, but now I want to change topics because I don't want to ruin next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I feel really bad for not knowing the guy's name, but the guy that they have in their commercials right now needs to be running that damn conference.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's the best marketing campaign ever for Sony.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would actually agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: For a company that's had lots of missteps, lots of missteps, remember the black and white PSP?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, remember that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the God of War lamb being served up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember the crane, baby?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a direction they should stick with.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I totally agree.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sure that guy will be at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Kevin Butler, I think, was his name or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: He'll be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And our chat is lighting up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kevin Butler, he's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the man, says Blaze.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Wolf says he's an actor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope he does the intro.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hope he's there.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's move on, though, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk a little more.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope he's in every press conference.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's one of the rumors about what's going to be seen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big, big, fat rumor, but it's kind of one of those rumors you look at and go, okay, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, Hulu is being teased as a possible addition to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is coming from Gear Live, which is a tech site.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, they have picked up on a rumor that Hulu's streaming functionality is going to be in the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be announced at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1Up ran with the same rumor, saying that a Hulu application for the Xbox 360 definitely exists, but the problem right now...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's tied up with rights issues.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody wants a piece of the rights to the application.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hulu on the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, for those of you that don't know Hulu, Hulu's a website.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of launched to say...
[SPEAKER_05]: How much is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, it's awesome that it's there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, prepare to be disappointed by the cliffhanger ending because the show got canceled midway through.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I mean, there's a lot of cool stuff like that that I think would be a great addition to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fact or crap?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hulu on the 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it definitely could happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it could happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: Going off the old standby that all rumors are in fact true, I could see it happening too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a good alternative to Netflix.
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing I didn't like though is they were saying that they were going to possibly charge more money to access Hulu on the 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, if that's the case, that's retarded because, I mean, if you just use your PC and stream your PC to your 360, you can watch Hulu for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: So why should I have to pay extra money?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bochikawa in our chat says, yeah, all the consoles have internets.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why couldn't you watch them on it already?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I don't believe... They block it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's blocked on the PS3, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I don't think the Wii has a high enough flash version.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the Xbox 360, don't forget, it's missing a web browser.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know a lot of people think, just assume, oh yeah, I can surf the web on my 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, you can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes sense why they don't do that, because there's already enough holes in their security.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Wyland in our chatroom says if you want Dark Shadows watch the original 1245 episodes bring them to Hulu and maybe I'll start although from what I understand you don't really start watching Dark Shadows until about episode 75 or whenever Barnabas is finally actually first introduced you can just kind of skip the first few that's what I'm understanding anyway but I could be wrong alright
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, so it sounds like it could be a fact we will find out in a week Because if it's not announced at E3 then it's not coming this year, that's for sure DarkSakura, what you got for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, this is more Xbox news, but basically, Robbie Bach, who is the entertainment dude, is retiring.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was a memo that went out that said that he is retiring.
[SPEAKER_03]: The memo was out by Steve Ballmer.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, Jay Allard is going to be retiring as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta wonder if that means like retiring, like the little quotes there, like retiring, or having their butt pushed out the door.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, there's always that kind of like, hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I mean, it's not like, I don't think Jay Allard is 65.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's not quite of that retirement age yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they've just been there for a while and basically Xbox is printing money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, weren't they tied to a failure that Xbox had?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wasn't there something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not Xbox, I take it that Microsoft was supposed to launch, was it a tablet computer or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that didn't do, and I'm sure someone in chat will jump in, that didn't, I don't think ended up happening at all, and now it's everybody's iPad, iPad, iPad.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, it's just not going to happen there at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wonder how they thought they could compete with Apple over that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of our people in our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com Guest 9595, I wish you'd change their name so I could give them proper credit, but Guest 9595 says, Hey, can't you watch Hulu and stuff with PlayOn for any of the systems?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, that little software that lets you transfer your...
[SPEAKER_05]: stuff over to the TV, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I mean, there's that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I prefer diversity.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you can stream Hulu.
[SPEAKER_06]: I use my PS3 to do that, and that works really well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, it works just the same on a 360, but yeah, you can do that, and that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why should I pay the extra?
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing I'm guessing is it's going to be HD streaming, maybe, and you're going to get...
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the rumors was they're going to start charging for Hulu if you want to watch some of the archive episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The recent episodes will be free, but the stuff past the first or second... Well, that's at the website now, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: You can watch the last five episodes of Glee, but if you want to watch anything older than that, you can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but they're going to allow you to, but you're going to have to bill the pay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good thing I don't want to watch any episodes of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you're missing out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's how Sue sees it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, and I'm just, and we're going to get into some Project $10 stuff soon, but just to kind of talk about it, I'm mad at the idea of it, and the reason I'm mad at the idea is not necessarily that it affects me, it affects a lot of other people, because me personally, I either buy new games or I don't buy the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not necessarily that I wouldn't buy used games, but
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if there's a game that I don't think I'm going to be playing, I probably won't pick it up just because I know myself and I know that if I buy a game that I'm not so hot on, I won't end up playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just be sitting collecting dust.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, for me, it's not such a big deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, if you just let one thing slide, then it's just going to be a whole mess of crap that's going to come out later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I'm kind of pissed off that EA is doing the whole Project $10 thing and then now THQ is following suit with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as I rumored last week, Microsoft will be probably following suit with that as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if Microsoft does it, then we'll have other people doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to talk more Project $10.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who else is going to join in?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sega is considering joining some sort of online pass system.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is me scolding Sega.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sega!
[SPEAKER_06]: and, you know, basically Ubisoft is also kind of liking the idea and Sega is saying, you know, it's a very clever idea and they're certainly taking looks to see what happens with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're saying, of course, you know, that they want to be careful to make sure that, you know, the EA, you know, sports thing that they're doing right now actually works out and, you know, the backlash isn't too big and,
[SPEAKER_06]: But if it ends up working out for them, then perhaps they will allow you to... They will do something very similar.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's kind of funny, though, is we were talking about the whole online pass thing and the Project $10 stuff with EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of the theories was they wanted to kind of put this out there so that they can make some money from used sales and also it may curb a little bit of the piracy because the fact that if you...
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be one reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: But then EA's, I guess, UK general manager, Keith Ramsdale, basically made a comment and said, no, actually the Project $10 online pass are not about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's all about the customer and improving their experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's simply not a defensive measure against pre-owned or piracy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, my bullshit meter was going off.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean... If that isn't a bunch of corporate speak.
[SPEAKER_05]: Improving the customer experience through... Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's retarded, then.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would rather they come out and say, yeah, it's actually the curb piracy and used sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because now the fact that you're saying no, it's actually just to make your online play even better, but the online play isn't changing, then that just means, no, you're actually just grabbing at money.
[SPEAKER_06]: at least, you know, give it the, you know, excuse that, oh, we're actually just trying to make some money off of used sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, don't even bother with the used sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just say you're just using it to combat piracy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, because everybody is like, oh, okay, piracy, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um, I...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, I don't play a lot of EA games.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least not the sports stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm guessing, just looking at this stuff, that Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11, when it's coming out on Tuesday here...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm guessing that the online play is not going to be that different from Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by all means, people should really look into that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because if this is their claim that, oh, we're doing this to the benefit of, you know, our consumers, then you need to look at... I think you should write a comparison for OrangeLawnTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't want to play Tiger Woods 10 or 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scour on the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you need access to games through your job or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they need to look at X and XI to see, okay, was X the latency better in XI?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is the options better in XI?
[SPEAKER_06]: And all this stuff, because I bet you if you look at that,
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet you it's the same damn shit all over again.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it really doesn't make any sense that they're charging people they're buying used for these games because they've already gotten the money for these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no reason they need more money for these games.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not adding more users to the online because this is still one copy of a game that's floating around out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've already made your money.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you can't run your infrastructure on the money they've made on new games...
[SPEAKER_06]: It just doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because what if, which is, it's not going to happen, but what if, you know, say, you know, this whole online pass thing ends up flopping and you're not making any money for, you know, the online games.
[SPEAKER_06]: People aren't paying to play online more than that seven-day trial.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then nothing changes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, because that's not going to motivate them to get rid of it because they're still going to make money off new games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if you think about it, though, what are they hoping to accomplish by this?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're hoping that people either buy the game new or they're going to basically hope that they pay the $10 or whatever, $5 to actually play online.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if people don't pay that and they don't receive enough revenue, then guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: The online experience doesn't change at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: So basically making their whole point, you know,
[SPEAKER_05]: you know, nonsense because if they're not making money from this extra use sales and using it to improve their service then they're full of shit alright let's move on with another story because this is like three weeks in a row we've talked about this stupid thing it's because it's dumb I know, I know something new is coming up every week and sadly we're probably going to hear even more about it at E3 and what other companies are going to jump on board yippee yippee
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of things that are full of bullshit, somebody has filed a lawsuit against Sony and Square Enix because Final Fantasy XIII caused severe and widespread damage to PlayStation 3 consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was filed by Daniel Wolff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a class action lawsuit, meaning if he wins, you'll all get a piece of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wolf reckons that it freezes PlayStation 3s and when you play this, you can get your PS3 console to become totally and permanently inoperable.
[SPEAKER_05]: The lawsuit says both defendants are eminently aware of the damage being caused by their defective products and have chosen to do nothing about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're being sued, I guess, for over $5 million in damages and relief is being sought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meaning that if you are affected by you having both of these things, you could get your very own coupon for $5 in the mail.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll probably be the piece of this that you're entitled to.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's usually what happens with these class action lawsuits.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't make any sense because it's not widespread.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did Xbox ever have to settle for the Red Rings of Death thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because in my opinion, that was a much bigger problem.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that's why they extended the warranty to three years, I thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it doesn't matter because this isn't widespread.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where are your data on this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, where is the data?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, because... Rob, you own Final Fantasy XIII on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is your PS3 inoperable because of Final Fantasy XIII?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but there was that one day.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, what, March 1st or whatever, when all the clocks were fucked up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_06]: But that wouldn't be because of Final Fantasy XIII, since it came out after that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would think that that would be hard to prove in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: That there is widespread damage because it's like a dude, you know, saying, oh, my system crashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, just randomly asking this question, how many of you remember the one day that the PS3s were down?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I bet most of you forgot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was only about three months ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there was that, remember that one day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I remember that one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: We should do that every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: We should have like, hey, you know, in case you forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll have a statement called never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember that time that Namco's really pissed off at us?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like it, man.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're full of ideas this month.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that should be a segment that we do regularly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never.
[SPEAKER_05]: It should be never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or no, we should do that on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that is a wonderful idea for a series of articles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is there an OLR fan that maybe wants to pick that up?
[SPEAKER_06]: But we need to do actually more stuff that's like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Never forget...
[SPEAKER_05]: when Xbox Live used to discriminate against the word gay being in your profile but they did get rid of that but I remember when I I think we were reporting it here on the show and I was like oh yeah I was really mad about that when that first happened but I kind of forgot that that had happened
[SPEAKER_05]: so we do need a never forget so that like things that I get mad about and you get mad about and Jamie gets mad about we never forget maybe it could be like a page on the wiki and when one of us says never forget this somebody can add it to the wiki so that way we never forget ah yes I like that idea
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, surely there's something in your mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget that this happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never forget that people are bitches.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's just a given.
[SPEAKER_05]: That has nothing to do with gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, I think the Portal 2 thing is still happening, but I think that they're under, you know, they're, oh yeah, the event was cancelled, but, you know, then there's gonna be like, oh, haha, Aperture Science has trapped you all, and now you must run through the maze.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let Jamie get her thought out, and then I've got an idea on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, from what I was reading, though, Half-Life 3 is gonna have, actually, Chell from Portal is supposed to be making her appearance, and then they also are talking about the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, what's the name of that ship that Aperture put out that's supposed to show up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's Cameo at the end of Portal, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they mentioned it in that retooled Portal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, um, but like, it's some ship that, of Aperture's that crashed or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, I don't remember the whole deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, here's what I was supposed to say about the Portal 2 party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that, I bet what they're doing, like did you hear that really fucked up story?
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget this, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you hear that really fucked up story about that school in like Mississippi or whatever where the girl wanted to go to the prom with her girlfriend but they were like, no, because you're a dirty lesbian and we're not going to have that happen at our prom.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what they did, you know what they ended up doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: They threw another prom in
[SPEAKER_05]: and invited like her and her girlfriend and like eight school misfits to like the fake prom and they had like a real prom somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that was crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was fucked up beyond belief, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: What if that's what they're doing with the Portal 2 party?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're like, sorry guys, the Portal 2 party got canceled.
[SPEAKER_05]: I seriously think... But then suddenly we'll see these reports on the internet about...
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, 1up.com got invited to this super secret party.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I seriously think that they're going to actually have, it's going to be this, you know, oh, it's actually a secret surprise.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, you know, the surprise is, you know, oh, look at this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, the, you know, GLaDOS has hacked the conference or something, you know, something ridiculous like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Salacious Pop saves the day, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Borealis is the ship.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew it had some sort of celestial name.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's like the Aurora Borealis.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Bobby's reminding us that he was supposed to go to the Portal 2 party and he's a misfit now, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Bobby Blackwolf, but it very well could be that you have something in common with a lesbian in Mississippi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Off to the island with you.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll throw you your improv.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's okay, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get invited to anything, so we can have drinks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do have an appointment to see Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woo!
What?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, there's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, steal a keytar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
Lord.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then you'll really be reading about that on the blogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, look, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, we need a dose of something really cool and awesome in this show.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about some class?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, this show could use a little class.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, this show could use a lot of class.
[SPEAKER_03]: More class than a class action lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, first, I must preface this by saying that it is about the recently knighted Sir Patrick Stewart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_03]: That makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_03]: About damn time.
[SPEAKER_05]: So now you must address him as Sir Patrick Stewart.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sir Patrick Stewart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Patrick Stewart.
[SPEAKER_03]: At any rate, he's basically on record saying that he loves his beautiful iPhone.
[SPEAKER_03]: That it has become an extension of himself.
[SPEAKER_03]: That he couldn't imagine going without it or his laptop.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that he has a stack of video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to hear Patrick Stewart narrate a story about how much he loves his iPhone.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a video on this one too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Talking about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But he's saying that...
[SPEAKER_03]: He has, in fact, I'll read the quote.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only aspect of all this that I've never taken to, in part because I have an addictive temperament, is gaming.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have a stack of games that I've never taken the covers off of because I feel that if I do, I'm finished.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I just listen to a little bit of Patrick Stewart?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I just listen to his voice?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, first of all, Rob, you saw Jeffrey, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see him in Jeffrey?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, God, I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love him in that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shh, shh, shh, shh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody, worship.
[SPEAKER_00]: Seems to me to be a little bit simplistic.
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe I like complexity and abstraction too much.
[SPEAKER_00]: But on the other hand, I just handed someone my
[SPEAKER_00]: Beautiful iPhone, which I never have out of my hand and that I do everything with and has become an extension of who I am.
[SPEAKER_00]: I travel with my laptop everywhere.
[SPEAKER_00]: Emails are absolutely essential in my life.
[SPEAKER_00]: His voice.
[SPEAKER_00]: It sounds like he said sexual in my life.
[SPEAKER_04]: He did say sexual, didn't he?
[SPEAKER_03]: He could just read the phone book to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, that was really quiet over the feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I apologize, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know why it's so quiet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beautiful.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Sir Patrick Stewart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sir Patrick Stewart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sir.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haha.
[SPEAKER_03]: All you people who don't like Apple, haha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sir Patrick Stewart endorses it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haha.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just because he hasn't touched a droid, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not since the days of Star Trek The Next Generation has he ever touched a droid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how about some release dates?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Data would like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Release dates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Traveling around the globe talking about what's coming out in a neighborhood near you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: This week, not a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's just some weird stuff and some decent stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's start with the weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: America's Next Top Model on DS in the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that was supposed to come out like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: As soon as Loki said that, I had to yawn really bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember cracking a Tyra Banks' crazy joke.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand that, and she is crazy, but it'll come out when it's ready to come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just like Tyra.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty, the War Collection, making its way out on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it's a bunch of re-releases.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wonder if the Top Model game will have a panty party in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you've never seen this YouTube, you need to YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: Google this on YouTube or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: YouTube it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tyra Banks Panty Party.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the funniest thing I've ever seen on the Tyra Banks show.
[SPEAKER_05]: She goes, we're going to have a panty party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, random.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been...
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been a woman most of my life I was a girl before that I've never had a panty party You haven't lived How about a manty party?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, thank you Let's play ballerina on the DS Let's hope they never put out Let's Play Doctor because that would be very inappropriate
[SPEAKER_06]: Green Day Rock Band coming out on Wii, Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 you also have Green Day Rock Band Plus in case you don't want to pay for the extra $10 to dump your songs it's included in the price this time and it's still $10 more
[SPEAKER_06]: Vacation Isle Beach Party Western Writing Academy Mega Man Zero Collection Samantha Swift and the Hidden Roses of Athena
[SPEAKER_06]: Disgaea Infinite on PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: What are you giggling about over there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Marissa Cungusto's comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Green Day Rock Band, play three chords on your balls.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's the new instrument in Rock Band 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your balls.
[SPEAKER_06]: you can do harmonies with your balls clearly it's nothing but David Bowie songs if that's the case Satisfaction Rock the Runway on DS I think that's also on the Wii as well
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do I know this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, and also on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Prince of Persia The Forgotten Sands finds its way out on the PC this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mind Over Matter, another brain training game on the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mel, you're solid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Peace Walker coming out on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's Play Garden on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that is it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have the time to listen to me whine about a bunch of release dates for Japan?
[SPEAKER_05]: Stuff that's coming out in Japan this week on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grand Theft Auto, episodes from Liberty City, that's right, the localized version, the retail release, June 10th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just Cause 2, also this week in Japan, and Saints Row 2 gets a price reduction, the Platinum Collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, Loki, one of the big rumblings about what's coming at E3 this year, Saints Row 3...
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's not being released until next year, and that makes me sad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, seeing how far they went with the Red Faction and the new Red Faction Armageddon game, or I think it's Armageddon is the subtitle on that, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if that looks awesome, Saints Row 3 is going to be that much more awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be more awesomer.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that should be what's on the title, more awesomer than Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: PlayStation 3 gets the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right, Grand Theft Auto episodes from Liberty City, Just Cause 2, and Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the same stuff on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Over in Japan this week Nintendo Wii gets Karaoke JoySound Wii Enka That comes with a USB microphone You're doing an Enka game?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what it says That's coming from Hudson Do you know what Enka is?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the Japanese version of folk country music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes, I have heard some of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember me playing you Jero?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks like, I don't know if it's like a version of their karaoke revolution or what, but that is coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Rockman Zero Collection Maru Gokaku Shikaku Dasu Gaishiyoshi Saiken
[SPEAKER_05]: Wanda of Fortune Portable is the big release on the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wanda Fortune Portable from Idea Factory, an adventure game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see any screenshots, but the characters look like anime Harry Potter people, so I'm sure that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never forget Zelda, Wanda of Gamelon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that the 3DO game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, one of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played that at a classic gaming expo a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, how about the old country?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, really not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the 8th is Green Day Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: 9th is Joe Danger.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then toward the end of the week on the 11th we have King Arthur Mega Man Zero Collection, Naval Assault, The Killing Tide, and Super Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's over!
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, surprised that no one in studio had anything to say on Super Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Wii is still not hooked up, that's why I haven't bought the game yet, but I am hearing phenomenal things about the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So have I, I'm just kind of... I know, it's kind of under the radar right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of one of those games I hope I can go back to and play at some point, but for right now it's kind of on the back burner.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, I've heard lots and lots of good things about Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently OutShines the first.
[SPEAKER_05]: In many ways.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'll be impressive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, the first was not a bad game at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps Nintendo can send me a free copy once I pimp out my room in New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Eh?
[SPEAKER_05]: You should try it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wink?
[SPEAKER_06]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, future gamer!
[SPEAKER_05]: Teaching them young.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling you, when you do that to your kid, your kid's going to rebel.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to have a kid that wants to go out and play football all day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't care if he wants to go play football.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's fine with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not forcing him to like video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just the theme we're doing his room in.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: He can do whatever he wants.
[SPEAKER_06]: If he wants to go work on cars and play football and that kind of stuff, that's fine with me.
[SPEAKER_06]: My mom was a painter.
[SPEAKER_05]: He won't, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: How do I need to poo?
[SPEAKER_06]: But my dad, on the other hand, he, see, he bought a ColecoVision for himself and Atari games and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I just naturally started playing those.
[SPEAKER_06]: They bought me a Texas Instruments computer.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, because you were born in like 81, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: When all that was out?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, in 80.
80?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, 80.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, all that stuff came out and just naturally I got into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the stuff that I was into, like, when I was that old, you know, I'm into now even more so.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to force it upon you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to play games because my wife hates games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is ironic that she suggested that we do a Mario Brothers themed room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never would have thought that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your wife does have those random moments of gaming.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: They only have so much ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like four feet worth of the ground vinyl.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we just can't circle the room with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we have to paint everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I'm not going to spend money to buy enough sheets to cover the whole room.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are all the guests leaving the funny comments tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Guest 5872, please change your name, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you get in there, type slash Nick and then the new name.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I congratulate you appropriately.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you get booted.
[SPEAKER_05]: Suki-ban-sa-chu-re-na.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You should do this room in President Cat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Clearly it's a listener of the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: We almost did it in Stella themed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stella would be my cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that would be weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kitty themed.
[SPEAKER_06]: She is a little bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: She wants me to play, because we made her a toy out of bag handles.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're these little string handles or whatever, and we tied them together.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now she'll go...
[SPEAKER_06]: She locked her in a room with Shermie
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta move on, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're an hour and a half into Part A and we're not even done yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we haven't talked about my cat enough yet!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really want a cat, y'all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm getting to that point.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's time for me to be a daddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob needs to be a daddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, you're in luck.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I have a cat for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't want your cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not my cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Screw that.
[SPEAKER_06]: My cat's
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about Barney, the female cat outside.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's still a wild cat, and yeah, I don't know why we call her Barney, but that's the name we gave her before we found out that she was a girl, and so it just stuck.
[SPEAKER_06]: But she actually is very friendly and comes up to us and stuff, so I will trap her for you if you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I brought you a kitty in a box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Adopt a cat, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm not going to do it just yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're so easy to take care of, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but remember, I'm gone every weekend, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every weekend I'm gone.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'll go take care of your cat on the weekends.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you won't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too far.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I go take care of Susan's cat when she goes out of town.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, I would take care of your pussy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you pet my pussy when it needed it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I would.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: And give it a bath.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, I've watched Shermie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you wash my pussy on the weekend?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I've got a schedule.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget how mature we are here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, a couple quick stories for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Classic Game of the Week coming up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, so we were talking a little bit about Project $10 and how EA likes to find ways to milk you for your precious money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, now they're doing it again, and this isn't something that you necessarily have to do, but it's something you may be tempted to do.
[SPEAKER_06]: Madden 11 basically logs everything that you do online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your play calling, what tendencies you do, and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it builds kind of a playbook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can't see your porn collection, can it?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can't see your porn collection.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it basically builds like a playbook that kind of revolves around what you do.
[SPEAKER_06]: and um now during if you you know play i guess enough people or whatever uh other people can get that from you but um you can actually purchase um these reports as well so that you can kind of get the dirt on the other players that you're playing against
[SPEAKER_05]: and um that's kind of strange like I don't really have another word for that that's just I don't know I mean well yeah you of course sell it take all that information and then sell it it's kind of shady but it's kind of like them selling the cheats that were in the games you know you cheats that used to be just button presses now you have to pay two dollars to unlock and type stuff
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just... It's such a desperate money grab.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're becoming that desperate chick, EA.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody likes desperate chick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anything they can do, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any place they can get more money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop being so...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's just there's no real benefit if you don't do it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're going to charge me for online for used or whatever than the real game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I guess if you buy it, you knew it really doesn't affect you anyways.
[SPEAKER_06]: But seriously, though, don't let it slide.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going to make you even more angry, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, there is a draft.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a law yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is just a draft that the Federal Trade Commission here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: making this draft.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're making some proposals to Washington, and apparently one of them is a 5% tax on consumer electronics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, some folks are calling this the iPad tax, but it's not just iPads, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: It really should be just iPads, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: iPhones, iMacs, Zunes, DSs, 360s, laptops, digital cameras.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, basically Best Buy is fucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of things you buy there are going to have a 5% tax on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just going to pass it on to the consumer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are they doing this, folks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it will generate $4 billion for the US government, which it could then use to subsidize failing media outlets like newspapers.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember reading, and maybe it wasn't on this show, but about how the iPad is reinvigorating the old school media because a lot of these newspapers are coming out with editions for the iPad that they're selling subscriptions to, and they're actually doing quite well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And magazines are doing this too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The iPad is becoming this new reading device.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like, why do we need to save your archaic ass if you're not going to evolve?
[SPEAKER_05]: It just doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, it hasn't passed yet, but it's a dumb idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't like what they're using the money for.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the money could go to the more important things.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do we have to bail out the news media?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they sell ads.
[SPEAKER_06]: They need to evolve and adopt to where their readers are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I get some of that money?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're media.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're floundering.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't made a dime since this show began.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want four billion dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop bailing out companies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well let's move on to a part of the show that needs no bailing out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very popular here on the Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: And every week you guys come to know and love this segment.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that everyone's going to figure out what this game is when you play the opening sequence.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so then, well, let me just say though, every week, for those that maybe have never listened to Orange House Radio before, every week, DarkSakura likes to go through the vault, the classic video game vault, and pick out a game that she says, hey, you ungrateful little bastards playing on the lawn, you need to go play this classic video game immediately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get off my lawn and play this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that's what we should rename the segment, get off my lawn and play this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here is tonight's classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Gear Solid Metal Gear Solid
[SPEAKER_03]: and who said Barbie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Gear Solid, a stealth action game that was directed and written by the guy I used to run into every year at E3, Hideo Kojima.
[SPEAKER_03]: It first came out in 1998 for the PlayStation and it's actually the sequel to the MSX2 Metal Gear 2 Solid Snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not the one that we got over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: The actual MSX version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, what in the actual hell is this video?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually 3 hours and 20 minutes long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, people can do this on YouTube now?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the playthrough of the first half of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought you were limited to 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: In theory.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the voice acting in this.
[SPEAKER_03]: And by the way, the guy who did Snake's voice was David Hayter and he also wrote the first two X-Men movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is why they were good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the third one blew.
[SPEAKER_03]: He had written the third one and it would have been good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both are being held as hostages.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is the one that brought Metal Gear up to the current generation of gamers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically he's going in and stopping a group called Foxhound, which was his old unit, has to liberate some hostages and basically stop them from...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, blowing up the earth, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Man, I hate it when people try to blow up the earth.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's play Thermonuclear War.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, it has amazing voice acting.
[SPEAKER_03]: And even with the limitations of the visuals back in the day,
[SPEAKER_03]: They really did a good job in covering up the things that would have been harder to show, like blurring the face a little bit, smoothing the line here or there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really did look very good for its day.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could get all kinds of bonus stuff to use in the game, because it's on-site weapons procurement, as well as being played like the old ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, you can also get infrared goggles and a cardboard box and he smuggles his cigarettes in through his stomach.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does it mean that he barfs up his cigarettes as soon as he lands?
[SPEAKER_05]: Perhaps, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, you have to use the cigarettes to get through a couple of stages, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are, as you can tell from listening to all the speaking in the background, lots of cutscenes and conversations.
[SPEAKER_03]: This game is very dialogue heavy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But on the plus side, it's very good voice acting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, why don't you turn it up a little bit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, it's a little bit quiet, but here you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, that's when he's about to land, so... There's no voice acting right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some in a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're at the part where he breaks through the water.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the start menu of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we can do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the music in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually have the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the soundtrack to all the Metal Gear Solid games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I also pick up all the art books for Dan every year.
[SPEAKER_03]: At any rate...
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole first part of the game is to teach you the whole stealth part of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Once you get the stealth down, you can actually go through the whole game for the most part without killing people.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get bonuses, I think, for the fewer that you kill.
[SPEAKER_03]: but you also have to sort of maintain a working knowledge of how the entire facility is laid out as you go through it because you have to run back through it part of the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: The characters you have in this one is, I think this is funny, the character designer said that Solid State's physique was based off of Jean-Claude Van Damme but his face was based off of Christopher Walken.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't see that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he's a little bit better looking than Christopher Walken.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you've got Roy Campbell, who is his former CO, and then you have Master Miller, and Mei Ling, and Naomi Hunter, and Natasha Romanenko, who is a weapons person.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you also get Otacon, who is named after the convention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's some voice acting.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the other thing I was gonna bring up is that this game totally breaks the fourth wall, like, all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, when you run into one of the other hostages, he tells you about a soldier that Snake ran into earlier who ends up being Meryl.
[SPEAKER_03]: He said, yeah, you can contact her on Kodak.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I remember, her number is on the back of the CD case.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Psycho Mantis
[SPEAKER_03]: You better hide somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, so yeah, you go through the game, you get to see Metal Gear Rex, and, um, oh yeah, you also have, um, a, uh, an informant called Deep Throat, which I thought was a kind of neat nod towards, um, well, you know, there was an actual Deep Throat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Towards Linda Lovelace?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, oh, sorry, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: The actual, yeah, no, I know Watergate, of course I know Watergate.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he finally, finally came forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, that's right, like right before he died, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I think he was declassified at the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, man, that's something else though, being able to hold a secret that long, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, you go through the game, you have an epic battle with Liquid Snake, who is the antagonist and Solid Snake's twin.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you also have two endings based on what you do during the torture sequence.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of them, Meryl gets to live.
[SPEAKER_03]: The other one, Meryl dies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's my favorite question in the whole game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, do you believe that love can bloom on the battlefield?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why does love always feel like a battlefield?
[SPEAKER_03]: Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, for tie-ins, and I know I've brought up Policenauts before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Meryl was a character in Policenauts.
[SPEAKER_03]: So she was included.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's references to Metal Gear in Policenauts.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually, I think scenes from Policenauts that go through when Otacon is talking about being a big geek.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, he's a big otaku.
[SPEAKER_03]: He pees himself, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first time you meet him, seriously, he backs into a corner and pisses himself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello LP joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's also preliminary artwork that was an Easter egg for Policenaut's pilot disc for the 3DO, which I think didn't come out, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, there were some side stories.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was Metal Gear Solid Integral, which is based off of the expanded Japanese version, except it had a VR mode with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got the VR missions as a separate disc.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it had like a PS, you remember the Pocket Station, Rob?
[SPEAKER_03]: It had a Pocket Station minigame.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could call the codec frequency and get commentary from the staff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you had a first-person game mode.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there was also Metal Gear Solid The Twin Snakes, which came out on GameCube.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's that sneaking suit working out?
[SPEAKER_03]: And also one that people may not be familiar with, the BLEEM version for BLEEMcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which basically, it ran it through with the Dreamcast's superior rendering capabilities, and it was really nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I totally suggest everyone look up BLEEM for Dreamcast, Metal Gear Solid, and then compare them side by side.
[SPEAKER_03]: It really is night and day.
[SPEAKER_03]: The soundtrack was amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was done by Rika Muranaka.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, actually, the ending song was done by her, and it's also sung in Irish for the ending.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, from there we got all kinds of others.
[SPEAKER_03]: We got digital comics, we got a graphic novel, and then, of course, there were all of the sequels.
[SPEAKER_03]: Metal Gear Solitude, The Avengers of Raiden running around naked.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pfft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you ever play that one, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_03]: The second one.
[SPEAKER_05]: A very little, very, very little.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Metal Gear, it was Sons of Liberty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Snake is in there calling himself Iroquois Plissken.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Plissken also from Snake Plissken.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Metal Gear Solid 3 Snake Eater, where he's actually playing as Naked Snake, who turns out to be Big Boss.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spoiler!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, where have you been?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Metal Gear Solid 4 Guns of the Patriots.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's wrong?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just didn't expect a world-class designer of military technology to be so... cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: You're just flattering me.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I know I won't be bored for the next 18 hours.
[SPEAKER_01]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can't believe I'm being hit on by the famous Solid Snake.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, if you keep talking to her, she'll give you like a little parable or a little phrase.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's basically your fortune cookie throughout the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you keep calling her, she'll eventually just get mad at you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And her answer will be dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_03]: And she'll have this big frowny face.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there's another... I think it was in the second one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or was it in the first one where you're in the locker and if you look at the picture of the girl and then call someone on the codec, it sounds like he's jerking off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's Easter eggs in this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like Otacon tells him, we don't have time for that snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the second one.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's like, we don't have time for that snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he's just got the O face.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I know a little bit too much about the Metal Gear games.
[SPEAKER_05]: You sure do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is that it for the wrap up?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta move on with the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was an epic game of the week there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm already losing my voice again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Metal Gear Solid is your classic game of the week, and a true classic at that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we are going to take a quick break so that we can rest our voices and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have plenty more Orange Lounge Radio to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a long episode tonight, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to talk about a new game from the creator of Parappa the Rappa, possible upgrades of old PS2 titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Goldeneye could be making a comeback.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to talk all about that in Part B of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go anywhere, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: We will be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, June the 6th of 2010 where we are doing episode number 369 of our show.
[SPEAKER_05]: E3 is just around the corner.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, we've had a lot of news and rumors and stuff about what's coming up at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I think our show is taping live tonight while the MTV Movie Awards are going on, I think is the big thing tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as to who's winning right now, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, are those awards relevant?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they actually mean anything?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is it just an excuse to get a bunch of celebrities together for ratings?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's pretty much how I feel too.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so let's get back into some gaming news then, some things we care about around here, and some rapid, quick stories for you guys here before we get back to some Twitter topics, which we're going to get to in a moment, at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you've probably got like three minutes to get in your topics if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, let's do some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the first of hopefully many pieces of download content for Red Dead Redemption will be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: On June 22nd, Outlaws to the End will be adding some new content to the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Six online co-op missions for two to four players.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, they're going to have some different...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, different types of missions in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like one where you're escorting a raft, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that would be great because I don't know about people that have played Red Dead Redemption, but the gang hideouts that you can actually play during free mode, I think we've gone through all of those at least six times now.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's getting old fast, and we need some more things to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: and of course that is going to be free on the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_06]: We Party is going to be one of the games that are going to be shown off this year at Nintendo's press conference and it's going to feature 80 plus games including some interesting ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remote Control Hide and Seek
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess the players will hide their Wii remotes somewhere in the room and the other players have to search for it by the sound coming from the controller's speaker.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: groundbreaking and revolutionary I will give them props for being somewhat unique some of the other games they were talking about called 1-1 Karuta wouldn't it be funny if like you hit the thing too good and then it's too far away from the Wii to make a noise or whatever so it gets lost forever
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sucker, gotta buy another $40 controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wanwan Karuta is a game where the Wii Remote will make a sound and the players will have to match the noise with an on-screen image, for example an animal.
[SPEAKER_06]: They also have a game called Sensitive Bomb which players will pass the single remote to one another without trying to jostle it too much to trigger the explosion.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what you do is you pass it to another player and then you push them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's playing with power.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that'll be, of course, shown at the press conference on June 15th.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some other fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Will Reggie Fils-Aim come out and try to blow somebody up and push them and all that stuff, you think?
[SPEAKER_06]: He won't because he's probably endorsing family play that's not destructive like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't give a shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are no rules in Wii Parking.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, K'nex is apparently teaming up with Nintendo to make some Mario Kart toys.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this is supposed to be happening sometime in 2011.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that is awesome that you can make toys based on Mario Kart and K'nex because, you know, hey, if it's not Lego, it's K'nex.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that would be, uh, be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love to have like Lego or K'nex toys based on like the Mario stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, Salacious Pop is keeping us updated in chat on the MTV Movie Awards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's why you're glad you're not watching.
[SPEAKER_05]: You ready for this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Best female performance, Kristen Stewart in Twilight, New Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best male performance, Robert Pattinson in Twilight, New Moon.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're clearly not the demographic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Best movie, The Twilight Saga, New Moon.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are not the demographic for MTV anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just the MTV we knew and loved is gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's dead.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what Twilight needs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Simon Belmont.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what Twilight needs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, going on to some quick fire news and some other stuff that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock Band Weekly updates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Deftones are coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoop-dee-doo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Grown up in Sacramento, I've heard way too much Deftones.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cherry Waves, Hole in the Earth, and Minerva.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whoop-dee-whoop-dee.
[SPEAKER_05]: individual songs Boys Like Girls with The Great Escape and Crown of Thorns with Rock Ready I will be buying none of those songs but maybe you're interested I too will be buying none of those songs here's a game that might actually catch my interest maybe I will buy this it's a game called Hardcore Uprising Hard Corps but I think the P is silent when you say it like that Hardcore Uprising
[SPEAKER_05]: for Xbox Live Arcade and PSN.
[SPEAKER_05]: And why am I interested in this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently it's a spiritual successor to Contra.
[SPEAKER_05]: It plays like Contra.
[SPEAKER_05]: It feels like Contra.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's high def.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's side-scroller.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's guns.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just doesn't have Contra in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the game looks awesome because it's done by Axis, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or not Axis...
[SPEAKER_06]: The people that did it are like, please blue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's all hand-drawn stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you might remember there was a Genesis game called Contra Hard Corps.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is apparently a successor to that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for whatever reason, they've just decided not to call it Contra.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they just didn't want people to know what this game was.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It still looks cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Arc System Works, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, Arc System Works, that's what I was thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it will be beautifully animated, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also coming out, Earthworm Jim HD.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently that is the big release next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also some deals.
[SPEAKER_05]: Worms 2 is getting a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_05]: Peggle goes down to 400 points.
[SPEAKER_05]: Duke Nukem 3D is down to 400 points.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to have to finally pick that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah, lots of good deals on Xbox Live next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, of course, Earthworm Jim, or as the intro says, Earthworm Jim.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, a little burping thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: HD comes out on this Wednesday, June the 9th.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's going to be awesome because you can play four person co-op.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: A couple stories about things coming out very soon on the downloadable platforms.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: and other news Sony Online Entertainment has actually released some information about PlayStation 3 and PC MMO for DC Universe Online but they really haven't said too much more about it there's no real release date but they said that both versions will come out at the same time it's likely to be in November which actually is what they finally came out and said
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's cool, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know how it'll play, but hey.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, the voice actor Phil Snyder, who we better know as the voice of Jiminy Cricket, is working on an unannounced project called Kingdom Hearts Recoded.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that... But that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: Likely a sequel to the mobile game, the mobile phone game, Kingdom Hearts Coded Could be a redrawn, you know, an upscaled version or ported too Could be You know, when you're going from mobile phone to PSP, you expect things are going to be upgraded quite a bit Not really I would hope so Could be an iPhone title
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that could be too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we've had some more Sims titles, domains actually being registered by corporate domains.
[SPEAKER_03]: There are...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Sims Medieval or The Sims Get Medieval so could possibly be old school jousting sims with chamber pots and chastity belts and tight lacing and
[SPEAKER_06]: What if they have it where you can design your castles and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not that you can't design castles and add motes, because hell, I was doing that in Sims 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the motes part.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've actually got out a Ren Faire set officially through the Sims store.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Mod the Sims, which is one of the mod sites I go through, they actually did a medieval challenge.
[SPEAKER_05]: Outro Outro Outro
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I've seen that movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: 1987 called.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: It misses you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I got it right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I am the Duke of Ted.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura is a freaking nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: So?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's why we love you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: So?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you're just a nerdy nerd.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, we're going to get into a segment here on the show we like to call the Twitter Topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm missing the theme music for Twitter Topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can we do Twitter Topics with no theme music?
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we have like music?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to sing the theme music?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you're saved anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We call stretching for time while I look for stuff for Twitter Topics.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not a lot of tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm frowning with disappointment at our listeners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's my frown to all of you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, lots of plugs for articles on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, I got those in earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dr. Noir sent his condolences to the Golden Girl loving crew.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I guess we didn't really talk about this enough earlier in the show, but there was a lot of celebrity death, obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't buy the whole death comes in threes things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think people just look for coincidences wherever they want to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because didn't, like, Art Link let her die, too, and nobody cares about him, though, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm saying, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Gary Coleman.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, who technically does have a video game tie-in.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was in Portal 2, er, it's Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Postal 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Much different.
[SPEAKER_05]: He still could be in Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: More importantly, he's in Avenue Q. Drew McClanahan, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: The man.
[SPEAKER_03]: Our zombie man, Dennis Hopper.
[SPEAKER_03]: I put on my Facebook that Dennis Hopper was going to come back as a zombie riding a motorcycle.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't he an easy rider?
[SPEAKER_05]: He wrote it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was his big movie in all the Romero flicks.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think my uncle added on there that Gary Coleman would be in the sidecar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Predator used Call of Duty to coerce kids into sending nude pics.
[SPEAKER_05]: A New Jersey man convinced four 13 and 14-year-olds to send him pictures of their genitals by saying that it was a membership condition of the clan he was starting in Call of Duty World of War.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jonathan Prime is 20 years old and faces four felony counts of communication with a minor for immoral purposes.
[SPEAKER_05]: He also has a previous conviction on a child porn charge related to this case in his home state.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's in jail on a $25,000 bond and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kids, don't send pictures of your penis over Xbox Live ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: You shouldn't really send pictures of your penis anywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let me tell you why.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets bigger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Until when do you stop growing like 23 or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, just wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait until you're fully matured.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's gross.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the real reason.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't send pictures of your dongle over the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Meow Frog sent us some tweets saying, First time listening to OLR Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, welcome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what's the chat for OLR?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I saw Meow Frog in chat earlier, so I know they made it to chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's chat.orangeloungeradio.com for anyone else who is listening and wanting to know how to join us in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, although if you ask in the all games chat, um, they'll probably tell you how to get over there too.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, what else do we have?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, except Jay, I hope I'm saying this right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jay Jugo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, I hope it's not Hugo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jay Jugo says, uh, the never forget segment should be added to the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Never forget.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just not sure how to make that like a piece of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loomis sends us a tweet saying, OLR, will you be going to BlizzCon Sky?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to buy you a drink.
[SPEAKER_05]: No homo.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura and I are, we're thinking about just going down to Anaheim anyway, if finances will allow.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll go down to Anaheim anyway and just go to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be called UsCon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can buy us a drink there, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: No homo.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to describe to somebody what the difference between girly and gay was.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: In decorating.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't, I just cannot even possibly understand.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for tweets.
[SPEAKER_05]: We didn't get a lot of tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we got, I mean, TigerClaw sent us other stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are things that are coming up later.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, we appreciate his Google foo, but I don't want to spoil upcoming stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, how about some other topics we want to talk about tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, let's talk about how Parappa the Rapper, well, the creator of Parappa the Rapper, is putting out a new music game for the iPhone and iPod.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks interesting, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's called, looks like Winta, or War is Not the Answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: War.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it good for?
[SPEAKER_03]: Butter.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: They didn't really say what exactly the game is going to be like, but it's basically tapping squares on a screen to time with music.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, kind of looks a little bit like it could be similar to Elite Beat Agents or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is the art done by Mr. Greenblatt?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about a new, like, actual, like, Parappa or Umjama Lamy type game?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, tell me that, like, Xbox Live or PlayStation Network, I suppose, more appropriately, would not be, like, the perfect platform for a game like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it would be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: You gotta believe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, the butter, you know where that comes from?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that from... Cheap Cheap's level?
[SPEAKER_03]: We used to just... For months, Dan and I would go around going, crack, crack, butter!
[SPEAKER_03]: So he laughed in the other room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Derek H. took my question literally, saying war saved us from the Nazis and war freed the slaves.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was singing a song.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't... Forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could Sony possibly be planning more PS2 remakes?
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, you know, they did the God of War remakes earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a survey going around again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The surveys sometimes leak things that Sony are thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Survey says?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, you didn't see that joke coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the things on the survey, well, the survey said, What titles would you like to see in a future collection?
[SPEAKER_05]: Two or more PS2 titles upgraded with similar features to God of War Collection.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I like this because there's this little screenshot that shows, like, Shadow of the Colossus, Ico, Gran Turismo, Final Fantasy, Yakuza, Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, just every single freaking franchise is being listed in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: Show me Twisted Metal!
[SPEAKER_05]: I realize, yes, there's that first generation of consoles that does have it, but most of us don't have it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The better consoles?
[SPEAKER_05]: And we all figured that they would end up selling it at some point, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I feel like there's something missing here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I'm one of those douchebags that has the fully backwards compatible system and doesn't play any PlayStation 2 games on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, congratulations, douchebag.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to trade PS3s?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I could sure play Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you ever upgrade your PS3 to lose the other OS feature?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're still holding out, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Still holding out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Haven't played 3D Dot Game Heroes 2 because that would upgrade my system.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm loaning it to a friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Toagak in our chatroom says, very eloquently, fuck PS2 remakes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, are they necessary?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, maybe he's posing a good question there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is this really necessary?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the God of War collection was pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, HD, widescreen, sexy...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya thinks she should be a game show host, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make, edit, get porn
[SPEAKER_03]: I got second place in that, didn't I?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't remember as long as I remember.
[SPEAKER_05]: I placed in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you and I both placed.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this was where basically you would make an edit to a DDR song because back in the day you could make edits in the home version of DDR and put them in the machines and Loki's favorite edits would receive a free gift of pornography.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did the hell edits.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was called Make Edit Get Porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the best contest the station's ever had.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did the DXY version called Another.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got all that XL Saga
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, is he still alive?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or is he still fapping right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, what you got for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: More news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, more news.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although, Rob, I'm honestly going to have to ask you your help with the mailbag today.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya is pointing out, that's fine, I'll do my mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkTetsuya is pointing out that that highlight is on the best hits that you can download at OrangeLondrina.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: So check it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there is something about Activision working on a GoldenEye title for the Wii and the DS to be released in November.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's theorized to be a remake of the Nintendo 64 version that Rare put out.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: Activision is working on a James Bond game a GoldenEye title, Rob and it's supposed to be out for Wii and the DS in theory released in November one of the going rumors about it is that it will be a remake of the Nintendo 64 version which as we all know is epic, classic, the game the game made me sick sick to my stomach Perfect Dark was redone recently and it was pretty awesome
[SPEAKER_03]: that's true but Activision basically let it off at the point that they registered domain names that were named after the film so we might see that coming they also did work on The World is Not Enough right?
[SPEAKER_06]: they've done the last few Bond films they have the rights to do the games for them
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I mean, if they bring us out a remade Goldeneye, that'll be pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's gonna be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it'll be as good as the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just the problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, nothing is really as ever good as the original.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think anything's gonna accurately capture the magic of the original.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I beg to differ.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because as I said in part A, when Metal Gear Solid Twin Snakes came out on the GameCube, it was a fairly kick-ass version.
[SPEAKER_03]: And don't forget the Resident Evil update where they did Resident Evil on GameCube and it was really hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_03]: There have been remakes done right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: They just have to make sure to stick with the essence of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do want to remind folks, sometimes we can't control the downtime of the feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's just random hiccups, although I like this comment from SSJ100Matt.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of porn, who's watching it in studio?
[SPEAKER_05]: He said right as the feed went down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's comcastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: It happens sometimes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, let's move on with a few more news stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then we're going to get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: We answer your emails live on air.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Grand Theft Horse.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: So apparently there's been some ratings that have leaked out from the Korean ratings board.
[SPEAKER_06]: And these are some Dreamcast titles that are going to be ported to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic Adventure and Crazy Taxi have been submitted for ratings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sega was unable to officially comment on the ratings.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic Adventure has popped up before.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they had some screenshots leak out a little bit ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crazy Taxi, I think the same thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I know or anything, but Sonic Adventure is most definitely real.
[SPEAKER_06]: Crazy Taxi is probably the same.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would not be surprised if these get announced at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think there's a chance they're going to come out and say, and they're out today!
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that happens once in a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic Adventure's done, so yeah, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could see that happening.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been done for a while.
[SPEAKER_05]: Definitely could see that happening, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Same as Sonic 4, but they're taking their damn time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's move on with some more news, and then I guess I'm going to do the mailbag tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's not feeling up to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, my voice has finally decided to crap out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dance on Broadway 20 songs from Broadway musicals
[SPEAKER_05]: All That Jazz, Roxy, Cabaret, Money Money, Dream Girls, One Night Only, Luck Be a Lady, Lullaby of Broadway, You Can't Stop the Beat, Good Morning Baltimore, Fame, My Favorite Things, Bend and Snap, Thoroughly Modern Millie, Little Shop of Horrors,
[SPEAKER_05]: Aquarius, Let the Sunshine In, and, and, and, and, the Time Warp.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tried to say woo.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura's making woo face right now, but you can't hear her.
[SPEAKER_05]: I already know how to do the Time Warp.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a jump to the left, and then a step to the right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this is supposed to be like Just Dance.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty much a sequel to Just Dance, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, except they're going to have Just Dance too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's like Guitar Hero 80s edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just dance, super duper gay edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: This actually reminds me that people need to stay tuned for Cage Match tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of show tunes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh heavens, why is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyhow, in the meantime, we're going to do something we can do on the podcast and live.
[SPEAKER_05]: We love to do this segment every week.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: X-Link in our chatroom says, nothing from Wicked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fail.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I actually don't like Wicked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, because I read the book.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't listen to this as a musical because the book was so dark and gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see the emails because there's a lot tonight because we kind of have a backlog from all the shows that we didn't do the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm going to start off tonight with this one from... Oh, that's a spam email that came in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do... I don't see...
[SPEAKER_05]: Redertainment Dear OLR, I was listening to your midweek discussion of the inclusion of a keytar in the next rock band game and a thought came to my mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: If this keytar is a plastic instrument with the keys in the body instead of the neck, isn't that like playing the plastic guitar backward?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mean playing it left-handed, but playing the guitar turned 180 degrees with the keys on your lap?
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, it seems to me that every numbered version of Rock Band gives the gaming public another gaming-related plastic dust magnet that is incompatible with other games, but gamers feel compelled to buy to play the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock Band gave us a guitar.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock Band 2 gave us a complete band set.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rock Band 3 will give us a keytar.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me wonder... I know, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got a correction there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes me wonder what useless plastic space hog Rock Band 4 will bring us.
[SPEAKER_05]: I vote for maracas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and it's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, our good buddy Rob with two B's, Rob-a-ba-ba-ba, sends us some impressions on Prince of Persia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Says, my boyfriend is a non-gamer, but he really enjoyed the Prince of Persia, The Sands of Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was fun to watch, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The criticism that Jake Gyllenhaal was too Caucasian for the role were unfounded.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's because the other two princes in the movie were whiter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, another thing I'm surprised I'm not hearing a lot of comment on this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, did you happen to see the movie?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't bother either.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only movie I watched this week is not out yet, so obviously not legally.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it was a good movie, and hopefully it will come out over here at some point, but it's just not yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, Super Mario Galaxy 2, Robway continues,
[SPEAKER_05]: There doesn't seem to be as much pressure to replay levels for Starz either.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm curious to hear your thoughts on the game, especially after hearing the Super Mario 64 classic as the game of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tune in to a future episode when one of us has actually played the damn game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my Wii's just not hooked up right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: My Wii's semi-bricked from New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: Blur and these other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Your Wii got bricked?
[SPEAKER_06]: Semi-bricked.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's that mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Semi-bricked is when you play a game of a different region on your system.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what happens is a second update gets put in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so now I can play games on it, but I can't go into the system menu and change settings.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've just been so lazy to fix it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't care, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been too busy playing other games to actually go and play New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: or Super Mario Galaxy 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_06]: I just don't feel compelled to do so.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if it's super awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Although my Trade Other M looks pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I watched a new video of that this week and it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Metroid Other M?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm Too Good Prince of Persia is an average movie, but that means it's like the moon landing for video game movies One small step for man, one giant leap for video game movies to not be a turd of shit
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the turd is now a measurement of shit as opposed to just being another name.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was the Keurig.
[SPEAKER_05]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another email from Rob that I want to bring up here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's suggesting that we should play the 369 music from Schoolhouse Rock for the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't have it queued up.
[SPEAKER_05]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: but I do want to address this other point in the email also two weeks ago I saw my first Tron-a-Rail in Disney World that's just what we called it but it turned out to be the official name for the decorated trains any sightings in Disneyland I don't believe they've redone the monorail as Tron I don't think they're planning to do that but you never know when it gets a little closer to the movie releases there was a rumor that the people mover with Tron was going to come back but I'm not holding my breath on that I think if it does it ain't happening this year
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, nothing at Disneyland yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we're all waiting on pins and needles that hopefully the PeopleMover will reopen.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also of note, not to turn this into a Disney podcast, but in about, what, one more month, Star Tours will close.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Star Tours is no longer going to be there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eh, big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: In its current form.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're redoing it for... There's going to be a Star Wars 2.0 that comes out later.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're going to make it all stupid in, like, the prequels, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's the pod race, I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the pod race, that's the rumor that it's a pod race ride now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that might be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And hopefully you get to run over Jar Jar Binks.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if Greg Proops is still one of the commentators, that's also amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's right, yeah, he was a commentator.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, he was one of the two heads.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it'd be funny, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Robot Chicken and stuff, where they have all the Jar Jar Binks stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should just make it look like it's going to be some sort of pod race.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lock the doors, and it's just all Jar Jar Binks talking to you for a good five minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: Children would cry and run screaming away.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would complain that my day was not magical.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was not magical.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am not having a magical day now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: This comes from Shook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big S, Big K Hi OLR, I'm here for a rant Lately in zombie discussions or something similar People act like they know everything about shotguns and .44s etc When really they're from a big city and have been nowhere near a gun Except maybe in their little gang I'm not trying to sound like some country bumpkin But it really pisses me off when they act like know-it-alls What are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't make me bust out my Glock.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think anyone really wants to shoot somebody in the face.
[SPEAKER_05]: In Red Dead Redemption, it's just funny to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_05]: I am an adult.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand what is fiction and what is real.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to go shoot someone in the face if it's going to kill them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I will be the first to admit, I don't know the difference between all these different types of guns because I don't like guns and I would never own a gun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, what guns?
[SPEAKER_05]: What are we talking about guns?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shotguns and 44s, etc.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying I know everything about these guns.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not me specifically, but just people.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't wait until I own a gun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not getting into this topic again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I learned a lot about guns from playing Airsoft.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because a lot of the guns that they have out there are modeled.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now I can say, hey, that's an MP7.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, hey, that's a G36.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: you know how I learned about guns very well writing G.I.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joe fanfiction about 10 years ago I'm not joking 10 years ago I was writing G.I.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joe fanfiction and I did my research I have no interest in firing a gun that is not of the laser variety or the shooting range I still I do still want a Hello Kitty we should go out to the shooting range I want to go
[SPEAKER_06]: Our friend used to go down there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to go with him, but he moved too soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to take a picture of this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan got to shoot off a .50 caliber.
[SPEAKER_05]: One more, you guys, from Dragonboy69.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was wondering if any of you might know why some games, specifically Vagrant Story and Breath of Fire 3, show up on the Japan and European PSN store, but not on the North American store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for any help you can provide.
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep up the great work.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because Vagrant Story sucked?
What?
[SPEAKER_05]: but wait here's the thing just sometimes it's a rights issue and Final Fantasy 9 I think is another big one right like it's showing up in other stores but not the current one just it's rights issues and sometimes timing and other things it's sometimes kind of complicated I think it has to do with the fact that sometimes different companies publish different games in different countries and that sometimes complicate things but I think Wikipedia keeps a pretty good list of what's available yeah it's true too
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm posting this picture up on the site of my Hello Kitty holding a .50 caliber shell.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also, too, it's sometimes just the ability for that company to be able to distribute the game in a timely manner.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, for example, MorphX, which was a game that came out in Europe just recently, is actually region-coded for both Europe and the North American regions.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, in theory, you could actually release the game here and it would be just fine, but for whatever reason, you know, it may have not passed the ratings board yet, maybe they don't have enough...
[SPEAKER_06]: Manpower to actually duplicate the units that they need.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of these companies, like Graffiti Entertainment or Zoo Games and stuff, their titles go for sometimes years of delays before they're actually released.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Graffiti Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to do it for our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com If you'd like to send us an email, please do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_05]: After the Mailbag is usually the section of the show where we get a little irritated.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we do a little segment on the show called the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we can.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you need a little inspiration, we have an inspiration for your FU story tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's about a Virginia man named Bruce Jamar Walston.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, authorities were called to his apartment by the girlfriend because apparently, a couple nights ago, the woman called 911.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not going to like this, folks.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're really not going to like this, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: And this really doesn't have anything to do with video games, but it does because I'm making the rounds on video game blogs, but just...
[SPEAKER_05]: You're not going to like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're really not going to like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, the guy here that was arrested, Bruce Walston, was angered that the video game he was playing was disconnected by his girlfriend's new kitten.
[SPEAKER_05]: So he picked up the animal.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to say what happened, but the animal died.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this all occurred, wait for it, wait for it, in front of the woman's children.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's being held without bond at the Middle River Regional Gerald in Verona in case you want to send him your cards and letters.
[SPEAKER_05]: For killing a kitten, for unplugging the video game console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not only did he kill the cat, he did it in front of the children.
[SPEAKER_05]: Psychopath Mental Problems
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: Who would like to start... Good without Bond.
[SPEAKER_05]: Would you like to start off with the FUs of the week, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have some inspiration now?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm disgusted.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, it's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I said you wouldn't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan said it's better he didn't kill the kid.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's better than...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan is yelling from the living room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie would be less mad if the guy had killed the kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's still messed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No matter what, it's messed up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to make mine quick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: My first FU goes towards losing my voice and the little bit of cough I have left.
[SPEAKER_03]: My next one is a humongous FU to Helen Thomas who is one of the senior White House press corps members who basically went on record saying that Jews should get out of Palestine and go back to Germany or Poland.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: She didn't say go back to Jew land.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: First of all, telling people to go back to places that, you know, they basically left due to, um, how about being murdered?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know?
[SPEAKER_03]: To go back to their homeland is just really insensitive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe Helen Thomas should go back to her homeland, because I don't think she's Native American.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, boat's coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just really, really... And you know, the only reason, she did apologize for it, but the only reason I think she apologized for it... She got caught.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they called her on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now they're calling for her resignation, or her to get sacked, and honestly...
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, if she had her own personal private blog and said this as herself with a these views do not reflect White House blah blah blah fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Insensitive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shitty as hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're still a bitch, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is America.
[SPEAKER_05]: She has the right to be a bitch and we have the right to call her a bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what free speech is all about.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to say it in her capacity in a public forum as a representative of the White House press corps, as a senior representative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now tell me that's just not highly irresponsible and incredibly insensitive.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think she should get sacked.
[SPEAKER_03]: And drawn behind a cart by her toes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see Obama just punch her on the White House lawn.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just go, bitch!
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, and that's just... Not that I'm advocating violence, but in special circumstances, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what is funny?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because her apology is not even...
[SPEAKER_03]: She's saying that she deeply regretted the comments I made last week regarding Israelis and Palestinians.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do not reflect my heartfelt belief that peace will come to the Middle East only when all parties recognize the need for mutual respect and tolerance.
[SPEAKER_03]: May that day come soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: She didn't really address what she said.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: She just let out a blanket statement to appease everybody that doesn't really address the problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: If she was going to have any sincerity of it, she was going to say, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: F you to myself for having the obsessive compulsion to spend money on stupid things that I really don't need to spend money on like Project Under $100 for example
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that it's going to stop me from doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also the fact that I don't have any airsoft guns.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm also not in the airsoft community right now because I don't have any airsoft guns.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I really want the Magpul PTS FPG.
[SPEAKER_06]: The folding pocket gun looks so awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a gun that folds out of a briefcase shape into a little personal assault rifle.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's also really expensive and I don't need it.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_05]: My FU of the week goes to the returning side pains that I've been having because, yeah, that's why I went to the hospital a couple of years ago and I really don't want to go back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe it's Mother Nature trying to tell me I need to go on a diet again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but I don't like being freaked out like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: A few to my body.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's move on with just a couple more news stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get to the Skype line here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Admittedly, it's going to be a little bit shorter Skype line tonight because we had a really long show and we still have an afterbirth yet too before it gets too late.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we will at least take some calls here in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, Loki, what you got for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: Games Convention Online in Leipzig is actually going to be going industry only this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, I guess they had 43,000 attendees in 2009.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now they're just saying the number of registered public exhibitors was insufficient.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that satisfy the interests of the visitors whose past experiences bring them with high expectations to Leipzig.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't make sense why they're going to cut it, but they're planning on, I guess...
[SPEAKER_06]: Having 30 companies attending this year, which is already bigger than last year But it will not be open to the public So it's basically, this show's got too many common folk at it So in order for our show to get bigger For business to happen, it's basically what E3 did But, I mean, this is maybe a good example of why we don't have E3 open to the public Because it would be a nut house Alright
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's move on with one more story
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep in mind, this is only announced stuff, because there's always surprises.
[SPEAKER_05]: Always, always, always surprises at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't take this as the definitive list of the only things being shown at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is just what is confirmed thus far.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2K Games is showing Mafia 2, Sid Meier's Civilization V, Spec Ops The Line, and XCOM.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even know they were remaking XCOM.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's supposed to be not so much like... It's more like a first-person shooter now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might remember hearing it on a previous show or something, but this is the first time I remember hearing it right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Activision has Call of Duty Black Ops and Guitar Hero Warriors of Rock, and supposedly that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I somehow doubt that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bethesda's bringing Brink, Fallout New Vegas, Hunted the Demon's Forge, and Rage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Capcom 2 has Dead Rising 2, Marvel vs. Capcom 3, and an untitled sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm ignoring the mobile stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disney Interactive Studios has Epic Mickey, Guilty Party, Pirates.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they really going to call that game Epic Mickey?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's a stupid title.
[SPEAKER_05]: It may be just the working title right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: God, I hope it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me go on record saying that is a stupid name for a video game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pirates of the Caribbean, Armada of the Damned, Toy Story 3, Tron Evolution, and Tron Legacy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I'm all about checking out the Tron.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those are supposed to be cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I want to see what that looks like.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA is showing APB, Bulletstorm, Crisis 2, Dead Space 2, EA Sports Active 2.0, FIFA Soccer 11, Madden NFL 11, Medal of Honor, NBA Jam, NCAA Football 11, NHL 11, Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11.
[SPEAKER_05]: Lots and lots of sporty games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hudson Soft, Beyblade, Metal Fusion, Bomberman Live, Battlefest Bonk, Brink of Extinction, Dekasports 3, Lost in Shadow, and Oops Prank Party on the Wii Oops I crapped my pants party Oh my god, Oops Prank Party Konami has Castlevania Puzzle, Angor of the Night, Castlevania Lords of Shadow
[SPEAKER_05]: DefJam Rapstar, Lucha Libre AAA, Metal Gear Solid Peace Walker, N3 99 Nights 2, Pro Evo Soccer 2010, Rocket Knight, Russian Attack Expatriate, Saw 2, and The Cages Pro Style Batting Practice.
[SPEAKER_05]: As I said earlier in the show, notice no DDR in that list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could DDR be dead?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will tell you what they're probably going to do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Surprise announcement?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to make an announcement that's going to support Natal.
[SPEAKER_05]: You think?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a feeling Alright, we'll see what happens Because, you know, Konami, they like doing gimmicky shit that doesn't make any sense for the franchise whatsoever For example, what they were showing off at last E3 with Dance Dance Revolution Playing Dance Dance Revolution on the Wii Fit balance board using your ass That made no fucking sense
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you guys want some video at E3 of me playing Def Jam Rapstar?
[SPEAKER_05]: You know who I want to see video playing that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Irene.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish she could go to E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heart Irene.
[SPEAKER_05]: LucasArts is bringing Lego Star Wars 3, Monkey Island 2 Special Edition, The Force Unleashed 2, and Star Wars The Old Republic Lots of stuff there Majesco is bringing Crafting Mama, Greg Hastings Paintball 2, Swords, and Zumba Fitness Microsoft No babysitting mama?
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently not Let's see, Microsoft is bringing Fable 3, Gears of War 3, Halo Reach, and Project Natal Games
[SPEAKER_05]: MTV Games is bringing Rock Band 3, Namco Bandai is bringing Ace Combat, Clash of the Titans, Enslaved, Dragon Ball Origins, Naruto, Ultimate Ninja Storm, an untitled Pac-Man game, and Splatterhouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: Natsume is bringing Harvest Moon Grand Bazaar, and Lufia, Curse of the Sinistrals.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did I remember Lufia?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's, I think, a remake of the old games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I have Lufia.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's coming back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: Sega's got Conduit 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know they were making a Conduit 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Phantasy Star Portable 2, Tournament of Legends, Wii, Sonic the Hedgehog 4 Episode 1, Sonic Chronicles, and Valkyria Chronicles 2 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_05]: SNK is bringing the King of Fighters 13.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony is bringing iPad, Free Realms, God of War, Ghost of Sparta, that's PSP, Gran Turismo 5, Hot Shots Tennis, Invisimals, Killzone 3, LittleBigPlanet 2, Move Party, PlayStation Move Games, SOCOM 4, Sports Champions, Slider, TV Superstars, The Fight Lights Out, The Last Guardian, and The Shoot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ooh, The Last Guardian.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was that epic trailer last year, huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that was, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see what else we got.
[SPEAKER_05]: Squeenix, Deus Ex, Human Revolution, Final Fantasy XIV, Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep, Kane and Lynch 2, Dog Days, and Lara Croft and the Guardian of Light.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that sounds kind of weird that that's at the Squeenix booth, but there's that whole merger now.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's how it works.
[SPEAKER_05]: THQ, The Underground, Homefront, Red Faction 4, Saints Row 3, The Last Airbender, UFC Undisputed 2010, Warhammer 40k Online, Warhammer 40k Space Marine, WWE Smackdown vs. Raw 2011
[SPEAKER_05]: and SmackDown vs. Raw Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Trying to wrap this up here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ubisoft, Assassin's Creed Brotherhood, Sean White Skateboarding, Tom Clancy's Ghost Recon Future Soldier, Hawks 2 and an untitled Driver sequel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Valve is bringing Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Warner Brothers is supposed to be showing Arkham Asylum 2 as well as Batman the Brave and the Bold.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cats and Dogs, The Revenge of Kitty Galore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Notice how that's Kitty Galore and not the James Bond villain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fear 3, Lego Harry Potter, Years 1 through 4, Lord of the Rings, Eragon's Quest, Lord of the Rings, War in the North, and last but not least, Super Scribblenauts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now with verbs.
[SPEAKER_05]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: A list of what is being shown to E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds like it's going to be a fun year, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I... I think it's with adjectives now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_05]: Adjectives, not verbs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't you have all of it, though, it seems like?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be hard to spawn a verb.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spawn run.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, this is the part of the show where we're going to get to some last minute stories because, well, actually, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_05]: We already have calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to go to the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've already got calls coming in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Ray Iannami.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Ray Iannami.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been back from Fanime for about a week now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fanime was over Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sadly, I was not there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in Portland.
[SPEAKER_05]: But how was Fanime this year?
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems to get better every year.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's a few crappy parts, but it doesn't detract from the experience as a whole, usually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, first things first, I've got to ask, since it is a video game show, how is the game room at Fanime?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I can't think back.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Gaming Room for Arcades, they had like the usual stuff from last year, but this time they have a few new things like Mushihime-sama and DJ Max Technica.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was especially excited to see Technica, even if they didn't have the Platinum Crew servers, but I expected it not to be there anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do they wheel that all over from SVGL or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, actually, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: From what I've heard, like some years ago...
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some fallout between Fanami and Goffland, so now Fanami gets their machines from university arcades, like someone from San Jose State and UCLA.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we ended up getting UCLA's machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It sounds like Gamer was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Consulate Gaming was a bit of a letdown this year, mainly because there weren't as many TVs, like
[SPEAKER_08]: The concentration of people playing fighting games to people playing other games like Classy Games and Shmucks and such was really high this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you pick a random TV, four to five times it's probably going to be Brawl or something else, or Rock Band or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I say it pretty much every damn con gaming room.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about some cosplay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there any good gaming cosplay?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know DarkSakura was showing me a picture earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it was from Fanime, but some Metal Gear cosplay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there any good gaming cosplay you saw?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, like what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw a picture of a Vanille from Final Fantasy XIII that looked really cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought she did a good job.
[SPEAKER_05]: What did you see?
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw a lot of Toho cosplay, though that's mainly because I went to the Toho gathering and the explosion of Toho-related events on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at some of your pictures, it looks like there was a Pac-Man there I'm looking at, and I'm looking at a Black Mage and a Sackboy Loki's Sackboy costume is better though
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw some BlazBlue cosplay, like Hazama and Lychee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw a couple Captain Falcons, which is one of the alternate palettes from Super Smash Bros., interestingly.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also the guy who does British cosplay every year, so glad to see him every year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, what's this about where there were some protesters?
[SPEAKER_05]: Were people protesting Faname?
[SPEAKER_05]: What's up with this?
[SPEAKER_05]: They weren't protesting Faname, per se.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's basically, you know about those Fire and Brimstone preachers that go turn or burn and such like that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You always see them out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, even when I was in Portland, there was one out at the fair.
[SPEAKER_05]: They do, like, a cute little fair downtown where a lot of local vendors come out and sell their, you know, local goods.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was some guy standing there on the street corner, you know, spouting their whole thing about, you know, everybody's going to hell and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Faname got a little bit of that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I came across a Guitar Freaks V4 machine with EMU slots, but it's not connected to EMUs No, I don't really play Guitar Freaks or Drum Mania, I'm more of a 2DX person and VGMAX person
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they did.
[SPEAKER_08]: And interestingly, it was a hacked version of 2DX Empress with DJ Maxx Crossovers and other things on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't play it because the screen was laggy, and laggy screens make me rage quit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was DJ Maxx Crossovers in this game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it a hack?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, someone hacked some DJ Maxx songs into 2DX, which was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've seen a video of it on YouTube before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I didn't even know something like that existed, but that's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, any other thoughts on Fandomay you want to tell us before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think what Fandomay could do next year for their console gaming is maybe have one section where there's no fighting games or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, classic games and shooters and other things that don't require you to kick ass and have fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all about a classic game room like they have at PAX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't seen you guys since 2007, so I'm getting worried if I'll ever see you at Fanime again.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll go to Fanime next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's in July, aka next month.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we'll go to that, because I've never been to California Extreme, and I'd really like to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think we'll make it to July?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to make any promises yet, but July would be a lot better than June, so maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, well, Ray, we're going to let you go so we can take some more calls, but thank you so much for your call, and have fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, see ya Later
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey Spazinator, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I had, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: One question that kind of ties in very loosely to the last call that you had.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was kind of wondering, is there any retro games that you would love to see either in...
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft Game Room or on PSN that's not already there or hasn't been announced?
[SPEAKER_05]: I would love to see stuff like Impossible Mission and so forth released over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope that my earlier inkling that if Game Room is going to reach thousands of games, then they're going to dip into the old Apple IIe library and the Commodore 64 library and some of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope my inkling there is correct because there's lots of Commodore 64 games I would love to see get the treatment.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you guys should see some of the EA games back when they were ECA.
[SPEAKER_05]: They made some pretty epic games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mule, M-U-L-E, was a great game on the 64.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd love to see make a comeback.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's just a lot of those classic computer games of yesteryear I would love to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if that happens on PSN, that would be great too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I sort of see the classic stuff on PSN as being more of a Sony-based thing usually.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't usually see a lot of old stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you know what's interesting?
[SPEAKER_05]: There has been some obscure stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me give you one retro title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Digger HD is out on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's kind of an overlooked title.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's a remake of an old, old PC game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what's really cool...
[SPEAKER_05]: The old PC game is in there and playable.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not one of my favorite classic games and not one that necessarily necessitated the treatment it got, but I think it's an example of a retro remake done really well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that is on PlayStation Network and not on 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's only on PSN, Digger HD.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's worth a look.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I got that one, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: In fact, I got that, too, I went to see roughly about a month and a half ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, at least in terms of game room, what I would love to see is virtually any old classic Capcom game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Capcom, before they really started going gung-ho on home consoles, they've been known for their arcade titles, whether it be the 1940 series, the
[SPEAKER_09]: Street Fighter series, Ghosts and Goblins, and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Room badly needs other publishers on board because right now the only Game Room games that are coming out are Atari, Activision, Intellivision,
[SPEAKER_05]: and Konami.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are not seeing games from at least I can think of off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't believe there are any other publishers games showing up in Game Room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is odd because they promised this thousand games thing earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what's also strange to me, this week in Game Room
[SPEAKER_05]: GamePacks 3 and 4 were packs of 14 games split into 2 weeks worth of releases.
[SPEAKER_05]: GamePack 5 just came out and we got 5 games this week, which makes me think it's going to be 3 weeks worth now.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're stretching these game packs out longer and longer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, they are going to run out of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: My hope is that they are going to make some big announcements at E3, and that's kind of why we're waiting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because right now, okay, well, the three weeks for Game Pack 5 would take us right through the end of E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was also a delay this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Game Pack 5 was held up by a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't know if maybe this all plays into it, but I really hope...
[SPEAKER_05]: that they are coming out at E3 and saying, hey, we have these other publishers on board for Game Room.
[SPEAKER_05]: If they don't do that, Game Room is doomed.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's really a bummer because there's so much potential with Game Room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I fired up Video Pinball this week, which was one of the releases.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, not what I remember when I was six.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of disappointed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, in fact, I had just recently bought...
[SPEAKER_09]: Super Breakouts, and, you know, as Bobby Blackwell pointed out on his show, you know, without the panel, it is kind of a pain in the arse to play Daggy, but still, even with that being said, you know, there's the whole nostalgia factor, you know, considering that, you
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the first game I ever played was Syphon Blackjack on the 2600, so there's something behind that.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: and I've gone on this tangent in previous shows I'm really worried that Game Room is going to be a giant disappointment and it's almost more disappointing because if it doesn't work you're not going to see anyone else want to try it and there was such good ideas here but I really think those Chrome layoffs affected things harder than they claimed it was going to but I hope they're at E3 because I'm going to ask some questions I can't wait
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I really hope that, you know, despite the layoffs, they do manage to really turn out the games for it and they get all the support from the gaming community that they deserve, you know, because I just hate to have to wait another generation or two for something similar to Game Room, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hope, let's hope.
[SPEAKER_05]: Spazinator, I've got to let you go because we're going to go and wrap up the show, but thanks so much as always for your call, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: You too, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry to close the phones, but we're kind of running long tonight because part A was really, really long tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was almost two hours long.
[SPEAKER_05]: So unfortunately, I am going to close up the Skype line so we can kind of wrap up the show because we still have an after work to get to and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_05]: We haven't let Loki finish last minute stories, but I did want to invite callers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please email us right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mailbag at orange lounge reader dot com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get your thoughts out so we can read them on next week's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a game that I think we talked about a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a Grand Theft Auto kind of demake, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were doing...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and it looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have a bunch of different parodies on different things like Metal Gear, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles and whatnot, Sonic and the game itself is pretty much an open world action game just like the old school top down Grand Theft Autos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently some of the Nintendo portables, the DSi XL, they are getting some new colors of the DSi XL.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be yellow, blue, and green coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also in time for all that stuff, they're going to be dropping the price as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So cutting it down from 20,000 yen to 18,000 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the DSI will also drop down from 18,900 yen to about 15,000 yen.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's kind of getting ready for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that blue one's kind of pretty, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is the green one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yellow one I could do without.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also in the UK, the DSi is getting the price drop as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could they be announcing one on stage next week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Could that possibly be happening?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and the funny thing is these are all starting on June 18th.
[SPEAKER_06]: June 18th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that does coincide with something, I'm sure, if I put my mind to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And yeah, they will be dropping the price as well from 150 euros to looks like 120 to 130 euros around there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a rumor that Kim Kardashian is going to be the next Lara Croft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got the assets to be Lara Croft, but that's about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: She can't act her way out of a box.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_06]: Motorstorm 3 apparently is going post-apocalyptic, and this is coming from some screens leaked on the French website PS3Gen.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have what they claim to be some stolen images of Motorstorm 3 showing kind of a, I guess, San Francisco map that has buildings crumbling and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_06]: To me, if this is actually real, this is kind of what Fuel should have been, but
[SPEAKER_06]: I kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't really get into the last Motorstorm game, but the first one was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm interested.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then finally, Def Jam Rapstar is going to be coming out I guess this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Europe, October 5th and North America, November 6th.
[SPEAKER_06]: The game will retail for $69.99 on the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 and $59.99 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm assuming it comes with one microphone.
[SPEAKER_06]: and some of the songs that have been announced for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got Biz Marquis' Just a Friend, Drake's Best I Ever Had, Ice Cube's With It Was a Good Day, Outkast's So Fresh, So Clean by Pete Rock and CL Smooth's The Reminisce Is Over You, Troy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, also Redman's and Method Man's Da Rock Wilder and Salt Peppers Push It.
[SPEAKER_05]: Push it real good.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to have a freestyle mode as well as a couple of original instrumental tracks, which I guess will tie in with the freestyle mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: comments from our chat room chat.org.com salaciouspop commenting on the Kim Kardashian role you can't do backflips with an ass that fat I'm Too Good says if the second Lara Croft movie was the first one it wouldn't have bombed it was much better than the first hmm
[SPEAKER_05]: I never saw either one, I gotta admit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't watch a lot of video game movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did see Resident Evil.
[SPEAKER_05]: Silent Hill was obviously the last one I saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go back and watch that again.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought it was underrated by most people, but whatevs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Different movies for different people, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_05]: We might just have to give them what they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice after all, so we'll be doing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: We might be actually doing a press conference live.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just have to steal the audio from another site, so we'll have to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: If anybody knows of a site that's doing the audio live Sunday, please... Which one is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Cirque du Soleil one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the Natal one.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll probably be on Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, maybe it will be.
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: All we ask you guys, if you enjoy what you've heard, please tell two people about our program.
[SPEAKER_05]: Help us spread the word because we are not a big magazine or a big website.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are by the people, for the people, and we really only get our advertising done via word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_05]: that's it we don't play any advertising on the show so that's all we ask help us advertise instead so that's it we can't close out the show though until we go around and give everybody's final thoughts Loki we'll start with you tonight what's your final thought Loki my final thought is I'm gonna be busy this week my final thought is I want a teriyaki chicken bowl from Jack in the Box that sounds really good right now DarkSakura what's your final thought
[SPEAKER_05]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_02]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!