[SPEAKER_13]: Tonight, March 7th, 2010, we get first impressions on Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_17]: One of our favorite games is patched with teasers of a sequel, and the Rock Band Network goes live.
[SPEAKER_04]: I come bearing a message from President Cat Here in California, home of Silicon Valley, home of video games We are in a budget crisis
[SPEAKER_04]: State employees are furloughed, meaning we can't go to the DMV most Fridays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Students are protesting out on the freeways amidst high tuition cutbacks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yet somehow our legislatures found the time last week to pass a resolution supporting anti-cussing week to take place this very week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: However, substituting words like oh pickles and sassafras, which have all of the same intent, is somehow okay and makes you a smarter person.
[SPEAKER_04]: As residents of the state of California, we reject this notion.
[SPEAKER_04]: As intelligent individuals, we take offense to the notion that using versatile swear words somehow demonstrates a lack of intelligence.
[SPEAKER_04]: As free citizens of the United States of America living under the First Amendment, we say fuck yeah to free speech.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will work tonight in protest of No Cussing Week to break the record for most uses of the F word on an internet podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight, on a very special Orange Lounge Radio, we bring you The Fuck Show.
America!
[SPEAKER_11]: America!
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: Come and if you have to save the motherfucker
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just fucking annoyed at people feeling like they have to defend their own fucking opinion every fucking time someone says something that's different from them.
[SPEAKER_07]: So fuck them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not really fuck them, but just fuck in general.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, just fuck them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right in their fucking ears.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, say hello to the one and only, he is so fucking smart, Tech Master Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: I keep fucking coughing.
[SPEAKER_19]: I wish this fucking gold would go away.
[SPEAKER_19]: You have been fucking sick for like three fucking weeks now.
[SPEAKER_19]: I haven't been coughing all day long, but then all of a sudden this fucking coughing started after I ate all my chicken.
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you like some tea?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I really hate fucking tea.
[SPEAKER_19]: Tea is awful.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I think it's the root beer.
[SPEAKER_19]: And while delicious the root beer was, it makes me cough.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you allergic to fucking root beer?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I am not allergic to root beer.
[SPEAKER_19]: Root beer is awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just, you know, the carbonation or whatever kind of loosens the fucking phlegm in my throat.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: But yeah, otherwise I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm fucking great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, glad to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, folks, we do have some gaming news to get into a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, we always fucking start off the show talking about our fucking gaming weeks, like anybody really gives a fuck what we've been playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's just how you do a video game podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've been doing it a very fucking long time, about eight years.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we used to start a little segment called How was your day?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: But no one really gave a shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we evolved it to fucking video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So how the fuck was your gaming week, DarkSakra?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was fucking boring.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played Star Trek Online and made it to Lieutenant Commander, finally, fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a guy, this weird Klingon chick and a Bajoran dude, but fuck him.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's about all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't do fuck all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's more fucking Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same fucking story every fucking week, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it's like to be fucking addicted to an MMO.
[SPEAKER_04]: I should know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not addicted.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe not fucking addicted.
[SPEAKER_07]: I set a day.
[SPEAKER_07]: A day that is my fuck off day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where I do fuck all.
[SPEAKER_07]: But play my damn game and fuck around on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's good to have a fuck off day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have fuck off days on days ending in one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've actually started a project.
[SPEAKER_07]: A fantastic fucking project that doesn't involve fucking, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Called Project Real Life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where this thing, this evil box, this fucking whore of a computer gets turned off How the fuck are you able to function?
[SPEAKER_19]: But you're fucking playing the game in real life So I don't understand what the fucking point is I'm paying attention to my own fucking real life
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, fuck me then.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how the fuck was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, let's talk about how awesome my gaming week was.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's talk about how awful today was.
[SPEAKER_19]: Today was a fucking mess.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_19]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Stockton would kind of be, it's kind of like between the asshole and the balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Stockton is kind of the fucking taint of California.
[SPEAKER_19]: And there's nothing on the way.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it's not pleasurable.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just cow country.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fucking shitty smelling cow country.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, so I decided, okay, mind you, I woke up at 730 this morning.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's fucking early on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_19]: I drove all the way down there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Met the guy just before 9, gave him my console, paid him the $60 it would be to solder in the chip that I wanted him to solder in.
[SPEAKER_19]: Told me it would take about 30-45 minutes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Four hours later, waiting in fucking Stockton, the guy's not returning any of my text messages, he's not returning any of my phone calls, and so I'm fucking sitting there going, okay, well, I guess I'm either gonna fucking sit here all day, or I'm gonna have to fucking leave and leave my console behind and assume that I'm getting ripped off.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, that's what happened.
[SPEAKER_19]: I got fucking ripped off, apparently.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, fuck him.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, fuck him indeed.
[SPEAKER_19]: And so I'm going to give him the benefit of the doubt for now and assume that this really was a mistake and his phone is all fucked up or whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: And so I will be polite and contact him by email, giving him the opportunity to fucking ship me my console.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, if he doesn't do that, then I'm fucking posting his phone number and posting his email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, don't forget, send me his IP.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will find his fucking address.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can go show up at his house and say, fuck you, give it back.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is not the C-Word show, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then Final Fantasy XIII, that's basically been my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, DarkSakura is just fucking openly swearing randomly at our fucking chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com if you want to join all the fucking action tonight in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, three hours of this tonight, ladies and fucking gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be this or the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, honestly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep track of how many fucks get fucking said so that we can fucking send it to fucking Guinness and fucking Ireland.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop trying to run up the counter artificially.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not artificial.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking stop it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm legitimately saying fuck and I can say fuck as much as I fucking want to, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: So fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: In a good way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, any more in your fucking gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking love you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking love you too, bitch.
[SPEAKER_19]: I also played some more of...
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, what the fuck.
[SPEAKER_19]: Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_19]: I play more Borderlands because I'm trying to get the game finished before I can fucking start the new expansion.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I'm liking it still.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I just have to level up my characters.
[SPEAKER_19]: I actually have to level up my friend's character because he's fucking 18 levels below me.
[SPEAKER_19]: So...
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, so I played a little bit more of that, and of course Grand Theft Auto, you know, fucking, what, rank like 74 now in the true skill ranks, and then I'm still fucking like 195 in the regular ranks, just because I don't play on the weekends, and it's, you know, kind of bounces around during the week, so, but true skill's really where I'm, you know, trying to get to the top of the fucking list, and doing pretty good, so.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You notice how our chat room has been increasing exponentially?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and fuckdeft, cunt.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate that word, and I said it, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at the chat, and all these fucking people are in there tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We love you all, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: We fucking love you and your support so much.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we have Hardcore77777.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a lot of fucking sevens in his name there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Says, oh, wow, I picked a bad night to listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you fucking... Welcome to your first fucking live show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't any week a fucking bad night to listen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hardcore 7777777777.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_19]: And Akula fucking GP says, Fucking GTA again?
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck, Loki, fuck.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, I play that every fucking day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Twice fucking day.
[SPEAKER_19]: Actually, sometimes three fucking times a day.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I fuck everyone up in it because I'm so fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, I have to.
[SPEAKER_19]: I have to mention it every week.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's what I'm proud of.
[SPEAKER_19]: In fact, actually, we'll get into this a little bit fucking later, but remember how they updated some TOS stuff for Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_19]: And now I can post my Ballad of Gay Tony ranks in there without the word gay being fucking banning me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, congratulations, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a good reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: That whole policy was kind of fucked anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was overcompensating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a story later we're going to get into?
[SPEAKER_04]: I should probably shut my fucking mouth then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to talk about during your fucking gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, my fucking gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing a lot of fucking WoW as usual.
[SPEAKER_04]: My character's probably to about fucking level 53, I think I finally fucking dinged this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucking addict.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bite my fucking ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: My boyfriend, though, he got to level fucking 55, so he can roll a fucking Death Knight now whenever the fuck he wants.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we might do like the twin Death Knight thing like fucking later, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like right now the fucking focus is getting his fucking character to 80.
[SPEAKER_04]: but the problem is I found another game that's gonna fucking sink all my time for the next two weeks which I'll get into in a minute but I wanted to talk about a couple of other fucking games real quick one of them is Critter Crunch it's so fucking cute and I finally played the full version of the game I played the fucking demo before it's fucking cute it's a lot like Magical Drop did you ever fucking play that?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I play that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't really care for it too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine if Magical Drop wasn't about matching the fucking colors, but it was about putting things in a fucking sequence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, instead of fucking all the blues disappear, it's like you gotta go fucking green, red, and blue in an order, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: That sounds too fucking complicated.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's not that fucking bad, because it's little bugs, fucking medium-sized bugs, and then big bugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's pretty intuitive to figure out it's not that fucking hard and there's these weird elements too where you fucking barf rainbows into little critters mouth and all these like overly cute fucking things well no wonder you fucking like it barfing rainbows shut up
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fucking cute, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's lots of modes in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I'd bought the fucking game when it was on sale, but it's okay because it's on Alan's PlayStation 3 so I can play it whenever the fuck I'm over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it was really cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played through a good probably 15 stages while I was there and got some trophies.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a fucking good deal and if I wasn't so busy playing something else right now, I might fucking buy the full version.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who wants some fucking tequila?
[SPEAKER_04]: You have fucking tequila?
[SPEAKER_07]: You bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I didn't have to fucking drive home, I would.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do a shot now.
[SPEAKER_04]: As if my swearing wasn't bad enough right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, fuck it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a night just to fuck it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want some tequila?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want any tequila.
[SPEAKER_04]: I better pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll drink my beer by myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: You fucking drink yourself into a coma.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I play Misty, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just tell me about fucking beer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck else is I playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Final Fantasy II on the fucking iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: but they have made some fucking adjustments to it to make it more touch friendly for instance when you're in a battle you have all these little fucking icons instead of the words to attack and even when you're in the menus to cast fucking magic there's these little fucking icons that show up that you use to cast your fucking spells and shit and you know if you want to cast your spell on all the fucking enemies you drag your finger to select all the enemies you can't unfortunately just fucking sit there and hammer the A button to get through all the fucking battles you know you have to kind of tap tap tap tap
[SPEAKER_04]: so everything's a little bit fucking slower that's not the annoying part I don't fucking mind that as much as I do when you're in the fucking towns and you're having to use the fucking fake d-pad that's on the touch screen and the fucking button to run and you're trying to talk to fucking towns people because the frame rate is so fucking bad and everything is so fucking jumpy that you literally have to chase all the fucking town people around for a fucking minute just to fucking talk to them which shouldn't be that fucking hard in a Final Fantasy game
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they don't fucking tell you that before you buy it, so you won't know until you buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say this, $9 is a pretty fucking good price for Final Fantasy 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, I bought Final Fantasy 2 because I played the original fucking Final Fantasy a ton of times, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: um but the Final Fantasy fucking 2 I only played once on the PSP so I decided what the fuck I'll buy this just to kind of check it out it's only nine dollars I will say this if you have a fucking PSP just spend the extra ten dollars to get a copy of the Final Fantasy probably not even that expensive nowadays yeah you could probably fucking find it used somewhere for cheaper so if you're gonna pay nine dollars for the fucking iPhone version did I say nucking is that a good
[SPEAKER_04]: Nuck and... Nuck and futz!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fuck-ing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, thank you, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're gonna spend half as much to get the iPhone version, then you fucking get what you fucking pay for.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: When it comes to controls, it's kind of weak sauce, but it is a beautiful game, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIII is on its way out on Tuesday, and we got a copy through legitimate purposes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you worry, it's totally legit and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a few days early, just so we could jump in there and have something to say about it today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: It played through the game and I've read a lot of the reviews that are online just like a lot of you guys have about how the game is really fucking linear and it's kind of just an interactive movie where you're just fucking bashing the X button for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I kind of go, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy VII, I see a lot of comparisons from XIII to VII, at least in the bits that I've played so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember in Final Fantasy VII, you started that game and you were in Midgar, and you were trapped there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I shouldn't say trapped, it makes it sound like you couldn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you were playing a somewhat linear story for about the first seven hours of Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: and tell you, depending on, you know, how fast or slow you are, you tell you get out of Midgar and explore the overworld.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I know an overworld, well, I don't, I don't really know what, I haven't read spoilers on 13 and I don't want to know, so chat, stay quiet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if there's an overworld that shows up, but I already know there's no towns, so I imagine it's going to stay kind of very 10-ish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they have Chocobo writing and they have the manual, so obviously...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so there's going to be some type of overworld later that's going to be similar to 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, honestly, guys, this game has a lot in common with 7.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of the same types of characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Lightning and Cloud have a lot in common, except one's got a vagina.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's, you know, the emo kid that you just want to slap across the face.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's your sassy black man that's there for comic relief.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, there's a lot of similarities.
[SPEAKER_04]: And...
[SPEAKER_04]: But that isn't a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Final Fantasy VII was a really good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It got overblown a little bit by the fucking crazy-ass fans out there, but it was still a good game.
[SPEAKER_04]: X2 or X2?
[SPEAKER_04]: X2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's a lot of... I mean, Lost Odyssey kind of had some of that too.
[SPEAKER_19]: A lot of the JRPGs are... It does remind me a lot of Lost Odyssey, actually.
[SPEAKER_19]: But Lost Odyssey was more like Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But when I say it takes three hours to get there, I don't want you thinking you're just fucking bored for three hours just sitting there jerking off doing nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of find this game to be like a banana or something that slowly peels and slowly unfolds and starts to show its true shape.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if you don't...
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know if you read any of the manual or anything before you started, but like Falsi and Lassi and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was like, what the fuck are they talking about?
[SPEAKER_19]: Turn the subtitles on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the subtitles on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interjection, just to fucking interject.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm currently not listening to this because I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to keep the spoiler free.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to give stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I want to be completely surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm
[SPEAKER_04]: I will give little spoilers about the battle system because it's essential to the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am zoning the fuck out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, fucking zone out all you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Loki, what were you saying?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it's confusing.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I do have the subtitles and stuff turned on because I don't want to... My audio or whatever, because I have the 5.1 headphones or whatever, it's very...
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: that occur in the story.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's a lot of similarities, I think, between watching Lost on TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you know how Lost kind of divides people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people are like, this show's too fucking slow for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to get to the fucking point already.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be what makes or breaks people on Final Fantasy XIII, I think, as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to speak really quickly about the battle system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real quick, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy introduces this new thing called paradigm shifts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the easiest fucking way I could explain it is that imagine you could flip your character from a black mage to a white mage right in the middle of battle.
[SPEAKER_04]: that's what the paradigm shifts are all about and it's a lot cooler than I think I'm making it sound because like you know you might be doing a battle and you're trying to chain things to get the monster to kind of slip into this mode where it's easier to hit it and then all of a sudden you're like oh shit I'm low on HP I better paradigm shift so I suddenly get a medic in my party and also maybe somebody that casts barrier and all that shit to protect people and then once everybody's cured up go back to assault
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot more fluid than X2.
[SPEAKER_04]: X2 had those big, big, big animations with the dress spheres and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot quicker than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not so over the top like it was in X2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It feels a lot more fluid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to say the battle system in XIII to me feels a little bit more like an action game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It takes active time battle to the next level.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is fast-paced.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is very fucking fast.
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember much like the other Final Fantasy games, to get a preemptive strike or whatever is kind of random.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it works a little bit different too where you don't necessarily do damage to them but it jumps that combo up so that you can do more damage to them later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, good question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really fucking great question from YYR in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: So does this mean you don't have to use any strategy when choosing your party because you can swap at any time?
[SPEAKER_04]: So far, and again, granted, I'm only five and a half hours in right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that are playing the game, I'm in a place called... I think it's called the Valley of Ruin is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'll say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to spoil stories or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: you don't have control over who's in your party people switch in and out based on the story in fact there's a lot of these people are over here and these people are over here these people are over here and their paths intersect once in a while there's a lot of that going on early on in the game so you don't really have a lot of control over your party I think later on you'll be able to control that more and also don't worry the way the XP works is very similar to Ten's experience system where you're kind of moving around the board spending points and
[SPEAKER_19]: and that was a little confusing too because I was trying to figure out I was like trying because they're all yeah you pick the direction you want to go and you hold this button down I'm like I want to go this way and it's going the opposite direction I'm like no I want to go the other way it's all right it makes it makes sense later on as you're using it's very similar to Ten's
[SPEAKER_04]: All your characters gain points when anyone in your party wins.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's not like you're going to have these obscenely under-leveled characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, there are no levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no levels for the characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no levels.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no XP.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you have kind of the 10 system instead is what you have in place of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: there's no magic points which is a huge shift there's something else they use instead of magic points but your characters are going to be flinging fire and arrow left and right with no consequence you have to really think about that and there is um what else do I want to say there's no magic and there's no oh and after every battle you're cured to full you don't have to cure your party after every battle you start heal everybody yeah it's
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of changes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people are not going to like it, but I say give it a chance.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a lot of fucking fun, and I'm five and a half hours in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am hooked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooked, hooked, hooked.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys know I have fucking gamer ADD really fucking bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm always like, ooh, shiny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to go play this fucking blur beta, or I'm going to go play Game Room or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will see this game out to completion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: You might hate these guys too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just a word of caution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I see a lot of similarities.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I don't want to fall down the path of the really nerdy gamer that's virgin in his basement and stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because we know that's not really the truth of me.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck those stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_19]: But here's what I'm saying, dude.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I feel really wrong saying this, but Vanille is fucking hot.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, it's like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_19]: She's like 15.
[SPEAKER_19]: That is gross.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking cocktease.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, she's a pedophile's dream.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of disgusting.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, but seriously, it's like, oh, not to spoil anything, where'd you get your seal?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, it's right here in my upper thigh.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm like, oh, come on!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was... Alan and I were both, like, just had that big reaction of, oh, I feel dirty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, oh, God, that was dirty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to go take a bath in Clorox.
[SPEAKER_19]: And what's up with her voice actor, or actress, I should say?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's just, like, got an accent, and she's way too... too upbeat and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know what's wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't play enough of 10-2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I watched some people play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't really get into it that much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep in mind that the ending cinemas, actually a lot of the cinemas were re-synced to also fit the English dialogue.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the end sequence, the little song that Yuna gets up and sings was completely re-animated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was fucking blown away by the like it's those little things that just made me go whoa and by the way since it hasn't really been mentioned yet the game is fucking gorgeous it is a beautiful beautiful game and I know I've seen those reports out there saying oh the 360 version looks you know worse than the PS3
[SPEAKER_19]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_19]: Just play the fucking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care what system you get it on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan has already said that we're getting the PS3 one.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's what I got too, but I was just... I just knew the 360 was a port, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I just... I wanted my achievement points.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you go 360?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: S3 Discs
[SPEAKER_19]: it's just it's a beautiful game it is so like I just blown away by some of the visuals and like it's not all just like the industrial looks that you've seen in the trailers and things it is a beautiful fucking game well it was funny my friend you know at work he was like oh I don't know if this Final Fantasy is gonna be good or whatever so we played you know I started playing the game and literally got five minutes into it and it got that first action sequence that's in the train where she's jumping off the fucking walls and shit and he's like
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, this game's not going to be a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, enough about Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure we will talk some fucking more about it next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I will work the F word more into my dialogue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I just want to have a serious conversation because that's like one serious topic I know people have been wondering about.
[SPEAKER_07]: But isn't part of this to prove that you can make a fucking serious point and sound fucking intelligent even if you're using fucking?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm still saying fuck a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still wanted to go over the top with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, quickly here, quickly, quickly, I want to play a fucking voicemail from our good pal Breslul about USL Madness, the fucking voting going on in our forums right now to determine the best fucking game of all fucking time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going on in our forums right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's an update from the one and only Breslul.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey Rob, Jamie, and Matt, this is Breslul, and I'm a bit under the weather as my voice is clearly giving it away, but I'm calling once again to promote USL Madness.
[SPEAKER_12]: here on the OrangeZonesRadio.com forums.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have four matchups right now, and the four games will be going to the Final Four.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have Mario 3 vs. Ocarina of Time, Final Fantasy 6 vs. DDR, Chrono Trigger vs. Super Metroid, and Link to the Past vs. Mega Man 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Four of those games go on to the Final Four, and it's up to you, the listeners,
[SPEAKER_12]: to decide who goes on.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have several, I guess four, we have like three of them that are actually really close.
[SPEAKER_12]: So log on to our forums by the end of the night tonight and get your votes in because Tuesday we will have the final four and I think things will get interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Until then, see you guys later.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone get Brestle a fucking cough drop, Jesus.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder where the term under the weather originated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if you're feeling really great, are you over the weather?
[SPEAKER_04]: is it on fucking Wikipedia or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll look it up you are not playing the fucking unicorn game again, are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I fucking played Robot Unicorn today I actually, I did download the anus game did you fucking play it yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't play any fucking anus you need to play the pink anus before next week trust me, once you get sucked into Final Fantasy XIII that's all you're gonna fucking play
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be pretty busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Real fucking life!
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, the 3D version was just not playing at the right time, and it's more expensive.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I honestly don't think the fucking 3D was that good, and, you know, Alice in Wonderland, just based off what I saw in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I neglected, some of our chatters are really fucking confused right now that we're suddenly talking about playing The Pink Anus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me give some fucking background to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, listen to last week's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all fucking explained there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's a game on Steam called, what the fuck is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Secrets of the Magic Crystal?
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a game that looks like you're breeding unicorns or some fucking bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: but one of the items that you're using if you look at the various screenshots one of the items you use in your fucking horse breeding has these little pink bars and they're called anus a-e-n-u-s so we officially have fucking called this the pink anus game because it's funny and you get to say anus and you're not being vulgar you're just talking about what's in a video game so there you fucking go there's some explanation on what's going on
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's see, what other fucking housekeeping do I have?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't you fucking following us on Twitter and Facebook and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR, we'll take your fucking Twitter questions later You know, because it is a show where every fucking gamer has a voice Even when that voice is very vulgar We also have our Facebook at Orange Lounge Radio We have a MySpace too, but I haven't logged in there for like fucking three months But I guess I should check on that
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I really should post more
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know a fucking lot about, but it's Yakuza 3 I haven't really been fucking following this very closely because I didn't really play Yakuza 1 or Yakuza 2 But I still found Dekeman's article very fucking interesting Because Sega made all these fucking localization changes to Yakuza 3 that have people pissed off And I think Dekeman does a very fucking good job of running it down And I'm also just kind of fucking appreciative that there's like actual content on our website besides just the show postings So I'm tipping my fucking hat to Dekeman right fucking now
[SPEAKER_04]: um so yeah and if you want to write stuff for our website get in touch with me you can send me an email rob at orange launch radio.com we're looking for opinions and shit stuff that fits into the fucking every gamer has a voice uh thing so if you're interested drop me an email uh we'll see what we can fucking do
[SPEAKER_04]: and go read Deekman's article.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty fucking great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Deekman posted, just for you, Jamie, something on Digimon earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you fucking saw it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, go to OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if I can see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's our own fucking website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take a look.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else do I want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: On OrangeLaunchRadio.com, on the left side, there's a little fucking box that says... I don't even remember what it says, but it's got all the links...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a fucking loser tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's where it has all the Twitter icon and the last FM and all the places you can follow us and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Extended Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it's fucking called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just look in that box.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like all the communities we're on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: A link to the OLR PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're on a PSP and you have not visited OLRPSP.com, you're fucking missing out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where the fuck have you been?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I know we get new listeners every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't fucking updated that in a long time, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm very sorry, by the way, if we have new listeners tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, honestly This is not normal If this is your first fucking show, you need to realize tonight is a fucking protest We are exercising our first fucking amendment fucking rights Congratulations if you made it this far And keep in mind, normally we are really Rob will say that He will literally say, quote, the F word, end quote Or F that Why am I doing quote fingers?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't fucking see what I'm doing That makes great fucking radio Bite my fucking ass, please
[SPEAKER_07]: I said it nicely.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please makes it nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please makes it very fucking nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the other thing to keep in mind is that I bet anything there's going to be one of those fucking like podcasts that reviews other podcasts or something or some fucking asshole on his blogs and say, I listen to Orange Lounge Radio and all they did was say fuck because they're just stupid and can't think of anything else to say.
[SPEAKER_16]: They don't know what the fuck they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why would you have a fucking podcast review other podcasts?
[SPEAKER_19]: That seems like a...
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, we are protesting the anti-cussing week that our government has seen fit to waste fucking money and time voting upon when we're in the middle of a budget crisis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Students are fucking going out on the freeway and threatening to get fucking run over by cars in protest of how bad the fees have gotten to universities.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a student myself and even going to junior college right now is fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: And
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on, look at how bad the fucking universities are if the students think that that's a good idea, running around on the freeway.
[SPEAKER_19]: Didn't they fucking learn that in, like, preschool?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we should have a 60-star 11.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I need the OL Army and the people that get it tonight, you fucking cool kids that are understanding the show tonight, if you see this shit out there on the internet somewhere, fucking tear them a new asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: because honestly fucking independent people should be supporting each other not tearing each other down I don't fucking talk bad about independent podcasts open fucking season on those that get paid to do it in the core podcast though I will rip them apart but indie podcasts need to fucking help each other out
[SPEAKER_07]: and if I may make my own statement about that and this goes even on an individual basis usually when someone puts down somebody else without giving any constructive feedback it's because they are having issues with themselves low fucking self-esteem leads to bitchiness
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, haven't you noticed that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Usually the people who are the loudest or certain people who are anti-gay are usually the closet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was just fucking thinking that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That happened in our backyard at Main National News.
[SPEAKER_04]: This huge fucking anti-gay Republican piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are some cool Republicans, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just the wrong fucking people are in control of that party right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Meghan McCain, I'm down with her.
[SPEAKER_04]: She is a cool Republican.
[SPEAKER_04]: But idiots like this guy who fucking voted yes on A and then fucking has all this legislation that's fucking anti-gay gets caught at Faces, a gay bar that Jamie and I have fucking gone to several times.
[SPEAKER_07]: This place makes gay look straight.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been there coming back from fucking faces with another guy in his car I mean, anyway, sorry we need to go back and do karaoke at faces that would be a lot of fucking fun I actually did have another point with this is that you know
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not really just the budget crisis that haven't we hit, what is it, somewhere between 14 and 17% statewide unemployment?
[SPEAKER_07]: So people, there's no fucking jobs out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yet, instead of doing things, you know, to help people get jobs, to create new programs, they're wasting their time and effort on...
[SPEAKER_04]: safeguarding morality which is an individual choice so to our government right now fuck you in your ear because your ass is not good enough some quick fucking comments from chat hardcore777 says both Republicans and Democrats are corrupt I'd fucking agree with that honestly because the budget crisis we have in this state right now it's everybody's fucking fault
[SPEAKER_07]: I totally agree.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate going back to the political topic, but this is something that needs to be said.
[SPEAKER_07]: Part of the problem is that we are so stuck in this bipartisan system.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure if you ask anybody, it's even on public sites that say America has a two-party system.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a fucking lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do have independent political parties.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just the Democrats and the Republicans are the ones with the money to spend on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the independents fall to the wayside.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, that is the reason why I wish that Perot had won.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know about you.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm saying that is... For what he fucking stood for, I get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: For what he would do for the, I think, morale.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's the one I'd pick, but okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not saying that he's the one I would have picked, but I'm saying that as an independent who came closer than anyone... To break down the fucking turd wall.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: 4 years, vote him out.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least business won't be fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's a businessman.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm saying that I would like to see the wall shattered.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to see people break out of their little voting strict Republican because, oh, they're Republican.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is why I get an absentee ballot every fucking year.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: podcasts I subscribe to and I unsubscribe from Orange Lounge Radio this week because I find them very annoying and the girl talks too much and the guy's too gay and the other guy's too angry and blah blah blah like just shut the fuck up talk about a podcast you do like nobody reads your fucking blog because you're so fucking negative that's the thing anyhow
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as I know, the other podcasts are cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: If somebody is talking about us, I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if I find out, it's fucking on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about 45 minutes into the show and now some fucking gaming news, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, let's get into this.
[SPEAKER_19]: So there's this bug that fucking popped up last week.
[SPEAKER_19]: We thought it was, you know, maybe someone hacking the fucking PlayStation Network or something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which, that's still...
[SPEAKER_19]: Bakes the question, what the hell was that webpage then that said, you know, hey, turn on your fucking Java and your whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I don't know what that was.
[SPEAKER_19]: But anyways, this was completely unrelated.
[SPEAKER_19]: All apparently the, well, most of the fat PlayStation 3s, the old style ones.
[SPEAKER_19]: had trouble connecting to the PlayStation Network due to a bug in one of the ARM chips and apparently this was caused by the PlayStation 3 thinking apparently that it was a leap year when it wasn't and it became unsynced and so because of this date-time desynchronization it was unable to connect to the PlayStation Network as a safety precaution or something.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, within a little amount of time, it was actually fixed.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, the only advice they fucking gave was, don't turn your system on because you may lose your trophies and some games may not work and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: My favorite was how when it was all fucking over, they were like, we fucking fixed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's okay to turn on your fucking PlayStations now when they didn't do a goddamn thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just waited it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't fucking fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a bug in the date.
[SPEAKER_04]: And as soon as the date changed, all better.
[SPEAKER_04]: So somebody fucked up and thought 2010 was a leap year and somehow that made it in the old fucking PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's my fucking problem with that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently those chips were actually the same chips that were in the Zunes.
[SPEAKER_19]: You may not remember the end of 2008, I think, when it switched over into the year.
[SPEAKER_19]: Isn't it like fucking New Year?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it was like New Year's and all the Zunes stopped working because of the ARM CPU chip and apparently there was a date bug in that too.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, guess what?
[SPEAKER_19]: The same chip was actually inside the PlayStation 3 all along and it was a known problem.
[SPEAKER_19]: But they just kind of... Oops!
[SPEAKER_19]: We forgot all about it!
[SPEAKER_07]: You have a Zune.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't... Didn't...
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I don't have one anymore.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_19]: Times get tough.
[SPEAKER_19]: But yes, I, I mean, you know, you don't really want your whatever to stop working all of a sudden because, oh, we didn't realize there was this bug in here and that's a problem.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it doesn't look good when your consoles stop fucking working.
[SPEAKER_19]: The only advice I can give you is,
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't play it.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: there needs it's very reminiscent of that very controversial Ubisoft DRM that I know we're going to get into later in the show but it just fucking strikes me as like a little hint of that and I do not like that do not fucking want so there's a piece of me that's like Sony doesn't need to fucking fix the date issue Sony needs to fucking fix the I can't play my games online if something is broken on their end issue that's the fucking problem
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, here's the other fucking thing that it's really bad is since they didn't really do anything, I mean, is this actually going to get patched out or like four years from now are we going to run into the same fucking problem again?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, don't forget about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yay.
[SPEAKER_19]: You remember that one time that all those PS3s went fucking down?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it's going to happen again because it's not a leap year, but try telling that to the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_19]: It makes whatever year it wants fucking leap.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, uh... Well, is there a fucking possibility this is gonna happen in the future?
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, I don't think it will be, because it'll be probably patched out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's put something to ignore it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, in other fucking Sony news, we have news about their fucking motion controller that's been kind of quiet ever since the last E3, but I'm assuming that it's because they're gonna have some fucking new news this year at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation Arc PlayStation Arc
[SPEAKER_04]: Arc, Augmentive Reality Controller
[SPEAKER_19]: Arc the Lad Games
[SPEAKER_19]: I somehow really fucking doubt that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or you'll be able to stick two of each animal into that controller.
[SPEAKER_19]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or it will be the fuck controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: How the fuck will that work?
[SPEAKER_04]: Playing fucking Gradius with a motion controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you fucking just flail around to move your fucking ship all around and then pew pew pew with your button?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like I don't fucking understand that.
[SPEAKER_04]: How is Gradius going to incorporate motion control?
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, by the way, Becky just alerted me to something.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: That Cuss Free Week did not pass the Senate.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was on the news and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'll see if I can get her to send me a link.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe there's more.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, still, still, it doesn't matter because it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fucking point still stands whether it passed or not because they wasted their fucking time actually voting on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's even worse if it didn't fucking pass because then they wasted all that fucking time for fucking nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So fuck them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Any attack on my freedom speech.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know how you would fucking play Gradius with a motion controller.
[SPEAKER_19]: The only thing I could think of is that maybe you control the options that way or something.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Me, I flail around and knock the ships out of the way.
[SPEAKER_19]: It sounds dumb.
[SPEAKER_19]: I like the name, but the thing sounds dumb.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did pass California Acupuncture Day.
What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_19]: I am not even going to try to dignify that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, maybe we would see them.
[SPEAKER_07]: and you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: As soon as I saw the little caption on Destructoid, I had to go grab my game and take a picture.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is a big fucking box for a video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: God bless those video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Baseball fucking stars.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and by the way, paid 48 bucks for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but keep in mind how much we paid for fucking King of Fighters 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Weren't those fucking games like fucking $200 when they first came out?
[SPEAKER_07]: We paid $350 for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the time, all the other sites were selling it for about $400.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we got a really good fucking deal on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some fucking clarifications in our chatroom because, of course, the chatroom gets all sicked on it and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It did fucking pass the assembly, but it was fucking rejected in the Senate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there like a high crisis?
[SPEAKER_04]: My point still stands.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a waste of fucking time no matter what happened and that this was even allowed to get somewhere and that people are fucking listening to this guy and, you know, what they stand for and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Point still stands.
[SPEAKER_04]: And besides, you all have been wanting a fucking fuck show for like a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a good fucking reason.
[SPEAKER_04]: The joke's been running for like a year and a half, so now's as good of a time as any.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_19]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_19]: and these two studio heads just all of a sudden aren't working there anymore and now more and more information kind of came out about that and apparently it was according to a bunch of lawsuits here because now they're filing lawsuits against Activision
[SPEAKER_19]: for unpaid royalties.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently, these guys, you know, they did all their hard work on Modern Warfare 2 or whatever, and Activision wanted them, you know, they were kind of strong-arming them into making, you know, the next Modern Warfare game or whatever, the next war game take place in Vietnam, and...
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_19]: and it says, after all we have given Activision, we shouldn't have to sue to get paid.
[SPEAKER_19]: And of course, Activision, you know, responding to their lawsuit, they say that they're disappointed in the lawsuit and that it's meritless.
[SPEAKER_19]: ActaVision is disappointed that Mr. Zemparella and Mr. West have chosen to file a lawsuit and believes their claims are meritless.
[SPEAKER_19]: Over eight years, ActaVision shareholders provided these executives with their capital they needed to start in Findy Ward.
[SPEAKER_19]: So basically they're saying, hey, we made you, now we can break you.
[SPEAKER_19]: as well as financial support, resources, and creative independence that help them flourish and achieve enormous professional success and personal wealth.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, because if they didn't give them money, I'm sure that they couldn't create these wonderful games, is what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_19]: Granted that studios do need money to get going, but I think it's just the creative talent behind it that creates the games.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, it continues.
[SPEAKER_19]: In return, Activision legitimately expected them to honor their obligations to Activision, just like any other executives who hold positions and trust in the company.
[SPEAKER_19]: While the company showed enormous patience, it firmly believes that its decision was justified based on the courses of conduct and actions.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically...
[SPEAKER_19]: Long story short, they were unhappy with what was going on with Activision, and so the rumor is that they were kind of shopping around elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not the only ones that kind of had their fucking fill of Activision, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I read this quick comment from chat from Oddfuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, the opinions in our chatroom are not necessarily those of us here on the show, but here's Oddfuck in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Kotek needs to die in a fucking fire with fucking fire ants on his face while everyone fucking pisses on him.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: you have the fucking all these subsidies of Activision getting shut down all the stuff that's fucking going on now with you know their biggest selling game I mean the Bobby Kotek looks like a fucking buffoon right now like if I were a shareholder I would be demanding some fucking answers and calling for some fucking you know I just think it's
[SPEAKER_19]: They look stupid, and unfortunately, you know, if Infinity War... What it comes down to is if Infinity War ends up, you know, dissolving or whatever, I mean, they'll just move on to... Because they were before, they were behind Medal of Honor and stuff, they were working on that series, and they left to go form, you know, this new company, basically, to, you know, create the Call of Duty series, and the Call of Duty series has been really awesome, but...
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, they're going to be treated like dicks.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Activision's been so awful now that they're making EA look fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to address some fucking good points in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: ShadowFuckingRunner says, Rob, are they still making money?
[SPEAKER_04]: And YOIR says, Rob, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are still buying their products in droves.
[SPEAKER_04]: The shareholders demand results.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hold on, guys, because all this fucking stuff has come out, like, literally within the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And although we've kind of known Activision's going down a shady path for a while, this whole one-two punch I'm talking about is just in the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't mean he's going to fucking get pulled from the board tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: But wait about six months to a year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a little while and see when that next Modern Warfare games comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: If it's not fucking up to par...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: The whole reason they even take on Brutal Legend, that kind of stuff, and Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, we can't figure out a way to pump out a new game every year in this franchise, so we're just not going to take it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then same with Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_19]: I mean, look how they're treating download content and stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Very little each month.
[SPEAKER_19]: And look at DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow, two download packs.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to support it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will fucking say this, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do have a fucking point that it's about the money.
[SPEAKER_04]: They can do all the fucking dickhead things they want in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the end, it's about the money.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my little butt with that is, or my big butt, depending on whatever you want to look at it as, don't underestimate the gamers and kind of the impact that all that negative press on all the blogs and shit can have.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be wrong, and that's fucking fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it's going to come down.
[SPEAKER_19]: Unfortunately, it's going to fucking be just like the protests or whatever with Call of Duty, how they were saying, oh, we're protesting this game.
[SPEAKER_19]: We're not going to fucking buy it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And sure enough, everyone's buying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the Left 4 Dead thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that's a different company.
[SPEAKER_04]: But still, remember fucking the Left 4 Dead fucking thing on Steam that all the fucking people were playing Left 4 Dead 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or they got the screenshot?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: same same story so if you really fucking mean it if you're really fucking you know pissed off that these guys got fired for all their hard work then you need to stop fucking buying the games just stop don't buy the next Call of Duty game it's not going to be an Infinity Ward game anyways I mean that's if you want to wait the way you want to look at it I mean look at they're gonna put Treyarch in you know charge of it and unfortunately Treyarch's just not as good as Infinity Ward I mean people even know that um
[SPEAKER_19]: I just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just, you know, vote with your money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about some fucking titties.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_04]: Perk?
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's one thing better than freedom of speech, it's nudity.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's some titties to be found in fucking Heavy Rain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won't try to spoil the story too bad, but there is a love scene that happens at one point in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it should be fucking obvious if you've seen some of the previous of the game that it kind of pushes the envelope.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's a love scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, if you decline the kiss and trigger the sequence anyway and reload your saved game right away, then you'll have the female lead running around, titties flapping around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is all just hanging out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can run around and play naked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, of course, the naked model was not made in the game to be run around and play naked.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's a shower scene that happens in the story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I saw this.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's interesting, here's the fucking part I think is interesting, though, is that, you know, since everybody gets all fucking bent out of shape because of nudity, specifically the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this game going to go back to the board for an AO rating?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't this the same fucking thing that happened in Oblivion for the PC version ended up getting pulled and fucking rated AO?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because even though you weren't supposed to be able to ever see the titties, the titties were there because they fucking would use them to base like a sheer top on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think though that it's still okay because you actually do see that model in the game it's just now that you're using that model for more than just that one scene but isn't I mean for whatever reason I think it's fucking stupid but the the fucks out there that rate things are like there's a big difference between a butt
[SPEAKER_04]: and a pussy.
[SPEAKER_04]: All that is is 180 degrees.
[SPEAKER_19]: If that model wasn't in the game, if it was just like she's behind a shower curtain or something like that and they're just using that model for a silhouette or something, that's different.
[SPEAKER_19]: But you actually use this model in the game for one of the scenes.
[SPEAKER_19]: You actually see her completely naked.
[SPEAKER_19]: If they're going to argue anything, it's going to be fucking duration.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why didn't they just do the Sims pixel thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss fucking Cleo right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next week on the fucking show, there's gonna be a story about some mother filing a fucking lawsuit against because they fucking found this in the game because their kid read about this on the internet on one of the gaming blogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they fucking go in and unlock the character and suddenly mom walks in and there's some fucking titties on the screen.
[SPEAKER_19]: and she fucking loses her shit not knowing that that's the game she bought for her kid and there's a fucking lawsuit next week's show, that'll be a story if not next week, two weeks but the nudity's in the game already it would be just the same as it would be just I'm watching it it would be just the same as if he didn't do this mod or whatever and you know if they didn't do the mod or whatever and just the shower scene it would be exactly the same
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you're right that there's no basis, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Her boobs don't move like real boobs, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a feeling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't think you were ever supposed to be able to just fucking walk her around and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, uncanny valley my ass.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry, that does not look real.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need some real looking titties.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need Team Ninja to fix this.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have range of motion in the face, but where is the range of motion in the fucking titties?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's got a fucking new story for us, then we'll get into some fucking release dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, fucking story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy fucking birthday, PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, I totally want someone to make me a PS2 cake.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, ten years ago, PS2 launched in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a Japanese PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have the first model one and it still works.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know if mine still fucking works.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't touched it in years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought it a little ways later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought it for Beatmania 2DX 6th style because I was fucking addicted to 2DX for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's what we got ours for too and that and playing some of the few JRPGs that I had.
[SPEAKER_04]: But some of the fucking cool kids in town, they had their PS2s for 3rd and 4th style.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't get on that train until about 6th style was my first fucking Beatmania game.
[SPEAKER_07]: The big thing that gets me on this one is that there actually are people that still use their PS2.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's still PS2 games being released.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're looking at a 10-year-old system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that funny that people never fucking believe that the PlayStation 3 has a 10-year life cycle?
[SPEAKER_04]: And people go, that's too fucking long.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at the PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is still fucking going after 10 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a 10-year life cycle is very viable.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's at the end of its life cycle, but yes, it's still going.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it needs to be put down, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, well, happy fucking birthday, PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just really fucking quick, just kind of reminiscing a minute here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would you guys say were some of the important PlayStation 2 moments for you that, like, had an impact on gaming for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like, as a Final Fantasy fanboy, I think playing fucking Final Fantasy X for the first time was a huge moment for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was, like, a huge moment in PlayStation gaming for you?
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet I know Loki's.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was good, but Driver 3.
[SPEAKER_19]: It introduced me to the lowest of the low.
[SPEAKER_19]: The guy game.
[SPEAKER_07]: PS2 for me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucking Beatmania 2DX, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: When I got my... I remember the day I beat everything on Light 7 in 5th style.
[SPEAKER_07]: I freaking called everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: And posted it on my live journal.
[SPEAKER_07]: I passed Regulus!
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate Regulus!
[SPEAKER_07]: I passed... No, it wasn't Regulus.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was... What was the Light 7 version of Regulus?
[SPEAKER_04]: I... I... I... Something into the lighter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right in the light?
[SPEAKER_04]: But no... The... The really fucking hard songs I think were Sync and Regulus, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't fucking remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how many fucking years ago that was?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's older than this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, now this is going to bother me, but just the day that I beat everything in Light Seven, though I still haven't done it in Fourth Style because of... No, I did beat that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I beat everything in Fourth Style too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Third Style I didn't because I couldn't beat... The Safari.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Safari, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But still, it was like, that was my squeal, I love the PS2 moment.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Synthetic fucking Koniko in our chatroom says Silent fucking Hill, oh my fucking god Yeah, yeah, yeah, Silent Hill 3
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, FuckDeaf says, I got my PS2 for DDR and Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Kingdom Hearts is pretty fucking epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of good comments in our chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm chat.originalsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR says, Boo PS2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still dislike you because those of all the people who didn't buy or develop for the Dreamcast because they were waiting for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: FuckingSharan says, Play Shadow of the fucking Colossus.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a pretty epic game too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very fucking epic.
[SPEAKER_04]: alright well happy fucking birthday PS2 and for those of you still playing the PS2 you might want to think about upgrading although I will say I do hope that the fucking backwards compatibility comes to the Playstation 3 at some point and I know this is a big fucking wrap around I don't want to dredge dirt mine has it
[SPEAKER_04]: Zero!
[SPEAKER_19]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_19]: I thought, oh yeah, I'm going to go back and play some Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've played a few.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember what, but we have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, Rob, crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: What game was it you said?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you know, it reminded me of a game, a franchise that I wish they'd bring back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jumping Flash.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could you imagine a PS3 Jumping Flash?
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be fucking crack.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be epic.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what else?
[SPEAKER_19]: I've played a lot of games on my Xbox 360 backwards compatibility as well.
[SPEAKER_19]: A whopping zero!
[SPEAKER_19]: None!
[SPEAKER_19]: And you know why?
[SPEAKER_19]: Because I have an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm buying new games for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've played Halo 2 a few times.
[SPEAKER_19]: Eh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've also used it for a few games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're so fucking nuts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did use my PS2 a lot for PS1 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mostly for my Japanese one to play my import, so I didn't have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might want to go get Shadow of the Colossus again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I play PS1 games on my PS3, but mostly the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that one game of the guy with the big fro that we were playing at All Games Lounge?
[SPEAKER_04]: On PS1?
[SPEAKER_07]: On PS1, but it was playing on a PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game was cracked out, but now I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a long fucking time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really tested my fucking memory on this show, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or God Hand might be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I didn't play that one either.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about some fucking release dates?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's travel the globe and check out some release dates.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sure there's something fucking coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Something's finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'd be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, so other stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: 50 classic games on the DS.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, I'm thinking that there's games in there somewhere.
[SPEAKER_19]: Resident Evil 5 Gold Edition.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's Resident Evil 5 but better with more stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_19]: And slightly cheaper.
[SPEAKER_19]: Sam & Max 2 Beyond Time and Space.
[SPEAKER_19]: Coming out as a compilation on PC and Wii.
[SPEAKER_19]: In case you didn't buy them all separately.
[SPEAKER_19]: uh Colleen on the Nintendo Wii which shares cover art almost with Final not Final Fantasy with uh obsessed much are we yes Final Fantasy Final Fantasy no um
[SPEAKER_19]: Now it shares box art with almost Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it looks Silent Hill-ish, maybe, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_19]: Photo Showdown for the DSi.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right, DSi, not DS.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a game sort of like Monster Rancher, except you use the pictures that you take with your DSi camera, and based on the colors that are in there, it creates different monsters.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not quite as cool as, you know, putting random CDs in your PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or the barcode scanner.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or the barcode scanner, yes, that's true.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, we need to bring back the barcode scanners.
[SPEAKER_19]: Assassin's Creed 2 coming on PC this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wait a second.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_19]: The Daring Game for Girls
[SPEAKER_07]: What, like pillow fights and braiding each other's hair?
[SPEAKER_19]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Count me out.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yakuza 3, coming out on PlayStation 3, and this of course is a game that's getting lots of controversy for stuff that they've localized and removed.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently people like their Japanese trivia and bar hostesses.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um...
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, of course, later on this week, BlazBlue Calamity Trigger coming to PSP.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's going to be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: On PC, Warhammer 40K Dawn of War 2, the Gold Edition, kind of a re-release compilation of those games.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then also the new expansion will be coming out for that, Dawn of War 2 Chaos Rising.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, if you want some real-time strategy on your 360 coming from Square Enix, Supreme Commander 2 will be making its way out in 360.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, on the DS, Spectral Force Genesis finally coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, uh, about a week from today, we get our Pokemans with, uh, Pokemon SoulSilver and Pokemon HeartGold, each coming with a stupid pedometer because, guess what, Nintendo wants you to fucking exercise, including Pokemon trainers.
[SPEAKER_19]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um,
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, it's a pretty fucking busy week in Japan, which is good because they've had a lot of slow weeks lately.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a lot of fucking releases for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of fucking price drops on the 360 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlazBlue, Dream Club, Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's BlazBlue, not BlazBlue.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always say BlazBlue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where is the fucking E?
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't need one.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's stylistic.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlazBlue It's marketing Fine Then fucking spell the game name right in the future BlazBlue, Dead Rising, Dream Club, Halo Wars, Lost Planet Colonies, Otomedia's Gorgeous All of those fucking games getting price drops in Japan this week on the 360 Some new games coming out as well including Red Seeds Profile Which kind of looks like a Silent Hill-ish kind of game It takes place in a remote village but this time in Canada It's supposed to be like 150 people there
[SPEAKER_04]: and then they find a body and it's about the killer in the rain, da da da, and you're an FBI agent, so I don't know if it's like their answer to Heavy Rain or what, but it kind of just looks like one of those scary thriller type of games, so that is on 360 this week, and then another game called Akatsuki no Amanika To Aikaijin comes out this week as well it's one of those cute girl comedy type games, it's not like a dating sim but it's just kind of like one of those adventure games with cute little anime girls in bikinis and all that stuff, so
[SPEAKER_04]: Super fan service there on the 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably won't come out to America.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Super fan service.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the PlayStation 3 this week, Blaze Blue also gets a price reduction there, as well as Initial D Extreme Stage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Seed's profile makes its way out as well in Japan, and Battlefield Bad Company 2 also comes out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that mean you have to wage battle with the band Bad Company?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Summon Night Grand Thesis, Horobi no Ken to Yakusuku no Kishi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck, they have some long names for games out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an RPG game on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, looks very anime-heavy influenced.
[SPEAKER_04]: Multi-hit combos, though, in some of the sequences.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some really kind of pretty-looking DVD-ish style cutscenes in a very anime style.
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks like, although it's RPG, it might be a little bit action-based in its battles there.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, they need to have more games with the word Grand Thesis in the title.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other games coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm checking the fucking handhelds real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony PSP gets Battle Spirits Hero Soul, Shin Sangoku Mosu Multi-Raid 2, Zetai Hero Kaizu Kekiaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: All of those fucking games are out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also out this week, Eye of Judgment Legends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not in Japan, though, but that's in Asia.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are all on the fucking Sony PSP.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I just need to fucking remind everybody that is not part of the deal because the game makes sense.
[SPEAKER_19]: On a PSP because there's no camera peripheral.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on the Nintendo DS, one really big game this week, fucking worth noting, RPG Tsukuru DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an RPG maker game on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a lot of folks I know really are into those games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, unfortunately, it's very Japanese heavy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're going to have to know your Japanese if you want to fucking play this game or you're going to need to beg somebody to localize it.
[SPEAKER_04]: EnterBrain is putting it out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I know that company over here.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, although it's technically next week, I should point out the DS releases are thinning out a little bit because next week is Pokemon HeartGold and SoulSilver are on their way on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: We know everybody fucking loves Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what the fuck for UK?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, a few fucking odds and ends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy XIII on the 9th.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 10th, Scrap Metal for Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: 12th is Benton Alien Force Viljax Attacks.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the fuck is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Last Rebellion, Warhammer 40k, Dawn of War 2, Chaos Rising.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boo, Warhammer!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you know what my problem with Warhammer is.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Yakuza 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all the fuck there is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, some more fucking news in the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody fucking loves the Classic Game of the Week, and I'm sure DarkSakura picked a pretty fucking good one this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: She usually does.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just a few more stories before we get there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you could all use a break to wash your mouths out with soap.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's been some interesting fucking updates to the game Portal.
[SPEAKER_19]: This week they had a couple updates.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see the cover of Game Informer?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jumping ahead of me here.
[SPEAKER_19]: So the first update that was out there was a patch that added some more radio dialogue, I guess.
[SPEAKER_19]: And there were some different messages that were in Morse code.
[SPEAKER_19]: Also some encoded messages with the numbers and equations in them.
[SPEAKER_19]: And this was all part of the radio that you would hear every now and then.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it was also in the room that you started off in.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it was all kind of hinting different things.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, the people that looked at those images or whatever that was in the little radio messages, it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: They actually found a phone number for a BBS account.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, those old things prior to the internet.
[SPEAKER_19]: I fucking loved BBS, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Pit, fucking Trade Wars 2002, or was it 2020?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, all those fucking games were amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of the Red fucking Dragon, enough said.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then on, of course, those BBSs, they found ASCII art featuring some stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Looks like different robots and whatever from possibly Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Very interesting looking.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some...
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently this is going to be some sort of ARG type of thing, so that'll be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh god, I just realized not all our chatters know what a BBS is.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I feel old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'm really fucking sorry for not explaining it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But BBS is, okay, back before there was the internet, or if you want to get technical, the internet existed then, but it was only for fucking government people and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: so back when like I was in fucking high school and probably about the time it's a bulletin board system yeah but you would have to dial in with a modem some guy would fucking host it on their computer or gal and you would dial in on your modem and connect to it and then it was kind of like it had forums and a lot of the stuff that you kind of see in a new forum on the internet today but you know it was a very community type of thing you didn't usually talk to people because you know people didn't want to call long distance and run up their phone bills so it was a very local thing usually
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, they had shareware, which is, you know, kind of like a little... Take you 45 minutes to download the fucking Wolfenstein 3D demo.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, like a demo, you know, for a game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not really even a demo for a game, but it'd be like the first episode for a game would be like about five bucks or whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: You would go, you know, buy a floppy disk from, you know, whatever retailer, and you would have the first... It'd be a full game, but it wouldn't be like the full, full game.
[SPEAKER_19]: You'd actually go buy, you know, a retail game, but it'd give you a really good idea of what the game was like.
[SPEAKER_19]: and, you know, you could go on these servers and sometimes they would host the full version of the game and you could download it for free.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or, like, you know, I would download, you know, back before MP3s, you know, mod files and stuff like that, you know, different electronica, you know, synthesized Amiga music files and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Mods.
[SPEAKER_19]: So they would have, you know, all sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I remember actually the first time that there was MP3s.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was like, holy shit, what's an MP3?
[SPEAKER_19]: So that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: Back in the day, you used to go on there and sometimes they'd also have it where you could host multiplayer Doom games online and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Doom 2 online.
[SPEAKER_19]: This was back in the day with... This was all that we had.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was not the internet.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was like, which BBS can you get into and what cool files do they have on there?
[SPEAKER_19]: I had to download them in the Y protocol or the Z protocol, X protocol...
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, the PC had a lot of support for it, too.
[SPEAKER_19]: They had, like, S3M, which is, like, Scream Tracker.
[SPEAKER_19]: Basically, it's tracker things.
[SPEAKER_19]: Like, it was like MIDI, where in the MIDI you trigger, you know, different instruments that are hard-coded into your sound card.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, mods, what they were is it was basically different sample files, like WAV files that you put in there, and it was triggered like MIDI was.
[SPEAKER_19]: So you would have, like, you know, people could record their voice, record, like, actual guitars and stuff like that, and it would be triggered, and you could create, you know, electrical music or electronic music with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anything else you wanted to say about Portal before we go to the next story?
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyways, yeah, so to get back into Portal, yeah, there's some pretty cool stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_19]: They also added an extended ending to Portal, which kind of made it creepy.
[SPEAKER_19]: You may remember, if you finish the game, and a lot of people have, you end up kind of outside while the whole lab kind of...
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, for your party.
[SPEAKER_19]: S-Corp Party Position
[SPEAKER_19]: And of course, it was already confirmed by Game Informer.
[SPEAKER_19]: Their cover is actually Portal 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it shows, kind of, looks like Aperture Science was just like all these vines and stuff growing from the outside, kind of in through portals and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: What's going to be kind of unique about it, the game will be coming out on PlayStation, or not PlayStation, PC, Xbox 360, and Mac platforms.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it will be two-player co-op.
[SPEAKER_19]: And it's going to have some interesting looking things in there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: If you want to learn more about that course, check out the latest game form.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, in other first-person shooter news, if you still can't fucking tear yourself away from Halo 2, you don't have much time left.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: April 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your attempts to try and fucking change your mind haven't worked because they are shutting it down April 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: 3 months of Xbox Live Gold and 400 Microsoft Points Now if you think, oh shit I should run online and play Halo 2 real quick Sorry, you're probably not going to get it now They probably did it for people that had played X number of hours in the past month But
[SPEAKER_04]: Still kind of pretty fucking cool of Microsoft to do, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's better than what they're required to do, which is nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm sure there's a lot of people that are going to be fucking happy that they can get some bonuses there if they're not too fucking pissed off about Halo 2 going away.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would be really fucking nice of Microsoft to do would be to just say, you know, if you want to run your own private servers, here you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess you can't really do that on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Halo 2 is not going away on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something to remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you really want to cling to your Halo 2 for dear life, remember you can't always play on the PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, in Europe, it was called Grisor.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um, it was put up by Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was originally on the arcade and came out for the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, for the PAL region, came out as Probotector.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me, I burped on the mic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and it also came out for the MSX, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there are a bunch of sequels.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, I mean, who doesn't remember Super C, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, so basically you are these guys called Bill and Lance who work for Red Falcon and are trying to stop an alien invasion.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Bill and Lance like to run around with no shirts on and carrying big guns.
[SPEAKER_07]: They wear vests, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Vests.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And wear headbands.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't help it if it's hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not about fucking.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yeah, you can get a whole bunch of different guns.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get a machine gun, a laser gun, a fire gun, a spread gun, rapid fire power-up, all kinds of different fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you also, besides having the typical side-scrolling levels, you also have a behind-the-back sort of 3D maze level where you have to go in a certain order and go through the bases, defenses, and get to the end.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's really fucking hard!
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, it's hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't use the Konami code and have somebody else playing with you and you can beat this game without dying, I want to meet you and have you sign my arm or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR in chat is trying to show off his big fucking skills saying, cleared both Contra and Super C on NES without 10 or 30 lives and without continues.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who else?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but did you die?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to meet the person who can do it without dying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't Dan do it without dying?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I fucking thought he could.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that's why you fucking married him.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it was our type that he could beat without dying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_07]: It also came out on the ZX Spectrum, Commodore 64, Amstrad CPC.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, I need to ask you about Commodore 64 stuff, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking love the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have a good emulator?
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't used one in a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping the game room is going to bring back some of the C64 stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Wii's done a pretty shitty job.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's for someone else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those versions all came out in Europe in 1988.
[SPEAKER_07]: The IBM PC version was also out in Germany.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Commodore 64 and IBM versions later came out in North America as Contra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, but yeah, the NES version was evil and hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was one of the earliest games to use the Konami code.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, um, one of the other games that did it was, you know, before that was, of course, Gradius.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and for the Falmicon, it used a multi-memory controller that, um, uh...
[SPEAKER_07]: and Konami made for the Japanese market that gave it additional graphical effects.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know if anyone's ever played ROM of this, but if you play the Japanese ROM, there's animation in the background and other stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: The leaves are moving and the grass is blowing in the wind and all kinds of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it also had extra cheat codes like a stage select and a sound test and hidden post-credits scene that you would hold select and start before and during the entire end credits.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, like I said, the European version was called Probotector and the main guys were turned into robots.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was just because of censorship laws in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck censorship.
[SPEAKER_07]: But when Contra Legacy of War and Shattered Soldier came out, they retained the Contra name.
[SPEAKER_07]: MSX2 was actually fairly different than the arcade and the NES version because of limitations in the hardware.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't scroll, but it used flip screens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sort of the way that Metal Gear and Vampire Killer did.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was only single player.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, it did change the last 10 stages of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the MSX2 version of Contra is on the Wii Virtual Console in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It came out on February 2nd of this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, there was a PS2 re-release version for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Digital Eclipse handled the conversion.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's Konami Classics Series Arcade hits for the DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: and you can actually get the Konami's Collector Series Castlevania and Contra for Windows in North America which also includes Super C and 3 Castlevania games and if you get Contra 4 Contra and Super C is also included that's the DS
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty freaking hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, there were a ton of Contra games that came after.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was Super Contra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Super C. It was Super Contra overseas.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Super C here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Operation C for the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Contra 3, The Alien Wars for Super NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: Contra Force for NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: Contra Hardcore, which that's really actually kind of hard, too, on Genesis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the Super Nintendo one.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami contracted out for PlayStation Contra Legacy of War, which also came out on the Saturn.
[SPEAKER_07]: See the Contra Adventure in 1998.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2000, we had Contra Shattered Soldier and Neo Contra.
[SPEAKER_07]: Contra 4 came out on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Contra Rebirth by M2 came out for WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our old fucking pal Kiriyamaoka did the music for Shattered Soldier, if I remember right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, if you were looking for any of the soundtracks from the arcade version of Contra, the soundtrack is included on Konami Game Music Vol.
[SPEAKER_07]: 4, Ajax, which came out in 1988.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's actually a vinyl version of that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fucking old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fucking great choice, and the chatroom's very fucking pleased with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Contra is your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I totally recommend watching the Angry Nintendo Nerd, or Angry Gamer Nerd, his review of Contra.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to take a quick fucking break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio in just a little bit, so fucking don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Perhaps one of the most interesting words in the English language today is the word, fuck.
[SPEAKER_13]: Out of all of the English words that begin with the letter F, fuck is the only word that is referred to as the F word.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the one magical word.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just by its sound can describe pain, pleasure, hate, and love.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck, as most words in the English language, is derived from German, the word frichen, which means to strike.
[SPEAKER_13]: In English, fuck falls into many grammatical categories.
[SPEAKER_13]: As a transitive verb, for instance, John fucked Shirley.
[SPEAKER_13]: As an intransitive verb, Shirley fucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Its meaning is not always sexual.
[SPEAKER_13]: It can be used as an adjective, such as, John's doing all the fucking work.
[SPEAKER_13]: As part of an adverb, Shirley talks too fucking much.
[SPEAKER_13]: As an adverb enhancing an adjective, Shirley is fucking beautiful.
[SPEAKER_13]: As a noun, I don't give a fuck.
[SPEAKER_13]: As part of a word, abso-fucking-lutely or infucking-credible.
[SPEAKER_13]: And as almost every word in a sentence, fuck the fucking fuckers.
[SPEAKER_13]: As you must realize, there aren't too many words with the versatility of fuck.
[SPEAKER_13]: As in these examples describing situations such as fraud, I got fucked at the used car lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dismay, aw fuck it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Trouble, I guess I'm really fucked now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Aggression, don't fuck with me buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Difficulty, I don't understand this fucking question.
[SPEAKER_13]: Inquiry, who the fuck was that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dissatisfaction.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't like what the fuck is going on here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Incompetence.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's a fuck off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dismissal.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't you go outside and play hide and go fuck yourself?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure you can think of many more examples.
[SPEAKER_13]: With all of these multi-purpose applications, how can anyone be offended when you use the word?
[SPEAKER_13]: We say, use this unique, flexible word more often in your daily speech.
[SPEAKER_13]: It will identify the quality of your character immediately.
[SPEAKER_13]: Say it loudly and proudly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio on this very special edition in celebration of our State Assembly wasting their fucking time passing a resolution to celebrate No Cussing Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if it did fail in the Senate, it's still a waste of fucking everybody's time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't you go play hide and go fuck yourself?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, I hear we're on against the fucking Oscars tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, who gives a fuck about a bunch of Hollywood people, uppity fucks, just sucking each other's dicks and giving each other awards.
[SPEAKER_19]: I forgot to submit my Oscar picks for a... Okay, so at my work we have this Oscar pool that we fucking do every year, and every fucking year I forget to submit them.
[SPEAKER_19]: I had it done.
[SPEAKER_19]: My co-worker fucking reminded me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I get home like, God damn it.
[SPEAKER_19]: I fucking forgot them again on my desk.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not that fucking hard this year.
[SPEAKER_19]: All my picks so far have been worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, damn it!
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a two fucking movie race.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though they upped it to ten, it's two.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares about the Oscars?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hurt Locker's gonna win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't fucking matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: And besides, you don't have to fucking watch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just read it on the internet later.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like four hours of bloated bullshit.
[SPEAKER_19]: Do what I do with American Idol results shows.
[SPEAKER_19]: You don't watch them.
[SPEAKER_19]: You just fucking read who wins.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or loses.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they waste all the fucking time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, loses.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: YYR is like, oh, but what are they wearing?
[SPEAKER_04]: OMG, look at that gown.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so daring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at how much skin they're bearing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll all be on fucking Perez Hilton and Oh No They Didn't and the OMG blogs, all the fashion shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tiger Claw's been keeping me updated.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those that care.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, sending you private messages or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really, you fucking care about the Oscars?
[SPEAKER_07]: I care to see what Star Trek wins.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's only going to win makeup because that was the only thing it was nominated for.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that is the first win for a Star Trek movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought even fucking Nemesis got nominated at least for like visual effects.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I said, the first win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: But actually, I do have to agree that Avatar did deserve Best Cinematography.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to some fucking video game news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, let's talk about some fucking sequels, including Scribblenauts 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right, coming from the fucking source for Nintendo news, Nintendo fucking power.
[SPEAKER_19]: There will be another Scribblenauts game, and how can they fucking put out another one, you may ask, because there were so many words that were in there before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe because the first fucking game sold like fucking hotcakes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it was a huge DS game.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, here's how they're going to fucking do it.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're going to add 10,000 more words.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_19]: 10,000 words.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's fucking more than 9,000.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's over 9,000 words.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just giving the... They were missing fucking 9,000 words before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be all internet memes this time.
[SPEAKER_19]: Baby Cthulhu
[SPEAKER_19]: Baby Cthulhu, you scare the shit out of me Over 9,000 It'll deliver 120 new levels, a level editor, a new hint system, and improved controls
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, better have improved controls because those controls sucked.
[SPEAKER_19]: So, how about actual controls first?
[SPEAKER_19]: Another not-too-surprising sequel.
[SPEAKER_19]: In fact, I've known about this for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_19]: SOCOM 4 being announced for PlayStation 3 by Zipper, the company that developed it the last time around for SOCOM Confrontation.
[SPEAKER_19]: But this is an actual sequel this time, and apparently it's going to deliver 14 missions with about...
[SPEAKER_19]: 12 hours of gameplay, and of course, you know, the developer has a pretty good track record when it comes to multiplayer games, seeing as they were behind MAG, which had 256 players.
[SPEAKER_19]: However, the game will only have 32-player online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, and this is great, apparently...
[SPEAKER_19]: At the 11th hour, Ubisoft has made some emergency changes to their DRM on their PC titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Great topic for the fuck show.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently, there was some fixes that needed to be made because people were figuring out how to crack it.
[SPEAKER_19]: And of course...
[SPEAKER_19]: They've already cracked it, but Ubisoft says that players should... Should players lose their internet connection, a requirement under the company's ridiculous new DRM scheme, their single-player offline game would drop upon reloading.
[SPEAKER_19]: You'd be left with your last checkpoint and not the actual point you were cut out on.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, their claim is that, no, the DRM has not been broken.
[SPEAKER_19]: In fact...
[SPEAKER_19]: Those who are playing the cracked version out there aren't getting the full game experience.
[SPEAKER_19]: In other words, they're not getting access to the Uplay stuff, which no one gives a shit.
[SPEAKER_19]: And to kind of go along with this, in kind of the worst case scenario situation, well, the worst case scenario situation happened, and apparently their servers went offline, their Ubisoft DRM authentication servers.
[SPEAKER_19]: They've been down, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently people that had Assassin's Creed 2 can't play it right now.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't!
[SPEAKER_19]: I smell a fucking class action lawsuit and apparently yes and it's been down for quite a long time and there's been people trying to log in for like 25 minutes and they're unable to do anything and a Noobisoft representative apparently responded to the forum thread that's over on the official Assassin's Creed 2 forum and saying clearly the extended downtime and lengthy login issues are unacceptable particularly as I've been told these servers are constantly monitored
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they apparently watched them go down.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, you fucked that up, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm honoring them!
[SPEAKER_19]: Crushing!
[SPEAKER_19]: And then they added, I'll do what I can to get more information on this issue.
[SPEAKER_19]: And here's more on what the issue is.
[SPEAKER_19]: First thing tomorrow, push for a resolution and assurance that this won't happen again in the future.
[SPEAKER_19]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_19]: They've already cracked it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Forget about it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because what apparently happened is there was a cracker group out there that figured out that, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_19]: They have some sort of failsafe in the case that Ubisoft decides to go out of business that they'll put out a patch that will apparently disable this DRM so that you can play your game just fine.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_19]: The code's in there, and they've activated it, so...
[SPEAKER_19]: Thanks, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_19]: You made it easy.
[SPEAKER_19]: We all knew this was going to fucking happen.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_19]: And we all knew it's a stupid idea.
[SPEAKER_19]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a stupid idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it a fucking stupid idea?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's a fucking stupid idea.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the worst idea ever because all you're doing is punishing the people that legitimately paid for the program.
[SPEAKER_19]: The people that want to hack it, they're going to wait for a hacked version to come out.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think there's a PC title out there that they haven't figured out a way around some sort of DRM for it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_19]: You tried.
[SPEAKER_19]: You failed.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe you shouldn't try because it costs money to try.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, so a lot of fucking confusion going on over a highly fucking controversial game, Six Days in Fallujah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might remember this game was supposed to fucking come out, and then it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, wasn't fucking Konami actually supposed to put it out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Konami was putting it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then they were like, no, we don't want to fucking be associated with this.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because they're working with terrorists or something, and they were also working with the soldiers that were there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that wasn't going to fucking stop Atomic Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently IGN reported this week that...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: So keep an eye on Atomic Games, I suppose, if you really want more information on this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know that old saying, strike when the iron is hot?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, it's like, you know, the air is frozen, put away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, on some other fucking news, if you still are one of these people that don't have a fucking Wii for some reason, Walmart can sell you the bundle that everybody fucking thought would be out already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Walmart is selling a Wii, a Nintendo Wii, Wii Sports, Wii Sports Resort, and the Motion Plus attachment.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's available right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: $199 is the price for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically it's a normal Wii thing with Wii Sports Resort with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, you know, although Walmart, I don't know, they can kind of be fucking shady about some things like, I don't know, censorship on albums.
[SPEAKER_04]: A good deal is still a good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you do not have a Nintendo Wii for whatever reason, you want the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_19]: It'll be in limited supplies as if the supplies aren't limited enough already.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: and one other fucking thing I have for you guys before I turn it over to DarkSakura Tecmo Bowl there is a new Tecmo Bowl coming it's a new old Tecmo Bowl it's a fucking throwback I am actually fucking excited about this I don't talk a lot about sports games on this show because I don't fucking play a lot of them because I know it's going to sound weird but a lot of them are too fucking complicated for me because I don't watch a lot of them on TV but I like the kind of overly simplified ones like NBA Jam I always love that game in the fucking arcades and
[SPEAKER_04]: And this new one is somewhat interesting I fucking love Tecmo Bowl on the NES I thought it was great So the idea that they're kind of doing this throwback I find very fucking exciting Will it feature real sugar this time?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know The idea of this was kind of leaked a little while ago Thanks to an ESRB rating But now it's been acknowledged Tecmo Bowl throwback is coming out on the Xbox Live Arcade And PlayStation Network sometime in the spring It's a remake of Tecmo Super Bowl You can switch to classic 2D Amongst I guess the 3D
[SPEAKER_04]: The people who fucking made it are South End Interactive.
[SPEAKER_04]: They also made that fucking Lode Runner game and R-Type.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did Lode Runner ever fucking come out?
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, some time ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: The R-Type one's pretty fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that's the R-Type that's on Xbox Live RTA, that's pretty fucking rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is a good studio to be doing this.
[SPEAKER_04]: All new 3D graphics.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, and, and, online play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: TechMobile Throwback will have 32 teams, online leaderboards, and customizable options for the teams and the rosters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, like, are they going to be actual teams or no?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to be fake teams.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're fake teams.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're called New York and Denver, but it's not like fucking the New York and the Denver.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still, I'm all over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet you never thought you would hear me say this about a sports game here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am all fucking about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am very excited to fucking play this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura's got a few stories for us and then some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: I sure fucking do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock Band, we are getting some songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: White Stripes Pack, which will be $4.40, $5.50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fell in Love with the Girls, Seven Nation Army, and You Don't Know What Love Is, You Just Do As You're Told.
[SPEAKER_07]: Individual Tracks, The Future Heads, Decent Days and Nights, Hounds of Love.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, wasn't that a Kate Bush song?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, anyway, The James Gang, Walk Away, Neil Peart, The Hockey Theme, and Seamus, All of This, and Tie You Down.
[SPEAKER_07]: And other news, there is a, uh,
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that was given to me as an incomplete link that I have no idea what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Max Technica 2 has a teaser out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess people can go watch it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the 8-bit Left 4 Dead dude is doing Mega Man 9 HD remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: So keep your eyes open for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I bet nobody's going to ever fucking play it because there'll be a lawsuit that'll stop it if they ever try to put that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's just the fucking way the world works.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, it's not Activision.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they'll be a little cooler.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, is Mega Man 10 too much or what?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't think it's too much.
[SPEAKER_19]: I think it would be pretty cool to see them release more of these retro games.
[SPEAKER_19]: The problem is they're just not as good as Mega Man 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_19]: and hell, I'd like to see a studio that only did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think DarkTouch Studio raises a fucking good point in chat saying, well, I don't think Capcom would want people playing the equivalent of one of their recent releases for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're still probably making some fucking money off Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, they would shut this shit down if it was getting out there too much.
[SPEAKER_19]: but I don't think it's a bad thing you know why not you know now that they kind of did the fucking retro 3 and just go in and make some HD sprites keep the same game keep the same just make it pretty or even you know what you could do and here's what they really need to do they need to put fucking Mega Man 9 and Mega Man 10 like on the DS or something like that so I can take it with me and play that shit well I mean those ROMs gotta be pretty small anyways that aside or a new Mega Man collection would be kind of cool with those in there
[SPEAKER_19]: If they want to make a 3D game, make another Mega Man Legends.
[SPEAKER_19]: That would be fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get to some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: See what you fucking people on Twitter have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week we read your tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Show us your tweets at OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of fucking celebration that finally, a year and a half after I think the idea was first announced, we are finally having our fucking fuck show up against the Oscars tonight in a moment of protest.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not everybody fucking on board with the fuck show though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sterlok sends us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be perfectly honest, this joke is already painfully old.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not gonna be for everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep in mind, we're not just doing it to say fuck a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, although I will say that's a nice benefit.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it is a protest against people taking their time out of their busy schedules.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should be balancing budgets to tell us that we shouldn't swear.
[SPEAKER_04]: That swearing makes us somehow unintelligent.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same fucking show tonight, just more fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I don't know, I was a little worried coming into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might get fucking old after three hours, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two hours and I still feel pretty fucking good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys, you doing okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator says some very nasty words to Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet he'll call in later and say some more about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But also says, let's see if I got this right This is in response to the heavy rain thing SpazinatorPSN says, let's see if I got this right Heads blown off, fine Hot crowbar up the ass, fine Mass murder, fine Tits are vag What sicko wants to see that fucking shit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, it's like the biggest, like, I don't even know what word you would say to describe this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just this big, glaring hypocrisy in the media and in society that has been going on for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just fucking...
[SPEAKER_04]: Video games, but it's movies, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: There was some movie about, like, it's called This Movie is Rated R or something like that that explores, like, the NC-17 rating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking fascinating.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTouch Studio wants everyone to fucking know that I Love This Song resumes this week on the site.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like seeing some more fucking content on OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully there's more than just the I Love That Song segment, which was, you know, everything that was on the website, but I do...
[SPEAKER_04]: I like music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming music is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I always like the I Love That Song segment and the diversity of stuff that they picked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, Takeo Ray sends his tweet, wants to know, so does anyone have an F-bomb count for the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they lost track in the first fucking five minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_19]: And, I mean, I doubt that Guinness will pay attention to something like this because it's just a fucking podcast.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, hey, they'll pay attention to, like, what the longest pretzel is or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't fucking get them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Some of the shit that they fucking record is ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, maybe we can be in the gaming podcast.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or, not the gaming podcast, the gaming Guinness Book of World Records thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was gonna say, maybe we could record her taking a shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I haven't started talking about the tester yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did watch episode two of the tester.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it worth a shirmy poop?
[SPEAKER_04]: I still feel the same about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the most terrible thing to ever reach my television, but it's no RuPaul's Drag Race, which would be the best thing to ever grace my television.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a big what the fuck ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It gets a three out of five RuPaul's Drag Races.
[SPEAKER_04]: um it should have to lip sync for its life I do think that is something I don't know it's pretty obvious that they fucking film this whole show in the scope of like three or four days like like they're doing a little challenge in the morning kick somebody off to a challenge in the evening kick somebody off to it was really fucking fast I'm sure whatever
[SPEAKER_04]: Just as quick as their career.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, $5,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, if it's just like four days or whatever to film the show, I'd fucking go on the tester, win the $5,000, and then quit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_04]: BoFuckYouIchikawa in our chatroom, chat.orangelaunchradio.com, said episode four of The Tester is supposed to be LARPing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only through the second episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just watched the first two.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm glad they didn't waste time on those stereotypes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see the people who were doing the live-action Avatar roleplay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on with some more fucking gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then the mailbag, then your fucking calls, which I'm sure are going to be a hoot and a holler tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't fucking wait for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, every call counts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might have to institute the time limit on calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we're going to do rapid fire calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just so everybody can have their say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I know everybody wants to get rapid fire calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone gives a fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rapid Fire calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm already throwing that down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your call is too long.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hang up on you now.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Instead of getting three calls, we could get through like seven if we do a time limit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to do that tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Loki, some fucking gaming news for us.
[SPEAKER_19]: This also has nothing to fucking do with the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, the PlayStation Network technically didn't go down, but PlayStation 3 did.
[SPEAKER_19]: Way back in late 2008, apparently a Pennsylvania teenager playing SOCOM US Navy SEALs got kicked out of a tournament for using a cheat mod, so he decided to take revenge by crashing the PlayStation website for 11 days.
[SPEAKER_19]: and what's funny though is Sony has decided, you know what?
[SPEAKER_19]: They filed a federal grand jury investigation which led to the perpetrator getting arrested.
[SPEAKER_19]: The hacker pled guilty to four felony charges in juvie court and apparently he got access to
[SPEAKER_19]: He apparently got access to the site's servers and let loose a virus that brought everything down.
[SPEAKER_19]: And his methods, I guess, weren't described, but some experts or whatever contacted by local TV stations said they weren't so sophisticated that someone else couldn't pull it off.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hopefully, by now, they've already fixed that stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently also it says, in exchange, the team pleaded guilty to four counts and lawful use of a computer, criminal use of a computer, computer trespassing and distribution of a computer virus in exchange for prosecutors dropping the 11 others, some related to the March 2009 cyber attack.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know what's even funnier?
[SPEAKER_19]: Is he's from La Trobe.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have a road over here named Latrobe, but this is all in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually know where that is in Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not just Pittsburgh, but what they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, boo fucking who for this kid.
[SPEAKER_04]: He got what he deserved, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't fucking hack the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got kicked out for fucking cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: You fucking deserved it.
[SPEAKER_19]: He thought he was leap hack source.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boo hoo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got banned for cheating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun in the fucking slammer.
[SPEAKER_04]: On to happier news, a really fucking cute fucking game on the PlayStation 3, LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who doesn't love LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so fucking adorable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of people do, apparently enough to make 2 million, 2 million user-created levels.
[SPEAKER_19]: There is some pretty fun stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_19]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: and uh this shouldn't really come as a big fucking surprise but Media Molecule has now been absorbed fully as a first party company for Sony so Sony has now sucked them up into their collective and Media Molecule now has their fucking checks signed by Sony so there it is
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Dan!
[SPEAKER_04]: Media Molecule is no longer an independent studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And by the way, a comment from Michael Denny, the Senior Vice President of Sony Worldwide Studios, quote, Media Molecule will simply continue to make great games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcoming Media Molecule into the PlayStation family will allow us to better support their future titles and ambitions.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're really fucked now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just kidding, I added that last part myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan yelled from the living room, that's only if Activision buys them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, if Activision comes for your company, run, bitch, run.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just say nay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't wait for them to close Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what you got for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there was a version of a number of different Nintendo games, some of them super rare, that were going on eBay.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was one in particular, Family Fun Fitness Stadium Events.
[SPEAKER_07]: It hit a bid amount of $800,200.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking eBay scammers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like anybody who has that much money to blow on an NES game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is actually the highest game on there right now is Bubble Bath Babes with the box for $2,995.
[SPEAKER_07]: Worth every fucking penny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll offer a one cent bid on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you can put a one cent bid when you have to have a minimum bid of $3,000.
[SPEAKER_07]: Best offer, five bucks.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, this is totally off topic here, just thought I'd mention this because this is funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not fucking allowed.
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, well this is going back to the fucking story we had about, um, during Rapid Fire, about the Ubisoft DRM.
[SPEAKER_19]: Here's why their server went down.
[SPEAKER_19]: Due to exceptional demand, we are currently experiencing difficulties.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, that's right, because their games sold and people bought them,
[SPEAKER_19]: and then try to play them and it logs in online, it causes server strain and therefore it's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: So basically, if you buy their games, it breaks the server.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why don't they just fucking say it's a DDoS attack?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's clearly what's going on, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just from people playing their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you think that's just a load of bullshit?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to fucking save face?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're just stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exceptional demand could be a bunch of inquiries to their server.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're being DDoS'd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which isn't okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's fucked up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't support that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's even worse if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, dude, the exceptional demand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that will be a problem going forward.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I would... You don't...
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking take all these statements at face value, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because look at what Sony said earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We fixed the fucking date problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: You waited it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You fucking waited it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then put out a press release about how fucking awesome you are to fix the problem in exactly 24 hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: We weren't born yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Due to exceptional demand.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're...
[SPEAKER_04]: Your fucking DRM is about as in demand as a fucking Yanni CD at Lollapalooza, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how fucking in demand your thing is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: More news than the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they launched with 105 songs, which is fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_19]: Try that, Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_19]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't even get me started with DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_19]: Two download packs.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I should have figured...
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, no, but seriously, compare this to what they have for, you know, Guitar Hero, where they have their basic service that you can, you know, create your own tracks and throw them on there for, uh, free download.
[SPEAKER_19]: But this is, like, way better.
[SPEAKER_19]: And 105 tracks launched.
[SPEAKER_19]: So far, the song ranges from, uh, price ranges are about 80 to 160 Microsoft points, or a buck or two.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, um, you know, just kind of some of the, um...
[SPEAKER_19]: MC Frontalot I love that song
[SPEAKER_19]: Also a little bit of Jonathan Colton in there, including Creepy Doll, Ikea in the Future Soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Another two bunch of good songs.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then a bunch of other artists I don't recognize, but a lot of other people might.
[SPEAKER_19]: Was it The Shins?
[SPEAKER_19]: Australia, I recognize The Shins.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's some other artists, The Main Drag.
[SPEAKER_19]: Let's see here, Scratching the Itch.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: But tons of stuff.
[SPEAKER_19]: And there's going to be more added each day as this goes on.
[SPEAKER_19]: So definitely worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_19]: They are exclusive on the Xbox 360 for 30 days, after which a selection of standout tracks will become available on the PlayStation 3 and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: OLR should have a fucking song on there like I don't know we don't really have any we don't do music really but I think we should just we should have a fucking song on the Rock Band Network somehow the problem it's it's not an original song
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, if someone wants to put all that effort and work into it, yeah sure I got one more story for you guys and then we can get to the fucking mailbag This has to do with an update to the Code of Conduct I gotta be honest, although I'm sure this probably pissed me off when I first fucking heard about it I totally fucking forgot about it until this story came out this week That apparently, Xbox Live has now lifted the ban on using the terms Lesbian, Gay, Bi, Transgender, and Straight in your profiles
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to put, hi, I like games and I'm a big lesbian in your profile, it is okay to do that now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So have a ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I talked a little bit about this on Bobby Blackwolf's show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's the show before us in all games radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a much cleaner show than we are, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's always kind enough to do a call with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you imagine how fucking bleeped out he is?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see Bobby do a fuck show, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to see him just go off one night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't fucking believe this fucking... I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: On Bobby's show, I was talking about this a little bit, and I was just saying, like, you know, okay, yeah, I'm a gay guy, and I don't think I really care that I can put this in my profile now, especially on Xbox Live, of all places.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to put, like, I'm a gay gamer, 31, from California.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's not fucking Match.com or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is anybody's business.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, why do people make that such a big deal?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, yeah, it's a part of your identity, but it's not like I go around saying...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, I like everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I also agree that if someone wants to do it, they should have every right to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't understand why you'd do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But okay, if you want to put it on your profile, you should have every right without repercussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're probably going to get all these messages from losers going...
[SPEAKER_16]: What?
[SPEAKER_16]: You're a fag?
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe I should put in my profile, send me boob photos, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be okay to put in your profile, I love lesbians.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's well on my rights.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big supporter of lesbian rights.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big supporter of lesbian boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun with your profiles and so forth.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dude, that's someone else I gotta follow on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: One of my friends on LiveJournal, they have Tom Selleck in an icon.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm like,
[SPEAKER_19]: Link the Twitter in chat, we will double the number tonight Link the Twitter in chat, chatters
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio loves Steve Guttenberg.
[SPEAKER_04]: You fucking know what to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to follow this guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: President Cat approves of Steve Guttenberg.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's three men and a fucking baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we know it's really him?
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's the only Steve Guttenberg on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it must be him.
[SPEAKER_04]: It must be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who'd want to impersonate Steve Guttenberg?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's see who's following him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not many actual famous people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look it up on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Link it in Chatters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chatters, you know what to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Steve Guttenberg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck, follow him.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to look and see if there's a Steve underscore Guttenberg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta stop looking for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who do you mean, nope?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, there's not an underscore Steve Goober.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you say no to the emailers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just followed him, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel like such a fucking sheep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll go fucking follow him too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: The emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week you send us your fucking emails and we read them.
[SPEAKER_19]: He has an official website, so we'll figure it out in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.orangeloungeradio.com is our website and I think there's an email link there or just open up your email browser and go mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com Read us the emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The emails were hidden under Yahoo Japan stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are you fucking doing on Yahoo Japan?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll tell you after the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't you tell me during the show?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it juicy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: This comes from JammerJ.
[SPEAKER_07]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who, by the way, sent me a very nice Christmas card with a Sudoku puzzle in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And... Isn't it fucking March and you're just now getting a Christmas card?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I got... It bounced back.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he sent, like, I think an Eye of Judgment card or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, here was a situation posed to me and I wanted to get OLR's thoughts on this since we are all about the same age.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here is the scenario my coworker gave me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dave and my other coworkers would put the money into a pot.
[SPEAKER_07]: In order to win the pot, I would have to stop playing all video games for a month.
[SPEAKER_07]: I told him I would not do it and that it seemed a bit ridiculous to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dave's reasoning was that my life would get immediately better and that I would be a better person and go out more.
[SPEAKER_07]: The ironic thing was that we were dragged out to a country bar and shooting pool, which I did not enjoy as much, but I could do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we were all meh anyways being dragged there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, like many others, he sees the gaming lifestyle as negative and he does not know even really what means, like many others not in Idaho.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do a large amount of gaming, everything from Beatles Rock Band on 360 to World of Warcraft, but I balance this out with my weekly workouts, including DDR and my other grown-up things quotes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am not a poop sucker.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe that it is what makes us individuals to be different and that we can have different hobbies and interests different than others to enjoy life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of the activities that people think are normal drinking, playing pool, partying...
[SPEAKER_07]: I have not done, but I feel empty doing them even with others.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would rather not conform and do what I enjoy by myself than to feel empty.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there anything else I should say to him to back up my point?
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, in Idaho, what most consider normal is all outdoorsy stuff, floating, river hiking, camping, BSU football hunting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not from Idaho.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a Floridian.
[SPEAKER_07]: This email has been brought to you by Red Robin, the home of the delicious Chop House Burger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I'm fucking hungry for one of those Western chicken burger things.
[SPEAKER_07]: We went to Fed Records today.
[SPEAKER_07]: I ate an ostrich burger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yummy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fucking delicious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, first of all, I know a lot of Floridians.
[SPEAKER_07]: I lived about an hour from Pensacola, and a lot of them were rednecks.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, all the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just tell them, like, you know, flat out say, I'm an individual.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is... I'm not going to change myself to please you.
[SPEAKER_04]: If he's your fucking friend, he should understand that there's some fucking things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if they're hanging out and going to country bars, he's a friend of some sort.
[SPEAKER_04]: If he's your fucking friend, he should understand there are things you like to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not hurting anyone playing a video game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not doing nothing but playing video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're holding down a steady job.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not anyone's place to tell another person how to live their life.
[SPEAKER_07]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: but I think in return you should ask he should sit down and play a video game with you and try to find a game that you think he might like I mean you know your friend better than I do you might find that new Super Mario Brothers Wii is a game or maybe Call of Duty Modern Warfare is a game up to you my friend but if this guy's really your friend like
[SPEAKER_04]: And he should just take you as you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even if he's just a co-worker, then if he's a co-worker, then you get this whole other thing involved where if he's... It's to the point where he's annoying you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have every right to tell him to stop talking to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, like... Then again, that only really works in California.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean... And I would hate that you would have to go that far with it, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just...
[SPEAKER_04]: Encourage him to be more open-minded and just let him know, hey, there's nothing wrong with video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Modern Warfare made more money than most Hollywood movies do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it is an art form.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know this guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe Final Fantasy XIII and the stories would touch him in a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe some of his people that plays the deer hunter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which that game is actually kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next fucking email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear OLR, I finished Heavy Rain last Sunday.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wasn't affected by the PS3 clock glitch and was able to beat... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Beat off to and beat Heavy Rain with no problem at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, oh, oh, special person.
[SPEAKER_07]: To me, Heavy Rain is comparable to a show like Rescue Me, Mad Men, and Burn Notice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Burn Notice is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan likes Rescue Me.
[SPEAKER_07]: These are shows that would have been absolutely dull to me when I was a young teenager, but really deep and compelling now that I have matured into more adult tastes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you feel the same way?
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not shows that I enjoy, but I see why people like them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I said, Dan loves Rescue Me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like Dennis Leary.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think he's pretty hilarious.
[SPEAKER_19]: I watched the end of Nip Tuck this week.
[SPEAKER_19]: It went out with a fizzle.
[SPEAKER_19]: It was just like, eh, we give up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was really upset because there was no new RuPaul's Drag Race this week, but there was a new Project Runway, and I completely agreed with who they sent home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that what we're talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's talking about serious dramas dealing with issues that people don't like to talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there are certainly some shows I didn't really watch as a kid that I could fucking appreciate a little more now that maybe I couldn't appreciate because I was too young to understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure there were shows like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't think of anything off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a few shows though that grow up with you, if you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like watching freaking Rocky and Bullwinkle.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Beverly Hills 90210.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I can't watch that new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's such bullshit compared to the old one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fucking grew up with Brandon and Brenda.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they're my homeboys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought she was on the show now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think she did like a guest thing, but it's not the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now she's going to be on Dancing with the Stars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jenny Garth is on it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, some of them are on the show.
[SPEAKER_19]: There was one I watched...
[SPEAKER_19]: God, I watch some weird TV when I'm at home sometimes.
[SPEAKER_19]: I watch this show, Overhaulin'.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's basically one of those, you know, they take a car and soup it up type shows.
[SPEAKER_19]: And they did one for, what's his name, Ian... I don't remember the guy's name...
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I need help with DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seem to be unable to perform the blue button scratch consistently and effectively.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't matter which hand I use or whether the buttons are on the left or right of the turntable controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I fail on a consistent basis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are there any tips you can give me, Loki?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm surprised it's the blue one that you're having trouble with.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is that on the inside?
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of surprises me is that he has the same problem even if he flips.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first thing I would have said is play left-handed mode.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's probably the inside one, I'm guessing, because it's hard to get a grip on it.
[SPEAKER_19]: What you need to do is when you have your hand on the actual turntable is I normally put my thumb, I rest my thumb on the outside on the actual edge.
[SPEAKER_19]: of the turntable and use that to kind of move the turntable because if you just rely on the friction of your finger on that button, it's not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you have to keep your thumb held down to create that kind of friction there or it's too loose and you'll get all these scratches you don't really want.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to use your thumb to get the traction.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's where your problem comes in.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm afraid we're going to get a follow-up email like, I'm already doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then you just need to practice more.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might just have to take down, honestly, take down the difficulty.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might be playing on two, I think maybe you're, I don't know, I'm guessing maybe you're a long-time fan of Bomani, so you're trying to take it a little more aggressive.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been meaning to do this, but I haven't done it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been meaning to take, like... Aggressively.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an adverb.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fuck adverbs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, fuck you back.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need to take a metal plate or something like that and find the actual dead zones on each side.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's little dead zones where you can actually move the marker and it'll finally move all the way over to the left and right and just put a plate there so that basically it's just all center unless you go far right, far left.
[SPEAKER_19]: I hate it where you just don't go far enough or something like that and it doesn't register.
[SPEAKER_19]: That'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: I haven't fucking played DJ Hero in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really need to.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of disappointed.
[SPEAKER_07]: They dropped the price of them at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a ton of them there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really fucking disappointed they didn't support it better with more DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have two download packs.
[SPEAKER_19]: They are not trying at all.
[SPEAKER_19]: They're like, eh, we released a couple.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now we're going to release a new game.
[SPEAKER_19]: They better blow my hair back at E3 with DJ Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if I can finish the email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course you fucking can.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for taking my question and posting the podcast episodes in an expedient manner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stay care, Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: This message has been brought to you by the following words.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck, shit, ass, piss, bitch, dumbass, cocksucker, motherfucker, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are quite fucking welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that on our fucking wiki?
[SPEAKER_07]: For in-show jokes, this message has been brought to you by...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone add it right the fuck now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to be fucking honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't read the fucking wiki in a while, but I imagine it's getting updated tonight with the whole fuck show business.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was listening to last week's show and I heard Jamie state that she really did not want to discuss the crazy things going on with GameCrazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I couldn't figure out why until I found out her husband works for the company.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a store manager for GameCrazy in Colorado and I think it would be interesting to hear the opinions and thoughts on what's going on
[SPEAKER_07]: especially coming from someone who works in a different district and region.
[SPEAKER_07]: Personally, I am very concerned of what's going on, and it would be interesting to chat about it on your show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please do not use my name for obvious reasons, but please do respond.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love your show and look forward to downloading it every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks, someone!
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan!
[SPEAKER_07]: We need you for an editorial!
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie is summoning Dan to the OLR studio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell them to make them wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live radio, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's always a fucking mess.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do tape live Sunday nights at All Games Radio www.allgames.com where you can hear fucking train wrecks exploding live.
[SPEAKER_07]: They also did get to hear my Dan voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can understand though if you don't want to fucking talk about it because it's a fucking day job.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't want to put that shit at risk.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I would completely fucking understand if the answer is no fucking comment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we can ask him.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: A wild Dan has appeared.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got an email from a listener in Colorado who is a game crazy manager and wants to know.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sucks to be her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Him.
[SPEAKER_00]: Him.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he wants to know what your thoughts are on it being from a different region.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't want to say anything on the show, you don't have to.
[SPEAKER_00]: About what?
[SPEAKER_07]: About the closures and how you feel and about what might be happening.
[SPEAKER_00]: Being out of money sucks.
[SPEAKER_00]: and the store's closing sucks and if more of you fuckers would shop there instead of going to GameStop, maybe we could stay.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, it's not your guys' fault.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's your guys' fault.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's really not a lot to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: The economy's tough.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of good people have lost jobs.
[SPEAKER_00]: A lot of good people are hanging on.
[SPEAKER_19]: And Hollywood and movie gallery are really mismanaged.
[SPEAKER_19]: True that.
[SPEAKER_19]: On a corporate level.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's... Don't you work... I've dealt with movie gallery and they're like... No, no, exactly.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a company that like didn't catch on to trends that were stupidly obvious 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: and that honestly enough that maybe if the bankruptcy works out, which it won't, and any of the game crazes end up staying open, which they probably won't, it would be really nice that the gamers will still have an alternative.
[SPEAKER_00]: To anyone else who works for the company, hey, I'm there with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's rough.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't speak for them.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to show up every day.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm going to try to help my gamers and I recommend they do the same.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you have a Game Craze in your area and you haven't gone there, hey, visit it while it's there.
[SPEAKER_00]: Give it a chance and hopefully you'll like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: And if you don't, go to hell.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe we should do an SOS campaign.
[SPEAKER_07]: Save our stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I appreciate Dan's perspective because, you know, there are some people that when it comes to the day job, they'd be like, I ain't fucking touching that shit with a fucking 10-foot pole.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I appreciate Dan speaking openly and candidly on the topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, sweetie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Support not just independent radio, but support independent game stores.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though GameCrazy isn't necessarily independent, it's important to point out they're not Walmart and they're not GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's independent enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a fucking endangered species.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like a goddamn unicorn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the kind that Loki's been playing with all week on that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are there any more fucking... You know, I actually went and downloaded that song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Always, I wanna be you Hey, we got another one from G-Ditz Hello there, OLR, this is G-Ditz writing in I'm the Swedish dude who called in a few shows ago and talked about the DRM and seeing as how exams are closing in Did I read this one already?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't it really long?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you did He must have re-sent this
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, and we also got one from Rababa with the stuff about Portal and the boing boing boing, which we already talked about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Portal at Circuit City R.A.P.
[SPEAKER_07]: when it was released a la carte.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have to see what it's all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Viral marketing at its best.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, Orange Box is only like $19.99 now, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really fucking cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a fucking steal.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have an Xbox 360 or PC or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wish I had the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_19]: I just didn't play it a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moved on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I may go back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you fucking done with the fucking emails?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, then you should send us your fucking opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm replying to the GameCrazyGuy, so email him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd be fucking curious, you know, whatever you can read on the show, obviously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com if you want to send us some fucking emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, it's time to do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, we're still having them tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just because it's a fuck show doesn't mean we abandon this segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, OrangeBoxes1999.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1799Us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a big story to inspire this tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: As if the whole fucking reason for tonight's show weren't enough reason to be angry, let me give you a little something extra here.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Korean couple this week has made the news for neglecting their infant to the point where the infant starved because they were addicted to online games at internet cafes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you might want to take this with a grain of salt because it's coming from the sun, but still, sadly...
[SPEAKER_19]: But I trust the sun with all of its sunlight and nutrients.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the irony.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were raising a virtual toddler in a game called Prius Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty much Second Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: But while they were doing this, they'd leave their real one at home alone each day with just a bottle of milk for nourishment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, it's even worse than Clara from The Guild.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least, like, she's sitting in the same room with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: One day, they came home to find the child dead and called the cops, claiming that they found the kid dead when they woke up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Investigators found, though, that the child was dehydrated and decided that the couple's story was full of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just pathetic.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is all disgusting, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, what else can you say?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of sad you don't have to take an IQ test to reproduce.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, some days I really wish you had to take an IQ test in order to successfully have an orgasm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm almost there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm almost there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, what's two plus two?
[SPEAKER_04]: I forget.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, if that doesn't inspire some angst within you, then I don't know what else will.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what's your FU of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you whoever hacked my Gaia account.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, yeah, I had about, um, a million in gold stolen and some of my expensive items.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, yeah, I play on it as sort of like a little, oh, I'm wasting time thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just that, it's just shitty, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I want people to give me my money back, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just completely horrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really it, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that and having no time to get my stuff finished.
[SPEAKER_19]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm tired, so this isn't as heartfelt as it was in the beginning of the show, but fuck you to the asshole that stole my 360 and my mod chip and my $60 that was gonna pay for installing the mod chip.
[SPEAKER_19]: and wasting my entire day and making me have to drive down to Stockton.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because Stockton sucks and having to drive back from Stockton.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, I was so pissed off.
[SPEAKER_19]: And not only that, waiting four hours in a car in front of an apartment complex.
[SPEAKER_19]: Which I assumed was his.
[SPEAKER_19]: It might not be at this point.
[SPEAKER_19]: I am going to email him this week, though, to give him a chance.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe there was some misunderstanding.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe his phone fucked up and he just didn't get any of my messages at the very end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe not.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or maybe not, but hey, I'm going to give him an opportunity to ship me that console.
[SPEAKER_19]: If he doesn't, then I'm going to fucking post his email and his phone number all over the internet, so...
[SPEAKER_19]: Good fucking luck.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has an iPhone, I know that.
[SPEAKER_04]: He pissed off a radio show host, be warned.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have a lot of FUs this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually do have a big FU, but it's not one I want to state on the show because it's a sensitive matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just FU to feeling underappreciated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for the FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: More fuck show.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple of fucking stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, what do you got on deck?
[SPEAKER_19]: So, apparently there's some fucking new design for the DS cartridge that's come out in a patent filing.
[SPEAKER_19]: It looks like a new DS cartridge that's a little bit longer than the normal DS cartridge.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's got... I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_19]: It looks almost like a button or something on the end of the cartridge there.
[SPEAKER_19]: Maybe either for some sort of rewrite thing or possibly...
[SPEAKER_19]: God knows if you ask me, because it's hard to tell based just off this little picture, but people are thinking that maybe it's some sort of expansion device that they're making for the DSi or something like that to allow other peripherals that you might use on, say, for example, the Game Boy Advance slot, like maybe a new Guitar Hero type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what this makes me think of?
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is the Rumble Pack that they put out for Pokemon Pinball.
[SPEAKER_19]: um you know it kind of looks like to me almost like some sort of wireless card or something like that but the DS you know already has wireless on it um it's just that button on top it almost looks like a sink or some sort of device maybe a motion controller type thing something like that maybe the button resets you know the orientation or some shit like that who knows we'll find out later on when this actually comes out um whatever the hell it is that they're using this for oh I don't know maybe around E3 yeah
[SPEAKER_04]: It is shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I got one more fucking story for you guys and we're going to open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: The three minute rule is in effect tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phone calls will be limited to three minutes so that every fucking gamer can have a voice tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Valve Games are on their way to the Macintosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess there were some rumors about fucking Steam going to the Macintosh because of some fucking files that were found in the latest beta build.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Valve has basically hinted very strongly that the games are coming to the Mac.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess Doug Lombardi, the VP of Marketing over at Valve, actually kind of gave the official confirmation.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no release dates or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's pretty fucking understood that Team Fortress 2, Half-Life, Left 4 Dead, Portal, those are all big, big possibilities.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be noted Team Fortress 2 is used in some type of little campaign there that is kind of a parody of the Apple ads.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some fucking Mac users are going to be very fucking excited, especially with a game like Portal and all those games, really.
[SPEAKER_04]: Valve makes some pretty fucking awesome games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are all going to be worth playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they're pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: They're pretty cool Yep So even Loki can support that on the Mac More games for the Mac, Loki That's all you ever wanted, right?
[SPEAKER_19]: I didn't want anything for the Mac, and I don't care.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's why I didn't want to release more games to the Mac, because there are people that buy those PCs.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't understand why, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, make the money where they can.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to share, while Loki was reading his last fucking story, I ran out to the fucking car.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, the skyline's open.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead and call 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: I ran out to the fucking car to get more of these PETA chips, which I've become really fucking addicted to.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is a different brand.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are from Trader Joe's, and these are reduced guilt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're not as fatty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sea Salt Chips.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've gotten Jamie addicted to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh no, I almost bought myself some.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only is it the Stacy's brand is really good, but these are really good too.
[SPEAKER_04]: These are almost better in some ways than Trader Joe's ones.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they have cinnamon and sugar ones at Trader Joe's too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have cheddar.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have all the different flavors.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very fucking delicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I give props to Pita Chips.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, our calls are coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's kick it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to the Orange Launch Radio Fuck Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's, uh, fucking Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, fucking Spazinator, it's been a long fucking time.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the latest with you and Sony?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know, at least in my fucking opinion, uh, this whole, uh, clock, you know, fucking deal is, uh, you put another, you know, nail into the fucking coffin, so, uh, you know, it just seems like fucking Sony can't do anything right, so, um,
[SPEAKER_09]: But on a positive note, I did speak to a Sony rep not too long ago, and they gave me another story saying that, yeah, once I send my system in, if they have to send me another system, they'll reauthorize me to download all my videos.
[SPEAKER_09]: So with that being said,
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, did you start to say something there?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I was just going to say, at least they're offering that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That seems like fucking more than you got before.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, even with that being said, I would still say that the DRR pretty much fucking sucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: No one should have to go through this kind of BS every single time.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, something goes up and then it goes down.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, like I mentioned time and time before, you know, I'm so of a big Sony fan.
[SPEAKER_09]: As you mentioned, I tend to pimp out, you know, this, that, or dollar on your show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking PSN is in your fucking Twitter name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you are definitely a Sony fanboy, and that's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, you've been pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not, like, you've been fair.
[SPEAKER_04]: You give Sony a bad time when they deserve it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's kind of sad that Sony would be, you know, pissing off a loyal fan like you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't set my system in just yet because I'm a few bucks short to cover the repairs I should have all the money in place
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, good fucking luck to you, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to get out with the last few seconds you have tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, great fucking show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, really fucking appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great fucking night, my man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator, poor guy having the Sony troubles.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least they're offering to re-authenticate another system, but it's just such a big pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't things just work?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't electronics just work?
[SPEAKER_04]: You buy them and you fucking expect them to fucking work.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have any last minute stories to fucking get out there?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh wait, we got another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on one minute, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll let you jump in right after this call.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on the Orange Lounge Radio Fuck Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's Legend of Zaku watching the Oscars and doing this at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bunch of fucking sucking each other's dicks with these awards.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all know who's going to win.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't fucking matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: They bumped it up to ten movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a two movie race anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess the word fuck could probably apply to someone who probably some entity deserves it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Case in point, Activision.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's all spat that happened recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your take on the whole fucking thing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I knew it was on its way.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I knew it was going to happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a matter of when.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, the writing was on the wall when Infinity Ward...
[SPEAKER_14]: was actually next to dedicated servers for Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: You knew that it was something that they probably didn't want to do, but they had someone's hand probably force them.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's kind of... In other words, the way I see it is that... I don't know, I guess Activision's trying to bring forth the great video game crash that almost happened but never did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you talking about the one that happened in the 80s?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that really did happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: The way you see it is that you have a company that's literally saturating the market, basically trying to bleed all their franchises dry and just minimizing the amount of properties that sustain them.
[SPEAKER_14]: In other words, if
[SPEAKER_14]: If it only comes down to Tony Hawk, Call of Duty, Guitar Hero bringing their only bread and butter, that's kind of dangerous.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's going to cause another fucking video game crash, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the video game crash happened for so many other reasons.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, you get to the point where Guitar Hero is pretty much panned, no matter what new release comes out, because they already know it's going to be the same thing, same drivel.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not going to be worth the effort.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, the last two proved that point.
[SPEAKER_14]: And when Tony Hawk
[SPEAKER_14]: Tony Hawk Ride pretty much bombed for all intents and purposes.
[SPEAKER_14]: It goes to show that they're not innovating but just releasing the same thing and trying to nickel and dime people.
[SPEAKER_07]: No innovation, more renovation?
[SPEAKER_19]: I think they tried to innovate, it's just it sucked.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, yeah, it's just the fact that they're not trying anything original like EA.
[SPEAKER_14]: EA's learning their lesson already.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you see Mirror's Edge, Dead Space, Mass Effect, because they're actually realizing that you can't put...
[SPEAKER_14]: You can't milk the same cow over and over and expect the same result.
[SPEAKER_19]: It just came down to where they basically had their control system in place and it worked okay for Tony Hawk.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then Skate came out and had a slightly better control system.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's where EA basically knew how to innovate.
[SPEAKER_14]: They found a way to create a skateboarding game that was outside of the status quo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Outside of what Tony Hawk has offered.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you see right there, when you feel to innovate, the only thing you have is whatever you're able to market and whatever you're able to litigate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I gotta jump in and call time on the call because we're on three minute limit tonight, but thank you, Zaku, as always, for your perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a fucking great night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do appreciate Zaku's perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a gold fucking star for Zaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not hear much bam-bam-bamming on the keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard little taps, but no worse than when Jamie points the mic at her keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love you, mean it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Jamie, you had a last minute story for us tonight, speaking of which, while we wait for another call at 877-GAME-OLR on our fuck show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did, and it was... Oh, jeez, sounds awfully loud.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did, and it was when, actually, our good friend Marin left, posted today, and I thought it was really neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to share it.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is...
[SPEAKER_07]: There was a report that is about a guy named Roy Williams who played through Ocarina of Time blindfolded to write a guide on how to play the game only by using sound clues so that...
[SPEAKER_07]: A visually impaired player could beat the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so him and three other guys took two years to write this, but Jordan Werner, who was living in Ontario, beat the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that nice?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, I know we have some blind gamers listen to this show that, you know, often kind of talk about, you know, using the kind of the sound cues in the games and being able to kind of play the games that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's cool that people kind of go out of their way to write things with sound cues and so forth in these FAQs so that everybody can really enjoy video games in one way or another.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think it's a great story.
[SPEAKER_04]: The black guy is sassy
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry, it's just that he just comes out kind of sassy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to admit, Ranma, Barret was kind of a little bit fucking sassy too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Barret was freaking hardcore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Barret was a badass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saz is sassy in a different way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, dude, Ranma, he has a fucking chocobo living in his fucking afro.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there is, you sense that there is, like, again, I don't want to give story spoilers, but you sense that there is a definitely deeper story to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's not just completely transparent comic relief a la Janssen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jansen was kind of sassy in Lost Odyssey.
[SPEAKER_19]: Well, they never explained right away, at least where I'm at, why he's even with them right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but flashbacks will tell you a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's all Lost style, remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he's a little bit sassy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's better than Ranma...
[SPEAKER_04]: He's actually, I will say, he is my favorite character in the game right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because everybody else is, in my opinion, kind of such a stereotype of the Final Fantasy VII characters in a way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I really, I like him.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think he's really interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the Chocobo in the Afro is so fucking adorable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is he like RuPaul sassy or just sassy?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, he's not like... Is he cheeky?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's not like, bitch, you better work.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just the comic relief.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is he cheeky?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's a little bit cheeky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cheeky.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, when you say sassy, I think of your sassy pants.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a whole different kind of sassy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That makes me think, though, of RuPaul.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why, but RuPaul makes me think sassy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Tyra.
[SPEAKER_19]: He does say, and I had to laugh because of the lethal weapon reference, I'm getting too old for this.
[SPEAKER_19]: He does, he does.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still don't think that no one is going to ever top Cid for the attitude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sit your ass down in that chair and drink your goddamn tea.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Ranma, be happy because I think they actually have a black guy doing his voice.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I will soon find out because I don't know if you guys realize because Otakon is in a few fucking months and guess who's going to have to cosplay this guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: You are.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes, everyone's like, you have to cosplay this guy.
[SPEAKER_18]: And I'm like, oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma, he's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It goes far beyond the color of his skin.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's just a good character.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he has a fucking chocobo in his fucking afro, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now one more thing before I get the fuck out of here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that make it a chocofro?
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, hurry the fuck up, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Time's almost up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can I borrow somebody's fucking Xbox 360 for the next few fucking weeks?
[SPEAKER_18]: Because we pre-ordered fucking FFXIII and the roommate's going to be playing it, so you know what that means.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm going to need to get the Jaws light to get him off it, but if I try to get him off, he's going to kick my fucking ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Loki might be able to let you fucking borrow one of the broken ones, but in the meantime, I think you better... Well, the broken ones aren't going to really help him.
[SPEAKER_04]: You better let... What the fuck?! !
[SPEAKER_04]: You better put a call out to the New York City OL Army, and I know there's a lot of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any fucking extra Xboxes out there, help a brother out.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's what's up, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma, gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Time's up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a fucking great night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranma's gonna come hang out with me this summer, and so is... Hold on, we're on another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to the fuck show.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Amiga fucking 777.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Amiga fucking 777.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the fuck is on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_15]: Motherfuckin' PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's, uh, or the Dreamcast killer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, uh, it, it, it killed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We know it killed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Amiga, what could the Dreamcast, do you think, in retrospect, what could the Dreamcast have done to save itself?
[SPEAKER_15]: Gotten someone who was more skilled in marketing, I guess.
[SPEAKER_15]: Someone that could have said, you know...
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, when it comes to porting or whatnot, you know, the PlayStation 2 kind of isn't so good on this.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, you know, our port of this particular game is looking better or something like that.
[SPEAKER_19]: You're in no way related to the Legend of Zaku by any chance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you high?
[SPEAKER_15]: Knock it off.
[SPEAKER_15]: Be nice.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I just got a quirky voice.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So do I. I was just going to say, though, if you were high, then you've got one of those really cool stoner voices.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I seriously think there are certain people who just have really cool stoner voices.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: There are some nice games, but a lot of the good games didn't really show up until it was almost halfway to when its successor came around.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: No Fantavision?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I love Fantavision.
[SPEAKER_19]: Fantavision, what the heck, man?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really quickly, we don't have a lot of fucking time left, but since you said you're a fan of Final Fantasy X, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XIII, you think you're going to be on board with that, or fuck it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, hell no.
[SPEAKER_15]: I am not interested in any next generation consoles.
[SPEAKER_15]: I have put up my wall here with the GameCube, PS2, Dreamcast, and maybe when I get another job, Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Props to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's still a lot of great games to discover from the last generation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XII, really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dragon Quest VIII, really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: All towards the end of that cycle before the news consoles came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, Amiga, gotta let you go, but just before I do, I just want to say, mod files for life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to the Orange Lounge Radio Fuck Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they hung up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, fuck them then.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they probably were trying to redial so fast to get in that they... Yeah, here it comes again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome to the Orange Lounge Radio Fuck Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yellow there, oh lord.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is that...
[SPEAKER_10]: Other Swede.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get it, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Other Swede.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should have... Like, you know how, like... And I'll credit this on your minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how we have the tester on PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need to have, like, a throwdown contest on who gets to be the official OLR Swede.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we might have to... I have something to say, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel a bit stupid in the sense that, well, I've missed that call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you've heard, but we do this thing called a podcast, and you can download old episodes and listen to them whenever you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Aki Ripper, I would love to bring the two Swedes together.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe G... What's his name?
[SPEAKER_04]: GK... G-Ditz.
[SPEAKER_04]: G-Ditz.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe G-Ditz will email us and let us know the next episode he'll be listening, and we can have our Swede-off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_04]: I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: An old-fashioned game of OLR match game.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can have the Swede-off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Misty has a good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking brilliant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ake Ripper is the original Swede.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do get dibs on being first, so nobody can take that away from you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was calling in about apparently something I think you've already discussed on the first hour, but still.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new Ascent expansion!
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I fucking touched on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, did you hit on this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The newest Sims expansion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking forward to it as soon as I can get my old ones to run.
[SPEAKER_04]: Akira Ripper's way too excited about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about the new Sims expansion.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the expansion is called Sims Ambition, and it was all like, uh-huh, in a kind of way, but still, it's like, yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: The only ambition though that they don't have in there is the ambition to be a porn star or stripper, so I'm really not interested in this expansion at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, well, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe... My ambition is to host a crappy podcast on the internet for eight years of my life.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or maybe they strive to be my wall slave.
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, the person that I trap inside my wall of death.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or drown in my pool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have like a saw house in there?
[SPEAKER_19]: No, that's what I do in my Sims games.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's basically, you know, you create a wall or room around the people and you starve them to death.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got to ask Aki Ripper, time's almost up, so I got to ask Aki Ripper, anything else you want to say about The Sims or anything else before we let you go, my friend?
[SPEAKER_10]: I tried to play Sims 2 since last week, and I played for like a half hour, and then, no, I'm going back to Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least now we know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, really quickly, in one word, in one word, Aki Ripper, why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: It wasn't all like, uh, what the oof?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's more than one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's more than one word, but that's okay, we'll let it go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, HockeyRibber, take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the oof?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did he say oof?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think was the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love Swedish people, I really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I swear to God I've got to visit Sweden before I die at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least when they open the ABBA museum, if nothing else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mamma Mia, by the way, the big play based on ABBA songs, because the Swedish people love it whenever Sweden gets brought up by Bring Up ABBA.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, uh, the Mamma Mia play is coming to San Jose in 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I have a friend that works for the, um, uh, the production company that puts all this on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, hey, I really want to, um, I really want to, uh, go to this play.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my friend's like, why do you fucking love such a shitty show?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, cause it's ABBA, shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR if there's any more phone calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meanwhile, Loki, do you have any other last minute stories for us while we wait for the phone to ring?
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm so disappointed that all my Oscar picks would have won and I would have probably won money.
[SPEAKER_19]: God, this will just teach me that I need to submit my Oscar picks when I actually do them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Stop being so fucking lazy.
[SPEAKER_19]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: Agent X-Link Hey, how the fuck are ya?
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's kind of hard at first.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was drooling for the first couple of days looking like a fucking idiot.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, hey, you know, you live, you learn, you do it very slowly.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, you know, and it got me a lot of time to catch up on a few games and such.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I had a friend that had to have that done kind of young, like in the early 20s.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much, you know, it's great to hear that the DRM is finally cracked so this way during hurricane season I can sit down with my laptop and play Assassin's Creed 2 and not worry about being connected onto a fucking internet feed 24-7, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I would give PS2 nothing but love for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I mean, a system that doesn't break or go down for two and a half days when there's certain leafy issues with other consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like, though, that we kind of get the back-to-back calls about PS2 love versus PS2 hate.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not hate, just, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you know, there's a shitload of games for PS2 right now I'm still going through.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I can't even start to sit here and tell you how many games I've got to go through for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sitting right across, I haven't even touched, or I went halfway through, and, you know, and I still have a lot of them, and I'm planning on going through them before I even consider to get a PS3 or anything like that, because, you know, that's going to be more...
[SPEAKER_01]: On my list, so I mean, you know, between that and my PSP and my PC games, I'm pretty much set for probably about almost a year, give or take.
[SPEAKER_04]: It does have one of the fucking largest libraries of video games just ever, and it's not stopping.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, if you listen to Japanese release dates, there is still fucking shit coming out for it now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but unfortunately the American version, though, is slowing down, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_19]: They actually have a Sakura Wars game that was coming out on PlayStation 2, getting the nice little collector's edition treatment to that.
[SPEAKER_19]: In April, there's going to be the Lord of the Rings Aragons quest, you know, Lord of the Rings for kids.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much that's it, unless you're talking about maybe a few EA games.
[SPEAKER_19]: Even EA is cutting them out now for sports stuff, at least.
[SPEAKER_19]: Madden probably will have a PS2 version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotta jump in here because X-Links three minutes are up, but quickly, do you have any other quick final thoughts for us?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nope, that's pretty much about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I had to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, feel better soon, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you on WoW.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I feel better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I think that's gonna do it for the Skyplane tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a lot of listeners in tonight, so thank you guys very much for the phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you didn't get through, sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really fucking sorry, but you have to send us a fucking email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnsRadio.com I know Loki's been fucking waiting to do some last-minute fucking stories, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: There's some interesting information.
[SPEAKER_19]: Apparently, Batman Arkham Asylum is getting the Game of the Year edition, which was supposed to be coming out over in the U.S., and as far as I'm aware, still is coming out over in the U.S., unless they've already announced that they're not.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_19]: 3D that will allow you to view the game in 3D and doesn't rely on red and blue lenses meaning the colors are preserved and apparently will work with HD and standard definition sets which, you know, if that works now, I think they should that sounds like a good idea, sounds cheap speaking of good ideas coming from Warner Brothers, okay, well I'm being sarcastic here they're in talks now to produce a Space Invaders movie
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, the movie industry has run out of ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least they could do whatever the fuck they wanted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's not like there's this big fucking plot to Space Invaders.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aliens are invading Earth!
[SPEAKER_04]: Shoot them!
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, so Space Invaders, apparently they're speculating that the film will be a big budget action blockbuster movie.
[SPEAKER_19]: Helm by some prolific director Sony has filed some patents for game demos apparently that will lose feature over time Which I have to say is the worst idea ever Can't you just fucking re-download it?
[SPEAKER_19]: well maybe you won't be able to maybe it's going to be like those time trials you know on Windows and stuff like that and why should I have to fucking re-download say if I want to show a demo I play a demo say for a game that you may not be getting a lot of press or whatever and I want to show my friends like for example Wet Wet I thought the demo was fucking awesome and I showed my friends and they got excited about it if I have to play the game again and the features are removed that's going to be pretty disappointing well it was cool the first time I played it
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, what you have to do is you have to make another PlayStation profile and have your friend sign in to play.
[SPEAKER_20]: No, not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um, apparently Ubisoft is looking to take on Tony Hawk, which shouldn't be too difficult.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh, at this point, and they're going to put out Sean White skateboarding.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yes, Sean White, um, apparently skateboards as well.
[SPEAKER_19]: And, uh, unfortunately though, in the screenshot that they have of Sean White snowboarding, looks like a Geico caveman.
[SPEAKER_19]: So I don't know what's going on there because he certainly doesn't look like a Geico caveman, um, normally.
[SPEAKER_19]: Um,
[SPEAKER_19]: and yes, so they're going to be releasing that game apparently and most likely on the Wii because that's where the last one came.
[SPEAKER_19]: Test Drive Unlimited is getting a sequel coming out apparently this fall to PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_19]: And apparently the sequel will also have new elements including day-night cycles, weather effects, and vehicle damage.
[SPEAKER_19]: And hopefully the cops will figure out how to chase you down when you drive off the road.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently our chatters are not big fans of my Muppet voice, which I guess is what that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fucking Shaoran in chat says, so is next show the Muppet show or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi-ho, Kermit the Frog here, and welcome to the OLR Muppet show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Muppet babies.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had that happen a couple episodes ago.
[SPEAKER_19]: Ake Ripper is the Swedish chef.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Swedish chef is racist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't appreciate your racist joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listen, frog!
[SPEAKER_20]: So yeah, that's... The OLR Muppet Show is all about moi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, I fucking made Loki shut the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, I'm just rolling my eyes, and unfortunately you can't hear that on the radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know you people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, you do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hiding.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're my BFF.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts tonight because believe it or not, we're at the end of the fucking show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you enjoyed your fucking selves tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a pretty fucking good time and I'm sure we said the F word a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll get a count after the podcast goes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't fucking know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't put a lot of fucking effort into it, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the beginning of the show, I had a lot more fucks in the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a...
[SPEAKER_04]: You get tired after a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't just have to fucking be on iTunes, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just tell a fucking friend, you know, in real life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Project Real Life, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell some fucking friends what you heard on Orange Launch fucking radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And tell friends to listen to shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you might want to not have them fucking start with this episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, this should be, like, maybe the fourth episode you listen to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't have this be somebody's fucking first episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just tell your fucking friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all we fucking got because we're an independent fucking podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and get everybody's fucking final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Sakura, what's your fucking final thought?
Fuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your fucking final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: We'll have to see where this thing goes with this guy ripping me off.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very annoying.
[SPEAKER_04]: And my fucking final thought tonight is Sassafras.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck.
[SPEAKER_17]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_17]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_17]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week