Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura
Sky and the Loco King
Tonight, September 13, 2009
You can emulate Commodore 64 on your iPhone, then you can't
An intentional glitch outs pirates of a popular game
And a popular franchise's sequel gets canned in Japan
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture
And the gamer lifestyle
Here with you over the next three hours, live every Sunday night on All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
My name is Rob Roberts, here with you for the next few hours
Also with me as well, say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Beer
What kind of beer tonight?
250th Anniversary Guinness
And what makes it so dang special?
Because it's 250th Anniversary Guinness
Oh, also say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hello
How are you, Loki?
I'm good
Alright, now of course before we get into gaming weeks usually
We somehow start off the show as Orange Lounge Radio Foodio
And tonight is no exception to the cause here
Loki, what the hell did you bring with you tonight because
I have to admit it actually looks kind of disgusting
I brought parts of Bacon Fest 2009
As Nellie would call it, it was the bacon themed birthday party
Some of the food that we serve there
Including bacon muffins
Which they're cornbread muffins
That have a little
I'm seriously looking at all this food, oh my god
It's just too much, it's too much
Don't get me wrong, I love bacon
But this is too much bacon
Bacon is meat candy
Ok, sorry to interrupt
Anyways, so it's
Ok, let me just run down the list here
The bacon muffins, they're basically cornbread muffins
It initially had a little bit of reserved bacon fat in there
To give it the kind of bacon flavor
And there's bacon inside of it
And then Nellie decided that they didn't quite taste like enough bacon
And she
Originally when I made them, I bought the wrong size tins
So I only made like 10 muffins
And I'm like, you can't eat any of those because we only have 10 muffins
So there's a piece of the muffin mix or whatever that had fallen into the bacon grease
And she snatched it up and ate it
And she's like, mmm that's good, you should rub all of them into the bacon grease
So we rolled the top of them really quickly into the bacon grease
To give it a little bit of extra bacon flavor
And then on top of it is like cream cheese, hot sauce, green onion, and bacon
It's kind of like a spicy, I don't know, frosting almost
And then we made these pancetta cups with mac and cheese inside of them
Just mainly because we couldn't think of anything good to fill inside of them
Ok
And they're ok
I'm about to eat one and just for the record
I have yet to touch the bacon food
This is actually funny because I was going to be
I had said I was giving up bacon and I had decided I'm going to do it tomorrow
So this is great because I can now make myself completely sick of bacon
Why give it up now when you can procrastinate to tomorrow
Especially with all these bacon temptations in front of you
Nom nom nom
I don't know, I've got to admit
I'm a little over bacon being the food of worship
Like, you know, bacon's kind of been the in-food for years and years now
I think we need to move on to a new food of worship
Like, what about the jelly bean?
I don't see enough appreciation for jelly beans out there
It has to be jelly bellies
Alright, forget it
And then the last one is shrimp wrapped in bacon with barbecue sauce
And mozzarella cheese broiled on top of it
But it's actually, the shrimp's pretty good
We ate mostly the shrimp
And then I had candied bacon
It was with, you know, brown sugar
You know, kind of caramelized on top of it and stuff
That I meant to put on ice cream so we'd have bacon ice cream
But everybody ate the bacon, you know, the candied bacon
Before I got a chance to bring out the ice cream
Now sadly I missed Bacon Fest because it conflicted with my dad's birthday
And I had a friend from out of town who I hadn't seen in years who was visiting
But thank you to Loki and Nellie for bringing a little piece of it here
It was very nice
I will try at least one of the bacon shrimp things
That looks kind of good
They're pretty good
And then Irene and Nathan brought these like mashed potato ball things that have like bacon and stuff
So I don't, I haven't tried those
But everyone liked those I think
Alright let's go to our chat room
Yes we do talk about video games occasionally on this show
But let me go to the chat room and introduce them
Howdy guys at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
They're always with us, the EverPresence fourth guest on the show
Tigerclaw says you guys should take a picture of this and post on the OLR Gallery
We are one step ahead of you sir
Dark Sakura I think already did that
They should be on their way up to the OLR Gallery
So if you want to check out the food
Go to orangelaungeradio.com
Click on I think it's galleries and you'll see
If you're smart you'll figure it out
Click on like pictures or galleries
I don't have it in front of me
And then you can find the bacon stuff that Loki brought
Sadly the one thing that wasn't there was super bacon
Just because I thought I had plenty of bacon
And I actually ran short of bacon
I had bought like five packages of bacon
And it was still not enough
Salaciouspopnchat says popcorn jelly bellies equal vom
The chat room by the way is called Kevin
I just want to point out though that I actually like the popcorn jelly beans quite a bit
But my favorite is toasted marshmallow
Jelly Belly makes a toasted marshmallow jelly bean that is delicious
In honor of Bacon Fest
The chat room is called Kevin
I'm very sorry I did not refer to them by their proper name
I still don't understand this whole renaming the chat room to names of people you know
You are Kevin!
Fine
Alright there you go
So okay I'm going to try one of these bacon shrimp things
Even though my pancreas hurts just looking at it
Dear God
Well that's two of them
There's two of them
You need to separate that
Okay here we go
Careful and chew carefully because like you said it's a little choke-y
This is not good radio
Sorry
It's delicious radio
It takes a while to chew through because unfortunately the bacon did not crisp up as well as I'd like to
It's pretty darn good
But no one seemed to care because you know
It's delicious
It's good but damn
This is probably all I'm going to have
I'm going to have another piece of shrimp
You guys can see in the picture gallery and even if you're listening on the podcast you can go on the website
I'm sure it'll still be there
You can go in that picture gallery and look and it's too much
It's too much
Yes there is a such a thing as too much bacon and it is sitting in front of us tonight
The important thing today Rob is that all I've had is a salad so I could safely eat this bacon
But tomorrow no more pork
See I'm already a little full because I had wings topped today which is not good
Oh my God all the weight I've worked so hard to lose I'm getting right back today
Alright
I'll move it out of here if you'd like
At some point we're going to need to do that
That's right not right now
Let's get into our gaming week
We should talk about video games that is what we do here on this show
Dark Sakura what type of video games have you been playing this week?
I don't know what type of games
Enough with the bacon
Put the bacon down step away from the bacon
Do you want me to have Loki go first?
Loki how was your gaming week?
My gaming week was awesome
Well you know played the usual stuff New Grand Theft Auto what not
Also got around to playing a little bit of Scribblenauts which it's alright
But I haven't really gotten past the tutorial stuff yet because I've only played it for a little bit
I've been busy messing with the little front end thing where you can spawn wherever you want and stuff
And let me tell you and I know this really sucks to say it but oh my god does it get old after 5 minutes
And you know that is really sad
I knew it I knew that's what was going to happen with this game
I haven't played it yet so I just you know it's one of those things I think it's like the Nintendogs of this year
It's like one of those things is going to be cute as hell for 30 minutes
And then you're going to be like okay I did all the lolsy things I wanted to do
And pretty much and you know I'm sure the puzzles and stuff are going to be fun
I haven't quite gotten there yet because I'm still doing the fucking tutorial stuff which is annoying
But just as far as messing with stuff it's kind of boring
And the other thing that I don't really care for in it is the control
The control you have to use the stylus and you click to where you want Maxwell to go
And it's so non-responsive it's just ah it really bugs me
But it's cool I guess you know that you can spawn all these different things
But like you know they've got like 2200 words or something in this
But a lot of the other words just you know create the same thing
If you type in any type of dog it just makes this generic looking dog or something
Now you're getting called out a little bit in chat from our good friend Bobby
Who's on Before Us on All Games Radio on Sunday nights
Black Wolf says so Loki played with the playground and not the actual game and called it old
Well I'm telling you what I played
I'm just saying I thought I'd be able to play this playground part
And just you know have a lot of fun with it for quite a while
Because I mean dude I made a cat
Well first thing I did was I did what the ESRB had
You know where they said you can lure a lion with you know meat strapped to a baby
So I strapped meat to a baby and you know lured a lion with that and that was kind of funny
And then I strapped the laser to a cat and tried to make a laser cap
But that didn't work because you know it just it didn't know what I wanted to do
But yeah I'm sure the puzzles are fun but like I said I haven't played there yet
And I'm just saying what this is my impression so far
It's a really quick impression but yeah it's not as much fun as I thought it would be
Fair enough I guess
Now the other thing too this week is I finally finally finally got my arcade cabinet
So I went down to the San Jose and picked up my Astro City candy cab
And brought it home and also with that I got a
Was it an MVS Neo Geo board a single slot with a 48 in one
Which I'm sure is absolutely not legit one bit
48 in one Neo Geo cart that's got a lot of King of Fighters and Metal Slug and whatnot on there
But you know basically I have that to hold me over until I finish my main computer and all that stuff
But it's kind of cool so I'm putting that all together
And actually going to be painting the whole thing black
So I have to do that as well because it's kind of scuffed up
And I tried to find a white paint or something that might match it
But I mean you can't match the color of the plastic there so it's just easier to paint the whole thing black
So yeah and I've got some pics on my live journal right now of just the cabinet
It's kind of taken apart a little bit the control panel wasn't on there
I had to re-screw that back on there because they gave me like two different control panels
None of which were the one I wanted but you know it's fine for now
And then I plan on getting the correct one later because I wanted a two player both with six buttons
But I have a two player with three buttons on each and a one player with six buttons
So whatever it'll work for now
And what other stuff did I have to do
Oh yeah I had to get a new halogen or not halogen a fluorescent light for the marquee
And of course it's some special fluorescent light that they don't make over here in the United States
You know because most of them are standard size like 12 inch, 18 inch, 24
This was 22 and 3 eighths so I had to go order that specially online from Atlanta
And they had apparently some of these Toshiba fluorescent lights so I had that
Now you are still taking late donations for your cabinet
Oh yeah definitely
Okay good because I never donated
I was going to do it on Friday but I got sidetracked so I'm going to give you a late donation
I still got lots of stuff I got to get online
I'm planning on actually rebuilding my DDR pads
And I have an email to channel Beat about Dance Maniacs sensors
Because I have the actual Dance Maniacs machine
I have two upper sensors but I need two lower sensors
And if I can get them for a good price I'm going to buy them from them
Now where did you put all these machines are you putting them in your garage?
Well I don't have a Dance Maniacs machine I have the motherboard inside of it
Right but you used to have your candy cab where's that going?
The candy cab is in the garage right now but it's going to go in the middle of the room
I'm taking the HDTV and there's an HDTV and a Stanford in the room right now
So you have to put the toys in the middle of the bedroom so the wife can close the door and not see it?
Well she doesn't close the door I just wanted it in there because that's where I'm going to put my DDR pads
And that's going to take up a lot of space
I could put it in the garage and that would be fine going through the winter
But in the summer fuck no it's like 100 degrees inside there I'd die
Yeah it's even worse than the studio where we were taping at my house
It's quite pleasant today though
Yeah it's nice today
Alright so that's it for your gaming week
That's it
Dark Sakura now that she's done with her bacon
Mmm bacon
My gaming week was a marathon session of Beatles Rock Band
Which I really loved I had a great time playing especially doing harmony
Because everybody doesn't have to do all the harmony but you get more bonuses if you harmonize properly
And I had a really good time with that that was a lot of fun except that my hands started hurting after a while playing some of the guitar
I was going to say I forgot I also did play the Beatles Rock Band and Rock Band 2
Did you know actually and this is kind of neat I just tried it because I wasn't sure if it worked
That the old Karaoke Revolution mics from the Playstation 2 actually work on the 360 version of Rock Band
Did you know the Lips mics also work on it?
I didn't know if they patched that stuff in yet but I know they were supposed to be getting patched in soon
Well we cause Dan made it out of his conference with a double set of Lips mics
And so we used those we had a really good time I thought it was great
So you guys both feel, no you kind of already gave your review last week Loki and you said
I'm not a fan of the Beatles so I'm not as yippy about this but I see where people are getting excited about it
Yeah it was alright but I think we came away with it like wow the Beatles had some really tripped out shit in there
Their songs were weird because we had Nathan singing this stuff and he's just like holy crap I didn't know that they had these weird songs
But after about maybe 10 minutes of it we were just like ok let's go to Rock Band 2 because we just got tired of it
But Dark Sakura is someone who is more of a Beatles fan you were like yay I'm in heaven
I was like dude I want my other songs in here because like the songs that I most wanted in there weren't there
Well a lot of the ones that I really liked like some of my favorite songs are like
Dear Prudence was in there which is one of my favorites and which is actually really easy and fun to sing
It's the only one I beat on Expert and then Something was on there which is another one I like
And we also the theme was we had a discussion on who had the better hair and we all agreed that George Harrison had better hair
Now quick question have you explored download content because you know some of it's there
We just rented it because Dan with a button didn't pre-order it for me
But the one song that I would have most liked in there I know it would make zero sense to put it in there
Because the only thing you could do on it would be vocals unless you could mimic violin on the guitar controller
Or something would be Eleanor Rigby which is my favorite Beatles song
There were really some fun ones in there like Taxman was in there and I think I saw She Came in Through the Bathroom Window
Which is a cool song
A lot of stuff you know but of course then I had to go and listen to all the stuff that Tiare gave me
So I actually listened to Rubber Soul like three times all the way through
I feel so uncool I'm like the only person that didn't play Beatles Rock Band this week
Because my ex and granted it's my own damn fault my Xbox 360 is still broke and I need to go get it fixed
I just you know I've just been complacent doing all this other stuff and I've just been busy with some other things in my personal life
So I haven't really gotten out to get it fixed but I'm not gonna re-buy the instruments just for the PS3 version
No I have all these money invested in instruments on the 360 that's where I want to get Beatles Rock Band
So I'm just a little behind and by the time I'm ready to play it there'll probably be nobody left playing it online
Well I also like I'm doing right now play Sims 3 because I love Sims 3
And it's actually really easy to run it during the show because I have to always be doing something
I also, what else did I play? No I don't think I played, I was gonna play a Dreamcast game and I didn't
You know, thought about it, didn't do it, played some Pinball
I go back to work Monday
Sucks to be you
Oh I played Peggle, lot of Peggle, lot of Peggle
My gaming week was not quite as exciting as Dark Soccer or Loki's, I had pretty mellow
I played a lot of World of Warcraft, don't judge, haters gonna hate
But I'm playing Alliance this time because I was Horde for years
Yeah I played that too
Good, I'm glad now instead of calling me an addict you're like oh okay yeah I'm addicted too
I'm not addicted, I played twice
Clearly I have issues because I'm already like level 24 but I have some friends that are playing so whatever
It makes it go by faster, and I'm sure these people are gonna be like you could have gotten your Xbox fixed
But you've been playing World of Warcraft, don't judge me
Let's see what else, I've been playing, I have been playing some stuff on the Playstation as well
Just kind of mostly the same stuff, Wipeout and Home, even I got some more invites to the club on there taken care of
So if you were waiting for that then you probably got that, and yeah just kind of playing that stuff
Oh and also Rock Band Unplugged on the PSP, that's probably been the game I've been playing more than any other console game
Is that, and it's difficult, it's way harder than regular Rock Band
I'm sorry some of those note patterns are really tough to do with the four buttons
So I can see where Rock Band Unplugged definitely polarizes audiences
But I'll tell you what, after having been missing frequency and amplitude for so long it's kind of cool to have this
I do miss the techno music, but Rock Band Unplugged has a decent song list
So I'm satisfied
Alright well that's gonna do it for our gaming weeks, so let's get into our housekeeping tonight
In tonight's housekeeping, there may or may not be a show next week
I'm thinking, and I kind of have to ask this live on air, no? No show? Are you out?
I'm out
Okay so then we're not gonna do it
I have stuff that needs to get done on Sunday night
Okay then fine, cause I was gonna suggest we could do it late cause my flight gets in at 5.30 so maybe we could start the show at 7
But we'll just not do it then if you have stuff going on too
So free night for Loki, woo, I gotta work in the cabinet, woo, woo
But the problem is I am also going to be out the first weekend of October
So I'll have to figure something out for that, where you guys can do it without me or something
Cause we don't want to miss too many shows, or we pre-taped that week or something, maybe we can do that
Yeah
Alright so yeah, there's gonna be no show next Sunday so just brace yourself for that and have a good week without us here
Alright, that's it I guess for housekeeping, otherwise you can always follow us on Twitter
We're OLR on Twitter, we're OLRME on Facebook, it's a club so you have to search for OLRMY
And Orange Lounge on LiveJournal, although I don't think we've posted to LiveJournal in about a year, but it's there
I should cross post some of mine
You should actually cross post some of it to Orange Lounge, it'd be nice to see that being updated, so there you go
Alright, let's get into some gaming news already and some long discussion tonight
Loki's gonna start us off with a four part story
Yes, well speaking about Twitter, apparently Courtney Love has one
And she wasn't too happy about some stuff that went down with a deal that she had with Activision
Regarding Kurt Cobain's appearance in Guitar Hero 5
Apparently, and this is her two posts that she had on Twitter
For the record, this Guitar Hero shit is breach of contract on Bully's part
And there will be a proper addressing of this and retraction
And then she followed up with, we're gonna sue the shit out of Activision
We being the trusty estates, the LLC, and the various LLCs, Cobain Enterprise
This is gonna be a completely unrelated statement, but I just have to get this off my chest
Isn't this fascinating that we live in a world now where Twitter is like a late breaking news source
And a lot of the reason why is because celebrities on Twitter are unfiltered
They're not going through their publicists and writing things like this
Like I don't know why, but like seven years ago when we started this show we would never have a story like this
But now it's kind of weird that we're reading about Courtney being pissed off like through her Twitter
It's just weird that Twitter is like this news source all of a sudden
Here's my thing
Why the hell is anyone reading CourtneyLovesTwitter?
I mean seriously
She has fans
Who?
She does?
Like convicts? I mean who?
I don't know
You know what? I will say this
When I was in high school, I was a senior in high school
We participated in the lip sync contest
You know how they do the lip sync contest at high school?
I'm sure your high school did one, like all high schools did this right?
So we decided to make a mockery of the whole thing, me and my two friends
And I dressed up as Courtney Love
And we did what's the song called?
Violet by Hole?
Go on take everything
And you know I had a wig and I wore this really trashy outfit and everything
Yes it's like one of the few times in my life where I've cross dressed outside of Rocky Horror
And let's see
Then one of my other friends put his long hair in pigtails and pretend to play the bass
And then our other friend dressed up like a Japanese schoolgirl and ran out on stage with these random signs
Like it was the most random anti lip sync thing you did
Because everybody else was doing like lollipop lollipop
And all this stupid shit and all dressed and clear cut
And here we are going out on stage in drag singing Violet
And it was all kinds of awesome
You know how we did? We got last place
Last place
Thank you Courtney Love
I was a hot ass Courtney Love though
I will just put that out there
Well they did have a picture of Courtney Love on Kotaku during one of the stories
It actually was one of the good pictures of her
I'm like wow she was hot at one time
What the fuck happened there?
I'm guessing a lot of drugs but you know
Anyways back to the story
So she was pissed off that you know Kurt Cobain is totally
Mainly the thing that they're pissed off about is
And I'm sure you've seen plenty of videos regarding this
Apparently these characters or these artists can be unlocked
As playable characters in the game
So therefore you can make them sing any retarded song that's in this game
Including I think they had one that had Flava Flav in it
So they had the clip of course of Kurt Cobain
You know lip sync to Flava Flav
And I mean that's just blasphemy right there
Activision responded of course after these stupid Twitter updates
Saying that Courtney Love signed a contract for this
And you know tough luck
Because they aren't in breach of contract
And then of course then her publicist I guess
Released a statement I guess it was
Oh I'm sorry then I have publicist
Other band members from Nirvana
They said this is a statement regarding Nirvana
Guitar Hero and the likeness of the late Kurt Cobain
We want the people to know that we are dismayed and very disappointed
In the way a facsimile of Kurt is used in Guitar Hero
The name and likeness of Kurt Cobain are sole property of his estates
We have no control whatsoever in that area
While we are aware of Kurt's image being used with the two Nirvana songs
We didn't know that the players have the ability to unlock the character
This feature allows a character to be used with any kind of song the player wants
We urge Activision to do the right thing in relocking Kurt's character
So that this won't continue in the future
It's hard to watch an image of Kurt pantomiming other artists alongside cartoon characters
Kurt Cobain wrote songs that hold a lot of meaning to people all over the world
We feel he deserves better
You read that about as enthusiastically as I feel about it
Just so you know
Well here's the thing, they have no say in it
They didn't sign any contracts, they're just giving their piece about it
They're just throwing gasoline on the fire basically
And then of course Cobain's attorney
Basically saying the same thing that they want them to kind of
Relock the character so that he can only sing certain songs or something like that
Which I can tell you right now is not going to happen
It's not going to happen because Guitar Hero 5 is out on the Wii right?
Whoops! We can't patch games on the Wii
You're fucked
So it's just not going to happen
They said that they, you know, of course they know that they signed the agreement
But they didn't know that he was going to be used in that way
That kind of thing
This says it all right here
Exactly where this whole thing is coming from
They signed the agreement but didn't know that it was going to be used in that way
And here's the thing, I'm sorry, go ahead
Because I have a rant on this
I think that's actually it
Good
Here's the thing
Obviously there's multiple sides to every story
But having covered this crap as long as we have
You know, I think, I think
I have a pretty good idea what's going on here
And I'm probably wrong and I'm pulling this out of my ass
It's complete speculation
But here's my thought
When this was shown to the people that it needed to be shown to
They didn't show the clip of Kurt Cobain doing Flavor Flav
They didn't say anything about Kurt Cobain being an unlockable character in the game
They probably showed clips of Kurt Cobain doing the actual Nirvana songs
And then, you know, the proper signatures were obtained or what have you
Although I hear that Courtney Love, like, she signed it then she resisted it
You know, even before this
That she didn't want to approve the likeness of the character and all this other stuff
So she was, she was kind of resistant to the whole thing to begin with
I don't know how much ultimate control she has over his likeness or what have you
But here's what it boils down to
You cash the check, it's done
You know, whether this was not an intended purpose of his likeness when they signed off on it
They probably should have thought about that a little harder or read the fine print
Because obviously they saw him being used in the Nirvana things
And that's probably the footage that Activision showed to them
Oh yeah
But didn't realize when they signed the contract that he was also going to be a character
Just like Slash was in Guitar Hero 3
Just like, you know, and so forth these other characters
Just like Johnny Cash is
I mean Johnny Cash can very well do the Flavor Flav stuff in this game as well
I mean, it's, it's, it's just, you know, a model of a person being thrown on top of these
You know, motion capture data that they basically collected for these different songs
Going to chat.orangelandradio.com and reading comments
Dark Tetsuya says, I could understand him having a problem with him singing stuff from other artists
I don't see why they couldn't just lock him to only the Nirvana stuff
See, well A, there's two things to that
A, you can't patch games on the Wii and you can't patch games on the Playstation 2
So, it's, it's done
I mean, they could recall the game, but what's the point, honestly
In my opinion, B, the damage is done
The YouTubes are out there and it's done
And even if they were to recall the game, people aren't going to send it back because they think this shit is funny
So
Exactly, I thought it was funny
Exactly, I kind of think it's funny too
I mean, I don't mean to be disrespectful, but I guess I am
You're putting him in a video game, what do you expect?
I mean, this isn't, this is Guitar Hero
I mean, if you want respectful treatment of artists, you need to go to Rock Band, I'm sorry
Burn
Does Rock Band really, they don't have artist's likeness in the games, do they?
No, they don't, except for the Beatles Rock Band, but that's the way you do it
But I mean, I'm sorry, it's just, God, it's Guitar Hero
I mean, get over it people, if you don't like his likeness in the game, don't buy the game
There you go
Or if you bought the game and it's too late, return it
At the same time, isn't it just a game?
Isn't this just a type of artistic impression?
I mean, what's to stop me from going on YouTube and making a sock puppet effigy of Kurt Cobain
Singing whatever songs I want, and then pretending to have that sock puppet effigy
Put a shotgun in his mouth and do away with himself
Is it in bad taste? Yes
But can Courtney Love really sue me over that? No, because it's art
And I can kinda do whatever the fuck I want
Well, keep in mind though, her perspective too
She is his widow
And that's gonna put a different emotional push on it for her than it would for anyone else
And why in the hell did she ever allow this in the first place?
Because she's stupid
If she's that passionate about it, why did she ever sign off to his likeness being in the game in the first place?
And B, why wasn't everybody more educated on what was going on?
I mean, you know, the Beatles were involved with Beatles Rock Band like the whole way through
Why didn't at some point someone send Courtney the game or send the lawyers the game and say
Here it is, here's your final review copy before we send it out
If you have a problem, speak now or forever hold your peace
I mean, in my opinion, before I signed, that's what I would have wanted to see
But I have a feeling that it didn't happen
So, I don't know
As your edge in the chat says, you should do that
I'm not gonna do that, that's kinda, that's like
Look, I may not be the biggest Nirvana fan in the world, but that is extremely disrespectful
What I just suggested doing and I'm not gonna do it
That's time out of my day that I don't want to
Exactly, I could be playing WoW, come on
I'm not gonna make a mess
Hey, do you know how much red corn syrup that would take?
At least, at least it's not Revolution X, okay?
I mean, they could have had it worse
Frisbee says, even if it's not art, lol, freedom of speech
You know, I suppose the difference though is
That if I were to make that whole YouTube as disrespectful as it might be
I'm not charging for it and I'm not making money off of it
And that's probably the big difference is that, you know
Activision makes a ton of money off Guitar Hero
No offense, I'm sorry, but I can't see people going
Oh my god, Kurt Cobain's in this game, I must buy it
I don't think so, I mean
I'm sure maybe there is one or two, but I mean, come on
I don't think people are gonna buy a game just because an artist is in it
Unless it's like the Beatles rock band where it's all about the artist
Oh yeah, yeah, I can understand like if it was, you know
Guitar Hero Navar
Or even the Metallica Guitar Hero, the Van Halen
There are gonna be people, as much as we've kind of made fun of Van Halen Guitar Hero
There's gonna be people that really want that because they're just diehard Van Halen fans
You know, I get that
Yes ma'am
We need Van Hagar
Different topic altogether
Alright, GS68 in chat says, Kurt Cobain confirmed for Super Smash Brothers 4
How about Silent Hill?
Now that's bad taste
Salacious Pop says, when he finds his way into Space Channel 5-3, I'll be impressed
It wouldn't be funny if she just didn't realize
I would like to see people make YouTubes of Kurt Cobain in other video games now
Like this should become the new meme or whatever you wanna call it that's out there
Somebody should do that, put Kurt Cobain's face on Ulala's head and have him doing the choo choo
Or would it be funny though if she accidentally signed off on his appearance being in any Activision game
Like Call of Duty or some Madagascar game
The other thing to consider too is how intoxicated was she when she signed
Because now
Well I'm sorry, that's her own fucking fault then
If she can prove though that she was sufficiently drunk enough or intoxicated enough
Then it actually could be considered null and void under federal business law
You have got to be kidding me
Even if witnesses signed it too
I took business law
Why should that be an excuse? Sober the fuck up before you sign something
The same thing applies to weddings too
Like I was too drunk to marry him?
Well no like
Isn't that why the annulment process is there? Like if you change your mind
That's what annulments are for
But it's the same thing
There's a big fucking difference though between a wedding and a likeness in a video game
But it's still considered business contract
I don't know
I just think if you're high you shouldn't sign things
Call me crazy
Well they shouldn't have got her to sign it
But you know she can say
Hey I was really drunk at the time then
And who wouldn't believe her
Then there is cause to take it to court
I don't know if she'd be smart enough to realize that
You wouldn't be able to prove that
Maybe
Salacious pop and chat says it is not legal to enter contract with an impaired person
Then how did they ever get her to sign?
Ever
Hey she's drunk let's get her to sign
I mean isn't there
Surely
I don't know
I'm thinking does she have soul
We can't tell the difference
Does she have soul power of an attorney over everything?
Probably
She probably does huh
There wouldn't be like a lawyer involved or anybody else that signs off right
I think she was a full executor wasn't she
And I don't think their daughter is 18 yet
No
So no
Although she's an attractive young lady I don't know if you've seen pictures of her
She's you know aging very well
Got stuck after her dad
Alright anyhow sorry we're talking a bit too much about this
And I think everybody's got their thoughts out on this
But yeah I honestly I don't think there's anything that can be done
I think the stink is out there
I don't think her lawsuit is going to hold much weight
Unless maybe Dark Soccer is on to something honestly
It could be very interesting if that is the defense that comes up in court
Is that she was too high to sign the document
She's a drugged up bitch
Clearly she can't enter into any contract
Which makes me wonder
That might violate other terms though
Because doesn't she have some sort of custody term with her daughter
For having to be clean or something
Oh maybe
Oh that would make a lot of sense wouldn't it
So then she couldn't say
Ah her answer ties
I'm fucked up
You know what I'm placing my bet on out of court settlement
That's the way these things always end up
Out of court settlement more money
Frisbee says zombies ate my cart
Alright shush
Let's move on to some more news
And talk about zombies of a different sort
And the type of zombies that are in Left 4 Dead 2
Now you know we've been talking about the boycotts of Left 4 Dead 2
I know we've talked about it previously on this show
About how there was this you know thing out there
Where all these people were signing it
Wah wah wah you shouldn't be making Left 4 Dead 2
Because you haven't supported Left 4 Dead 1 enough
And I think the agreement among us here in studio was
Get over it
Because you know tons of games are re-released every year
With different types of skins and everything
And you don't see hundreds of thousands of people bitching about that
And Valve's done a pretty good job supporting Left 4 Dead 1
As it is
Like those
They got a heck of a lot more support
Than I think people do for their maddens
For their DDR's
For their what other games do they re-release every year
You know those are two of the big ones I can think of
But you know what I mean right
Guitar Heroes
And so forth
Okay
Well here's an interesting tactic by Valve
I actually have to hand it to them
They actually invited the two Steam users who started the boycott
Their online names are Walking Target and Agent of Chaos
Right after the game was announced at E3 2009
They invited these guys to Valve's offices to play the game
Interview members of the development team
Now the interesting thing is that the resolution of this
Is that these two guys say they're going to continue boycotting the upcoming title
But at the same time
Reported that the game seemed balanced and tight
And did not feel like a rush jobs
Now of course
The people that all signed this petition
There's a lot of them saying
It's corrupt
You guys are corrupt
And now you guys should step down
You should no longer be admins of this
And the guys that went say
Hey what we did
We did way more than most people thought we'd get done
Meaning they have only over 40,000 members in the Left 4 Dead 2 boycott group on Steam
And they are still demanding that Valve release this as a low cost expansion pack to the original Left 4 Dead
Is what the community is bitching for
What I think, I really don't think that it's in any way kind of selling out
It's that Valve offered an olive branch
Yeah, I don't think these guys sold out
By any means
I think that they out of
I actually think it's a very mature thing that they did
Going, you know, humoring them
Looking at it, you know, trying to see if maybe
They were justified or not, you know what I mean?
But doesn't that strike you as weird that on one hand they're saying
We're going to continue the boycott
And on the other hand they're saying
But the game doesn't feel rushed, it does feel pretty complete
Like, don't you get the sense that they're only continuing the boycott
Because they don't want to have that percent
Like, imagine they come home and drop the boycott
Like, what's that going to make them look like?
It's going to make it look like their silence was bought, right?
No
Don't you wonder if that's coming into play
That they just don't want their integrity questioned?
See, if they came out and said
We played the game
And, you know, we'd like to retract our position
Everything that we complained about
We were wrong
I think that is bigger balls and shows more integrity
But have they provided a reason that they're still going to continue their boycott?
Do they say it still doesn't feel like a sequel?
You know
To be fair, I'm reading this off of another news release
So I don't have their full statement on whatever it is they went and visited
We need to wait to see if they say why they're continuing
Let me see if I can find that
Or chatters, feel free to help out if you have a link to something that they said
It's just a safe face on their part
That's all it really is
Because, like you said, if they came back and said
Oh, the game's awesome, you know, we should drop our boycott
Then, you know, 39,998 people would go
You're fucking retarded
Here's another quote from them I found on another news source
What we can say with confidence is that the quality of gameplay in Left 4 Dead 2 is not in question
And it will only get better
But they will continue the boycott until their, quote, individual concerns are addressed
Which, you know, I don't
Big fat paycheck
No, I don't think it has anything to do with that
I think, again, it's that they've dug themselves in too deep in this boycott now
I don't think Valve was under any obligation to do what they did
I think that was actually kind of nice of Valve
And sets kind of a sad precedence
Is that if you bitch enough about something they'll fly you out to fix it
It almost kind of makes me go
Hmm, where do I want to travel
Oh, I would like to kind of go to Boston
Hey, Beatles Rock Band blows
And it was released way too soon after Rock Band 2
And you know they're going to release Rock Band 3
You know what, Rock Band 3 needs to be an expansion to Rock Band 2
A cheap upgrade
Yeah, that's right, I said it
Come sign my petition
Yeah, free trip to Boston, yeah
I'm just worried about the precedent that sets
But, again, I'm not blaming Valve
It was very cool of them
Well, but this has been a very big thing
They've got a big gathering
Like, you may have people go
If you had like a hundred people or so
That would be big enough
But they've got, you know, in the tens of thousands
You know, they've got a big following
TheRobDeeInChat, chat.orangelandradio.com says
The gamers who support this boycott in the first place
Have way too large of a sense of entitlement
I almost kind of think that hits the nail on the head
If these guys feel that strongly about it
You know, and I realize we've debated this topic to death on the show
And I really don't want to rehash the whole damn thing
But if you really feel that strongly about it
The best message you could send is don't buy it
Honestly, at the end of the day
No petition you sign or anything like that
Is going to have the impact that your wallet has
At the store
So there it is
And let's see
GameGuru says Left 4 Dead 2 exists
Because what Valve wants to do requires a sequel
SalaciousPop says
Valve has already done a ton of stuff
That is anthema to pretty much every other developer
Anathema
Using big words in my chat
How dare you, I'm just kidding
By the way, there was a somewhat related story
Going on
Where I guess there's a campaign
Going on to fly the
Valve boss
Gabe Newell over to Australia
To actually look at a
Left 4 Dead campaign
That was made called Shotgun Sunrise
It's a custom campaign
That he basically
Wanna fly the guy out there
To release this
They raised $3,000
In donations
And
I don't know how they raised all that money
Just trying to get this guy to fly out there
And look at this expansion or whatever
I think he actually made like a quote
Kind of tongue in cheek that
Oh well I'll go look at it if they fly me out there
And they actually raised the money
But now he's kind of backing down or whatever
So
Hopefully they donate the money somewhere
Or something
I just
But again it kind of goes back
To that entitlement thing
Okay yay for you you made a mod and spent a lot of time
Making the mod but why did you
Do that? Did you feel entitled
To the fact that Valve should release that as an
Official expansion? I mean
You know
Don't mod if you're not gonna be
Content with getting nothing
For what you did
That's what I don't understand
So
People suck
I don't know I think the Left 4 Dead community
Some of them
I think they should be happy
Where they're being angry
I think that's a waste of money
What? Well I mean I can understand
If you feel passionately enough about something
Especially if you put a whole lot of work into it
And you have enough other people that
Enjoy your work that they're willing to
Contribute to that yeah
But in the end it's a game
You know why not
Save that three thousand dollars for
You know people who need it
Aren't we in a global recession?
God damn they raised that much
Money over this
I'm just kind of surprised
You know that could go into an
Arcade cabinet
Shush
The Rob D in chat
Says I would love love
For Valve to cancel Left 4 Dead 2
Just to see how they would react
I don't think that's gonna happen and I don't think
You should let a few bad apples spoil the barrels
So to speak
I don't see how this is different from
The sports games that come out every year
And the DDR's and music
Games that get re-released every year
That people buy
I don't see how this is that much different except it actually
Sounds like Valve is doing more
Than what a lot of these other games that come out every year
Do it actually sounds like there's more to it
So
I don't know I think they should be happy
I think some people just need to
Get over themselves
Well guess what came out for
iPhone
Commodore 64 emulator
Isn't that great?
Awesome where can I download it?
You can't
Because they have found
Problems that will be problems
For Apple actually
Yeah there were
Ways to access
Basic programming
Like the language basic
And so Apple's like ah no
And stopped it
Because you can't release
An application that programs
Or something like that like you can't
Have an application on the iPhone that can program
The iPhone to do anything
You want all they have to do is
Edit the
The emulator just to
Disinclude the basic
What's funny is I think people
Are going to constantly find ways to
Get to basic you know because obviously
They figured out a way to abort the game somehow
And get into basic so I would think
They're going to keep doing this somehow but
I guess if they patched this to keep Apple happy
Then that's kind of cool because
I grew up on the Commodore 64
Okay that was my gaming system
Until our family had an NES
That was my gaming system from ages like 5 to 10
So you know
I would love to relive some of those games
For my youth but
Well it's been resubmitted
So we'll see if it hangs around
That would be
Kind of cool
I wonder though if the games that are being released
On this emulator are legal
Like I know they say that
They have kind of like this mix of games
Is the guy getting permission from these companies
Or does he have to? Maybe copyright
Laws are up because it's been about
25 years since most of these games
Were released what like 84 yeah about 25 years
Since most of these games came out maybe
Copyright law comes into play if none of these companies
It's only a handful of ROMs that are actually licensed
The ones that came out were Dragons
Den, Limons, Jupiter
Lander, Arctic Shipwreck and Jack Attack
Okay Limons I recognize
As an official Commodore title that was one of the
Games that was put out by Commodore
So I'm wondering if and I don't know if
All of these fit in that same car I actually
You know why? I actually owned Limons
It was one of the few paddle games that you had
You played this little car and you held the little
It was actually one of my favorite games to play
You held down the little fire button to drive
And you turned the paddle back and forth
To kind of move back and forth on the track
It was a lot of fun you had to avoid other cars
And you could race forever
That would be even though that's the type of game
I think would throw me for five minutes
Now like hours I played
This game as a kid but it was
Like I guess you could call it a first party
Or whatever it was actually put out by Commodore
So I'm wondering if all these games don't have
Commodore's sort of blessing or what's
Going on so
Frisbee in chat says
Dear Apple what about some
Open source on the iPhone
I just don't think
You're going to see that happen because what they're
Probably worried about is
People getting into the phone aspect of it
Using all these programming
You know hacking it so that the phones
Get open and suddenly you can make
Phone calls without having to pay for it and so on
Like I just think they're really worried about how
Far you can hack these devices
GS68 says I want to see
MSX games on the iPhone dammit
Oh wait Americans don't care about
MSX I'd like to see the
Original Metal Gear Solid
The original Metal Gear for one
Before it was Nintendo-fied
And the original Metal Gear 2
And I wouldn't mind seeing
Gardic but the problem is who's
Going to translate those
Fans!
Better learn how to speak Japanese
Something like that
Coming to the PSP is yet another firmware
Of course why not
They have plenty of other firmwares
Like all the other firmwares
It's been cracked already
Which is really important
But what this firmware does
Hint at though is
Some things that possibly will be coming out
Later on including game rentals
Apparently
As part of the change log
They have ways that you can
Now group different folders
It says games now can be grouped
And displayed in folders based on their
Expire dates under game
So that means that there's
Going to be some sort of trials or something
That will expire after a certain amount of time
And then of course
Some other stuff
They changed settings
Network updates have been changed
To system updates
The number of colors that can be selected
Under settings has been increased
And revisions to strengthen
Security of course
With the internet browser
And
The other
Of course
Before they already have support now for
Video rentals so maybe
Now they're going to do it with games
I think it has to be something big like that
Because what else justifies the
6.0 I mean it's not like
5.3 or 5.0
Like this is a major release
Or they wouldn't call it 6.0
It's the PSP Go because it's coming out in like 2 weeks
Oh that makes sense too
Fair enough
Do you think though that game rentals is something
It's nothing I ever thought of before
But then when I thought oh my gosh
Like companies get mad
At the game rental industry
Because they don't see any of those profits
But this would
Let them get a chunk of those profits
Where the rentals are happening
And Sony gets a good chunk of that too
Because they're endorsing the service
And they kind of can put the rental thing
Out of business
It's not going to happen right away or for a long time
I mean this could be something huge
That we're looking down the barrel of
I mean really it's not going to cut into rental business
Because most rental stores
I mean you know how bad
The PSP is doing I mean it's hardly
Selling anything there's not a lot of good games
Out for it most stores do not
Bring in PSP as a rental
Category
Okay but only a matter of time then
Before it's on Playstation 3
Although those games are ginormous
I don't know the feasibility
Of that but
We're years away
From that being possible
I mean technology gets better data moves faster
We're five years away from
A PS3 game being
Downloadable as fast as
Super Nintendo ROM is these days
Yeah but in five years it's going to be a Playstation 4
And no one's going to give a crap
About Playstation 3 titles that are downloadable
Just like Playstation 1 titles
That come out now
Yeah that's kind of cool that they're re-releasing them again
But really is it such a big deal
I mean is it even something that you would go rent
I mean especially when the titles are like
Ten bucks
What are they going to charge for rentals? Two dollars?
I mean it's just it's not really
Cost beneficial
To actually rent a title
Frisbee in chat says there's already game rentals
It's called DRM
I'm not sure I quite understand that comment
Is that like a dig on the fact that
When you download things you can't share it with other people
And all that I don't know
Or I was thinking that the comment was going to say
It's called demos is kind of a way of
Doing it and seeing if you like it
Well that's kind of an asinine way of doing things
I mean oh
We could put out demos for free
So that you can test our products
And see if it's something that you want
But no we're going to be assholes about it
We're going to allow you to buy a demo basically
Of this game
Rent it for a little bit and decide if you want it
And that way if you don't like it
Hey we still got some of your money
But at the same time what about
We drop $60 on a game that we play for a week
I mean imagine if we could
Spend only $10
You know $9.99 to rent the game for a week
That would be
Maybe something I'd rather do for a lot of games
I would go rent them at
Like your mom and pop rental store
But they're always out
Imagine if I can go onto this digital thing
Click a button it's downloading I got it
Well good if that's an option for you
I mean that's awesome but
The thing is
I mean it's always good to have more options
To forego demos for this
You know rental stuff because
You know they feel that they can make more money
If you don't have a way to try
Out this game
Without you know paying money
I just think
Especially PSP games I think you're going to see
And you're right
I don't think PSP games are really
Rented at stores so I don't think you're going to see
This dig into the real rental market
Right now but it's about setting a precedent
You know especially with
PSP Go being digital
Download only and that they think
This thing's going to be huge although I don't think
It is Oh it's going to fail I think they're
Setting the stage for you know this whole
Rental thing that is first party and we
Haven't seen anything like it before
I think this is
A pretty big deal on what's coming
And I think probably it sounds like by the holidays
This is going to be something that's launched
Oh man PSP Go is going to be
It's going to fail so bad
Don't get me wrong I like
The PSP 3000
I just
Yeah well
I hate going over the same
But still
I mean there's other stories
I'm sure we have coming up
It's like
What exactly are you doing different with the PSP
Go other than charging me a lot more money
And not having the ability to play
UMD games I mean there's really
Nothing that's going to be exclusive to that
Maybe rentals are exclusive
To the PSP Go?
It won't be because you know why?
Because if they do it exclusive to the PSP Go
Then they lose out on all the
PSP 3000 stuff
I don't know Deathwishing in Chat says
I love renting PSP games
Renting PSP games are awesome when you go on trips
Makes sense
I mean if you're going to go on a long road trip
Why not rent a game?
They do have PSP rentals and NDS rentals
With like the
Kiosk and airports
And stuff like that you can do that
There's a place in the airport here that has
Rental thing and you drop it off in the box
Oh good I'm going to LA next week and I'm flying
Maybe I'll have to utilize that
Yeah it's actually pretty cool you rent it
Where you're
Flying out of and you can drop it off
They have one in every single airport
Major airport yeah
Alright well
Moving on to another story
We'll see what unfolds with the PSP
possible rental system a little later on
But I want to move into this because this has to do with
Copying games too but of a whole different
Sort now of course Batman
Arkham Asylum was huge it came out on
All these consoles this past week but don't
Forget it also came out on the PC
Hello there's still quite a few people
That are very into their PC gaming love it
And Batman Arkham Asylum of course was released
On the games for windows platform
So that those folks could play it there as well
But of course where there is
PC gaming there is piracy
So I guess an early version of this
Game leaked out and there was
A user that actually posted on
The official Eidos forums
With a post that went something like this that he had a
Glitch with his PC version of the game quote
I've got a problem when it's time
To use Batman's glide in the game
When I hold like it's when I
Hold the comma like it's said to to jump from one
Platform to another Batman tries
To open his wings again and again instead
Of gliding so he falls down
Into poison gas if somebody could tell
Me what should I do here and
It was actually replied to by an
Admin on the forums Keir
Responded to the thread and said the
Problem you have encountered is a hook in the copy
Protection to catch out people who
Try and download cracked versions of the game
For free it's not a bug in the games code
It's a bug in your moral code in other
Words this
Crack or this version of the game
Was put out there with this bug in it
So that when people call
Support to complain or go post on
The forums to complain or spend the time to
Download it or what have you to do it
They essentially out themselves as
Pirates isn't that entrapment
No because they're not
Really implicating them of a crime
It's just so that they have
An unplayable copy of it if they but
Here's the thing here's the funny thing about it
One they've done this before with Grand Theft Auto
If you pirated Grand Theft Auto
4 on PC they had this
Thing basically it was drunk cam all the
Time it was shaking around making it really hard
To play
And then the other thing is
This problem with Batman Arkham Asylum
Got patched within like a day
It was only effective for about a day
And then that was it
And that's what TigerClaus does in chat
As well as the glitch was later fixed
And yeah I think we're all not surprised
To hear that but
How many people do you think
Think to find the fix
Do you think that maybe
This does still defeat
A lot of pirates because they'll get the game
Play it go this sucks and delete it
Without ever thinking to look
For a patch
No maybe stupid people
That you know are
Not really normally pirating
Games but a lot of people will
Get frustrated with it and then
Like a week later they'll read on the forums
That this was intentional and then they'll re-download it again
I mean it's just like the guy that
You know had ran into this
He's not going to go oh my goodness
I can't believe they got me
Well I'm just going to buy games from now on
No he's just going to go and re-download the game
When it's been patched or fixed
Wait for someone smart to do it
And that's what's going to happen
If they have no intention of purchasing the game
They're not going to purchase the game
El Non Hombre Hombre
In our chat room says
No it's not entrapment because they're
A. Not law enforcement and
B. They aren't asking them to pirate
Well I meant that
I thought that they had called the police on them
No it looks like they just banned
This guy from their forums or what have you
Well to be fair
Couldn't they report it?
They could report it but
They sort of set him up
I don't know I'm kind of reminded of
And this is going to make me sound super gay
But Madonna
When one of her albums was leaked to the internet
It was actually something Madonna's record label
Released themselves and it would
Start the song and you would hear like the first
15 seconds and then you would hear Madonna's
Voice come on and go what the fuck are you
Doing?
So she basically put out all these
Bogus MP3's that started off like the real
Thing and then would just cut off and it would be her
Going what the fuck are you doing?
I'm kind of reminded
Of that this is essentially the
Video game equivalent
Of that except the game doesn't taunt
You well
It taunts you without directly taunting
You if that makes sense
I don't know if entrapment
Would be the word I would use though
Yeah that wasn't quite what I was thinking
I don't know what legal
Recourse they could seek with this
Because
I certainly think it's a
Good way to out the people that
Aren't supporting them
To go so far it's pretty bold to download a
Pirated copy of the game and post on the forums
About it that is kind of a stupid
Thing to do in my opinion
Is that if you're gonna
Steal but I don't think that they had
Any way of knowing that it was an intentional
Glitch
Salacious pop in chat
Says that it would defer anyone
Even the idiot makes it worth
It in my opinion I kind of tend to agree
With that statement because
You know even if it took a day
For that patch to came out
That patch to come out that fixed it
That was still one day
Where you might have some of these pirates get fed up with
Waiting and go I'm just gonna buy it
It looked cool enough from what I saw
I'm just gonna buy it
And even if that drove sales it did curb
A low percentage of the piracy
And had more of an impact than not doing anything at all
Sure
I guess
Alright
The Rob D in chat says the best part would be
If the game crashed before the final boss
That would be the best middle finger to the pirates
I think that Rob D
Yeah but the problem with things like Earthbound
Is one thing but I think the problem with what Rob D
Is suggesting as funny and clever as that is
I think that most people
Would say at that point I played enough of the game
Forget it I mean I love the Earthbound
Thing we talked about a couple weeks on the show
That you know it doubled the number of monsters
And you know would crash your game
Delete the save and everything but
I think there's a lot of people that at that point would just go
Ah fuck it I don't need to worry about this game anymore
I'm gonna move on and steal something else
Also after having seen the last
Boss and ending of the game
First of all the last boss
Is actually kind of easy
Um you know Uber Joker
And uh the
Ending was uh less than a minute long
Really for Arkham Asylum?
Well
It was it was short okay
Spoiler free please but
Less than five minutes is fair but
Although I don't remember it even being that long
Wow okay fair enough
Rob D in chat says
I think that if they played that long
They would be really frustrated with the inability to finish it
Yeah to some extent but I
You know I do think
I think Eidos or you know did
Did a funny thing here because
I think people that are gonna be bold enough to steal
And then complain about their stolen game
On the official forums I think they deserve
To kind of be made a mockery of
You know what I mean? So
You know he kind of got his just desserts and I think that's
Where a lot of us are doing the Nelson here going
Ah ha
You know it's one thing to steal but it's
It's like even it's like the different
Circles of hell
Like stealing a computer game is it's
It's one of the circles of hell but it's like you know
It's just getting poked with a hot prod
But then to like go and actually complain about it
On the forums and try to blame the
Developers for their borked game
That's like eternal damnation
Come on
So alright anyhow
More news stories and we're gonna get into release dates
Dark Sakura
Let's see
Well Lucas Arts
Um is actually
Working on a new game
And now Lucas Arts
Loom 2
I wish I so wish
But this is actually kind of cool because they said that they took
Their inspiration from games that are like
Braid
And of course Braid was you know pretty freaking cool
Which by the way has gone down in price on Steam
It's on sale
Um
But it's called
Lucidity which is supposed to be an
Xbox Live arcade game
And um there's rumors of a PC
Version but they didn't say anything about that
It's a 2D side scrolling
Um
Platformer but it has puzzle elements
Um we play as a girl
Called Sophie and
She keeps moving you just have to move
Things out of her way
Kind of lemming-ish right you know
That's kind of what it sounds like to me a little bit
But I guess your
Goal is to get her from point A to point B
But is she stupid?
Like you know lemmings were stupid that was the whole point of the game
They would just keep walking right off a cliff
If they you know needed to
They said that she's like in her
Abstract dream world
So maybe she's just
Dreaming you know
Kind of out of it but the art
Style is supposed to be the cut paper
Look of a pop-up book
Oh that's kind of sounds neat
So it's going to look like an old school children's book
Hmm
She's dreaming stupid
What was the last time
We got a um
Game
From LucasArts like
It wasn't Star Wars related
Like at Indiana Jones?
Oh I didn't realize they were behind the Lego games
It is LucasArts
Oh gotcha
Well this sounds like it could be cool but um
I'll wait to see if there's a demo
Before that there was fracture
Alright so there's just games I missed
Somehow there's too many video games you can't play them all
I think that was them yeah fracture
Fracture sucks
Underachiever
I want to go back for a minute because I think this chat room
Comment bears repeating
To Arkham Asylum, Tigerclaw wanted to clarify something
On the ending of Arkham Asylum
He says Arkham Asylum continues on though
After you beat the game you can still click on
Continue story and you have free roaming
Of the entire game so you can go and find
Those Riddler trophies, the alignment
Puzzles and interview tapes
Yeah but that's just for completion
So that's not really the ending
Or to do with the story itself
That's like New Game Plus
You can go taunt Harley for a little while
Alright fair enough
Ok
Let's get into some release dates we're going to travel the globe
And talk about what's coming out in your neck of the woods
Starting off with the US, Loki
Yes this week actually quite a few things coming out
Starting off with of course
Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2
Woohoo
Yes which will be coming out on pretty much everything
Need for Speed Shift will be coming out this week as well
On Playstation 3, Xbox 360, and
PSP and I believe the PC version as well
Scribblenauts will be making its way out on DS this week
Actually I believe like a week from today
I think
No Tuesday my mistake
Actually tomorrow Mario and Luigi Bowser's Inside Story on the DS
Some other crappy games on the DS
My Boyfriend and Princess in Love on DS
Woohoo
Yeah
Let's see
Animal Planet Vet Life
I just want to say though I saw Commercial for Need for Speed Shift the other day
On TV and it looked pretty hot
Because it was in high def
It's like Project Gotham
Looks kind of neat
And speaking of piracy
Batman Arkham Asylum on PC
So if you're complaining about it now you don't have it yet
Liars
Bleach the Third Phantom on DS
Chicken Blaster on DS and Wii
Another movie tie-in game
Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs on pretty much every system except for the Playstation 2
Heroes of the Galaxy
On Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
Which looks like an OK World War 2
Played some game
NHL you've got two games coming out this week
NHL 10 from EA on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
And NHL 2K10 on Playstation 2, PS3, Wii, and Xbox 360
Pinball Hall of Fame The Williams Collection on PS3 and Xbox 360
Red Faction Guerrilla finally making its way out on PC as well as Resident Evil 5
Time of Shadows
I didn't even know they were giving that a PC release
Time of Shadows also on PC
This week that really crappy game they played on Konami's booth at E3 this year
Tornado Outbreak formerly known as Zephyr Rise of the Elementals
On Playstation 3 Wii and Xbox 360
You remember that as kind of the tornado Katamari type of game
Toy Story Mania based off the ride and in 3D coming to the Wii
A game I ranted and raved about last week
Wet coming out on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
And then finally just thought I should mention this since we talked about them around E3
Madballs in Babo Invasion making its PC daily
That will be coming out as well
And then finally on Xbox 360 the Q Entertainment Trilogy on Xbox 360
Qubed which features Rez, Every Extend, Extra Extreme, and of course Luminous Live
And they left out 99 Nights
Well that's not Xbox Live
I know but still
And I don't think it is
Is there anything extra in this though?
You know what's funny?
Besides some of their misfires like 99 Nights
I really love Q Entertainment
Tetsuya Mizuguchi is the man
He's one of my favorites
Most of the games he puts out I love
So I'm kind of curious if there's anything extra in the collection that would make it worth getting
Probably the download content is probably in there
I'm not positive but it would make sense
Oh and how did I miss this?
Naruto Shippuden, Ninja Destiny 2
Who cares about Naruto
Going over to Japan, September 17th
Fuel, the localized version for Japan finally hits on September 17th
Also Left 4 Dead gets a price drop
It moves into the Platinum Collection
These are both on the Xbox 360
Terminator Salvation from Squeenix is putting it out over in Japan
A game called Velvet Assassin from Ubisoft makes its way to the Xbox 360
Moving on to the Playstation 3 coming out on the 17th
Also Fuel there as well
Makai Senki Disgaea 3
Appendisk, Razz Barrel, Hen Hajime Mashita
I'm assuming that is some type of extra scenario for Disgaea 3
Tales of Vesperia makes its way out on the Playstation 3 in Japan this week
And then lastly Terminator Salvation and Wet
Both on the Playstation 3 this week as well in Japan on the 17th
Moving on to the Nintendo Wii, checking out the games there
Forever Blue 2, Beautiful Ocean comes out from Nintendo in Japan this week
House of the Dead Overkill that comes by itself and a version with the Wii Zapper
The Wii Zapper is not dead in Japan apparently
It's coming out with that little bundle out there
Or they're just trying to unload the remaining supply they had
Probably
Playstation 2 sees some price reductions this week
Bully the Scholarship Edition and Biohazard Code Veronica
Which of course is Resident Evil Code Veronica in a bundle with Resident Evil 4
Or Biohazard 4 as it is in Japan
And lastly on the handhelds
Trying to see if there's anything
Saga 2 Hyou Densetsu Goddess of Destiny comes out from Square Enix
So this must be another Saga game that's coming out in Japan this week
So I know that series has its fans
So maybe there'll be some folks wanting to import that
Although they'll have to try and read it
And Idolmaster, Dearly Stars, DS, get it?
Idolmaster definitely has its fans in Japan
That is coming out on the Nintendo DS this week
Do you think that's a franchise we will ever see happen over here?
Probably not
Why not?
Because
It's too Japanese
Exactly
I hate to say it because it sounds weird but yeah
Quite a few games to pick from on the PSP this week in Japan
Ys 7 comes out this week
Yu-Gi-Oh 5D's Tag Force
Katakyuu Hitman Reborn Battle Arena 2 Spirit's Burst comes out this week
As well as a price reduction for Irregular Hunter X and Rockman Rockman value pack
I'm assuming that is just the Mega Man games all packaged together
And lastly, Iki Utsun Eloquent Fist gets a price reduction this week
I'm trying to see what game that is
I think that's one we have over here
No
No, one of the characters looks just like Sakura though
But like an older version
Look at that, she's like wearing the same outfit and everything
Well it is a, you know, high school uniform
I guess
That's just what it makes me think of though
And it's Ys chatroom
Ys
Okay there you go, there's your release dates for Japan
Dark Sakura, how about the UK?
For the UK we have, on the 15th as we discussed last week, Azuma's Revenge
And then on the 18th a whole crap ton of stuff
We have Batman Arkham Asylum for PC, don't pirate it or you'll get laughed at
Blood Bowl, Katamari Forever for PS3
One Piece Unlimited Cruise 2 for Wii
Order of War, Raven Squad, Red Gorilla Faction, I'm sorry Red Faction Gorilla, sorry
I was reading Gorilla and thinking beer
Resident Evil 5, Spectrobes Origins, The Humans for DS and PC
Wacky World of Sports for Wii, and Wet
Also Yamaha Supercross for DS and Need for Speed Shift on a crap ton of systems
Hmm, very cool
So there's some new stuff finally making its way to home
And this is kind of cool, I fully endorse this
Robot Chicken is coming to the PlayStation Home Theater
I did that off camera, sorry
Dark Sakura's making sound effects in the studio
I'm singing the Robot Chicken theme
It was actually really funny, it's a bummer you couldn't hear her
I'm stealing a cookie
So now they will actually have a bunch of different clips available on their theater screen
That once played Twilight's, I remember when they were playing the Twilight trailer on there
Well thank god they got rid of that
Yes, so you'll be able to watch Robot Chicken for free even though you can pretty much on your TV as well
But neat I guess, something else to watch while you're doing the Running Man
Well I think it's nice they're putting more useful things in home, does that make sense?
You know trailers are one thing but it's kind of nice that they're actually giving those theaters something a little more
I don't know, in demand to watch
Although I heard there was a soup, you know that show The Soup?
I think there was a clip show that was supposedly on Sony Home, I couldn't find it
But I didn't look very hard to be honest
I noticed that Sony's kind of branching out into putting some of these TV shows for free in home
And I think that's a good use of home, makes it a little more appealing in my opinion
I think it's just a matter of time before you start seeing the first episode of TV shows that they're trying to get you hooked into
Like the Glee pilot or what other pilots they've been trying to sell this year
There are other science fiction, Caprica's pilot, some of these shows that are coming out in 2010
Trying to kind of push those in Sony Home, I bet, especially for the next fall season you start seeing more of that
Yeah
We'll see
But that's kind of cool, I think that's a good use of Playstation Home
By the way there's some free stuff on Home this weekend too if you haven't logged in
And search for the OLR Club, I don't actually have to invite you, if you want to join the Orange Lawns Radio
Just search for it in Clubhouses, either search for Orange Lawns Radio or O-L-R-M-Y is like the keyword for it
So search for either of those and you'll find the Clubhouse and I'll invite you in
One more story before we get to the classic game of the week and it has to do with Penny Arcade Expo
And some unfortunate kind of side effect of so many folks being all contained in one place
PAX organizers did report this week that a confirmed swine flu case did break out at the show
And unfortunately this has grown into about a hundred cases of swine flu
Of course H1N1 is the real name for it but everybody calls it swine flu
Coming out of Penny Arcade Expo so kind of scary that you get all those people together and these types of things break out
Now it's not just the swine flu but of course the regular flu is showing up as well
You know as is various types of con things
Now this came up and we talked about this for a little bit on our phone call with Bobby Blackwolf
That we do on his show right before we go on the air tonight
So we talked a little bit about this and you know a couple bottom lines that come out of this
Is that A, this is just an unfortunate circumstance of cons
And Jamie you said something very smart about the fatigue that goes on at cons
And why this happens a lot
Well and keep in mind I was a long time con goer ever since I moved out here
And before I moved out here
You know my first convention I slept like three hours
And it was a three day convention
So yeah
A lot of people will do that
It's a big thing
Like for people who don't you know buy their hotel room and sleep in the lobby
People do that sorry
You are typically saving the typical con goer
May not be thinking in terms of proper nutrition for one thing
They'll be eating cheap con food
They'll be bringing snacks like when Julie used to go with us to cons
She would pack nothing but like croissants and cookies and all this crap
And I'd be like bring me some freaking carrots
You know because I can't eat that much sweet food all the time you know
And like I even ran away and got Moroccan food once
At AX one year
So um
But people don't really think in terms of their health
And the precautions they should be taking you know
At least have a couple of good decent meals you know with vegetables
Bring your vitamins with you take a good supplement in the morning
You know all of that contributes to your level of fatigue
And sleep please sleep
You know the con is a few days
But you've got to live with your health for the rest of your life
Now I know that some people have kind of been wondering what my piece is going to be on this
Because you know if you were listening to show a couple months ago
You know I have been very personally affected by swine flu
I lost a good friend of mine who is only 24 years old
She passed away of H1N1 a couple months ago
On June 23rd right before my birthday
I realized that what happened to her is not going to happen to everybody
Okay so I don't think there needs to be paranoia out there about the swine flu
But it pisses me off when people don't take this shit seriously
And I don't think that people have to like you know
Oh my god mass hysteria like no nobody wants that
But at the same time don't belittle what disease can do
And whether you know you know if you want to argue with me
The whole well swine flu is just like the regular flu
Blah blah blah fine whatever
You know yes I admit you can die from both
And I don't want to because I actually know people like on Twitter
That apparently caught this at PAX
And I don't want people to freak out like oh my gosh am I going to die
Probably not
It's you know what happened with Beth was certainly an isolated circumstance
There's still many questions
We're never going to get answers to as to what happened there
My point is though
Don't belittle this like it's the common cold
If you have a high fever
Call your doctor
Go in make an appointment
Get checked out get told it's nothing
Don't wait because the longer you let it go
The worse it's going to get and I don't want you to end up
I don't want anyone I know to have what happened to Beth happen to them
So you know please
You know and again this is not something I really get into ever on the program
But my day job is I work for a health insurance company
I'm a corporate trainer for a very large health insurance company in the state
And we work directly with the members in the center that I work with
So I know and I'll tell you
Most health insurance companies at least any decent one I know mine does
Will pay for urgent care
If you suspect you know whether you have PPO HMO whatever
It will pay for urgent care if you have symptoms
So you don't have to go to the ER because you have a high fever
You can go to an urgent care center
You can make an appointment with your doctor
Just go get checked out
Get told it's nothing get told it's the common cold
It's better you do that than the alternative
And if you don't have coverage
Still a lot of those urgent care places
Will treat you for
The last one I ever went to was 75 bucks I think
If you're uninsured you know and
They're there for that reason
Yeah go to an urgent care center not the ER for this
But get checked out for heaven's sake
You know don't sit on it and don't wait on it
And the other side I want to do with this is that
When you go to cons
And when you go to these places
Please be hygienic
I know a lot of people make jokes about this stuff
The whole con funk and all that stuff
But that is a very real thing that can continue to spread disease
And I want to reiterate one thing that Beth's mom Lynn
Said to the media when she was interviewed
Because Beth was the first person to die in this county from H1N1
And the one thing that her mom said to me
I will never forget this for the rest of my life
Is her on the news saying this
And I want you all to remember this
Wash your hands wash your hands wash your hands
I am not fucking around when you go to these conventions
And you're touching these controllers that hundreds of people have touched before
And so forth
Wash your hands
Please help stop the spread of disease
And wash your body while you're at it
Well I remember
I don't actually know if you remember this Rob
The last time that we went to E3 together
What did I have on me all the time?
Probably hand sanitizer
Hand sanitizer
I also had antibacterial lotion on hand
I had band-aids
And now this is something else I learned being a massage therapist
You don't want to have an exposed open wound
When you are around that many people
You do not want to touch other people's blood
Because first of all for example hepatitis
Lives outside of the body I think for two weeks
Active, live
Even if you think you've wiped up all the blood
It'll still live on the surface of anything that's touched
Unless you wipe it off really good
That's why they always say if you're going to be around someone who's bleeding
You put on latex gloves and then you take care of them
Put on your own mask before
And speaking of latex if you're going to have con sex use a condom
Use a full body condom if you're having con sex
But I'm saying you may not think about this
And the average person doesn't
But there are so many different ways to get sick
And I'm not saying be paranoid
But really take precaution if you're going to be around that many people
And at least always keep hand sanitizer around you
And at least be considerate to other people
If you've got like a paper cut or a cut on your arm or something
Put a good watertight bandage on it
So that you don't you know
I've got like for example
And no I've never had it but I have antibodies for hepatitis
Because I inherited it from somebody
But that still puts me at danger for exposing other people
So that's why I'm always extra careful
I always bandage up my cuts and things
Because I mean you always have
It's a matter of also being considerate to other people
And if you are sick and you do go
Wear one of those little paper masks
Don't cough on anyone wash your hands all the time
You know be considerate of other people
If you are going to be so inconsiderate
That you're going to go around other people while you're sick
And possibly contagious
If you have a sinus infection I don't care
That's not contagious
If you have the flu
If you have the cold
If you have something that is communicable
Take a precaution that you don't share it
And honestly it's not worth it
Stay home
There'll be another convention
Now I'm hoping you're sitting there on your chair
Going okay get on with it O.L.R.
I know this crap
But please understand if like one person's kind of sitting there
Going oh yeah maybe I should take like
Extra soap to the ex-con I go to
Then this whole little rant was worth it
Because I see a comment in chat
Frisbee says O.L.R. dash common sense
I really hope to everybody it is common sense
But if you've ever made the con-funk joke
Then you know it's not common sense to everybody
Okay so just please
From your friends at O.L.R.
Wash your damn hands
And again I do see
I see the con-funk around two particular groups
The really young
And the I have no life
I've never you know been on a date
You know 50 year old con-van boy
That's probably why they never had a date
S.H.A. 100 Matt also wants to put out
And don't pee on the seat when you use the toilet
Yeah don't do that Nope
I will say something this
Do not be afraid of urine on a seat
It is sterile
Just wipe it off Ew
But I'm telling you if you see poop on the seat
That's different No
Okay this is too much I'm done I'm done
Rob it actually is true urine is sterile
You have more germs on your hands and mouth
Than you do on your butt
I'm done nope too much done
Just wash your hands okay
That was the point I wanted to make
Before you pick up a controller at a gaming convention
Just wash your hands
Alright let's get into the classic game of the week
True though I know
Somehow we always end up with the show in the toilet
Even literally
Hey every week here on Orange Lawns Radio
We urge you kids to go visit the archives
And check out a classic video game of years past
And tonight is no different
Dark Sakura's gonna go into the vault
And pick out a game she thinks you all should be playing
Dark Sakura
What is the classic game of the week?
It's Pissarama
No I'm kidding
I hate you
Heart heart heart heart heart
Okay no it's Space Harrier
About damn time I did Space Harrier
I actually just got an IM from Becky
Saying that she thinks it's funny whenever I go off about pee being sterile
Will you get to the game
Get ready
Go back go back cause people have to go that far
Alright
We're looking at an arcade version of the game here
Yeah
It has my catch phrase on it
Here we go
Welcome to the fantasy zone
Get ready
Now everyone knows where that comes from
That has been like what my catch phrase as long as you've known me
It's been your little quote on forums like ever since I've known you
Yeah
Why why that quote of the thousands of quotes out there
Why this quote do you love so much
Because it's just cool
Welcome to the fantasy zone
Get ready
Alright
It's like it really makes no sense
Um Space Harrier is my third favorite video game ever
Which is me which means I have now covered all three of my top three favorite video games
The first being the Guardian Legend
The second being Fantasy Zone
And the third being Space Harrier
Space Harrier is set in the same universe as Fantasy Zone
So moving forward
It is a game that was produced by Yu Suzuki who did a lot of Sega's really good games
And sitting right next to me is a picture of my husband shaking hands with Yu Suzuki
That was pretty cool
So Space Harrier is a sort of a fake 3D type of game
It is a sprite based game and it scrolls towards you
Well not kind of like a real over the shoulder cam but it's from behind you
And it has 18 levels each with a boss
And you have to shoot you know everything that gets in your way before it shoots you
And you can run on the ground or you can fly in the air with a jet pack
And everything really does come at you very quickly
It's brightly covered levels
Even for you know as old as it is because it came out in 1985
It is a fantastic game and it's one of the early games to use digitized voices in it
And after you beat a boss it tells you that you're doing great
It constantly encourages you I mean how many games do that
Anyway
By the way I just want to point out and I'm sorry Darsak if you were going to get to this
But since I was a Nintendo kid and not a Sega kid growing up
There was a game on Nintendo called 3D World Runner
That was a direct rip off of this game
I was going to get to it
Sorry
Actually that game was put out by Square by the way
And there was also Pony Canyon did a parody called Animal Attack Academy
That had a Japanese school girl fighting Australian animals
But yeah the game is also that along with After Burner
Was one of the first cabinets that had you in a seat
And that the whole cabinet would move along with your joystick movement
There also is one that doesn't move that sits down and an upright version
So it was really really cool to play
I haven't played a space harrier in the you know with the full motion sit down cabinet in ages
It also it used the same music for the most part over and over again
But I really loved the music
I put up a link also to just the music
I will bring that up so you can hear just the music without all the explosion noise
Let's listen to a little bit of that
Not bad for a game from 85
It really is one of my favorites
Now as far as other releases we got a there was a computer a home computer version
There was also the 32x version and one thing I will say is that the 32x version is a direct rip from the arcade
In fact you actually have a little trick that you can do with it where it changes from press start to insert coin
So that space harrier of course
But After Burner were both direct arcade ports
There was a Sega Saturn version
There was a Sharp x86000
It only came out of Japan
All of those were supposed to be the most arcade available
There is a Dreamcast version that is playable within Shenmue and Shenmue 2
And the Suzuki Gameworks Volume 1
An Xbox version of course it was in Shenmue 2
And in the Sega Arcade Gallery for Gameboy Advance and the Sega Classics Collection
For the PS2
Space Harrier 2 was the Genesis version
Which actually also just came out on Virtual Console December 2 years ago
My head students they just came out
In Europe it came out in October 2008
And over here on November 3, 2008
For the Master System
Also the arcade version is unlockable in the Sonic Ultimate Genesis Collection
For Xbox 360 and PS3
And apparently it has sound issues by everything being just off pitch
That means I couldn't play
Actually I know that first hand because I tried to play Space Harrier
And the music sounded wrong to me
But I also have this thing where I hear anything off pitch
Really strongly perfect pitch for listening
I can't do it
There is also the Space Harrier Complete Edition
But you know what
They've done the series an injustice
Because they didn't release the sequel at home
The sequel being Planet Harriers
Have you played Planet Harriers?
I've heard of it
I've heard you talk about it before
Actually you know what
I think that you've seen me play it
Because they had it at Great America
I probably have just seen it and don't really remember it
Well I don't know if they still have it at Great America
But that one was pretty much a fantastic follow up to a great series
I think this game
And again sorry if I'm covering something you're about to get to
But I'm pretty sure this game is in that Sonic Genesis Collection
That just came out
That's what I just said
Oh sorry
I said it was Sonic Ultimate Genesis Collection
But it suffered from
Oh I was zoning reading the Twitter
So okay yeah it's there
Yeah the reason why I couldn't play it is because it had pitch problems
All the voice and sound was just off
Gotcha
Enough to drive me nuts
I have the same problem with music on the radio too
If they play it too fast
I hear the pitch
But anyway I digress
But yeah go out and play Space Harrier
It's a lot of fun
It's one of the few games of that perspective
That doesn't make me utterly motion sick either
Unless I'm playing it in the cabinet
The motion cabinet
Then I will get very sick and throw up all over you
Which is not sterile
Lovely
So that's your game
Alright there it is
Your classic game of the week is Space Harrier
And I think Dark Sakura prefers the arcade version
But there are some other places
Actually
If I'm gonna play it at home
I'm gonna play it on the 32X
Just so I have a reason to play a good game on the giant mushroom of death
Alright then there you go
Space Harrier on the 32X is your classic game of the week
Something non-Sega next week Dark Sakura
I tried to pick something non-Sega
And then it occurred to me that I have done dozens of other games that are among my favorites
And have not done Space Harrier
Alright fair enough
But next week
I got them on a month streak of Sega
So next week we'll have to do something non-Sega
Next week something non-Sega
Alright
Maybe I'll do something on the Atari 2600
That would be cool actually
I would love to see some Atari 2600 games
I'm actually just looking at a game on the Atari 2600 we have sitting around
Alright
Anyhow
We'll get into that next week
For now we're gonna take a break
We will be back though in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio and Part B tonight
Twitter topics
We're also gonna talk a little bit about Final Fantasy 13
Some more Sony news
Including news about the minis
And some Playstation 3 bundles
And we're gonna talk about a possible Wii price cut
We'll get to all that and rapid fire news after this
We'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
And welcome back everybody to this Orange Lounge Radio
We are live on September the 13th of 2009
Taping live at All Games Radio
The folks that always are kind enough to host our show
And let us steal their bandwidth every Sunday night
They have a new show starting by the way this week
I just heard about it on Bobby's show tonight
The Escapist Live
I'm probably getting the name of that show wrong and I apologize
But I do know the cool thing about it is that you're gonna hear
The Yahtzee interviews early
Like that's the first place you can hear
The Yahtzee reviews
The zero punctuation reviews
Yahtzee's the guy that does it right?
Like the nice game?
Okay
You're gonna hear those reviews early before they actually go out
And that's gonna be live on Tuesday nights at All Games Radio
And it's sandwiched right in between Dead Pixel Live and Video Game Outsiders
And Video Game Outsiders are another cool bunch
It's actually funny because they're very similar to us
Because it's like two guys and a chick
But they all do it over Skype
And I think one guy's in Canada
But it's funny because one of the guys on the show reminds me of you, Dark Sakura
Because he has a classic arcade game collection that he always talks about on the show
And how he's getting these new video games and so forth
Just like you have your pinball tables, right?
It's kind of funny how our shows kind of complement each other, but they're very different
Like we don't...
They play more like Warcraft and stuff
And we're more, you know, music-based games and RPGs
They're very Xbox-centric, you know, it's just kind of funny
That we have so many similarities yet differences
But anyway
I wasn't meaning to plug them as much
Although they are a good show
I want to plug the Escapist show that's brand new that's coming to All Games as well
You know what, I say just go to All Games on Tuesday
Just leave it running throughout the day
And you're gonna hear a lot of great radio
That's just what you need to do
And then don't forget on Sunday nights
Come back and listen to Bobby Blackwolf and ourselves here at Orange Lounge Radio
Alright
Let us move on and get into some Twitter topics
Before we get back to some news this week
And very thin on the Twitter topics tonight
I guess everybody's too busy with the Video Music Awards
And all this other garbage that's going on tonight
We didn't get a lot of tweets
In fact we really only have one tweet
And it's from Spazinator tonight
And the question is
Oops, it's down here a little bit
He wrote like five tweets, good lord
How about either Home, upcoming 1.3 update and OLR Club
As well as sale on the PSN Video Store
I don't know what they put for sale on the PSN Video Store
It's funny enough
Because I was actually looking at what kind of offerings were in the Video Store this week
Because since my Xbox 360 is broken
I can't do Netflix right now
It's kind of too bad though
Because a lot of stuff that is available on the PSN Store
And not to say the 360 is any different
But it's a lot of movies I'm just not interested in
It's all like slasher flicks
And action packed
Which I understand who their target audience is
But forgive me if I like a good chick flick
Or art house film every once in a while
I don't really find those on either network to be honest
But then also the OLR Club
I did plug that at the top of the show
But if you haven't joined the Orange Lounge Radio Club
In Sony Playstation Home
We do have one
So check that out
Search for Orange Lounge Radio
ORMY is our little buzzword
And we have some arcade cabinets
That I got from the Namco Collection demo
That we put there
So you can play like Dig Dug and stuff in our home
And I'm trying to get other furniture as I find it
But I don't really want to pay for a lot of furniture
But I guess there's some free stuff this weekend
So if you go into the stores
You can find some new shirts and things like that
And I guess some new furniture is free too
So I want to try and dig that up
Because I guess there's a coffin you can get for free this weekend
So I thought maybe I'd plop a coffin on the stage
Of our Orange Lounge Radio Clubhouse
Wouldn't that be lovely?
Wouldn't you like that, Dark Sakura?
Just a coffin?
That would be fantastic
Alright
Anyhow, let's get back into some gaming news
And kick off with some rapid fire news tonight
Starting off with Loki
Yes
Of course, Rock Band's got new stuff coming out each week
And this week we've got some new songs
Including Tenacious D
Yes, that's right, Tenacious D will be getting a couple individual tracks
With Rock Your Socks and Tribute
Both available for $2 each or 160 Microsoft points
I'm totally getting Tribute
Also part of the individual songs
The Guess Who with Hand Me Down World and No Time
And then finally Dinosaur Jr. with Pick Me Up and The Wagon
All those available as individual song downloads
Of $2 each or 160 Microsoft points
Or I guess 200 Wii points
But that's a little easier to figure out
Then to kind of coincide, I guess
I know there's a new Anvil documentary coming out
Well, they have the Anvil pack
Which is available for 440 Microsoft points or $5.50
Included with that is 666, Metal on Metal
And this is 13
And those also can be purchased individually for 160 Microsoft points or $2 each
And then finally coming to the PSP
We've got Evanescence with Bring Me to Life
And Spinal Tap with Back from the Dead
And then also we've got Forza 3 going gold
And of course with that they announced the demo for the game
Will be hitting the Xbox Live Marketplace on September 24th
You'll be able to check out some of the new cars
As well as some of the tracks
And the demo will include 5 playable vehicles
Including the 2007 Porsche
Number 80 Flying Lizard 911
Looks like an Audi R8 5.2
The Ferrari California
Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution X
That would be 10
Whatever
And the mini John Cooper works
That's interesting
Finally, a game I'm quite excited about
DJ Hero will be getting its healthy dose of Daft Punk
And they will be contributing 11 unique mixes for the game
As well as being playable characters in the game as well
Included with that would be Daft Punk Ride the World vs. Young MC Bust a Move
Defunk vs. NASA Strange Enough featuring Karen, ODB, and Fatlip
Daft Punk Defunks with Queen, another one bites the dust
Robot Rock with Hashim Al-Nayefish
I guess that's translated to the soul
I'm glad I'm not the only one that horribly butchers pronunciations on this show
Robot Rock vs. Queen, We Will Rock You
I guess that's kind of appropriate
Short Circuit vs. Boogie Down Productions Jack of Spades
Technologic vs. Gary Numan's Cars
I think there's too many tracks mixed with Cars
That's just my guess
Television Rules the Nation vs. No Doubt Hella Good
And I'm very disappointed to see that there's not anything for like
Some of the songs One More Time or something like that
Last, well, I guess that was their last album, maybe the album before last
But man, maybe some download content later on
And I think that all that is probably download content, all those songs, right?
Did they say that? Because I wouldn't think Daft Punk has that many songs in the game, do they?
No, I think that's that many songs in the game
Wow, that's kind of cool
Yeah, so that was only 8 of the 11 songs too, so there's going to be more
Well, getting into the Nintendo Virtual Console releases from this week
On Virtual Console we had the Super Return of the Jedi from the Super Nintendo
Came out this week and that was 800 Wii Points
And I think every week they've been doing a Star Wars game, I think for the month
So there you go
DSiWare, they had Clubhouse Games Express Family Favorites
Which has games like Hearts and Bridge and so forth
On WiiWare though, they had a game called Color Z, or Colors
Which was where you go forth in spaceships on a mission to clean up virus infested planets
I guess you absorb viruses of your color, but you want to stay away of other viruses
But who cares about that when you have Contra Rebirth hit for 1000 Wii Points
Which is kind of like a Super Nintendo-ish looking newer version of Contra
Which, funny enough, our caller last week, nailed it
That they thought Contra was going to be out on Labor Day and they were correct
So good job on that
Hey, Capcom vs. Tatsunoko has some new, apparently leaked, characters from poor website planning
Apparently somebody was able to mine the website and find some images that were missing on the website
That apparently are going to be added later, which include Frank West from Dead Rising as a playable character
Ah, we knew it
As in Tatsunoko vs. Capcom
Apparently Zero from the Mega Man series is there as well
And Yatterman number 2 and Joe Asukara
We should have been in it to begin with, yes
He's always the one that wants to push the button
Now see, I don't know dick about anime, so I guess Jamie's excitement has me excited too
Woo!
I guess that's good news, right?
The Pac-Man world record was broken, apparently the kill screen was reached in 3 hours 42 minutes and 4 seconds
I'm sorry, that was the old record from Chris Ira
Now it has been beat by David Race, I think is his name
3 hours 41 minutes and 22 seconds is the new time
Wow, Billy Mitchell once held that spot
But Billy Mitchell's a dick
I don't know, it's a movie, I'm not going to
He really is
I don't know the guy, I'm not going to bother
Alright, let's finish off the rapid fire news, Dark Sakura
Well let's see what else we've got going on
There's actually an ESRB rating for Castlevania The Adventure on Wii
Which really wasn't that good of a game
It was, you know, the Game Boy one that came out
Also, and I mentioned this earlier, Braid is cheaper now on Steam
It's $5 now, or 3.39
And it's a pretty cool game
And also, Final Fantasy VII on Wii has more download content
Chapter 9, The Crystals, which is the final part of the story, that's 800 Wii Points
I need to finish up that game
Yep, I thought you'd be interested in that one
Yeah, I kind of stopped playing, but it was a really good Wii download game
A little other news in WiiWare, is that for 800 Wii Points, Spaceball Revolution
Not to be confused with Spaceballs
Then 2 and 1 Solitaire, which is Spider and Klondike
And then, Sullivan's Key and Rygar for 500 and 600 Wii Points respectively
Alright, let's get back into some long discussion topics tonight, Loki
Yes, the music game sales are down
But, even though they are down 46%, it is still the third best selling genre among video games
And of course, this is coming from the NPD group, they do all these sales tracking and whatnot
And I guess, year to date sales have declined quite a bit
But, when you look at it, they're pretty much calculating stuff from up until
Up to Guitar Hero 5 and the Beelz Rock Band
I think a lot of people were anticipating those two games
I was going to say, because I've seen this story spread like wildfire through blogs this week
And I'm like, this is completely misleading, in a way
Because the big music games for the year haven't even come out yet
Or just came out
Well, you obviously can't have that data right away
I mean, they usually release the previous month's data like halfway through the next month
I think that it's even selling half of what it used to is pretty damn impressive
When you consider a year ago, we had Guitar Hero World Tour, Rock Band 2
I mean, those are both huge titles
The DS games were just coming out too
Those are all huge stuff
So, I mean, I'm not surprised
I mean, since I don't really think that Smash Hits and Metallica sold
I mean, they sold alright, but not like, you know, a Guitar Hero 5
They're just not going to sell the way a Guitar Hero 4 or a Rock Band 2 does
Exactly, and the track packs, I mean, that doesn't really count
So, it's a little misleading
It'd be more interesting to see what happens after the holiday
At the end of the year
I would like to see an end of the year wrap up as compared to last year
You think it'll be kind of in the same?
I think you'll still see a little decline
I don't think the Beatles Rock Band is going to sell quite the way Rock Band 2 did
Don't get me wrong, I think it'll still sell pretty big
And I think Guitar Hero 5 will probably be on par with Guitar Hero World Tour
Which, if I'm not mistaken, didn't Guitar Hero beat Rock Band last year in terms of sales?
Um, yes
Yeah, because Guitar Hero is still, you know, despite the fact that, you know
Rock Band gets more press usually because they have done more download packs
And, you know, so forth, Guitar Hero still sells better
Because they have more releases
Well, and also, I would say they have better peripherals too
I wouldn't call their drum set better than the other ones
Alright, I'm basing it off the guitars, I am
But I like the Guitar Hero guitar much better than the Rock Band
Yeah, definitely they're going to skew everything
Because now they're going to consider, you know
Each copy of Guitar Hero Van Halen that people redeem for free as a sale
You know, just stuff like that
It's, they do a lot to really skew their numbers
And they're like, yeah, look how much Guitar Hero is selling compared to Rock Band
And you can't compare the two because one has way more releases than the other
Because they refuse to embrace download content on a regular basis
I mean, they do have download content on a regular basis
But nowhere near what Rock Band has
Alright
Well, moving on with other stories
Completely out of the Music Game League
Final Fantasy XIII finally had its release date revealed
There was actually like a little conference earlier this week
Where they finally revealed some details about the game
But, you know, the biggest thing, because we weren't there
We didn't get to play the playable demo
December 17, 2009 is the release date for Final Fantasy XIII in Japan
But, I will say this, don't forget the Playstation 3 is region free
This game is not coming out on the Xbox 360 in Japan
That was not something they said as part of the announcement
So it is only PS3 in Japan
And I bet you, you're going to have a lot of folks that import this
Although, it's going to be very Japanese heavy still
That's the problem
I don't think I will though
I mean, I've done that in the past
I've played Final Fantasy games in Japanese and never had a problem
Well, look, I don't know Japanese like you guys do
I don't know Japanese
I would get nothing from this
I print out a nice little fan translation of everything and that works
That's why I played through Final Fantasy VIII when I originally imported that
It would be cool if they had English subtitles
But they don't want to dip into the US sales
Naturally, it's not going to be there
However, though, that doesn't happen until the international versions
That they have English subtitles
My copy of Final Fantasy X-2, my Japanese one
Well, I have the international version
It has subtitles
No, but I haven't heard of any type of extras
That we're going to get in Final Fantasy XIII here in the US
With the exception of the fact that we have a 360 version
So do you think there will even be an international version this time?
Maybe
Or maybe, I guess they could always do a remixed version
You know how Final Fantasy X, I don't think there were a whole lot of differences there either
But the international version had the different
What was the name of the board where you leveled?
You filled in the spots on the board
That was how you leveled your characters, remember that?
They have a different version of that board in the international version
I wonder if they'll do things like that, I don't know
But I am certainly excited for Final Fantasy XIII
But not excited enough to import it because I don't know Japanese
And for me, the story is everything in Final Fantasy XIII
Well, it's not everything, but it's like 90% of it
So I'm going to wait for the English one
Which I'll be able to comprehend
Atdeft points out in our chatroom at chat.orangewashowagerdoo.com
The international version would probably be on the 360
I don't think it will in Japan
I mean, I see where your logic is going and that's a logical thought
But again, you have to remember the 360 has not penetrated the Japanese marketplace the way it has here
Sony is still on top, well Nintendo is still on top in Japan if I'm not mistaking
But Sony has a clear second place
And I think Microsoft has gained some ground
They're not a laughing stock in Japan at this point
But they're even further back than where Sony is here
I mean, at least Sony has been gaining a lot of ground here
In this generation
But I think in Japan it's a whole different story
And Game Guru says the 360 version is your extra
Keep in mind 360s aren't region free
So if you live in Japan and for whatever reason have a 360
You're out of luck unless you can figure out a way to mod or whatever
Also, I wanted to kind of point out one thing
This had me thinking about was Final Fantasy XIV
When do you think we're going to start seeing more Final Fantasy XIV?
Do you think it's going to come out?
I don't know if the game itself will come out next year
But do you think we're going to see a lot more information start to spill out really quick?
It seems to me like we're going to have our shortest window
Between Final Fantasy games with this and XIV
Being that we already know there's a playable alpha out there
That they demoed at a show
I'm wondering if XIV is not going to show up at Tokyo Game Show as well
It might, they may have a little bit there
But I don't know how finished they'll be
That's true, well maybe that same alpha that they had at the Gamescom in Germany
I don't know
But I think it's very possible that we're going to at least see the beta
Final Fantasy XIV by next year
One of my friends was trying to tell me it was going to be this year, the beta
I'm like dream on
There's no way that XIV is going to be out there before XIII is
That would just be weird
That's like dividing by zero
You can't do that in the Final Fantasy universe
Of course there's a lot of people that think those online games
Shouldn't be part of the regular numerology anyway
As much as I love Final Fantasy XI
I sometimes tend to agree with them
Anyhow, let's keep moving on with some news, Darcyra
Well there is a rumor going around that there's supposed to be
Three different 250GB bundles of the PS3
Coming out in the UK in October
There were FCC documents showing that there was supposed to be a PS3 Slim
And a retail source to a Eurogamer
That said that there was supposed to be three different bundles with different games
As in Uncharted 2 Among Thieves, Gran Turismo 5, and Assassin's Creed 2
And they were supposed to sell for 299 which over here would be 494
And there's of course no statement made to the rumor
I don't know, are all these different bundles necessary?
I guess so, I guess bundles help drive sales
There's a ton of different PSP bundles here in the States
There's the Hannah Montana OMG Girls one and the Rock Band one
No, I think that's seriously what it's called
OMG Girls Play 2 or something like that
Kind of their way of getting girls to get Sony PSPs
Because right now they all have DS's
That's funny
We'll probably see something over here too
As far as US bundles, I'm guessing
In time for the holidays, certainly
Definitely
So to kind of go back to something we were talking a little bit about
Or complaining about I guess in part A
Was the PSP Go
And one of the things that they were kind of showing off during E3
Well actually not so much E3, but during Gamescom was the PSP Minis
And they said that there is a possibility though
We will see collections of these Minis available on a single UMD
At a later stage later on
Where maybe a publisher or whatever can put out a bunch of these little games
I guess like you see right now on the Xbox 360 every now and then
You'll see an Xbox Live game collection or something like that
They also said that there's a possibility that the Minis will jump to the PS3 as well
To be downloaded
I could see that happening especially if they feel that
They're not making up enough sales with the PSP Go
And I have a feeling that's going to be the problem
But at the same time
And to kind of go back to what we were saying before
What exactly does the PSP Go have going for
Other than it's more expensive and slightly smaller
I mean nothing
It's new
Oh goody
So if Nintendo came out with the Wii Gold
Or something like that
It's a gold colored Wii, but it's $500
Does that mean I have to go buy it?
I mean that's stupid
But
Oh well
I mean to me
Saying that they're going to re-release these on UMD later on
Makes me feel that they're not really confident in the PSP Go
And that they will need the supplement or sales by other means
I just thought it was interesting that they were talking about putting these on the PS3 as well
I mean it makes sense
But then again we kind of talk about this
Oh you know they're going to do all this with the Minis
We don't really know what they're going to be yet
We haven't seen what the Minis are
Right? Like I know that little picture you have there
Looks like a little bejeweled thing
Well they have like Tetris and stuff
Do they already have some Minis out there?
Tetris is supposed to be one of the Minis
I heard by the way that there was somebody
I was trying to get them to tweet us about it
Because I didn't have a story on it
But I heard about it
That there's like a new Tetris in development right now
Not the Nintendo one, but like a new Tetris
There's one for the DS I think, maybe the Wii
No there's a different one even outside of that
Yeah
Is it now going to have like more blocks?
Tetris now with more blocks
Tetromino is made out of five cubes instead
No I imagine it's more like probably more competitive in internet things
You know like I'm sure there's some people out there
They're like how many times can you do Tetris?
But like look at Tetris DS
A million
Yeah I mean but realistically yes you can
Because look at Tetris DS
That was an awesome version of Tetris
You know one series they've managed to re-release several times
And actually do a pretty good job with every time
Is Tetris
Like if you look at the original PC game
Then you look at the NES Tetris
Even Tengen Tetris versus Nintendo Tetris
And then Game Boy Tetris with its whole link play was revolutionary
And then Nintendo DS is awesome I mean
Tetris is kind of actually one game that they've done right
Many many times
Not to say it's been perfect
Because there was a Tetris on the Playstation
By Jellico I think it was
Tetris Plus
That was awful
It was an awful awful game
So it's just kind of interesting
Agreed
You know it's kind of interesting that you can take like
A game that's essentially the same and do it so many different ways
And sometimes it's very very good like Tetris DS
And sometimes it's very very sad like Tetris Playstation
So
Anyhow
Let me move on I didn't mean to get into a different topic
But I did
I want to talk about Silent Hill Homecoming
Which you know was the fifth game in the series
Even though it didn't carry the number 5 on it
And was somewhat razzed here in the states
As you know kind of because it was by an American developer and so forth
Well the game was set to make its way to Japan
But guess what
The website was updated this week
The Japanese Silent Hill Homecoming website was updated to say
The game has been cancelled
Silent Hill Homecoming will not be out in Japan
No reason was given for the decision
It just said on the website simply quote
Please look forward to future titles in the series
Kind of interesting that
They
That this game was developed in the west
Took some shit for that
And now the Japanese aren't even going to release it at all
But it's not too surprising considering the site hadn't had an update
Until this
Since November of 2008
I don't know what do you guys think
I don't think Silent Hill Homecoming was terrible by any means
But I can see where
It's different
And maybe
I don't know I don't know it just seems weird to me
That they're not releasing it at all
Like even under a different name or anything
Given the reviews that it got here though
That's really not very surprising
Because it doesn't I think
The biggest complaint about it was that it didn't have the same kind of
Scare factor that appealed to Japanese players
It wasn't the same type of a scary game
I don't think the game was terrible it was different
But you know I also like Silent Hill 4
I didn't say it was bad but I'm saying that it wasn't
What was up to snuff
For that series
It's just interesting that
I wonder if that's because of sales figures here
I wonder if that game just didn't sell well here
I don't know Loki from your inside perspective
I don't know if you would know this but
It didn't sell that well here
It didn't sell well in the beginning but that's it
It's not something that's constantly being reordered or anything
It's too bad
Yeah
Alright let's get into tonight's mailbag
A part of the show where you can interact with us
By sending us emails to mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com
Dark Sakura's gonna dive in head first into the mailbag
And find some emails to read for us
I am
You are, you is
I is, okay
Greetings Rob, Loki, Dark Sakura
Here's the dilemma
I'm a hardcore PC gamer and want a PS3
But can't justify bringing one
Buying one because
Any of the games I like for it I can buy for the PC
And play with better graphics, cheaper and less hassle
But I like the idea of having one
If only for Gran Turismo and Blu-ray
To get a system I would have to buy an HDTV
Which is expensive
And I don't know whether I should wait
For the 3D TVs
So many questions so little time
Are there any good PS3 exclusives
That would justify me buying this system
And should I wait for 3D TVs
Also, how do I vote for your show
Without going through iTunes, I hate Apple
The turtle
Wait, just wait
And you can get a Blu-ray player, you know, for your PC
So wait, they're getting cheaper
The one thing that
I kind of have to say on this though
Is that, you know, one thing to consider
And has always kind of been a drawback
Of PC gaming is that you have to constantly
Build your PC
And I realize there's PC gaming fans that are gonna
Hate me for kind of calling that out a little bit
Cause there's a lot of people that do spend the kind of money
To keep on tip top shape
But the nice thing about console games is that
The metrics are already established
On console games
And that, you know, the game is always
Going to play the way it was
Meant to be played on a certain console
Whereas on the PC sometimes you have to deal with
Frame rate issues and so forth if your PC is not up to par
But it sounds like you are
An established PC gamer and you have a lot of games
On PC, you probably have a top of the line computer
You may have hit the nail on the head
If every game you want to play
Is coming out on PC
Then maybe you don't have a reason to get a
PS3, Dark Soccer makes a good point
Get a Blu-ray player for your PC
They're coming down in price
But keep in mind too
The Playstation is a bit of an
Entertainment hub, quote unquote
Not just the Blu-rays, but you know
Home and the download movies and so forth
I don't know if it's really enough to justify a $300
Expense, especially if you're saying you get all
Of the rest of it on your computer
The only other thing I do want to
Say though, Sony exclusives, keep that in mind
There are certain games that
Will not come out on the PC, period
Games like LittleBigPlanet, which are
Pretty awesome, I gotta say
Mag, the ModNation Racers
These games are not going to ever come out
On PC because they're made by Sony and they want you
To have a Playstation to play it on
So, if those games are
Worth it to you, then you're going to have to take
The plunge, but if you know the types of
Games you're getting are, you know, Batman Arkham
Asylum, Call of Duty and the games
That do come out on PC, then
You might be right, you don't need a
Playstation 3, so don't spend money on one
Um
I personally just love the
Controls and sitting on my couch
And all that, you know, but that's
I realize it's not for everybody, that's
Why we have choices, as far as the other part of your question
About iTunes and you want to leave a review
That is not on an Apple place, that's fine
We always ask, look, just tell
A friend about the show, you don't even have to leave a review
I think there are other places
That take them, I don't know of any other big big site
Like, I know of one called Podcast Alley
That has some reviews, like PodcastAlley.com
You can always use that, or Dig.com
If I could also say something really quick
About iTunes reviews, I've become really pissed
Off at some of the things I've read on there, and I know I
Shouldn't care, but I kind of do
That there's some one star reviews
First off, there's a troll on there, and I'm not gonna
Say who they are, because I'm not gonna give them attention
But all I'm gonna say is, when I find out your
IP, I'm gonna ban you, so that you
Can never download the show and listen to it again
It's not that I can't take criticism of the show
But this person is probably
Jacking off right now to listen to me talk about
Them on the air, like, this is why you would write
A negative review of a show over
And over again, that says nothing constructive
About the show, so if this is you
I want you to know you're banned from this program
We do this for free, out of
Our spare time, because, you know
We like to do it
You pay nothing for this, and for you to continue
To troll us like that is just ridiculous
You're banned, and if I ever find out
Your IP, I will block you from the domain so you can no longer
Continue to download the show
You better pray I never figure that out
So, just go get fucked with a chainsaw
If you write a negative
Review, though, and say constructive
Things, I'm fine with that
As long as you've shown that you've listened
To the program, because then I saw another
Review that talked about how we were
Box fanboys and fangirls
And I'm like, and that we were always too critical
Of Sony, and I'm like, okay, we're critical of
Everybody when we need to be
Critical, and especially tonight
We've barely had any Microsoft
News, and maybe a little bit of Sony
News, so it's kind of unfortunate because
That person clearly based their review off one
Episode of the show, I'm not mad
At that person, I just wish they would've tried
A little more before writing that, but I'm not gonna say
Oh, I'm gonna ban you because you don't like the show, that's ridiculous
But if you're trolling, that's the difference
That other guy needs to go get fucked
And I wish, more people need
To report that to Apple, too, that's what I did
So hopefully, because I just, I hate that you can't
Review reviewers, you kind of
Can, you can put, was this review helpful
And I just click no all the time, but the problem
Is when he rewrites a new review
Complaining about something in the show this week
That, you know, didn't even happen
Then it just
Gets rewritten, so
There you go
And I'm looking at chat.orensonsrated.com
ActDef says
Sky rant and FUs incoming, no not yet
Not yet
SHA100Matt says the troll is a
Former all games listener that one stars every
Show, including Bobby's, that guy
Needs to go get fucked, and like I said
He's probably jacking off right now because I'm talking
About him on the air and he got the attention he
Looked for, so I'm going to stop talking about him
And just hope that a meteor
Falls on his head
Next email, please
Okay
Um
Next email, um
Okay
I guess this was sent out to multiple people
But I'm going to use the part that's addressed
To us, um
I know what you're thinking, dslover the person who
Despises 360 wants
One, I can't read this
Why is the grammar
Okay
Almost no
I'll go read it if you need somebody
No Rob, it's not just that
They hardly use any punctuation
So it's hard for me to get phrasing on this
Just go slow
Um
Gosh
Okay, well if you were wondering
Why here's the things
That pushed me over the edge
During my boy scout, oh that's it, you're a boy scout
You know, funded by the Mormons
During a boy scout troops holiday
Party where we stay up all night
Playing games, I saw one of my
Friends playing Guitar Hero 2
And we played over 13 songs, then we played
Thunder Horse, okay you use a hyphen
In a song that doesn't even have a hyphen
In the name, okay
Then at the end of the song, I saw an achievement unlocked
And then I saw another one of my friends
Playing Burnout Revenge after he left
His 360 in my hands, I plugged in my
MP3 player to the 360 and started using
My own music like Dragon Force and Anthrax
While doing takedowns
And crash events made my eyes open
And especially when I started playing with my friend
Communication, flawless, comma
Finally, compared to the PS
Doesn't even
Need a comma, okay
Compared to the PS3, it can suck my balls
Sony, I ain't buying your stupid PS3, period
I need some recommendations
On games and accessories to buy with my system
And I'm needing one on
Should I buy it used or new
I've been waiting for a price drop on 360
Comma, doesn't need to be there
I'm wondering which, WITCH
By the way, configuration I should start off with
Sincerely, dslover, PS
Keep the shows rocking
It wasn't even addressed to the right
People, was it?
We were in there
I don't know what type of games
This guy likes, it's so hard
To recommend games when I don't
Her inner grammar Nazi
Is crying
I don't know what type of games to recommend
When, put the Dalek away
When I don't know what type of games you like
Did he say what type of games he likes to play
Guitar Hero 2, I don't know
Get Rock Band Beatles, Guitar Hero 3
I mean Guitar Hero 3, Guitar Hero 5
What game has takedowns in it
Oh, Burnout
Burnout Paradise
Ok, Burnout Paradise and Split Seconds
Gonna be very cool, and that comes out
Need for Speed, Fuel
I liked Fuel even though a lot of people gave it
Kinda mediocre reviews
Yeah, I don't know
See, when you say what PlayStation 3 game should I get
Oh, LittleBigPlanet, I think that game's amazing
And I think everybody should
This person asked about Xbox 360
I thought they said PS3
That was the previous one
Oh, they want Xbox 360 games they should have?
No, they want, they're thinking about getting an Xbox 360
I thought they said PS3 at the end
I wanna know, I wanna know which
Version of the Xbox 360 to get
It was the last one
That asked about what PS3 games
Were exclusive and what to buy
You need to find
One that matches what needs
Do you have an HDTV
That can benefit from HDMI
Do you have, you know
I don't think you need all the frills
But I think you do need a hard drive
So I wouldn't get the one that doesn't come with a hard drive
I think that you need to stop thinking about an Xbox 360
You need to sell your DS
And you need to freakin' hire a tutor
Wow
If you would like Dark Soccer to criticize your emails
Please send us an email
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Okay, last one's from Deathwishing
Um, well
Thanks to this game, oh let's talk about Beatles
Rock Band by the way
Well thanks to this game, I like the Beatles
Sure, I liked a few songs before, but now I like them all
It doesn't even have all of them in there though
You need to go download some
Or pay for the new albums
Yes, pay, pay, pay, pay, pay
It's also very cool to learn about
The, about the fan with
Photos and pictures
Dark Soccer, I'm sure you saw the Jelly Babies photo
Slayers
My favorite song by them is Here Comes the Sun
And you know what, I think that's the part
That makes harmonics and the
Surviving Beatles and relatives of
The deceased ones very happy
Is that it's like a whole new generation
Discovering the Beatles, and I think what they
Would say to your email is, mission accomplished
I think that's a very good thing
So, um
Congrats to you discovering your love for
Beatles music
I don't, I always kind of
I respect the Beatles
I don't like, love them or
Foam of the Mouth about them
Or even really buy a lot of their albums, but I respect
Them, I really understand what they did for music
And why they were so popular
But I'm thinking that maybe playing this game
Will kind of open up the catalog, but
I also like the movie Across the Universe
Somewhat, I actually
I love that movie
I didn't like the movie, but I like the parts of the movie
It had nice parts
I do, that's a perfect
Comparison, it has nice parts, but the whole
It adds up to is WTF
Well, that, therefore the Xanady rating
I actually love the whole movie
Um, I was gonna
Say something else too, yeah, if you had to say
You had a favorite song by them, Rob, what would it be?
Probably Across the Universe
But I also know
Covers of that song that kind of, you know
Skew me a little bit like that
Don't say Fiona Apple
I do like the Fiona Apple cover, but I also like
Oh, he has one too
I also really like Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds
William Shatner version? No
And I like Strawberry Fields Forever
And I've been to Strawberry Fields
And it's beautiful, in New York City where the
Imagine Memorial is, so I think
I think Strawberry Fields Forever
And it does make me think of that scene in Across the Universe
Which I think is one of the better scenes in the movie
That seriously is my favorite scene in the movie
I would say that's definitely one of my top songs
I met the guy that was
In the movie, oh really?
How random, I know, there you go
Well, do you have a favorite song?
In what, in Across the Universe? No, Beatles, Beatles song in general
No
Strawberry Fields isn't in the rock band, is it?
Uh, no
It should be
Um, I did want to say though
Um, one of my
Probably my favorite favorite song of
The Beatles as a
Not just the band itself, but all the members
Was Imagine by John Lennon
I mean, that is a
Song that will live on forever
And it rightfully should
I mean, I think
That song, to me, even transcends
Anything the Beatles ever did
But that's just, that's my opinion
So, alright, anyhow
Um, moving on
Why isn't my Sim dying, by the way?
Was that it for the mailbag? Yeah, I'm trying to kill the Sim too
Alright, cause he's a dick
Let's get into the FUs of the week
I don't have a story to inspire the FUs of the week
But certainly Darksiders, but her Sim is a dick
Yeah, that's right, her Sim is a dick
So the FUs of the week go to that Sim
Ooh, DarkTetsuya in chat says
Less Sims, more show, please
Um, I can do both at the same time
And you are totally not one to talk, okay?
Addict! That's right, I can text message
At five at the same time, so she can play Sims
Rob
You saw the video, didn't you? Yes, I saw the video
That was fantastic!
It was stupid! It was great!
It was the most over-the-top thing I've ever seen
I know, but it was gorgeous
And I've been to the Rocky Horror Picture
Show 300 times, and that text messaging
Crash video was the most over-the-top thing
Yay, my Sim is drowning! Alright, shut up
Why'd you build a wall around the pool?
So that he couldn't get out?
You're killing your dick, Sim
And the Sims 3 have learned
That they can pull themselves out of the pool
Without the ladder? Yeah
Damn it! They're always getting smarter
She built walls around the pool
As you should
Well, you can't put a fence around him
But what I could do is the moving
The move objects on, and then I put
The little sign, neighborhood sign
Can you douse him with gasoline? No
Alright, can we get to the FUs of the week?
I guess
Um
FU to, um
Going back to work
Bogey!
Um
Huh, I had something
And I don't remember what it was
I guess FU to
Having a bunch of new locks for my arcade cabinet
But not any of the keys
That's it
Um, I don't really have a lot of FUs this week
I think, um, I've actually been in somewhat
Good mood, so, um, I don't know
FU to the fact that I'm not
Already at Disneyland, because that's where I'm going to be in a few days
I'm so
Freaking excited I need to be there
So, oh, did Death show up to get your little
Yep
And Death can't get to the person?
Oh yeah, Death can't do anything
Alright, anyhow
See how Sims is derailing the show?
Now you need to drown Death in a pool too
Because that'd be ironic
Back to games, Loki
Yes, I am not going to be talking
About The Sims
However, I am going to be talking about Fallout
And apparently Bethesda is suing
Interplay over the
Fallout MMO
Um
I guess, uh, you know
They wanted to make a Fallout MMO
I guess called Project
V13
And, um
You know, the problem is, though, that
I believe Bethesda has the rights
To Fallout right now
And, um, Interplay infringed on
Its trademark
So, um
Interesting
I'm surprised, though, if we did see a
Fallout MMO, that it wouldn't be coming from Bethesda
I would think that that would be kind of right up
Their alley
I think Bethesda's
Gotta be working on some MMO
Right now, but it's probably in the Elder Scrolls
Universe, not Fallout
But, who knows? Anything's possible
Both those games are huge. How about combining
Them?
Nuclear Holocaust in, like, the medieval
Times? A nuclear holocaust hits
The world of, what's the name of the world that
The Elder Scrolls is set in?
I can't remember. But that's what we need
We need a crossover game of the two
And it's an MMO. There you go
Or that they
Turn nomadic and they're back
Now to, like, you know, medieval
Technology
You know I still haven't played Fallout 3
Like, I'm like
It's Oblivion with guns. I don't know how I wouldn't like
This game, but I just somehow haven't played it
I'm too addicted to Warcraft
I have Fallout 3 and I have still not played it
I also have Left 4 Dead and still have not played it
Can I borrow your Fallout 3 if you're not gonna play it?
See, Fallout 3 is pretty cool
Is it?
Becky's Husband was playing
Quite a bit of it and it just looks
Really cool. I liked it
No, I've never heard anything but good things about it
And even when I've watched it, it looks like a lot of fun
Remember guys, I don't have time to play
Every game, especially when you're addicted to an MMO
Actually, no, I take that back
I think I did sell it already
Cause I don't have a lot of
Games anymore
Wow, you unloaded all your games? Why?
Different reasons
Alright, well
Do you think Bethesda has any ground to stand on with this?
I mean, do you think they'll win, Loki?
Yeah, if they have the rights for it right now
I mean, I know Interplay I think was the one that actually
Came out with the original Fallout, but
Um
I don't know, they're saying that
This has caused
Immediate, substantial
Inrepairable harm, I guess
I don't know
It probably wasn't going to end up working out for them anyways
Okay, well
I want to move on to one more story
Before we get to your phone calls tonight
And it has to do with the Nintendo Wii
Apparently, Nintendo
Is going to price
The Wii
Rumor is that the Wii is going to get its price drop
The first week of October
Which makes sense, cause the machine still costs $250
And you know, isn't the Xbox 360
Now $199?
Yep
And it has been for a while, so
I think the Wii is probably going to have to move
To a price drop
Their sales have been kind of slowing down
Well, plus it's time to update with the pack too
You know, I think it's inevitable
They're going to put Wii Motion Plus in it
And Wii Sports Relevance
I think is what you're going to find
In the new pack
No?
No, it's going to stay the same
Really?
I think it is
You don't think they'll bundle in an extra game?
No, because you can't get Wii Sports by itself
What about a Wii Sports and Wii Sports Resort bundle?
What about it comes with Wii Sports
No, because that would impact their sales of Wii Sports Resort
Really?
Yeah
Well, we'll see
This is from an early version of a Walmart ad
But apparently it is coming soon
I don't see the exact price though
It's just apparently the ad says
That it's coming
So we don't know exactly what the new price is
But
Now, Nintendo doesn't
Do Tokyo Game Show
But they will be participating in a thing called
Kyoto Cross Media Experience 2009
But that's at the end of September
September 26th to October 4th
So if they're going to announce a price drop
That's when it's kind of expected
To happen, because Nintendo never does
Tokyo Game Show
I don't remember the reason behind it
They kind of do their own media thing in Japan
Got it
So, very interesting
It is
I wonder if there will be a fitness thing
Like maybe the original Wii Fit
Or something, I don't know
Because then you'd have to throw in the Wii Fit
Balance board
I can see maybe some holiday bundles
If they're going to do anything
What they're going to do is some crappy
Holiday bundle later on
That it's going to have new Super Mario Brothers
Wii bundled in it, and maybe that's it
But, you know
At the same time, they may think that their
Game system stands alone
That it's just super awesome
That they're going to drop the price a little bit
Just to kind of spark some more sales
But, I don't know
I mean, we'll see
Yeah, I mean there's really nothing on the Wii
I'm really looking forward to
Even the new Super Mario Brothers, I'm very meh about
I kind of wish
I was just thinking the other day
Even though I understand they have the new
Super Mario Brothers and so forth
I wish they would just release a game called
Super Mario Brothers 4
And make it very similar to like Mario 3
But with the whole like
New graphics and the types of things
That you can do on the Wii
That's not 3D
Would that be Super Mario World?
Well, I would like to just see them make a game
Called Super Mario Brothers 4
That kind of does away with
You know, a lot of the changes to the Mario Universe
That might be too difficult for Grandma
Maybe
Maybe I just live in this weird fanboy bubble
Or I just miss the old school days
Of Nintendo, but
It'd be kind of cool
Alright, I guess it's time
For us to open up the Skype line
We're ready to take some calls
1-877-GAME-OLR
Go ahead and give us a call if you'd like to
Give a comment on any topic that you've heard about tonight
And we'll take some calls
To see what's on your mind
I'll ask if there's any last minute stories
Here in the studio because we have a delay
Oh, no, we just, we're getting our first call
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
Well, I'm the first caller, hey, this is X-Link
Well, hello X-Link, congratulations, you've
Beaten some of our serial phone callers
That seem to get through every week
It's been a little while since we've heard from you, what's on your mind?
Yes, actually I played
A really cool demo on the Playstation Store this weekend
It was called the Half Minute Hero
Which was really interesting
It had a Final Fantasy 1
Dragon War 1
Type, you know, NES
Roleplaying type feel to it
But they give you 30 seconds
From the time you start
To get to the boss
To beat the boss
But in order to do this
You like, really, it plays like
Basically you're playing the game in fast forward
I've heard about this, isn't this the one, doesn't it switch
Genres too, like every 30 seconds?
I remember, there's a demo for that
Out now? Yes
Is that on PSP? It's coming soon
Yeah, it's coming
It's coming on, it's supposedly October 20th
Is the release date for it
Is that on PSP or PS3?
PSP
Oh, I want to check that out, that game, I remember
When we reported on that game and I was like, oh, it's kind of like
WarioWare, but like
It sounds even cooler than, what was the
WarioWare clone we got on PSP, WTF, right?
WTF was kind of funny
This sounds even cooler, like
I definitely want to check this out, so
Did it feel like WarioWare to you, XLink?
Was it? Kind of, yeah, but it had
More of a, when I played it, it had
More of the Roleplaying type feel, so it's
More like playing Final Fantasy 1
On fast forward, like I said before, so it was
Really good though
Cool
How far did the demo let you go? I mean, it sounds like
With games like that, I wouldn't think you could do much of a demo
Because, well, you start on
This small island, and they're like, okay, you're
Here, the boss is here, go
And then they give you the 30 seconds, we'll count
Down, and then
There's like one or two islands you can choose, the first one
Does that one, and the second one's more complicated
Where it's like, here's the
Town, here's where the
Boss is, here's where it doesn't, where you can get more gold
For, you know, items and stuff
But in the town, it has a statue
Where we'll reset the timer
The 30 seconds, depending on how much
Gold per time you do it
So the demo
Was cool enough for you to go pre-order the game?
Oh, definitely, I would definitely
Pre-order it
It had like
Other elements I saw from the
Trailer, which really piqued my interest
Like shootings and stuff like that
And summons
A successful demo, thank you for calling me
To tell me about it, because I'm gonna go
Put that in my queue to download my PSP
No, no problem
I got to get my PS3 and PSP to work together
And I got a better memory card for my PSP
I'm all about checking out all the latest
Demos and so forth, because I know I've been critical
Of the PSP as a gaming device
But there are some gems out there, there's some real
Gems out there, definitely, and I'm looking forward to
Two percent, which comes out in about two weeks
I already had that pre-ordered and paid for
Awesome, well anything
Else on your mind tonight, buddy?
Nah, not really, I've been too busy
Doing my live journal game, so I've been
Really trying to catch up back on the
News here during the weekend, so
Of course I'll send it to you guys and give you guys five stars
I know what you're talking about, and I hope it's
Fun for you, in fact I'm going to be talking about
Live journal games on this show in a couple weeks
Because I'm going to be hosting another one, and I want people to
Sign up and play
Real quickly, it was very unique
The way some of you guys approached me and told me
Oh hey, if you like doing this kind of stuff
You might like doing this, so I signed up for it
It was very unique and very fun
And I got to meet a lot of
New people through it, and if
Everybody has to do it or wants to do it
I'll give you more details in a couple weeks here on Orange Lawns Radio
He kind of already had it lined out
He spoke very well, obviously tested
This connection before, and you know
Just kind of laid it all out there
When I asked him if there was anything else, he kind of
Added a little more, and I just
Very good, everybody take notes
From that last call, so sorry about that
Rama, now you have to follow that
I'm not trying to say we get bad calls
I'm just saying that if you want to know what I think
A perfect phone call is, that last call was great
So now you have to follow it Rama
What's on your mind tonight?
Well, I will do my best, but first off
Me and Jodea, we went to a
Classic gaming convention yesterday
Called Gamecore
First of them post
A link in the chat
Makes for great radio, doesn't it?
Yes, exactly, that's okay, I'll forgive you
Thank you, the pictures are on
Small and large size, because it was
A lot of stuff
I can call this convention like
Jamie's vault
Game six, that's how much
Stuff was there, you had a lot of
Classic arcade machines there
That were for sale, such as the
Simpsons arcade machine for like 400 bucks
Oh my god, I would have went home with that
Seriously? Even though I'm supposed to be
Saving for a new car right now, I would have went home with that
Dude, it was cash and carry
Do they really?
Oh my god, I should get an arcade machine
For my house, you should
Wouldn't my roommate fucking love that?
Sorry, by the way
Rob, I met your picture gallery, there's a lot of broken pictures
You might want to check that out
I don't know if it's me or...
It's an issue with the gallery sulfur, but if you click on the broken
Link, the picture will actually show up
Okay, I probably shouldn't look at them all
During the show, but I am looking at some of these things
Yeah, I see some things that are reminiscent
Of classic gaming expos, certainly, did they have a lot
Of playable stuff out there?
Pretty much they did, a lot of
Arcade machines, they had a
Roll of Dreamcast set up to celebrate
The tenth anniversary of the Sega Dreamcast
There was an actual Neo Geo
MVS machine set up, not the whole
Arcade unit, but the actual console
And board, you know?
I have an MVS board now
Sweet
Dude, what is up with everybody getting fucking Neo Geo
MVS boards? You, Bobby
No, okay, here's the thing
They threw it in with my cabinet
Because I was testing
To test my cabinet, they plugged an MVS board
In there, and they're like, okay
And he's all, hey, you want this board for
You know, 60 bucks, and I'll throw in this bootleg
48-in-1 cart with him, like
What?
What? I am so uncool
I have to get one
I have to fit in with
Everybody else, I'm gonna have to get a fucking Neo Geo
Now, just so I can feel cool
Sorry, Rama, I didn't mean to derail your call
See, this is an example of where the hosts
Derail your call
Which happens, what town was this
Convention in again?
Oaks, Pennsylvania, it was about
20 minutes outside of Philly
I wonder
Was it at, like, an actual classic gaming store
Or is there one, like, right nearby?
No, it was an actual
Convention center
Oddly enough, a lot of the people that are selling
Old school games and accessories
Were right out of Jersey
Because there was a classic gaming store in Pennsylvania
I was gonna visit when I was out there
Because, you know, I spent several weeks in Allentown for work
And I just never got out to the store I was gonna go to
I don't even know if it's still in business, it was a few years ago
I'm sorry
Did they do panels or anything else at this con
Or was it just mostly, like, a sales floor
That you could test the merchandise
There were panels there
But I didn't get a chance to check them out
But what they were mostly also focusing on was
Nerdcore rappers
And Chiptunes music
Nice
The list of people that were there
Performing was MC Lars, YT Cracker
Super 8-Bit Brothers
Armadillo Tank
This is cool
Yes, yes
Did you go to the concerts at all?
I went to a couple of the concerts
I walked in on Super 8-Bit Brothers
And since I was dressed as Luigi
I got a lot of props and shout-outs
Very nice
There was actually a couple of classic cars there
Such as the DeLorean and Kit
Huh
Well, sounds like you had a lot of fun at the convention
Is this something that travels
Or was it just the one place
I was talking to some of the people
That helped create it
And they were seeing some ups and downs
They had with it
So they're looking to do things a little bit differently
For next year
And also I have a bit of a game review too
Oh, please
Yes
There was a company there called Storm City Games
Independent publishing group
They had a game there
They were demoing out called Hands-On Tangrams
Like the Tangrams
Like we used to play with in junior high school
That game came out a long time ago
Interesting
Alright, well how was it
Did you get your Tangram on
Yes I did
And for 20 bucks I think it was well worth it
This is like a perfect time waster
If you need to kill 10-20 minutes while you're waiting for something
I came out back in spring
Okay, Debbie Downer
Hands-On Tangrams
They said they had the demo
And this is actually coming out October
Maybe it's a new platform or a new version
Maybe that's what's going on
Probably so
Alright, well Rama we're going to let you go get some more calls
But I'm glad you had fun at the convention
Sure, sure, sure
Can we talk to Jamie for one quick second please
I suppose
Hello
Hi
While we were there they were actually
Doing viewings for
Nerdcore Rising
Which is the film by
MC Frontalot
And they were actually giving a couple of them out
I
Had asked Rama to go up there
And see if he could win one
And he did
So we're going to be giving it to you Jamie
What
Yes
It's a copy of Nerdcore Rising
And if you open it up on the DVD itself
It is signed by
MC Frontalot
And it says
Win win win on there, we don't know exactly
Who wrote that on the DVD
But we think it was Lars
Sweet, we're not exactly sure
But yeah, just wanted to let you know that
And who is this on the phone right now
This would be Giove Day, Patty
Hello, well welcome to the show, I don't think you've ever
Called in before, but what a great first
Call, we like when new
People on the show give stuff away
I don't remember her talk, I know she's been in
Chat and Twitter and all that
We've heard her
With Rama before
Well that's awesome
And then you have to deliver it to me in person
I will attempt that
I swear to God
I will try and attempt that one
If not, I am actually
Looking to get to New York, possibly as soon as
The end of the year, so I may just have to come pick it up
That would work too
On behalf of Dark Soccer
And then I can forget to give it to her
I'm just
Just kidding, no that sounds really awesome
That's so awesome
Of some of our listeners to do
Thank you guys
And how did you like the con, Giove Day
How did you like it
I liked it a lot, it was
I'm not really big into loud
Crazy conventions, it was nice, it was mellow
But there was enough stuff there to do
That you didn't feel that you were bored
Alright
Very cool, and any favorite classic game
That you discovered or something that you played
No, I was actually
In the booth most of the time
Chatting with the guy next to us
Who was selling all the D&D
Stuff and he sold me
D&D dice for two bucks
That made me happy
Hey, nerds need their dice
Yes, we do
Well, we're gonna let you go so we can roll the dice
On another phone call, but thank you so much you guys
That sounds like an awesome present and you guys didn't have to
Do that, so I know Dark Soccer
Is bouncing as she's playing The Sims
Hey, I'm bouncing in like
Most of my parts, they're quivering with joy
Alright
Before this gets dirty, I'm gonna have to let you go
Night guys
Alright, take care
We've had some good phone calls tonight
Any call that gives Dark Soccer like something
Free is always gonna be a good call
That makes my liver quiver
There's just no way that that's gonna be a bad call
Hi, you're on Orange Launch, wait, did I answer this one?
There we go, hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
This is Cheeseburger
Hi, Cheeseburger, have you been on the show before?
I don't think you've ever called
No, I haven't, I've been in chat
You've got a deeper voice than I imagined
I've heard your name before
Like reading the Twitters and the chat and all that
And I just want to point out
The icon on Skype is
A picture of a cheeseburger
Why do you go by cheeseburger?
I know why I guess by cheeseburger, because I read his emails
Are you just a big fan of cheeseburgers?
No, it's extremely similar to my last name
Oh
See, I know
Okay, I get it
If you go on the wiki, I put it on there
Alright, cheeseburger, I'll stop interrogating you
Because you called us, what's on your mind tonight?
I know you played WoW for a while
And I just want to know why you got back into it
I didn't know you got back into it
I'm trying to think how far I want to get into this on a public radio show
The reason why I had to stop playing WoW
Was I found myself kind of getting too involved
With some of the stuff that was going on in the guild
And unfortunately
As seems to always happen in various guilds in WoW
There was some very unfortunate guild drama
Where people went their separate ways
And it really kind of turned me off to the game
Because part of me
Actually, all of me felt it was very unnecessary
And that I think if people across the board
Had been a little more reasonable
And open minded and hadn't reacted
And I think some very selfish things were done by certain people
And god, I hope I'm going to get in deep hot water
For getting into this on my radio show
But unfortunately, that's just kind of how I view things
And I just thought
You know, I am taking this too much
For something that's an online game
I need to just step away and involve real life for a while
And you know, at the same time
I was starting to date somebody new
And kind of get into a relationship
And you know, anything that happens in real life
Is more important than WoW
WoW is what you go to when you're bored
So the reason why I got back in
Well, I found a new group of people to play with
That have different goals in the game
That aren't so focused on the end game rating
And so forth
And just kind of rediscovering what makes WoW fun
And also I dumped the guy I was seeing
So I have a little more spare time now
It's kind of like what I told one of my friends
When she criticized me, she's like
I can't believe you went back to Warcraft
I said, this is what depressed people do
I wouldn't really say I'm depressed
It's just, you know, it's a time waster
But like I said, I think real life
If there's stuff going on in real life
It will always be better than WoW
And this is kind of what I tell people
I don't watch a lot of TV
There's some things I watch
But I don't watch as much as probably most people do
I'm playing while I'm not playing as many console games
It's just my entertainment of choice
But, you know, finding a balance is important
What realm do you play on?
Right now I am playing Alliance on Blade's Edge
Is the server I'm playing on
Is it alright if I join your guild?
Possibly, send me an email after the show
It's not my guild
That's the difference this time
Actually, I wasn't in charge of the guild before
But I knew the people in charge more
Than I know the ones here
As long as you're not a dick
Which you don't sound like from your phone call
I don't see why not
Cool!
Alright, well you take care of yourself
Thanks for the call, okay?
Alright, you too. See ya. Take care
See, I was gonna say at the end of that phone call
For the Horde! But then I was like, oh shit, I'm Alliance now
I can't say that. I'm playing one of each
You're playing what? One of each
One of each? You're on a different server, right?
I am, but I'll play on another
I think I'm actually gonna pay for it
But I'm playing
A blood elf
And I'm playing a goat girl
Alright, fair enough
You know what I mean by a goat girl
Yes, Draenai
Draeno!
Alright, that's gonna do it for the Skype line tonight
And those were all excellent calls tonight, so thank you very much
I think we'll leave it at that
I do still see calls coming in
But no offense, all those guys that are calling in
Have been on the show before
So we're gonna leave this as a
New caller, well even though Rama's not a new caller
So
Two out of three at best
Plus about three phone calls
Tonight's good, so
If you didn't get through tonight though
Twitter topics next week, we didn't get a lot tonight
And don't forget you can always interact with the chat room
Mailbag! Mailbag at orangelandtrader.com
Always plenty of ways to interact with the program
So let's get into some
Last minute stories, I never
Allowed Loki the chance
I'm not gonna steal one more cookie, because they're delicious
That's fine, they're there for stealing
And we can throw away all the
Bacon stuff, except for my plate
I need that plate
Well, why don't we feed all the bacon stuff to Dan?
Well, if he wants it
What the hell is this crap
Anyways, Sonic is
Possibly gonna come back in the way that it
Should've been coming back in the first place
None of these 3D
Crapfests with were
Hedgehogs and that kind of stuff
No, we're actually gonna get a brand
New 2D HD
Sonic the Hedgehog game
It's gonna be as old school fun
As it can get
And it's in the early planning stages right now
But they do have a wonderful teaser for
What they're calling as Project Needlemouse
The working title for the game
So that's kinda neat
King of Fighters
You may remember that they had a
Japanese
Shoot-em-up version of King of Fighters
Called Sky Stage
To Xbox Live Arcade
Well now it's also making its way
To arcades as well
And
I don't know man
I've seen screenshots and video of this
It just looks weird
I don't think King of Fighters really translates itself
Well into
It's one of those things I wanna see just once though
Just like for the WTF value
Yeah
By the way, the Sonic 2D thing
I'm a little nervous about that
And I'm with everybody else in the camp
Of OMG Awesome
Sonic 2D
Hopefully it's kinda influenced by Mega Man 9
Just to go back to your damn roots
But I am a little worried because
This is like the third time Sonic has been
Reinvented
And the last few have not been that great
So I really hope this one's good
I'm hopeful
But I'm a little apprehensive and I think I have the right to be
As do all the rest of you
Yeah
And then
Also to kinda go along with
Some stuff we were talking about before
You may remember that porn has been
Kind of
Making its way to the Playstation 3
Playstation Network
In Japan
Well now apparently Vivid Entertainment
Is hoping to do the same thing in the US
They're making a stand
Trying to convince
Sony that their porn
Should be on
The Playstation Network
Bravo I say
So that'll be kind of interesting
And
Apparently
You know to kinda go back to some of the
Piracy stuff we were talking about
We may have talked about this in the past
But yes
They have finally released the sequel
The official sequel to
Don't Copy That Fluffy
Don't Copy That 2
And let me tell you this much
And then promptly copied a floppy
And it's horrible
If I still had a floppy I would copy it
And my favorite
Thing about this is they're talking about how
Oh copying is a crime and stuff
And yeah piracy is a crime
Whatever but the guy that they show
At the very end there's like a real pirate
I guess who
He was selling copies of stuff
Okay I think that's something
That's gonna probably land you in jail more than
Pirating games for your own use
Can I get into this a little bit
Because I haven't seen the video
I've purposely not watched the video because I
Thought maybe I would watch it here on the show
So how long is it? Is it long?
No it shouldn't be that long
About five minutes
Well it's got a funny song
He raps in it
And we can laugh at it
I don't know legally how much of it we can play here on the show
It's a YouTube clip
I think they want it
Freely distributed everywhere
Even if we're critical of it?
Even if we're critical of it
So are we gonna copy the
The thing
Read that in a minute DarkSocker I know what you're looking at
It's related
Where is it here who linked it in chat here
It's this right
Okay hold on I'm bringing it up in studio sorry
Okay here it is
Don't copy that floppy 2
Welcome back to 90's Time Trip
It's that anti-piracy classic
Don't copy that floppy
Can I just skip ahead here
I don't wanna watch this whole damn thing
I just wanna see what the song sounds like
And I wanna see that bit at the end
He looks kinda like Max Headroom but black
Like is it just me?
But that's kinda what it looks like
Sorta
Don't copy it
Oh he does
See?
I don't know it's not
As funny as the other one was
I think the old 90's
Value of the first one is what made it so
Funny and catchy but this one
Is like
Technically enough is a copy of a copy
And you know how copies of copies
Like lose quality over time
That's what I feel this is
Like a unnecessary
Sequel okay I wanna see the bit
Woah what happened the thing stopped
Don't do that
Don't stoppie my floppy alright
Let me see the bit at the end
It's about the last minute is where the pirate shows up
Um yeah even
I wanna see
I wanna see the little like
Message to kids
Would I be immature for making fun of his voice?
Because
I wondered if that was a woman
I don't mean to sound rude
And or petty and I should really
Not be the first to talk but
Like
He doesn't sound like he's ever gone through puberty
Maybe that's
Is that a disease?
See what happens when you copy
Does piracy
Does selling pirated
Does selling pirated games cause
Your balls to go back into your body
Or something like
I think being in prison causes your balls to go back
Into your body
I had to look at his neck
I guess it's okay for me to make fun of him because he is a felon
To see if there was an Adam's apple?
Oh he's got too much facial hair
Even if that was drugs
A woman can grow that much facial hair
With hormonal therapy yes really
I wanna see the rest
Can I see the rest of this uplifting message here
Oh he's
Sad face
It was just a sad face that was the end of it
Nevermind
So now he's serving four years in jail
I learned my lesson
And now he's being made fun of on the internet
Well how about you don't
Sell pirated copies of stuff
Stupid
Of course see that's the people that they go after
Is the big piracy rings that
Cause companies money because they're actually
Selling bootleg copies
Amazetatsuma in chat says his body
Copied too much estrogen
And Rama says and people wonder why
Software is so fucking expensive
By the way that's a free download
At iTunes
Yeah better be it wouldn't be worth
Someone should go copy it
Ha ha ha
Oh you gotta love irony
Alright guess who's never gonna download that
Me
DarkSocker you had a last minute story and then we'll let Loki
Finish up if he has anything else
Yeah it's actually somebody
To quote Silent Scope
Let's play Metal Gear for real
A guy
In France who was
Accused of killing
The
There's an actor Roland Gerard
He was convicted with
Well supposed to be going actually in jail waiting
Trial for killing the guys daughter
And her friend
He escaped
From jail in a box
In a box
Playing Metal Gear
Not really
He had put himself
In a box that was
Being
Loaded onto a truck to take to southeast
Of Paris
And he broke free
And the driver didn't even figure it out until later
And so the guys from what I can
See is still at large
His name is
Jean-Pierre Trebert
I think so
Trebek
Not Trebek
But uh
I just thought it was kind of funny
That he shipped himself out in a box
Like Solid Snake
It's myself in a box
Anyhow sorry
Like Solid Snake you know
Oh no
Cause you know in the game he was in a box
And he moved the box in the truck
And says oh no the truck have started to move
The truck have started to move I love that
I need to play through old school NES Metal Gear
Hey that gaming marathon
We're doing on the 17th
I want to play Metal Gear for an hour
Old school
What?
Yeah
Hey by the way
I hate you
The other thing I wanted to say
I was watching Saturday Night Live last night
Those of you that follow me on Facebook
Probably saw I made a little joke
I'm watching Saturday Night Live drinking wine and eating ice cream
And two of the three things are good
There was actually
One funny thing they had on Saturday Night Live last night
It was a repeat but I never watched Saturday Night Live
So it was new to me
But they had like a sequel to the Dick in the Box thing
With Justin Timberlake and whoever that guy
Andy Samberg is that his name?
It was like something like
We're gonna fuck each other's moms for Mother's Day
Or something like that
It was actually really funny
I hadn't heard that one
That was the one funny thing I saw on that show
It's not on the album
Cause they tried to do this parody of the Governors of New York
For a very long time
Where it's like you're just watching someone embarrass themselves
And you're like please stop
Please stop
Much like you probably do listening to this show
Did you see that Tina Fey won an award?
For what?
For her portrayal of Sarah Palin
Well she deserves it
Everybody thinks that Sarah Palin
Actually said I can see Russia from my house
She never actually said that
People think she did
I just think it's funny
So Mother Lover is what it's called
And that's what they're saying in chat there
Thank you
Alright anyhow, Loki did you have any other last minute stories?
I don't have any last minute stories
That's it, we're done, we're out of here, time to go
Time to say goodnight
I guess that's it
That's gonna do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio
But before we close the door on tonight's program
We do have to go around and get everybody's
Final thoughts
Darth Sockery your final thought tonight
Bacon
I have now officially
Given up pork
Good luck with that
Well I'm gonna be very sick tonight
So it's fine
Have you ever talked about why you're doing that?
Or is that not something you want to get into on Orland?
I don't want to get into it
Loki, what's your final thought tonight?
My final thought is I'm gonna be working on my cabinet all week
Yay
My final thought is
Disneyland
Yay
Thank you guys so much for downloading and tuning into
Orange Lounge Radio
We really appreciate your guys' support
And remember if you like what you've heard here
All we ask, please tell a friend about the show
You know
Oh my god that scared the hell out of me
We had the window open and Dan walked up to the window
That scared the hell out of me
That was like Satan on my shoulder
Telling something
Did that get picked up on the mic?
I don't even know
Wow, if you like the show
Please tell a friend about the program
Even if you say you have no friends
Or you want to help us even more
Leave us a nice review on iTunes
Or one of those other websites
Like Podcast Alley or Dig or something
And help spread the word because we don't have
Thousands of dollars backing our show up
We do this stuff for free
That's all we really ask
Thank you guys so much
Have a great night everybody
And thank you for tuning into Orange Lounge Radio
The return of Orange Lounge Radio
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
See you next week