[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight, September 27th, 2009, a controversial rumor hints at big Sega and Sony plans, PlayStation Home spinoff is PSP down, and is the sequel to one of this year's biggest hits already in the works?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are that video game program dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_02]: So pull up a chair and join us for the next three hours as we talk about video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be myself, Rob Roberts, and as always, your lovely co-host, Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you, my friend?
[SPEAKER_08]: I am contemplative.
[SPEAKER_02]: Contemplative?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, that's a very good word for how I am right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Things you want to talk about on air or private things?
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to have a Dr. Phil therapy session here, an Oprah moment, if you will?
[SPEAKER_02]: Live on our video game program?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I am going to only be here for about an hour, and then I'm going to a temple tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: For...
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, services.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you have fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, sorry that you won't be here for the whole show, but certainly understanding.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you have other commitments, you have other commitments.
[SPEAKER_08]: Try not to ruin my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, this isn't the first time we've taped a show at Studio DarkSakura without DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's gonna be a little creepy.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you will be here for a little while to, uh, give your colorful insight, as always.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also say hello to Tech Master Loki!
[SPEAKER_02]: But what are we gonna do?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I don't have Sims 3 on my laptop right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, what we'll do, we'll have DarkSakura bring it up on her computer and just put the microphone kind of like at a distance from the speaker.
[SPEAKER_08]: I turn off the sound during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it'll be like she's here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we'll hear the simlish every once in a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that'll be her input.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds about right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what did you think about Tokyo Game Show this year, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, actually, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a friend that went.
[SPEAKER_08]: One of my friends from Berkeley, she lives in Japan now, and she went to Tokyo Game Show and posted lots of pictures of the cosplay and the win.
[SPEAKER_02]: I heard it was kind of a mixed bag this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our buddy Bobby Blackwolf, who of course tapes before us at All Games Radio, where we always tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plug, plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_02]: 5 Pacific, gotta plug All Games because they let us steal their bandwidth every week but of course there's a bunch of great shows on All Games and the one before us is Bobby Blackwolf and he was kind of talking his piece and we were doing a little phone call at the end of his show as we always do and he had mentioned that some of the things he had heard on Tokyo Game Show this year, not so hot
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that it depends on what you go there for.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I think she was just going there just to see and to look around, so I think she had a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I got the impression he didn't say who it was for whatever reason, which is fine, but I got the impression maybe because it was an industry person, so I didn't want to say who it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: So probably maybe from the industry perspective, it's eh.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the cool thing about Tokyo Game Show is that it is open to the public.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's something E3 is not.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Join us at our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to chat with us during the program.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are back after a week off last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, we're a little spotty in our schedule right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to be out next week as well, but I have some good news.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are going to have a best of show airing next week With some new content We're going to get together next week and tape some new content So we won't be live next week sadly But you will get to hear some of our best bits Going back a little ways too So some of our new fans in the past year or two And this will actually go to the podcast feed as well So you'll be able to hear it It'll air live first of course as it always does And then go to the podcast feed a little later So if you want to be the first to hear it Just stay tuned after Bobby next week like you always are Sadly we won't be here live But um
[SPEAKER_02]: Then after that, that should be it for the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be here every show up through Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think Christmas is on to Sunday this year or New Year's and all that, so I think we'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking at our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com Actdeft says the OLR dinner table, yay I want to welcome all of our new chatters as well I'm not sure who exactly all in chat is new tonight But I do want to say welcome if you are new to the program And of course welcome to our veteran folks as well Especially those of you that have been with us for a long time Like Dark Tetsuya, I think he's been here every week since episode one You gotta love that
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was, um, not very eventful, I should say.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really didn't play much of anything this week, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except for, um, like a game of pinball.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um, because I haven't paid for my World of Warcraft account because of financial issues here at home, which hopefully I'll be able to rectify next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played some Sims.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually did for about 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say, as far as the pinball thing goes, one game that I played a little bit of this week, not a lot, but was Zen Pinball on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I know Bobby was giving you some crap about that a while ago, saying, you gotta check it out, you gotta check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm gonna jump on board and say, you gotta check it out, because it is a pretty good pinball collection and some fun tables in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was finally getting into one of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's called V12.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a racing table, and it's one of those things where there's like a field on top and then a play field underneath the glass.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the way they do it on the PlayStation 3 is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_02]: XBOX 360 XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't play a lot of games, mainly I played Grand Theft Auto, Lost and Damned This time though...
[SPEAKER_03]: Since they went and broke our modded games, which had us depressed for a while, we didn't really know what the hell we were going to do with the game now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So to kill our time until the new expansion comes out, we've been playing ranked games actually, and it's quite fun because we kick the crap out of everybody that plays with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: And normally I don't talk crap during my games, but if there's someone else that's playing outside of our group, I talk shit the entire time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you now go, now ever since they banned your private games because you were doing the hack thing or whatever, you now go out on the public and play public matches.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: We play ranked games all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: So will you now take challenges from all our listeners?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, ranked games, it's just kind of a matter of chance getting into the same game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But honestly, right now, there's so few people playing ranked games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, at lunch, sometimes, because we have five consoles that all happen to be gold accounts, I can literally put all five consoles in a game and just take sniper shots at heads and stuff to kind of boost my stats a bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But cheater, cheater.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I only do it for the costumes and crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because really, there's no point in getting up the leaderboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess if you get ranked 10 or whatever, you get 20 points.
[SPEAKER_03]: Big fucking whoop.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I do want to say real quick before we get too far away from the topic, but Pinball FX is the name of the pinball game on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you HitStun who said it first, and BlackWolf points out it's the same company that makes both games.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why some of the tables hop across both of those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: And VidPower wants to point out, if you're listening live on this Sunday night, Pinball FX is on sale for the rest of today.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you are looking for... And I do have that game on 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just haven't played it in a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have a Bork 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm finally taking care of that this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a decent pinball game as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's pretty much the same thing that's on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I would totally urge you to check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but yeah, we're not really just cheating and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're just doing it to kind of... Because the other thing, too, that happens a lot of times is it will roll back our stats.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, like, I was ranked 4 the other day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, like, the next day I was back $25,000 and back to rank 3 again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there...
[SPEAKER_03]: Leaderboards kind of fucked up anyways, and instead of just wasting another 20 days to get the same amount of money, we're just going in there and doing headshot kills and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, actually when we get into the games with everybody else, I definitely hold my own, so that's no problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then, on top of that, really it's not game playing, but I've been working on my arcade cabinet that I got, and it's actually pretty much done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's
[SPEAKER_03]: I finished sanding the whole thing and then re-spraying it with black spray paint.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got replacement buttons, replacement joysticks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually converted the panel that I had because it was a two-player panel with three buttons each.
[SPEAKER_03]: I drilled three more holes in there for the other six buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should come over and play with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once my life stops being so crazy and I'm going on all these trips and stuff, I will.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I'm just going to get the damn thing at some point, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we'll rock out.
[SPEAKER_02]: A couple more weeks and DJ Hero will be out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rocket Beals will be like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: But honestly, between that and I've been getting back into WoW lately and you all know how that goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually did play some new games this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got to interrupt you real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you see the new video for Final Fantasy XIV?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that awesome?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cannot wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is going to be a whole new crack right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the greatest thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I can't go back.
[SPEAKER_02]: This looks amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to talk about some new games I played this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny enough, I played some portable games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played on the PSP Phantasy Star Portable I decided to pick up because I was traveling this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: and you guys know I like to play portable games the most when I'm traveling as I'm sure a lot of you do so I picked up Phantasy Star Portable which is kind of a port of Phantasy Star Universe to the PSP which is weird because Phantasy Star Universe is an online game but Phantasy Star Portable doesn't really have that it has an ad hoc mode so you can play with local people but you can't really go online and play the universe is like online as in like Phantasy Star Online was online whereas you can play it offline though
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, well, Phantasy Star Universe has both a single player campaign and an online mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Phantasy Star Online was pretty much only online.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the only place you could play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always played Phantasy Star Online offline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you had to have a hack disc or something to do that, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you just make your own private rooms or something, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you just play it offline.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could you do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, you could do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been so long, I can't even remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I didn't want to do dialogue because that was, you know, crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Fantasy Star Portable is kind of a port of a single player campaign.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is not the same campaign.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to make that clear.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a much different story going on to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's weird because they made some weird decisions with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A, they added voice acting, which is kind of not that great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the interesting thing that they changed when they ported Fantasy Star Universe to the PSP is that they made...
[SPEAKER_02]: Space Station, Homebase, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: because it says, well, if a person's name is green, they have new information for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't want to just kind of like sit there and highlight different icons on a 2D map.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like you're browsing the mall map at the mall saying, oh, I want to go to Hot Topic, I want to go to Sears, I want to go to, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just didn't like that design choice.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's my negative for the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The positive for the game is that they did a pretty good job porting it over to the PSP graphically.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game still looks...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: All together.
[SPEAKER_02]: And thusly, Phantasy Star Portable.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think I'm going to get some shit for this, but this is the reason why I couldn't continue to play the game online.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's too damn repetitive.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't have the variety that an online game such as WoW, Final Fantasy, even some of these other MMOs we've talked about in the...
[SPEAKER_02]: History of Our Gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I love the idea of an action-based MMO, but honestly, I feel so constrained as to what you really can do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do these same sword moves over and over.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, you can pick different weapons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I realize there's skill-ups, but you don't really mix and match things.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not a lot of strategy as to what you mix and match, like how you chain things in Final Fantasy based around the elements, or how you...
[SPEAKER_02]: P.V.P.
[SPEAKER_02]: is very intensive in World of Warcraft and even some of the boss strategies go way beyond hack and slash I think that's part of the reason why Phantasy Star Universe just didn't end up being that fun I think a lot of people I know that played this game just played it for a little while and was like, eh, bored and I think that's why it kind of got old quick Phantasy Star Online I think was a little different because I think at the time we really didn't have anything like it I think of a game, honestly, and I know I'm going to get crap for saying this but I don't care
[SPEAKER_02]: as much as I love Phantasy Star Online I've played both online and universe pretty extensively as much as I do love and respect Phantasy Star Online I think if that game came out now it would tank
[SPEAKER_02]: But, granted, it's unfair to say, well, this game came out 10 years ago, let's hold it to today's standards.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was important for what it did 10 years ago, and it's always going to hold a place in gaming history.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I just think the problem is, Phantasy Star Universe didn't evolve on that as much as it should have.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's its biggest weakness.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they should have a Gauntlet Legends online, like a version of Gauntlet Legends where...
[SPEAKER_03]: You can basically throw as many players as you want together and the game scales itself based on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: X-Link in our chatroom, chat.orangelongeradio.com, says part two for the Phantasy Star Portable is coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that is one story that didn't make our show roll tonight, but that came out of Tokyo Game Show this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are making a Phantasy Star Portable 2, and that looks pretty cool that they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the reason why I say that's cool is because it's going to have online multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But even then, what are they going to do to make the game not so repetitive?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my biggest question.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hardcore fans of Phantasy Star Universe are going to enjoy Phantasy Star Portable 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Personal Trainer Walking Personal Trainer Walking Personal Trainer Walking Personal Trainer Walking Personal Trainer Walking Personal Trainer Walking
[SPEAKER_02]: It's because I haven't reached my 3,000 step goal for the day yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once you hit your 3,000 step goal for the day, it turns green.
[SPEAKER_02]: There really is no game in personal trainer walking.
[SPEAKER_02]: All it does is that you communicate.
[SPEAKER_02]: The pedometer has an infrared device and so does the cartridge, which I thought was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: You hold the device to the cartridge and you press a little button and it communicates like a graph.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's how you walk today.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's where the hours were that you did the most walking.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you were an animal, you would be a night owl or you would be a morning deer or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Owls don't walk.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's kind of smart, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it says like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's tracking your activity in general.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing, and I can't stress this enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: There is really no game to this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a tool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They did add some frilly little things.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use your Miis.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually the first DS game where you can actually take your Mii from your Wii and put it on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take your me from your we on your d-s
[SPEAKER_02]: or you compete because the game actually comes with two pedometers so you can compete with somebody in your own house.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game will kind of pitch you against each other and see who's generating more power for the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the only online mode that this thing has is that you communicate with the Nintendo Wi-Fi connection and it will send your steps and it will say, this is how many steps the world has walked cumulatively.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can put it in this mode called Walk the World, and you can see how long it took for everybody to walk from the world to the moon.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that took about three months.
[SPEAKER_02]: So right now, everybody that's playing Personal Training is trying to walk to Mars, and they're about a third of the way to Mars from the moon.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but it's a little silly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I think it's a fun kind of silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a little noby-noby void.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was just thinking that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the thing, is that unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot more that could have been done here.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about me getting to compete with my friends?
[SPEAKER_02]: I also don't think the challenges are particularly that challenging.
[SPEAKER_02]: 3,000 steps in a day, either the device is very generous in what it's measuring, but in looking at the graphs, I can kind of remember, oh yeah, this is my lunch, this is when I was walking down to get coffee for the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of funny that you can remember those things, but I didn't find 3,000 steps particularly challenging.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of do that in a normal day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it's because I'm a teacher and I pace the room as I teach.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, can you increase it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: At least I haven't seen that happen yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can set your own goals for yourself, but the game always challenges you to get to 3,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I normally wouldn't get up and walk, except I get up and walk all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's to encourage people to have a normal amount of activity.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's what the game is ultimately trying to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think the other thing I want to point out is that the game also, you know, it gives you these little mini goals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, hey, your mini goal for today, watch the number of calories you consume.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or go for the longest walk you possibly can today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does give you little mini goals, but the game doesn't really reward you or punish you if you don't meet them.
[SPEAKER_02]: You track them on a calendar, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I find this game to be an enhancement to an already... If you think this kind of information is worth it to you, like you want to be able to track your walking patterns, you want a little bit of incentive, go for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think there could have been a lot more that could have been done with this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's worth $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: What they should have done, and what I'm guessing they probably didn't do because this is Nintendo and they take the easy way out, is they should have integrated this game where you can track that data for Wii Fit+.
[SPEAKER_03]: They probably didn't do that because then that would mean effort and they're not going to put that effort in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I think a better comparison would be EA Active.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think EA Active probably does the best job that I've seen so far out of all the games that have really given you a plan and having you stick to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So proceed with caution with personal trainer walking.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you are interested in this, I don't think you absolutely need it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And really what you need, not this game, is Walk It Out from Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: A game where you're not only walking, you're fake walking...
[SPEAKER_03]: In a game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Listening to music.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you're basically marching in place.
[SPEAKER_02]: This sounds idiotic.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a walking game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a rhythm music game that's walking.
[SPEAKER_03]: You walk to a rhythm basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have to leave your DS on to track it?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the little pedometer must have a pretty powerful battery in there because it just works.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just communicate with your DS once a day, you know, and then you don't have to leave your DS on at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: The little pedometer is very tiny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about the size, a little larger than a silver dollar, honestly.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, maybe not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe like a quarter of the size of the iPhone is about how big it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you just leave it in your pocket and that does all the tracking for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I do also want to say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is a bit of
[SPEAKER_02]: that's not an easy thing to have to say or do especially when you consider it's charity however there is a conflict has arisen with my day job it is one I have to do and I'm sure and as you can all understand work comes first even before some of these other things so unfortunately we will have to back out of the Extra Life event and not participate but we will make a nice donation on behalf of Orange Lounge Radio to one of the groups participating there may yet be something to be mentioned later we might do something in the future that we'll do
[SPEAKER_02]: so but as as far as us doing our show for 24 hours and all that we're not going to be able to do that because unfortunately I'm just not going to be available I have work commitments and
[SPEAKER_02]: yeah so that's a really sucky thing but you know best of luck to those guys I think it's for a great cause we'll certainly be donating and you know again good luck I hope we can do our own charity thing in the winter also I believe Bobby Blackwell's Friday Night Gaming is doing something in the next couple weeks I think they're doing it like two weeks after and I apologize if I'm misstating anything but I think he mentioned something about that so lots of fun charity events coming up all for good causes so keep your eyes out for that
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, for our UK release dates, we have on the 29th, Jam Sessions 2 for DS, and Left 4 Dead Crash Course, and Tales of Monkey Island, Lair of the Leviathan, and on the 30th, Fate Unlimited Codes, it says.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, on the first Fallout 3, Operation Anchorage, Fallout 3 The Pit, and Gran Turismo for PSP, there's...
[SPEAKER_08]: and Beater Raider on PSP and Dead Space Extraction, FIFA 10, Ninja Gaiden Sigma 2 and Risen for PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to quickly say Bobby in chat clarified his charity event is October 30th.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's him and his Friday Night Gaming project.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, keep an eye out for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beater Raider, that's the Timbaland game, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: On PSP?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Beater Raider.
[SPEAKER_08]: That just sounds vile.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds like beat it off a raider.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had to go there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't we do US next, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, US.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we're getting quite a bit of stuff this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting off with a re-release of Midnight Club LA, the complete edition with all the download content intact.
[SPEAKER_03]: Available for $30 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also this week, Tornado Outbreak on Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Family Feud coming out on the DS and the PC and Wii Battle of Giants Dragons on the Nintendo DS also Animal Kingdom Wildlife Expedition on the Wii from Tecmo Family Fun Football also on the Wii Ninja Gaiden 2 or Ninja Gaiden Sigma 2 or Gaiden sorry I keep mispronouncing that Ninja Gaiden Sigma 2 will be coming out this week as well on Playstation 3
[SPEAKER_02]: Hidden Mysteries Titanic on the Wii and DS My Sims Agents on DS and Wii
[SPEAKER_03]: Family Party, 30 Great Games, Outdoor Fun on the Wii Kingdom Hearts, 358 Slash 2 Days on the Nintendo DS On PC, Fallen Earth, Welcome to the Apocalypse The Wizard of Oz, Beyond the Yellow Brick Road on Nintendo DS this week Imagine Salon Stylist on the DS
[SPEAKER_02]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you chop hair with your stylus or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Undead Knights on PSP from Tecmo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Deck of Sports 2 on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Valhalla Knights Eldar Saga on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Grand Turismo, PSP coming to the PSP and then about a week from today actually, we're going to be getting Wii Sports, or not Wii Sports Wii Fit Plus, which will be available in the game only and bundle that's coming out on the Wii but the game only is $20
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, does it have like an internet thing now?
[SPEAKER_03]: DreamerTopModel on DS Risen on PC
[SPEAKER_02]: X-Edge Dash Shin Sangoku Mosu Multi-Raid Special PlayStation 3
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's kind of more of a light and fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Due to a freak accident during an important ceremony, you are turned into the puppy demon lord.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that sounds unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's got the Disgaea penguins in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell are these things named?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: The little penguin dudes from... God damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Somebody will remember in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have to say goodbye to Dark Sakura, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's on her way out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's actually the Trinity thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's actually one of those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a cross game where they have the characters from everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Jay Dizzle, who was first to say it in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, the name was on the tip of my tongue.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to go ahead and leave my name in chat just in case anyone wants to send me a message.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_02]: And hopefully we'll see you when you get back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if we'll still be on or not, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Should be.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on to some other releases on the Nintendo Wii on October 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dead Space Extraction Karaoke Games
[SPEAKER_02]: Hero no Kakera Shin Tamayori Haimei Denshu Momosuki Kofu no Misasiagi-O
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: so keep an eye out for that moving on to the handhelds real quick on the Nintendo DS this week nothing I recognize with name stuff by name but I do notice Blue Dragon is next week there's a Blue Dragon game coming out on the DS over there coming out on the PSP if anything this week Gran Turismo comes out in Japan just like it's coming out over here on the PSP also Macross Ultimate Frontier
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually missed quite a few titles here for the US as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Real quick, we're also getting...
[SPEAKER_03]: TheBeaterRaider on PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's going to be a new Cabal's game, Big Game Hunter 2010, also on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sideswiped on the DS, which looks like a pretty cool full-auto game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rapala WeFish on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Obscure the Aftermath on PSP.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then some other games, but I'm not going to mention those.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, now we can get into some news.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we're going to get into tonight's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now it's just Loki and I just holding down the fort over the next few hours.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you guys in chat as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, Loki's gonna steal Jamie's chair so he has a better place to sit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That chair is way uncomfortable and too small and I'm getting a headache from sitting on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh no, we'll have to figure out something in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, that's much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I have a folding chair in my car, of all places.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care, this chair is much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it is her throne after all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, why don't you start us off with some gaming news tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: So, in case you weren't aware, there was a wee price drop today.
[SPEAKER_03]: It dropped down to $1.99.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was one of those really well-kept secrets, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like numerous ads leaked out and leaks everywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so maybe it wasn't so secret, but it is official now, and that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: To kind of go along with that, though, in Europe, you don't get a price drop, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, you do get a new bundle, and they're going to be including both Wii Sports and Wii Sports Resort in that bundle.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I guess a little more bang for your buck, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny is that on last week's show, I predicted that that would be a bundle, so I was kind of half right, because I kind of meant that it would be a bundle here, but it ends up that it's going to be a bundle over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, we may see something like that come over here if they're really hurting for sales but I don't think that right now they're going to bring it over here I don't know if you did see though Wii Sports Resort though is going to be getting a different bundle over here actually in a few months where they're going to be including two Wii Motion Pluses with it instead of just one so you get a little bit of a savings there as well hoping to drive some more sales for that I guess
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to read this lousy statement in chat first before we discuss this story.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm amazed that Suma in our chatroom at chat.orangelaunchradio.com says, Headache for sitting in a chair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guess we know where Loki's brain was located.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a tension headache from my neck because it's bad posture in that chair and I have to sit forward and there's, I mean, literally the back of the chair comes up to like,
[SPEAKER_03]: and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, right now the problem is that they've... I mean, there's already plenty of systems out there, so they're going to be the number one system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure this will help.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Wii's going to be popular anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: Software-wise, though, there's nothing really other than the new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii that's that amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: A AAA title.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no real, like, must-have titles coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, there's going to be good titles coming out, but nothing like, oh my god, it's a new Zelda game, or oh my god, you know, it's, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii just seems like, eh, let's throw a game where there's four players and stuff like that and kind of run with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if I remember correctly, isn't that the one that plays the game for yourself or plays the game for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it has that whole little controversial pause and skip ahead mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was just going to say, old school is new school, remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not so hung up on the graphics and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm cool with the way they're doing the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to see a Mario game like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm fine with the game being that way.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm talking about the effort put into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not saying that they went and improved the graphics or anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saying, I guess the example would be Mario 1 to Mario 2 in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was some new levels in there, but they didn't go and add anything really new as far as the game and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whereas Mario 3 was completely new, Mario World was completely new.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, I don't know, this doesn't really seem... It's like half-assed releases is what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny, though?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think this game's still going to be huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know why?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody fucking loves Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I say everybody, I don't mean just gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody knows Super Mario Bros., the old school Nintendo game.
[SPEAKER_03]: People are retarded.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will buy anything that has Mario in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why Mario Tennis sells well.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fucking tennis game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's got Mario, so I must buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they came out with like... And you know what they're going to fucking do.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is how they're going to sell that crappy Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be Mario, like Dr. Mario's Vitality Sensor or some shit like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dr. Mario Visits Trauma Center?
[SPEAKER_03]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to have like a... If Dr. Mario was a puzzle game, that doesn't get your vitality.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: The character Dr. Mario will be in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, because people are like, oh my god, Mario must buy it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It... Well, it's, you know, effort for trying, but it's going to be hard with not that many big releases coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whereas the 360 and PlayStation 3 have a lot of releases coming out that are going to be really big titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, then again...
[SPEAKER_03]: The people that buy the Wii aren't necessarily looking for the big titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just going to buy Mario games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, I just want to go on record and say I think this new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: game is, for that audience, the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think you're giving it enough credit.
[SPEAKER_02]: From a gamer perspective, I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: But from an accessibility perspective and selling to the soccer moms of America, I totally get what they're doing here.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think the game will sell pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it were Mario Galaxy 2 right now, it'd be a little bit different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Weird that that's not out already.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they have teased that game that it is coming out, but it's surprising it's not coming out this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're first-party games now, it's only like one or two a month.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or not even a month.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, let's throw some really obscure DS games out there that suck and end up being like something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, okay, Professor Layton's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, that did well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fossil Fighters, though, is exactly the same as this other game that was put out called Fossil League DTS, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: And
[SPEAKER_03]: It came out from Sega a while ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's literally almost exactly the same game.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: It kind of tanked.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then Wii Sports Resort, it's doing well, but I don't think as well as someone would figure for a Wii Sports sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You would think that that thing would be flying off the shelves, like selling millions of copies.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be a gradual sell throughout Christmas.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that that's going to be under a lot of Christmas trees this season.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wii Fit Plus?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop re-releasing the same damn games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do something absolutely new.
[SPEAKER_03]: Something groundbreaking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, I think all these games, the new Super Mario Bros., the Wii Sports Resort, the Wii Fit+, these games are going to show up under many Christmas trees this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those games are still going to sell very well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I get, believe me, as a hardcore gamer, I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: They cashed out.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: They sold out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're making, they're shitting money at this point.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you blame them?
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario Hockey
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: and it did okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, not... Well, what else to sell to soccer moms but a soccer game?
[SPEAKER_03]: They had Mario Football.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, maybe that'd sell better.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: and then again, it doesn't matter because it has Mario in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, when I'm selling this to my customers, if I said, hey look, it's Mario Dodgeball or something, or not even Dodgeball, let me think of a crappier sport.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mario Curling, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: And they'd be like, oh Mario, I'm buying that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be something completely crappy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Mario...
[SPEAKER_02]: Water Polo or Mario... Hey, we might have some Water Polo players that kind of resent that remark you're making.
[SPEAKER_02]: What they need is like a Mario snowboarding game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about another Mario Paint?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I want to see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And where the fuck is that damn Bob Ross game that they promised us from a long-ass time ago?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where the hell is that shit?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did it get canceled?
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't we have a story on that a while back that got canceled?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a painting game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's perfect.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I do know that they do have a Mario snowboarding game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Mario and Sonic, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on and talk about something besides Mario, but we will stay on the topic of price drops, and we'll talk about Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, we already know that the Xbox 360 recently got a price drop, but there, of course, is a mole out there that helps out the website Ars Technica.
[SPEAKER_02]: and apparently they had reported earlier this week that there was going to be some other types of price drops going on and apparently there's going to be a holiday bundle that includes Pure and Lego Batman with an Xbox 360 Elite kind of like a little bundle coming out over there which apparently Joystick has their own mole, that's Joystick with a Q that got a picture of what it looks like although it looks like it might be like an Australian box because of the ratings on the cover there the other ones are U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_02]: Once pictures surface, you kind of know that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it was photoshopped either.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked pretty legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, supposedly getting a price drop over at Microsoft's World, the 802.11n adapter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, that is the new one because it's N. That's coming out for $100.
[SPEAKER_02]: The G is getting the price drop to $79.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still way too damn expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: for a feature that you should consider that the PlayStation 3 has built into it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And seriously, you could go buy a wireless switch or whatever way cheaper than that, and it would work perfectly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I have a non-Xbox 360 router.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a wireless gaming router that's supposed to work with all my systems that I just basically run a Cat5 from my box to this gaming router and it works fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It works perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when I had my PlayStation 2 online once in a while for the DDR games that were online and Amplitude and stuff, I would just switch out the Cat5 from the Xbox and the PlayStation 2 and it worked fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: It worked great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think the original Xbox I would use that with too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it worked great for all those systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Some comments in chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft says there's going to be a bundle that includes the wireless adapter, a media controller, 1,000 Microsoft points, and three months of life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and it looks like a big box of popcorn.
[SPEAKER_02]: How cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess is that targeted at the Netflix audience?
[SPEAKER_02]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Again, if you want to join our chat room, chat.orangelantradio.com as we tape on this lovely Sunday evening at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, it's not too big of a surprise, I mean, because the Japanese love their Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, of course... I love my Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm with Japan there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, announced at Tokyo Game Show to go along with the...
[SPEAKER_03]: Gonna be, you know, epic release of Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, the Final Fantasy XIII PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, but it gets better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's also got a 250 gigabyte hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently the FCC doesn't lie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, but wait a second.
[SPEAKER_03]: The FCC is only in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: So maybe that's coming out over here later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it is... Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it is coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's got...
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck, I wish I'd waited for the PlayStation 3 then.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're going to release a Final Fantasy XIII one here, that sounds awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it dropped in price.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyways, does yours have backwards compatibility?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have like the crappiest PlayStation 3 possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a fat and it doesn't have backwards compatibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I bought it six months before the price dropped.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just praying mine doesn't die.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I've got full backwards compatibility.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I use it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Never.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, backwards compatibility might be coming back, but that's in the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get to that story later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a big thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Out of price.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so this new system is going to be coming out for 41,600 yen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, it's got... It basically looks like a white, possibly silver system with a pink silk screen on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And to go along with that, though, there's going to be some more bundles coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, not in the U.S., because God forbid we actually announce something over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to be having a 250 gigabyte system for quite a few different games, including the new Ratchet & Clank, Kraken Time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also...
[SPEAKER_03]: Assassin's Creed 2, FIFA 10, Need for Speed Shift, and Uncharted 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these are all kind of leaked out of a Norwegian GameStop database.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so you better believe if the Norwegian... If they're getting it over there, we're probably going to get it over here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe not that many bundles.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be really freaking crazy, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure we'll get something.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to announce something in time for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just to cash in on that, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, if you see Xbox 360 getting one, you know that PlayStation 3 is going to have one as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, they do one every year.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've done it for the last three years with the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: This year, they're actually... Because the arcade, I think, last year had one game bundled with it, and then the other ones had two.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had the Kung Fu Panda...
[SPEAKER_03]: and Lego Indiana Jones.
[SPEAKER_02]: These games we had a million extra copies of sitting over here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, the Lego one sold pretty good, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: But that Kung Fu Panda couldn't have been a huge...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually supposed to be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like my kid's first action game.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki is now going to take us to the next story, which is probably, in my opinion, I think kind of the biggest news story this week, even though it is a huge fat rumor, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a fat rumor.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's absolutely true.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason why it's absolutely true is it's coming from Sega's FTP site.
[SPEAKER_03]: It just got leaked out there, and they're like, oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pulled it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's absolutely true.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's their minutes from a meeting that they had.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, there's a few things in there that don't really make any sense, but for a while, though, they did have a link straight to that file on their FTP site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Were you able to grab it when it was up there?
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't able to grab it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't able to get it either.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they have it basically transposed on here, so it's everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: But here's what it did entail, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of new... Wait, back up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this was from a meeting between Sega and Sony, apparently, that occurred.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was like the minutes... August 6th.
[SPEAKER_03]: ...we're sitting up in the FTP.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess August 5th was when the meeting was, and then August 6th they kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: So, the motion controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were talking a little bit about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of stuff that was pretty much at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mentioning it's coming out in the spring, which I think they've already mentioned anyways.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, seeing that they can differentiate with a different PlayStation SKU or something like that with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Talking about Alpha Protocol, Planet 51.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get through the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do-do-do-do-do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: PlayStation 2 emulator for PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: Confidential!
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't leak this out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently they want to sell all PlayStation 2 titles on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: See how that works.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why bother giving you a free update that includes the emulator for your system when we can sell you every single game all over again for a price?
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's weird, they're gonna, I mean, you know, we kind of saw this coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: But isn't it weird, though, that they're gonna have some PlayStation 3s out there that can just do it, and some that can't?
[SPEAKER_03]: I would hope that, I mean, if they were sporting like that, I would hope that they would actually update it like they did with the PlayStation... Well, actually, I think the original PlayStation 3s had the PlayStation 1 emulation already built into it, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: They still do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mine will still play PS1 games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they'll still play it because the software emulation is built in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But this is something they could add with a patch if it's running through software where you could be able to play the PlayStation 2 games straight from your drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just not because they're assholes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're assuming.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are making an assumption here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't know this for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the memo's not even out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're kind of making an assumption based on just how long we've been following the gaming industry and what we just kind of expect is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sony's going to find a way to cash in on this, and that's why.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't anticipate them being generous with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you remember a theory I had a while ago that the PSP Go  because I was like, why the hell  I mean, honestly, we're trying to find reasons to buy a PSP Go, and we can't think of anything
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get me wrong, PSP 3000, I can think of plenty of reasons to get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP Go, can't really think of one, unless you need a smaller system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess that would be one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I theorized a while ago, what if the PS2 games you can only play on the PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_02]: But the thought is, no, there's no real change in the hardware on the PSP Go, so what have you.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would make a little more sense to me and it's a little weird that they are going to lose one big perk about the PS1 games paying for them on the PlayStation Network because that is one thing you can't do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if you have the PS1 disc, you can't just beam it to your PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can only do that with the downloaded ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the thing I could see them adding the backwards compatibility because really the PlayStation 2 is at the end of its life cycle.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of game series already have cut their PlayStation 2 versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's slowly dying out.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll probably be gone by the end of next year.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, and then other things that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: They were talking about the possibility of import games coming out over here, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it might be neat to see some of those over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they're saying that also with the PlayStation 2 emulation,
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess they're saying, now this doesn't make any sense because it's all abbreviated, but it says, for company marketing money show, PlayStation 3 controller on TV ads, similar to EA Sports Spot, since you don't even know what the hell that means.
[SPEAKER_03]: PSP titles, massive franchises, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get to the good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, all this is pretty boring.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about the Dreamcast stuff?
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that was in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something about the Dreamcast games are going to be coming to the PlayStation 3, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't that something that was in there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I better read the abbreviated stuff here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Definitely, they're talking about the Dreamcast stuff coming in.
[SPEAKER_03]: The possibilities of Japanese import games and possibility of Dreamcast titles on the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: X-Box 360 X-Box 360
[SPEAKER_03]: I wouldn't buy a game for $100.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't care how many Sonic games it has on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just want to say, I don't think the DC Dreamcast emulator is as big of a deal as some might make it out to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because there already are ways out there that you can get the Dreamcast games emulated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like GameTap has some of the Dreamcast games available on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And since the PS3 is supposed to basically be a computer, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Xbox 360 is to an extent too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not surprising that they're able to emulate Dreamcast on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they are giving them the option to be exclusive on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says if we give them a long period of exclusivity, they will give us more marketing support.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it says if we provide a list of Dreamcast titles, Sony will let us know which ones they're interested in having exclusively.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there may be some that you see exclusive because they're going to go where the money is.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about a patch that lets me on PS3 read my Dreamcast discs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wouldn't that be amazing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, too bad the Dreamcast discs are a proprietary technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know that's not going to happen, but a man can dream.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that proprietary.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, shit, I can read them on my computer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wasn't there something special to them, though, where you had to compress some Dreamcast games to fit on a CD because they actually held somewhere between a CD and a DVD?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like GD-ROM or something, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that was the whole thing they were saying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I'm thinking Saturn, my mistake.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: All that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of it is still, you have to consider, is in negotiation.
[SPEAKER_02]: That doesn't mean all of this is happening tomorrow or at the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of this, you know, you were talking about talks between two companies, and this whole leak might also change things dramatically.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, heads are rolling over this shit right now about the fact that this got out on the internet, whoever uploaded it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if it was an accident.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's going to be huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: And could actually damage the relationship between the two companies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I think ultimately, you know... Sony just can't keep a secret.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be fair, neither can Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But like, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: A big nugget like that, you know, with backwards compatibility.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really got screwed at E3 this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how Jack Trenton came out there and he was like, Hey, there's one thing you didn't spoil, Final Fantasy XIV, huh?
[SPEAKER_02]: You didn't see that one coming, did you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Everything else we got screwed on, but at least we got to wow you once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, speaking of Sony, it is official.
[SPEAKER_02]: There will be no UMD conversion program for the PSP Go, meaning if you wanted to convert your UMD discs, they were talking about this whole, you know, you could do a kiosk and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh, not happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: It all boils down to, and actually, the way it's phrased kind of makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me read the quote here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were evaluating a UMD conversion program due to legal and technical reasons.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will not be offering the program at this time.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a Sony Computer Entertainment of America spokesperson in an interview with Kotaku.
[SPEAKER_02]: But not surprising, the reasons that kind of when you further get into it have to do with the game distribution licensing and probably the agreements with the developers.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it does and it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: by March 31st, 2010.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think you have to connect your old PSP model to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's like they know you have both, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just for buying the machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to connect your old one.
[SPEAKER_02]: You will get three free UMD... I'm sorry, UMD-less games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they are from a list.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't get any old games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to pick from a list that includes Killzone Liberation, Wipeout Pure, Patapon, some of the BuzzBrain and BuzzMaster games, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's more of an incentive than we're getting here, at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still, even with the three free games, I'm kind of sitting here going, So let me get this straight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Your system is more expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's no way for me to transfer my old games that I bought to this new system.
[SPEAKER_03]: The system doesn't do anything differently.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't play my UMD games on it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's chic, and it's new technology, and it fits in your pocket.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And then that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to die a slow death.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the system is going to bomb terribly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not saying that as a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm saying that as a I can imagine people going into their local GameStop or GameCrazy just knowing the type of people that usually work there at the front desk making decent recommendations.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be a lot of these people that say, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: That's where it comes in.
[SPEAKER_03]: A credit card.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need a credit card or these points cards in order to get it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the parents are going to say, fuck that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's in GameStop or GameCrazy's best interest to sell the ones that require the discs anyway, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And on top of that, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: On top of that, and I hope this doesn't happen over here because really it's just like, you did what?
[SPEAKER_03]: On top of that, they're dropping the price to the $3,000.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?!
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you stupid?!
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the system's more expensive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, let's... Well, no, that's great, because the PSP 3000 is the system you should be getting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would recommend you get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, but it's like you're not gonna sell more PSP Go's if... It's like they're putting it out there to get people to go, well, you know, hey, I want a PlayStation Portable, but I'm not buying this Go, I'm gonna buy the 3000.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha, we tricked you, you bought a PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't see any GameStop employee recommending the PSP Go when they can say you can get $3,000 and you can get a game or two for the same price which would look better under the stocking I think the system with a couple games I'm very curious to see how the sales figures look this system comes out this week right?
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Puzzle Quest was basically Bejeweled anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's been playing Bejeweled Blitz like fucking crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, she's been beating my scores.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's been just sitting there playing it all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's addictive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here...
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't Discount Facebook Gaming
[SPEAKER_02]: Look at your friends list.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have non-gamers at your friends list, look at the amount of Facebook games they're playing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the moms playing Farm Town and Bejeweled Blitz.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gamers, look out.
[SPEAKER_02]: This Facebook games thing is going to be huge.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully there's some good news for us in there too, but I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even I play Bejeweled Blitz.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a nice little time waster.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can totally respect what PopCap is doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they're a pretty cool company, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's funny, we're actually clearing out some old-ass games that we've been just sitting on.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one of the games that we have is the Jonas Brothers, or not the Jonas Brothers, it's the Naked Brothers Band.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a karaoke game, but we're selling it for like five bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot that was even a musician.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly, but it's got a USB microphone, and a lot of those USB microphones, regardless of what system they're on, will work with Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: We used, at my birthday party...
[SPEAKER_03]: The old PlayStation 2 Karaoke Revolution mic worked flawlessly.
[SPEAKER_02]: I noticed at Fry's, next to the Rock Band 2 games, they sell just regular USB mics in the same section.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, if you got a microphone from Karaoke Revolution, pretty much anything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're all using those stupid Logitech mics.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just give it a shot.
[SPEAKER_03]: It probably will work.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're looking for an extra mic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so beyond all that stuff, they've also added in some new... They tweaked the hammer-ons and pull-offs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently something that they had improved for the Beals Rock Band is now being added into Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also Audition Mode, which will allow people on the Rock Band Network to be able to upload the songs that they've created from their PCs to test them out in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: So before they upload them into Rock Band Network and stuff like that,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and also I guess in the sort menu you may now arrange the songs according to star rating that you've achieved in each of them and also unplayed songs will be grouped together accordingly.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Taiko no Tatoujin
[SPEAKER_02]: Tycho Drummaster Tycho Drummaster
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Scratch, The Ultimate DJ.
[SPEAKER_03]: Man, haven't heard about that game in a while, but they've announced a few more tracks coming out available now, including, and of course this is all going to be R&B stuff, Push It, Salt-N-Pepa, Friends, Houdini.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope it's the Glee version of Push It.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Gifted, starring NASA, featuring Kanye West, Santo Gold, and Like Lee.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to let you finish, but Hip Hop Master was the best hip hop game in the US of all time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Looking Fly, by The Mers, Skanky Panky, Kid Koala, Iced Lightning, by RJD2,
[SPEAKER_03]: They Reminisce Over You by Pete Rock and Seal Smooth.
[SPEAKER_03]: And Life in a Cage by The Knucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: And of course that...
[SPEAKER_03]: Also is added to the previously announced artists and licensed tracks, which I'll read now since there's only four of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Peter Piper, Run DMC, Feel Good Inc.
[SPEAKER_03]: by The Gorillas, Hot In Here by Nelly, and Mastermind by Deltron 3030.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as this isn't my preferred genre of music, there are some very catchy, dancey party songs in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am curious about this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is yet another one that got pushed back to 2010, though, after the whole lawsuit and mess and studio change and all that, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably a good thing anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's too many damn music games coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well guys, we are getting towards the end of Part A tonight, but not before we cover the classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I fucking love Railroad Tycoon because it was made by Sid Meier.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know he is a god amongst PC gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: He made the Civilization series.
[SPEAKER_02]: He made a game I actually really like a lot on the PC that I almost picked for tonight, but I couldn't find a good YouTube of it anywhere called Covert Action.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when I was thinking about it, I was like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Railroad Tycoon, especially the deluxe version, I spent hours upon hours playing this as a kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let me tell you a little bit about Railroad Tycoon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: SID MEIER'S RAILROAD TYCOON
[SPEAKER_02]: You could even do England, Europe, whatever You basically manage the business, you manage where the trains are going to go You build industries and basically transport goods from one end to another It's kind of a strategical game But it was cool because you kind of built your own little empire And it was very kind of single player They didn't have a lot of multiplayer in it That didn't show up really until Civilization, kind of a little later on But it was a cool little strategy game that you could kind of play on your own
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: by the way the original Railroad Tycoon and one reason I bring this up is the classic game of the week it is actually free because when they went back and released a sequel to the game later on called Railroads they actually made the original Railroad Tycoon free and I'm not sure if you can still get it on the website but it was basically free out there on the internet for you to download so you can hear some ambient music of building the tracks between the different towns there it looks like right now they're playing on a South African map and they're kind of connecting Johannesburg with some other towns there um
[SPEAKER_02]: Railroad Tycoon, of course, got a reskinning and a redone version called Railroad Tycoon Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was released in 93.
[SPEAKER_02]: It basically upped the graphics from the, like, 16 color level they were at in the original to more VGA graphics, but unfortunately the game was very buggy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember it being super buggy, but they do say that the game ended up getting very buggy in certain parts of the ending.
[SPEAKER_02]: SIDMAYER SIDMAYER
[SPEAKER_02]: Railroad Tycoon 3 had a full 3D environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could build overpasses, tunnels, totally improved graphics, but honestly, none of the sequels really kind of, I think, reached the way the original did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sid Meier did come back to do a sequel to the game in 2006.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was Sid Meier's Railroads.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically different scenarios and trains that you could do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a little less focused on industry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had a more streamlined interface for doing the track laying, but it was more focused on the full 3D graphics and some real-time gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: so that is my classic game of the week I know there's not a whole lot else to say about it but I think it's a game you just kind of have to check out it is very yes choo-choo it was fun to kind of build the different buildings and watch your station get bigger and bigger and watch the new trains because you get to pick the cars that were with it and how much they would transport it's very much a micromanaging game but it's a lot of fun and one of my favorite strategy games of all time Railroad Tycoon the one I spent the most time on was Railroad Tycoon Deluxe
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll just call the whole Railroad Tycoon series my classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you ever play Railroad Tycoon, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: No?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you play any of the Sid Meier games at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: There's this little train that they drive around the complex that little kids get to ride it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's not on a track or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just kind of drives around and takes kids on.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I was convinced that the train was trying to run over me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I was like, Melody, we've got to run away from the train.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she was laughing her ass off because I was really, really drunk at this place called the Alcatraz Brewery, which really cracked me up because it was like
[SPEAKER_02]: that's what it felt like because you know we're from Northern California we go to San Francisco a lot I'm sure it was kind of funny seeing like the big replica of the Golden Gate inside the building and just all this stuff all the little tie-ins with NorCal terms so it's cute so there you go anyhow sorry for my tangent that was your classic game of the week Railroad Tycoon
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to take a quick break, but we will be back with plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are not done yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got more news coming up in Part B. Part B tonight, we're going to talk about some rapid-fire news, including another big game delayed until 2010, PlayStation Room we're going to talk about after the break, and World of Warcraft went down for a couple months.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank God it didn't happen here, or places probably would have burned down.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday evening, September the 27th of 2009 for the second half of our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: The tape's live every Sunday night on All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got a lot of great programming every night at All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they even have some new shows and I think they're...
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, that guy, Jeremy Soul, I don't know if it's Soul or Soleil, he does some awesome orchestral music.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, just between that and Oblivion, I really enjoy his stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really sounds like kind of listening to a movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes, I want to play Guild Wars sometimes just to hear the music.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just wanted to give him props, because I think he did some really great work there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think he did the music for Prey, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that was one of the best parts of Prey, was the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know a lot of people didn't play that game, but it was actually... All things considered, that was a shooting game made for people that really fucking suck at shooters, and so it was perfect.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just ended abruptly.
[SPEAKER_02]: The story kind of just cut off.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think development was probably cut off of that game, because that game was going on Duke Nukem Forever time...
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy VIII is out on the PlayStation Network in Japan
[SPEAKER_03]: Disney, there was that rumor of the Epic Mickey game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Disney is set to make an announcement in London on the 28th of October.
[SPEAKER_03]: People think it's going to be this announcement.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, apparently there was also a teaser in Game Informer saying that this announcement is coming as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, could it be something that's on the cover of the next Game Informer?
[SPEAKER_03]: God of War 3 Demo
[SPEAKER_03]: Check out the demos.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sweeten the pot a little bit for the people who already own God of War 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think you definitely owe it to yourself to play these games if you haven't yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be worth checking out, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: And finally, something for free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, if you have LittleBigPlanet, you will be able to soon pick up Viking costumes for your Sackboy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these will be coming soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they've actually got a website that you need to go to to go through this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Family Zone, which is, I guess, a cross promotion with Sony Pictures.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you're going to be able to, I guess...
[SPEAKER_03]: Go to their website, and they actually have a link here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it's the PlayStation site.
[SPEAKER_03]: US.PlayStation.com slash SonyWonderGames And then you just go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a button to redeem a code, and you can get the free Viking costumes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's not something you can just go on PlayStation Network and download, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, apparently not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cross-promotion, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, as Loki spoiled earlier in the show, there is a little bit of crossover going on between Ninja Gaiden and Dynasty Warriors.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's, of course, because of the Tecmo-Koei merger that happened not that long ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ryu Hayabusa is actually going to be an unlockable character in Dynasty Warriors Strike Force.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's not where the love stops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, there's going to be unlockable Zhao Yun and Sung Shang Xiang costumes in Ninja Gaiden Sigma 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I'm sure I completely butchered those names.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deal with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be a lot of crossover happening there, I'm sure, to no one's surprise.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blur was a racing game I was very much looking forward to this year and I will just have to look forward to it a little longer it has been delayed to 2010 with a host of quite a few other games that have been delayed to 2010 which is now looking pretty full the delay happened because according to Activision CEO Mike Griffith they need to quote fully optimize the vision Bazaar set out to create for Blur including a distinctive and groundbreaking multiplayer mode that will appeal to a broad audience I take that to mean multiplayer was fucked and they needed to fix it
[SPEAKER_03]: I also take that as we're not going to compete with ourselves and decide to push Blur back a little longer since they're the ones releasing Modern Warfare 2 and it's supposed to be coming out around the same time, within a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they've
[SPEAKER_02]: Did it for that reason, then F them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if they did it for the reason that they needed to go back and make multiplayer better, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, you know, I'm sure if it came out and the multiplayer was screwed up, bitching upon bitching on the blogs about how borked multiplayer is and we need to patch immediately, etc.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, if it's truly to fix multiplayer, then fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've never remembered the multiplayer in Project Gotham being too bad, so I can't imagine that that would be really an issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, hey, give them the extra time, whether it be for, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think there's room for more than one
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of games are kind of like, you know, there's going to be a lot of people buying Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's move our game a little away from it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Smackdown vs. Raw 2010.
[SPEAKER_03]: Normally a title comes out in the middle of November.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now it's coming out in the middle of October.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is a little bit of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: But not with Modern Warfare 2 being there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Grynn Studios
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: And who's cashing in on this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami
[SPEAKER_03]: Are they the ones behind it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Go, Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: God forbid we get a good music game from them, but seeing it, Twilight.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we get sparkling vampires.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, they go where the money is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not a fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry to be a hater.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have some friends that are into Twilight, but I just don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, honestly, it's coming out before the second movie, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: And granted, I'm sure people that are playing this game probably read the books.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deathwishing in our chatroom is making his thoughts very strong.
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, kill the devs, kill them all, fucking skull fuck them.
[SPEAKER_02]: That might be a little bit harsh.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, skull fucking?
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, that's pretty harsh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just saying...
[SPEAKER_03]: How much trivia can there be for Twilight movies if there's one Twilight movie out already?
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, this game is slated right now I think for... I want to say I thought it was October.
[SPEAKER_03]: Probably around the release of New Moon.
[SPEAKER_03]: But New Moon's not supposed to be coming out until after it, so either it's going to spoil the...
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's really going to spoil the plot of the movie because there really is no plot to the movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, and the books have been out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you can go read the book, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've decided this story has taken up way too much time on our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I do want to read this witty comment from chat.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw in chat says, We need a seen it OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_02]: No video.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess you could call it hear it OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would anyone actually play that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the listeners know the trivia of the show better than I do.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got this best of I've got to do next week that we're going to be taking some parts of the show and then kind of doing some new stuff with it as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know where I'm going to find out where all the good bits are?
[SPEAKER_02]: Our Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_02]: The OLR Wikipedia references what episode number some of the funniest stuff was in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like what episode the whattheyplay.com snap was in and some of these other things I'm going to kind of pull and put in there is all in there, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, let's get to some Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I forgot to get the theme music for Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just so broken tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't multitask.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie and I here is ruining everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm getting it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to do theme music tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's just get to the Twitter topics because I don't want a dead air here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going to the Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, we got quite a few tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ray Ayanami says, here's a story that people might actually care about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mushi Misama Futari for 360 is going to be region-free.
[SPEAKER_02]: A region-free 360 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: They call it a bullet hell shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: He links us to an article on Kotaku that talks about a shooting Xbox 360 game.
[SPEAKER_02]: No screenshots from the gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one up here in the upper right-hand corner.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it looks like one there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be region-free, so this game comes out in Japan, but you would actually be able to import it here in America and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of cool because a lot of the 360 games that come out over there are not region-free, especially in Japan, man.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just like, fuck you guys, you ain't gonna import this shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Raisin Chat right now says it is an existing arcade game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say, we saw a clip of this on an earlier show, because I'm looking at the screenshot now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it does look familiar.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's the thing that sucks, too, because my arcade cabinet, I could play vertical games, but it's such a fucking pain in the ass to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to rotate the monitor and all that shit, and I just don't want to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: TigerClaw305 on Twitter wants us to mention the Florida Fugitive was apprehended after attempting to steal DS games.
[SPEAKER_02]: He links us to an article on Joystick where apparently this guy was out there trying to steal DS games.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a loss prevention specialist.
[SPEAKER_02]: got to stop this shoplifter the fugitive's name was Daniel Larson he was already wanted for violating probation and apparently he shoplifted $120 worth of Nintendo DS titles from the local Walmart but a loss prevention officer actually caught him and stopped it joystick the blog goes on to joke don't tell them about my insatiable addiction for Imagine Babies games I know you could say I planned on pawning them to buy heroin please come on then man this would ruin me
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to be able to read all the tweets tonight, but let me get to a few others here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ryan Belknap on Twitter wants to know, what game coming out this fall are you looking forward to buying?
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, it would be Dragon Age and Press Your Luck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Games this fall.
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Hero and Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and of course...
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, because it's more of a download title, but Grand Theft Auto, The Ballad of Gay Tony.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, most everything I was looking forward to got pushed back to 2010, Blur, White Knight Chronicles, but one game that's still coming out that I am looking forward to a little bit, there was one, I just had it, and now I just get my memory.
[SPEAKER_03]: New Super Mario Bros.?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dang it, no, I'm not really interested in that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: What kind of a game was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lego Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_02]: DJ Hero DJ Hero DJ Hero
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I heard about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think this is in our show role either.
[SPEAKER_02]: This just came up today.
[SPEAKER_02]: He links us to an article on Kotaku that talks about apparently there's a crash screen in Need for Speed Shift that when you go into the PlayStation Store, it crashes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the funny thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on the 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: with the PlayStation Store logo showing up and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what the hell happened or what you do to get this, but apparently this is a really bad bug.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: When navigating menus today, when connected to Xbox Live, the game suddenly crashed again.
[SPEAKER_02]: When my rage subsided and I got a better look at the screen, I was pretty shocked at what I saw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was my Xbox 360 version of Need for Speed Shift really trying to access the PlayStation Store?
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft's not going to be happy about this at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So apparently there is a bug in the game where it tries to access the PlayStation Store.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoops!
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: 360 can be fixed PlayStation Room
[SPEAKER_03]: Interesting enough, the logo for PlayStation Room is R-Infinity-M.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may remember way back in the day when there was a rumor, according to a trademark, that the PlayStation DualShock 3 or 6-axis was going to be, well...
[SPEAKER_03]: We called the poos because it was P-Infinity-S.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I did not remember this until you said like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You joked that it was poos.
[SPEAKER_02]: We did joke about this on the show a while ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm thinking maybe that wasn't for the controller.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it was like PlayStation Infinity or some crap like that and it was actually this.
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like home with a big anime flair to it and really scaled down.
[SPEAKER_03]: Neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have they really said what the hell you're going to be able to do with it, or are we only seeing these screenshots of these kind of chibi characters?
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, by the way, it should be said, even though you're saying it's kind of like Home, it doesn't really, I mean, it looks like a very, very, very much spin-off.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not your same characters, it's not that same 3D environment.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like Home, like, you know, the Disney's, was it, um... Looks like some of the chat rooms I would see on Prodigy back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like the Channel D stuff, or, I forget what they call it, on, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: D-Gamer, that's what it was, on the Disney's DS titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's very similar to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not, but it's a similar type of service.
[SPEAKER_02]: Funny enough, Ray Iannami in our chatroom says, wasn't that like three years ago that that joke happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: He says, wait, I've been listening to this train wreck for three years now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, maybe it was, I don't think it was quite three years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was before the PlayStation 3 came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, remember, we were, like, were they going to call the controller?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Poohs The Poohs
[SPEAKER_02]: But what has PlayStation Home really done for PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_02]: Even though I got a plug that we do have a club on PlayStation Home, and there's got to be a good handful of people in it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been getting slow requests for invites.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't imagine this would be too popular.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, yay, you can be able to run around in Avatar and stuff, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: I did check out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did sign into home.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Home's one of those things I'll just kind of poke around in if I'm really bored.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did check out the new SingStar space in home and it's a little ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Graphically, it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a nightclub and it's laid out like a nightclub.
[SPEAKER_02]: Graphically, it's kind of cool, but you log in there, there's really not a lot to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do all the different dances on the dance floor and you get three shirts.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just quickly go through the character and do all ten dances or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you get shirts to pimp out their products.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I gotta say though, it was nice to look at for a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, oh hey, they put a little work into this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This actually kind of looks like a nightclub and I like how when you dance, the little spotlight on the floor is different colors and it's all high def.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, done now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not sure exactly what I gained out of this, except I guess maybe knowledge of the SingStar product.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a little video wall that'll circle through different music videos that are in the game, and you can actually pick which video you want to come up next on the wall.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the catch.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a 30-second clip of videos.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not even like the full, like, you can't touch this, or baby one more time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just these 30 seconds of it, not the whole clip.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jay Dizzle in chat reminds us, Home gave us hamsters versus humans dance-offs.
[SPEAKER_02]: How could I forget?
[SPEAKER_02]: And now there's a whole nightclub you can do it in, in the SingStar space.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, how could I forget?
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: The transfer is all done now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chinese MMO players can now get back on to World of Warcraft, which might not be the biggest game in China, but I guess it does definitely have their following over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sure that took a big chunk out of their economy since all the gold farming and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, NetEase, by the way... Well, no, they'd log into the American servers to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not mixed like Final Fantasy XI is.
[SPEAKER_02]: China has their own servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because remember, they don't have Undead.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the Forsaken, which is just the unskinned Undead with more skin or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But anyhow, here's the other thing I want to point out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, the servers are... To give you an idea how many people are playing, the servers are expensive to maintain.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have to pay a million...
[SPEAKER_02]: of their Chinese dollars a day, which boils down to about $146,000 a day to keep the servers running.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, China's a pretty big country, and the game obviously is doing very well there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But then I was thinking, oh my god, three and a half months this game was down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you imagine, what would happen if World of Warcraft, and I opened this question up to chat as well, what would happen if World of Warcraft shut down?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just...
[SPEAKER_02]: All of a sudden, out of the blue, World of Warcraft shuts down for three months in America.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would rain cats and dogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: With no rhyme or reason, just Blizzard, the server facility just goes kaput.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what happens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody gets charged for it or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing malicious happens, but just World of Warcraft gets revoked for all the 11 million players or whatever for three and a half months.
[SPEAKER_02]: What would happen?
[SPEAKER_03]: The internet would be in a shitstorm.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'd be just like, fucking bitch!
[SPEAKER_03]: Just complaining like you would not believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkTetsuya says, divorce rates go down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft says, I already said it, massive tantrums.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, there will be many a blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: Many an angry blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: People threatening to quit and never return.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to Aeon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go to Aeon, possibly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ray Ayanami says, whatever, I'm going to keep on playing not MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rama says, if World of Warcraft shuts down for three months, people would return to real life and shit would get done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jay Dizzle says, Mom, bathroom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deathwishing says, remember that episode of Robot Chicken where a virus deletes all the prawn?
[SPEAKER_02]: Could you imagine that?
[SPEAKER_02]: A computer virus that just targets World of Warcraft?
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: If there was ever a virus out there, conceivable, to actually delete all the porn on the internet at one time, who would do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's just mean.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second off, you know how fast porn gets on the internet?
[SPEAKER_03]: It wouldn't matter.
[SPEAKER_03]: The porn would be back up to the levels it is now in like a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: It would just be like, porn back!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, was it gone?
[SPEAKER_03]: Didn't even realize it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, all new porn, sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you think there would be... The sad thing is, I think for a lot of people... They would cover this on...
[SPEAKER_02]: CNN.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be in the Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really would.
[SPEAKER_02]: World of Warcraft went down today.
[SPEAKER_03]: What about Twitter going down for three months?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Facebook going down for three months?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so over Twitter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember Friendster?
[SPEAKER_02]: Friendster was what we had before MySpace, before Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently it's still popular in Asia.
[SPEAKER_02]: Friendster is what we used to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: When that went down, people went somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Friendster was not quite as integrated into culture as I think Facebook has become.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, people's mothers didn't have a Friendster account.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, you know, college kids had it.
[SPEAKER_02]: People's mothers have Facebooks.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, what would happen if Facebook went down for three months?
[SPEAKER_03]: People would go back to MySpace, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think a lot of people would.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, BaconBits says, if WoW was shut down for three months, the internet speeds would go faster.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deathwishing says kids would run out in the streets going, God damn it, my raid was halfway done.
[SPEAKER_02]: I lost my epics.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a lot of people seem to speculate people would just go somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that, you know, as much of, you know, fandom as World of Warcraft gets, people are fickle.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it goes away for a while, they'll leave.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then when it comes back, they'll come right back.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to be doing something.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if they're going to be MMO players, they're going to go play another MMO or play something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not just going to go outside and go, Oh my God, there's a world out here.
[SPEAKER_03]: What have I done with my life?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, World Warcraft's back!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh shit!
[SPEAKER_02]: You have so many businesses out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Think about the online banking that goes on and just all of the online things.
[SPEAKER_02]: So many companies that do their business online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the internet going down completely would be pretty chaotic.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be a mess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, there's a lot of stuff also connected with the internet like banking, ATMs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty big.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might all be secure, but imagine if it was suddenly unaccessible.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I guess that's why we still have tellers working at banks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had my bank's infrastructure go down for a day.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Marissa Congusto in the chat says, I couldn't do my job without the internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of people in that situation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I work for a big call center.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I've mentioned that before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm a trainer for a big call center.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually have reps in other offices that take phone calls from their homes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like a work at home program.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I believe they use the internet to do all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: When the internet goes down, those reps can't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a lot of people that really rely on the internet to do their jobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it'll be a mess, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there was a day without internet, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you kids are old enough to remember, but there was a day without internet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Back in my day, we had dial-up and BBSs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Those were the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trade Wars 2002 for life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember BBSs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of the Red Dragon, bitches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wasn't that long ago, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_03]: The pit for the win.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: We downloaded porn on 28 modems off of BBSs, because that's the way it was.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember when porn would be separated into VGA and Super VGA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Didn't they call it XGA back then, I think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: EGA.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, hooray for CGA porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's like those old strip poker games on the Apple IIe.
[SPEAKER_03]: Especially working with arcade monitors and stuff like that, yeah, arcade monitors, most of them out there, CGA is what they consider them because it's ultra-low resolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: And VGA monitors, 640x480, and that's really good for arcade stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, I digress.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a 300 baud modem on my Commodore 64 that plugged into the cartridge port in the back.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was epic.
Epic.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think the slowest modem I had was a 2400, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, switching that to like 56k, oh my god, we're blazing speeds!
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, going onto BBSs on a 300 baud modem, it was like watching print be typed on the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, it was just insane.
[SPEAKER_02]: But dude, I...
[SPEAKER_02]: Just to reminisce for a bit here, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there used to be a BBS here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think it was called like the Open Forum or Open Mind or something like that, which was this  all it was was really a bunch of forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this was back when like 2400  I think 14.4 was like the speed everybody had at that point.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was 14.4K.
[SPEAKER_02]: And really all it was was just message forums.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was just like a cool place to just kind of meet people.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually  some of the greatest discussions I ever read online were on that site.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it was all local people too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some days I miss the days of BBS.
[SPEAKER_03]: CCN.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember that magazine?
[SPEAKER_03]: California Computer News?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do!
[SPEAKER_02]: Aren't they still around?
[SPEAKER_03]: They used to have, I don't know, but they used to have... They have the BBS listings in the back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there was one BBS that was on there that you could sign into that BBS and actually get internet access for like an hour a day or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember I got banned from a BBS once because I pissed off the sysop.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got tied up in some drama.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, now I'm looking back on it going, this is all retarded.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, I was a dumb kid.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Deathwishing says, LOL, dial-up porn.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be like, okay, gonna eat dinner, come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn, her tits loaded up yet?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously, it was sad because, you know, back in the day, it used to take an hour to download a make, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: It did.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember downloading the Wolfenstein 3D demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_03]: and you better hope that's a good picture because you don't know what it looks like because it's just a text file.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just like, big boobs, sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Womanhorse.gif?
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, what could this be?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_02]: The stories I will tell my children
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Summer of Arcade, you know, Microsoft's kind of big push for some good Xbox Live Arcade games coming out, of course, in the summer.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a 200% growth over last year's sales, and this is mostly in part to, actually, a good selection of games coming out, including Marvel vs. Capcom 2, you know, even Battlefield 1943.
[SPEAKER_03]: lots of good stuff you know and even you know Shadow Complex their kind of Metroidvania game Trials HD and
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, let's move on and talk a little bit about a story about IGN and an old website that we love here at Orange Lounge Radio, whattheyplay.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you've been a longtime fan of Orange Lounge Radio, you'll know why this is funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: If not, listen to the best of next week because that clip's going to come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: But IGN, of course, the big, huge website that's kind of like game...
[SPEAKER_02]: All those, you know, one up or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually purchased WhatTheyPlay.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: WhatTheyPlay.com is a site that is basically, you know, it's kind of catered towards families and kind of the concerned parent about what kids are into in video gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why IGN bought this, but that's what they wanted.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess there was a pretty big audience there and maybe IGN kind of feels that it's a new audience that can, that ad buyers will be interested in buying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: They buy a lot of different websites.
[SPEAKER_02]: IGN has bought it to conduct all the polls they want on that audience.
[SPEAKER_02]: That happened earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You may remember us reporting on a game announced at E3, Joyride, which is basically a game that's kind of debuting the free-to-play model on the Xbox Live Service.
[SPEAKER_03]: Joyride is going to be kind of an avatar-infused kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Of course, they're going to have a little bit of an MMO twist to it as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing some stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember where you can actually... I guess it would be a little bit similar to Noby Noby Boy.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Battlefield 1943 where if you play the game enough that you'll actually as a whole unlock new levels which is kind of cool and then of course if you want to customize your carts and what not you have to pay for that because that's what free to play means you have to pay for your premiums
[SPEAKER_03]: and it will be a free download coming this holiday and apparently the content to buy will be available around that time as well also including avatar costumes and new tracks and cars
[SPEAKER_02]: So, what do you think about this whole new model?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it kind of the future of Xbox Live Arcade, or what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it allows you to try out the game, and if you don't want to buy all this extra content, you don't have to, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's a lot better than, say, buying a game, or trying a demo that maybe doesn't really give you a good idea of the game, and wasting your money on a game that you end up not liking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: And hell, it can't be any worse...
[SPEAKER_02]: I suppose that's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, as long as it's better than Yaris, I think it'll be okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, DarkSakura is not here right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: She'll be back a little later, hopefully, before we finish up.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm going to open up the mailbag right now, but I was a slacker and didn't go into it before we started this segment because I was getting text messages on my phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was answering those.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a lot of emails tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if I'm going to be able to get through all of these, but I'll try and get through as many of them as I can.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you didn't get through tonight, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Try again next time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to an email from Shook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starts us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, to kick off this email I'd like to say that I'm at peace with my dad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, this is the emailer that was having problems with his dad, remember that?
[SPEAKER_02]: The dad didn't want him playing Final Fantasy X, remember that?
[SPEAKER_02]: I talked to him about the Final Fantasy X thing and he seemed willing when he listened to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got him to try the game and he loves it!
[SPEAKER_02]: So no more of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So a round of applause for the douchebag father.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: The rational thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've unduced yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: You did the right thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: No more hazing for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: So no more of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now on to my main story.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other day I had gym class and we played football.
[SPEAKER_02]: When a kid in my class saw the football laying there, he ran over and teabagged the ball a couple of times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let that sink in.
[SPEAKER_02]: My gym coach grabs the kid by his neck, says, get the hell inside, and pushes the kid towards the front door.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just goes to show how far teabagging has gone in our culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: The kid was suspended for lewd sexual behavior, according to the superintendent.
[SPEAKER_02]: My opinion, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the shit that gives gaming a bad name.
[SPEAKER_02]: I close with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S., pardon my French, forever and always, not like anyone censors themselves anyway, yours truly, Shook.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it has anything to do with gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: One day I want to hear Rob go, we got a lot of emails tonight, sorry guys, I'm only going to get through as many as I feel like, so suck it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I guess you could say that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: This next email comes to us from AZHP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was listening to your last available podcast the other day and remember Rob saying something about a homosexual tambourine game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I believe the game you're thinking of is Minimoni Shakato Tambourine, which I actually played when I went to Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're not familiar with Minimoni, they're a branch of Morning Musume.
[SPEAKER_02]: An extremely popular J-pop girl group with, get this, 23 girls, at least the last time I checked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Minimoni is a subset of them, four girls who are 15 to 16 and look 11 to 12 and sing things about telephones, rock, paper, scissors, counting to 20 in the bathtub, and in general being obnoxiously cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Therefore, you are most definitely correct in saying that the game you saw slept with tambourine games of the same gender.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it sounds like that game sounds like it could go to jail for the things it's doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: I recently got a new job.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I just want to say before I get into the P.S., I actually don't think it was the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The one I saw, and this is how you could tell, it was Samba de Amigo.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the exact same game as Samba de Amigo, basically, except with a different character, not the little Samba dude, and with a tambourine.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if that's the game you're talking about, then it's the same game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't remember a Morning Musume or even a Japanese pop 23 girl group being involved at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me read the PS here real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: I recently got a new job and have been listening to your podcast while at work.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to stop, though, because when you guys make terrible and awesome, extremely inappropriate jokes, I can't help but burst out laughing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not conductive to keeping a low profile in a quiet office environment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a testament to your chemistry, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's very kind.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: He signs it.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR's premier gold star recipient, AZHP.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: He was a previous gold star.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was another very worthy email there, so thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to get through some more emails here.
[SPEAKER_02]: This one comes to us from... They didn't sign it, so I'm just going to say Sam is the person that sent this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, OLR crew.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying very hard to use the best grammar possible so the grammar Nazi doesn't permabam me or start yelling or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you're lucky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight I'm reading them and I have terrible grammar too, so I'm not going to be too critical tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, I'm Blade3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm sorry, that's the name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blade3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't emailed you guys since 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm older and I slapped together a PSP website that has awesome functions and I wanted to let you know that I put your feed on there because everyone deserves to listen to the awesome Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out at rmedia.webhop.net.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will automatically route you if you are on a PSP and if you have an iPhone, it will route you to the iPhone site.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you use a computer, it will route you to the main site.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congrats on many fantastic shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep up the fabulous work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow, I just gave that dude free advertising.
[SPEAKER_02]: for just kissing our ass in an email
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd rather play video games, yeah, and it's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email, hey guys, JD here, long-time listener, first-time emailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I'm a listener from the UK, so I can't really tune in live.
[SPEAKER_02]: We do have listeners from the UK that tune in live, but I understand, it's like two in the morning over there, so those guys are just really hardcore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for the email, anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is concerning something DarkSakura mentioned quite a while ago when she heard the theme from Shaft in a Czech restaurant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember this?
[SPEAKER_02]: She talked about this earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, today in my college induction day, my teacher was warning us about the dangers of leaving our phones on, and with perfect timing, his phone started ringing, and his ringtone was none other than the theme from Shaft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anywho, I must head off to bed now, so goodnight, OLR, and Sky, you need to update the podcast on time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad host.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bad panda.
[SPEAKER_02]: No cookie.
[SPEAKER_02]: that email from JD reminding us of an old inside joke if I can find that clip off to put that in the best of too I just don't remember what episode that was in just a couple more emails for you guys here and then I'll get to it let's see I'll get to probably just one more email here from Rob with 2B's
[SPEAKER_02]: and he sent us quite a few emails this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to pick a couple of these here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob from 2B's wanted to know if any of us were going to Disneyland from September 23rd to 27th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, I went the week before and I'm going the week after.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm very sorry to say it, but we didn't make it to Disneyland the same week you were.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I hope you had a ton of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: The good news is all the Halloween events started this weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also...
[SPEAKER_02]: Send us a link to this interesting article on GamesPolitik.com about a study linking youth violence depression to peers, not video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, it says here, one, depression is a symptom.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is pointing out that many of the youths surveyed have depression problems to the point where it seems correlated to youth violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd say that the issue of depression is something that should be tackled all by itself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two, peer pressure is also the cause of good behavior.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we have a tendency when we see something that's kind of on our side to rah rah rah around it a little bit and yeah there might be a lot of variables in this study and I kind of agree with this whole notion that this is probably something that's way too hard to gauge way too hard to gauge I think
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the best cure to that sort of depression is to stop that behavior and go outside.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to have a healthy balance of video gaming when you're that age.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I don't think too much gaming is the cause.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think too much gaming is a symptom, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they're trying to isolate themselves from everybody else.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sometimes games make them feel better about themselves, especially if they're really skilled at something.
Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, JD is in chat right now and says it is 4.30 in the morning where he's at and he is listening after all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thank you very much for tuning in and listening.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to do it for the mailbag tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you guys for the emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to send us an email, please do a mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll get to some more emails next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we want to get into the FUs of the week as we always do around this point of the show and we have a good little inspiration story for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: To inspire tonight's FUs of the week, I bring you a principal from Germany who was quoted this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: His name is Bernd Denning and said, kind of maybe along this whole line with depression and so forth, he believes that video games play a major role in a child becoming a homicidal maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quote, even if killer games are not the trigger of a killing spree, this guy said yesterday, they still take a major part in turning minors into homicidal maniacs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if there isn't a mono-casually relation between excessive playing of games leading to acts of violence, it still provides a twisted frame of reference of solutions for their problems and hardships that they learn and may transfer to the real world under certain circumstances.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, but how is that the game's fault?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're kind of admitting that they're going to the games because they have a problem in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game doesn't turn them into a homicidal maniac.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: To his defense, I think it's like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have a crazy person already, the games mainly give him inspiration to how, I guess,
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: Art does it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's because he got in a soapbox and wanted to say something controversial so people would listen and people did and then they blogged about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Art can be influential.
[SPEAKER_02]: Period.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyhow, so we dedicate the FUs of the week to this guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: FU to my headache and it's from sinuses I'm guessing because I got it when I got back here and my eyes are burning and my head hurts so it's got to be a sinus headache.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe someone in this house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shermie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shermie's not in the room.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has to get out of here tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: No pun intended.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, my FU of the week goes to the food poisoning I got from a popular sandwich chain earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to name them because I can't prove it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_02]: They toast their sandwiches.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're very famous for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got another one from... They don't have footlongs, but you can get stuff to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I, you know, I can't prove that they gave me the food poisoning, but I'm pretty sure that's where I got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, man, it was hell for three days, but I lost some weight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, it wasn't really, I don't know if it's bad sushi and then bad sandwich.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to just food poisoning, because it sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a couple more stories for you guys, then we're going to get to the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We probably have time for quite a few calls tonight, so we'll try to get through everybody tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: This week, we've got some new Xbox Live Arcade games coming out, and quite a few of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Usually we get one or two, but we have three.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, unfortunately, starting things off, and you know, I'm a pretty big fan of the Warriors game that was out on the PlayStation 2 and the Xbox, but now we get the Warriors Streetball, which is...
[SPEAKER_03]: Zombiapocalypse
[SPEAKER_03]: which is kind of like a top down version of Left 4 Dead and that's going to be available for 800 Microsoft points or $10 and also Ion Assault which I believe is a tower defense game and that's also available for 800 Microsoft points or $10 and um
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I'm right about the ion assault thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope, I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a space shooter with an interesting twist, they say.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, you can draw in energy from particles and use them to blast foes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've actually seen that in a freeware game made by some Japanese guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: This looks neat.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of a little bit like Geometry Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't it about time for a new Geometry Wars, by the way?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you would think with a new Project Gotham game you'd get something like that, but since there's not going to really be a Project Gotham game from Bazaar, I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me do it later.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it already kind of got leaked.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, did it?
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't hear the follow-up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yosho, what was it, Yoshinoro Ono, and some other guy, and they were kind of doing like a fireball pose.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in the background, what is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like Street Fighter 4, but then there's T-Hawk there, and then also a big giant banner with what appears to look like an S from Super Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oops!
[SPEAKER_03]: So yes, you're probably going to get some either download content or perhaps a re-release of the game, you know, greatest hits type thing or something like that with new characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other words, a way to milk more money from you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that is it for the stories that we have tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's now that time for us to open up the Skype line and take your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, why don't you give us some last-minute stories before we get to the phones?
[SPEAKER_03]: The Xbox 360 Elite is actually going to be a little bit cheaper until October 5th.
[SPEAKER_03]: With a cool deal that's going on with Netflix, you will be able to buy an Xbox 360 Elite between September 22nd and October 5th and go on to Xbox's website.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a link, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can check it out where you can mail in for a rebate for $50.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's not a bad deal if you're looking to pick up a console.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, there you are.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, did you guys hear about how I think I read on Twitter from Inside Gaming that...
[SPEAKER_01]: The memory cap for Xbox Live arcade games is being increased to 2 gigs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I did remember reading an article on that earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doesn't that have to do with the whole, what is it, Command & Conquer 3?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the new Command & Conquer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Doesn't that kind of like defeat the purpose of games that are not that big and now you can have these 2 gig games which basically...
[SPEAKER_01]: I think what they're trying to say is go buy our expensive overpriced hard drives, is what I feel like they're telling me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really, because when you consider now that the main system that's going to be available out there is the Xbox 360 Elite with a 120GB hard drive, I mean, you could fit like 60 games on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, probably less than 60 games, but pretty close to 60.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but what happens to all the people that didn't buy the Elite?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know there's more people with the standard edition console that had a 20GB hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Microsoft doesn't care about you.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: There's hundreds, literally hundreds of games already available that are very small.
[SPEAKER_02]: Indie games, don't forget those, in addition to just the past three, four years of what's been out on the 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, and I also picked up ODST.
[SPEAKER_01]: And what did you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: I love it, but I also know a lot of people that hate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you love about it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I notice it's been half and half.
[SPEAKER_01]: I notice people love it or people hate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is strange for a Halo game because usually everybody's dry humping it.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you love about Halo 3 ODST?
[SPEAKER_01]: I just love that it's actually a fun campaign.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's an interesting story.
[SPEAKER_01]: The voice acting is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: The music in this game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Firefight's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played it for like three hours one day with a couple friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate to sound so ignorant, but what is Firefight mode?
[SPEAKER_02]: Firefight is... I don't know enough about Halo.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_01]: Gears of War Horde.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Halo twist with skulls and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yeah, it's been taking up my whole time this week, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: What would you say to the haters?
[SPEAKER_02]: What are the haters saying about it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Most of the people that hate it are either A, kids that were looking for Master Chief and didn't find them so they cried and maybe people that aren't fans of the Halo series looking for a different game and then there's the people that don't play Halo games but they bought Halo because you know you have to have it and most people, I know a lot of people who did buy Halo for their Xbox because it's like a staple game like Call of Duty and Gears of War
[SPEAKER_01]: I've read most of the books.
[SPEAKER_01]: Halo Reach is a prequel to Fall of Reach.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are one hardcore Halo nerd.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wouldn't say hardcore.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like the story.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually like Call of Duty 4 a lot better.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, there's people that read the Warcraft books and some of the books based on other games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Man, those people are nerds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta love the video game culture.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gotta love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll look at just another subgroup and say, you guys are nerds.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like the Star Wars guys and the Trekkies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, Deathwishing, we gotta let you go so we can get some more calls, but any quick final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw the former lead singer of No Doubt or one of them at Chain Reaction last night.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gwen Stefani?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, Alan.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, like from the old school days.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, he has a band called Starpool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get a picture?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, but I was too busy skanking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, well, good luck with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio If you'd like to go ahead and give us a call We'll take some more calls Any other last minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: EA has confirmed that they're going to be doing a Beatles Rock Band SingStar Pack Basically Beatles Rock Band for PS3 With two SingStar mics We have another call Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, it's Brad from PodCulture.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which it isn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you talk about Olive Garden 2, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: We actually usually do go out to eat before the shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice, very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, I know you didn't call in today just to plug your shows, but what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Halo 3 ODST.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, you're another Halo 3 ODST fan, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: I really enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's definitely not an F minus minus kind of a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, a little dig there at Bobby on the earlier show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, what grade would you give it and why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd give it a good solid B. Mainly, you know, it
[SPEAKER_07]: Bounces around between the different viewpoints of the characters which some people I can see would like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me, I like a little bit more of a linear type of story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know you guys are hardcore into that universe so just the voice acting alone has got to sell this game to you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, Nathan Fillion's character actually looked like Nathan Fillion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did some of the modeling really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alan Tudyk's character, there's one scene where he actually flies a Covenant ship.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you sound like you're actually into the campaign mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you play any of the multiplayer at all, or are you all about the campaign?
[SPEAKER_07]: Every once in a while, but I usually get my ass handed to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are a busy man, Brad.
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you have time to play video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, you just don't sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else you've been playing lately, Brad?
[SPEAKER_07]: Beatles Rock Band and Guitar Hero 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what do you think of both these games?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really, really neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like in Guitar Hero 5, it's kind of cheesy, but I like the fact you can play as your avatar.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: and with the Beatles rock band, come on man, it's the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, it's the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have yet to get on this Beatles train.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to be late to the arrival because I know you were making fun of me over my 360 earlier, but I'll get on the bandwagon soon enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm fine with everybody else's hype for right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you think is going to be, I hate to make you pick, but which game do you think is going to trump at Christmas?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to actually probably say Beatles Rock Band because you have more of the, it would appeal to more of folks who normally wouldn't pick up a video game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like I took it over to my mom's to play with my, over for my birthday and we played with my sister and brother-in-law and their kids and everybody loved it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, any final thoughts for us, Brad?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, sir.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just keep up doing the great show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you have a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And good luck with your multitude of shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Catch you later guys
[SPEAKER_00]: Nothing much, just chilling right now because the weekend was New York Anime Fest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yet another damn con.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are spoiled out there on the East Coast with all your cons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you go to this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, yeah, not only that.
[SPEAKER_00]: The creator of Gundam was one of the guests of honor, so I managed to go to both of his panels and I had him autograph one of my copies of Zeta Gundam.
[SPEAKER_00]: and a picture with him.
[SPEAKER_00]: It'll be up on Facebook eventually, but right now I'm just tired.
[SPEAKER_00]: I gotta relax tonight because I've been going through this rat race this whole weekend.
[SPEAKER_00]: But yeah, basically I wanted to bring up a good point that I don't know if it was probably already discussed, but the fact that the creator of Mega Man
[SPEAKER_00]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_00]: The Con this weekend, which was basically a debate between Western and Japanese video games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And they did bring up that particular rant.
[SPEAKER_00]: And from how the debate went, we pretty much settled on the fact that Japan is a clash of cultures.
[SPEAKER_00]: You could put it that way.
[SPEAKER_00]: In other words, where you have the Japanese with their strong work ethic and the fact that they only help themselves, not each other.
[SPEAKER_00]: Whereas Western developers, or just Western business companies for that matter, you have to work within a team.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, isn't this just a little bit, though, I wouldn't see it as the apocalypse that all these guys are proclaiming.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: And that says he's probably crying wolf a bit too early.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I think, here it is, Zaku, American development for many years sucked balls.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where did we get all of our games from?
[SPEAKER_02]: All of them, Zaku, came from Japan just like 20 years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like when American developers would do it, they would almost like just fail miserably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like remember Secret of Evermore?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that game, but a lot of people hated that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But here's the thing, just Japanese development has dominated for so long.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's so much that Japanese development is dead, it's just Japanese development is having to share the spotlight a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, right now, they have to contend with the fact that the Western video game market at this point is pretty solid.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, you have the 360, which has the largest install base of any console right now on the planet.
[SPEAKER_03]: In the US, the Wii is still number one.
[SPEAKER_00]: In the US, Europe, I mean, you'd be surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact of the matter is that there is... And actually, no, it doesn't have the largest install base because the Wii is still number one around the world.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, alright, aside from the Wii, but I mean, in terms of hardcore, I mean, I consider the Wii more of a...
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, more of the casual system, even though it hasn't really appealed that much to hardcore, with the exception of Super Mario Galaxy and Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this is another reason why... So you're just saying compared to Sony?
[SPEAKER_02]: You're saying compared to Sony?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess the point that I'm trying to make is that Japan...
[SPEAKER_00]: I couldn't see the writings on the wall a lot sooner than later.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now it's just, they have the deer in the headlights look all of a sudden.
[SPEAKER_00]: Even though Wii and most of the world already knew that they weren't the only game in town anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I mean, to give you an example here, the Wii right now worldwide is 53.47 million units, whereas the Xbox 360 is 32.10 million.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, of course, the PlayStation 3...
[SPEAKER_03]: A little bit catching up now, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're down to 24.55 million.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right, I mean, it pretty much goes back into what others... I guess in a way he's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: And this is what happened.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, Microsoft pretty much realized that
[SPEAKER_00]: The only way to create a powerful platform, a world-class platform, is that they have to listen, appeal more to developers, and essentially throw money at them.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's how they managed to roll out more 360s in Japan than the original Xbox.
[SPEAKER_00]: So even though it still hasn't beaten the PS3 yet, it's getting close.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, for all intents and purposes, you could say that it's razor thin at this point, the margin between the two.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, well, Zaku, we've got to wrap up and let you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have any other quick thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, worst game of all time, Final Fantasy VII, and that wasn't me saying it, that was pretty much a panel that I went to today.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think there are millions of people that would disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Alright, take care, Saku.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everybody knows that the worst game of all time is Draft 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anybody that says that Final Fantasy VII is the worst game of all time, I laugh in your face.
Ah-ha!
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's what you meant to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just like...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time is overrated.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could think of literally hundreds of games off the top of my head that are worse than Final Fantasy VII that I think we all could agree on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's plenty.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just had two quick questions because I know you're about to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're kind of interrelated.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as far as home is concerned, have you heard anything about their announced update?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they're calling it 1.3.
[SPEAKER_02]: For what is this?
[SPEAKER_05]: For PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I saw some stuff online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't think there was anything super major that I read about in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't think this is getting the showing of the trophies or any of that that we saw about.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to say I thought I saw something when I logged in the other day, but I don't think there was anything major, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I don't think I ever saw a bullet point on there for fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't really interested in it at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, Spazinator, you've checked out the OLR Clubhouse, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have I done a nice job decorating it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, in fact, since you touched on it, I did have a question.
[SPEAKER_05]: My second question relates to the clubhouse.
[SPEAKER_05]: I noticed that, you know, right behind the stage, you know, near the ceiling, there looks like there's some kind of TV screen or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Does that, like, serve a purpose, or is it, like, just, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: because I would love to give you an exclusive little OLR behind the scenes video or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to put a five minute video of us taping the show or something before or after the show in home.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome and give people a reason to go to home.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I can't do that yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not something they're letting us do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they're still working out for a reason to buy the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, yeah, I was thinking, I know you guys have a whole bunch of videos on YouTube, you know, like just recently you put up the video of Jamie's, you know, vault, and along with their pinball machine collection, that would be great for the TV screen, and for anyone that buys any of the content through the video sector in the store, you know, I would imagine in the 30s,
[SPEAKER_02]: Spazinator, I would, the minute that Sony lets us put those YouTubes on that TV in the clubhouse, I am so there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, I would love them to just open up the clubhouse to everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why be a member of the club?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to make my club public so that way lots of people can explore the clubhouse, see the video and go, oh, these guys look kind of crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe I'll listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it would be great promotion, but sadly, you know, and I understand, you know, it's a big deal for Sony to hit the switch because if they allow people to post their own videos and
[SPEAKER_02]: there's huge copyright things they're going to have to deal with so I can understand why I don't get what I want but believe me the day they figure it all out even if they have to review each piece of submitted content we don't have anything copyright in ours so we would submit it and hopefully it'll be on there well thanks for taking my call and I'll want to go like I said you're probably going to wrap up the show pretty soon here
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, well, thank you, Spaz.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take care, and we'll talk to you later week, all right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why we can't take a couple more calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not even 9 o'clock yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're good.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can do, like, one more call.
[SPEAKER_02]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Use the name on Skype as Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have any other stories you want to get to?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Frank West, coming to Tatsunoko vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we already kind of knew that, but they have pictures now.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it looks like he has all sorts of crazy moves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hello!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is DSMaster26.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I just picked up the phone, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: That bitch!
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Girls 101, don't laugh at me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Threaten to kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, then I replugged it in.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's my friend's 360, mind you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can borrow it for the weekend, thank God.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've been wanting to try a 360 for a while, full one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not one of those demo kiosks.
[SPEAKER_04]: and so then it red ringed on me and then I'm like oh crap so I have Rockman for the Wii and I'm like okay I'll put this under the tell trick thing for the 25 minutes or whatever and we'll play Rockman on the Wii well lo and behold it has an update and in the middle of that power outage for a second it bricked my Wii and now I have the blue light of death not kidding
[SPEAKER_02]: BlueLateSpecialDeath Hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get to grab your girlfriend's boobies tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but... Well, you have had a really bad day then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I would think that at least to some type of concession for your bad day, she should be like, okay, I'll let you grab a boob.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know?
[SPEAKER_04]: We did actually kind of started crying on the point where Kairi disappears on Kingdom Hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: 358 and a half days and spoiler alert sorry but um basically oh yeah and I forgot to mention I saw an Xbox 360 console with a pay-to-play method at the arcades where it's like okay four tick
[SPEAKER_04]: 4 Tokens, 4 Minutes, 8 Tokens, 8 Minutes, so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I saw one, it was a modded Xbox, I swear to God, it was a Japanese weak copy of Beatmania 17 2DX.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've seen arcades put Stepmania machines in and try to make money off of it, so you know, I was part of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of all things, it was jerry-rigged into an actual Beatmania cabinet with the controller and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I thought was kind of cool, but it was right next door to an actual Beatmania machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not only do they have that, but they also have it with DDR Universe in there, one with the hardpad.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have the Rock Band game there to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they even got some PlayStation 3s jerry-rigged up that way, too, with the token play stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's this place at?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's it called?
[SPEAKER_04]: Family Fun Center.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in Omaha.
[SPEAKER_04]: FamilyFunCenter.net.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, thanks for ratting them out.
[SPEAKER_02]: The developers that listen to this show will be glad to know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And when that place closes down, rest in peace knowing it's all your fault.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly, they're not doing anything wrong.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I don't think he... I'm sure that there's some fine print or something, but they do sell those actual kits that you can do pay-per-play stuff on the PS3 and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hooks up via JAMMA and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I was actually looking into getting some JAMMA connectors for my Wii and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: That way I can do Tatsunoko vs. Capcom on my arcade cabinet or, you know...
[SPEAKER_03]: stuff for my 360 or whatnot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, because it's all available out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just pay-for-play stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's annoying, I guess, because consoles aren't meant for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you get for playing V. Because seriously, that song is just overdone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Let it sit.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what you get for playing me.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: All joking aside, I know I've been rousing you tonight, but you let me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for calling in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Any quick final thoughts for our listeners before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely keep the good shows rocking.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, I'm the one who sent that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: D.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: Silver's my code name.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like RPGs and music titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me a few quick recommendations on XPLA and normal titles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, on my Xbox?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't signed into my Xbox in like a week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, I mean, a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: On just Xbox 360 itself, what would you recommend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, what would I recommend on Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_02]: You said you're into RPGs?
[SPEAKER_04]: RPGs, Music, and Racing RPGs, Driving, and
[SPEAKER_02]: Music.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm waiting for Scratch, because that's the only thing close to Beatmania with DLC we're ever going to get here, because I figured out now they're never going to release Beatmania ever again here in the States, which sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome to what I told you years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: They'll probably do a Beatmania on PS3, and that way it'll be region-free, so you will be able to get a Beatmania here.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got to let you go, DS Master, but take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep the shows rocking, and peace out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Peace out.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I give him a hard time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why does my head hurt more?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, it makes your headache get worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a loud caller.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I said we could walk it out in twilight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yippee skipy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Doesn't that poppin' music game on the Wii look horrendous?
[SPEAKER_02]: But granted, isn't Japan getting that too?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not just us.
[SPEAKER_02]: They already got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting it soon.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we get the crappy DDR.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which, by the way, remember how it was just Dance Dance Revolution at one time?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they're breaking it out into three different games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now they're going to do X2, Hottest Party 3, and then whatever the fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to call it PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 versions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the new, new one on the 360 and PS3 looked pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looked pretty epic, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm curious on this.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the thing is, though, they're going to be identical games.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're just changing the names so that people don't realize it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well...
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't we see the same game get ported to two different systems all the frickin' time?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're combining resources to make one really fucking good game across both consoles, I'm okay with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except it's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jury's out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, we're going to go ahead and wrap up the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're done with Skypline tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry to those who didn't get through, but consider sending us an email.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd love to hear from you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to wrap up and get everybody's final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, DarkSakura is not here right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe she'll come in during Afterbirth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: For live only folks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm sure she would say goodnight and reject fault icons or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want my headache to go away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is I am looking at Loki's bag from McDonald's and my mouth is watering because I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's fries in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're cold by now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They weren't good to begin with.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll stop by on the way home.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a pretty good McDonald's by my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're done.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're out of here.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will not be here next week, but we will have a best of.
[SPEAKER_02]: So stay tuned to All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll have a best of on the network next week and with some new content.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't want you to think it's simply old rehashed stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're going to give some new stuff for our faithful listeners too.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will be back in two weeks live.
[SPEAKER_02]: I apologize for all the time off recently.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's totally my fault, but I'm in it for the rest of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just so happens that October is a crazy month.
[SPEAKER_02]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have a good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll see you in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here on Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_06]: See you next week!