[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, September 6, 2009, a Once Pay We channel goes free, a new racing game will be integrating Twitter and we recap and talk about the news from PAX 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week here of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: We tape live every Sunday night at www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: A big thanks to our friends at All Games Radio for letting us steal their bandwidth every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm here with you for the next three hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me, as always, for the past seven and a half years, say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nom, nom, nom.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nom, nom, nom.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nomming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, quickly, Orange Lounge Foodio, what are you nomming on tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Brains.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pizza.
[SPEAKER_06]: With extra garlic.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a cheese pizza, but I added garlic to it because garlic makes everything better.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will keep the vampires away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us tonight, say hello to the one and only Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you look like you're listening to something else over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to, but I hate these earbud headphones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any hints?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this a cage match for later?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I didn't pick anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Per usual.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you don't know what I'm talking about, that's because you've never tuned in live before.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do a little special thing after the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll have to tune in live sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping, because it's Labor Day, maybe we get some people listening live that haven't listened before.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a big hello to all of you that are new to...
[SPEAKER_04]: us broadcasting live be sure to join our chat room chat.orangeloungeradio.com and we will read some comments from chat and comment from the Rob D in chat early this evening you know it's PAX weekend when Orange Lounge is talking old DDR and allgames.com is discussing condom reviews I guess the allgames chat is talking about condoms so
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to be mature.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm just... Please, my guy should be judging on that part.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're completely immature here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm glad that Rob D. brought up PAX because it is Penny Arcade Expo weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, the three of us could not go this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all went last year, but we kind of ate the money in the budget for E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: But our dear friend Bobby Blackwolf is live at the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to call him right now and talk to him about Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_04]: One ringy dingy dingy Ferret Exterminators Hi Bobby Hey Rob, what's up guys?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not much, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Bobby Blackwolf, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to give you a proper introduction.
[SPEAKER_04]: He is the man who takes the Bobby Blackwolf show live at 5 o'clock, right before we are live.
[SPEAKER_04]: He sadly was not live tonight, but he did have a sneak peek of the rock band Beatles that he got a little early from Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_04]: So props to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, it's the Beatles Rock Band They are very strict on that
[SPEAKER_08]: I had fun, and I mean, I kind of did kind of what you guys did at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did not do any appointments.
[SPEAKER_08]: We did not set any interviews.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we were able to just kind of go around and spend as much or as little time as we wanted.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for those of us who did go to E3, there's a lot here that was repeated and regurgitated.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of the same E3 builds, the E3 demos were here on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was nice to see...
[SPEAKER_08]: Regular folk get a chance at the same things that we saw a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was a lot of fun to see their reactions, see what they thought about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see anything interesting to you that you did not see at E3?
[SPEAKER_04]: Some new things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one of them I saw was Star Trek Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I want the details on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, I played through one of their episodes, like they did any episode type of thing, where you start off in your ship and you kind of fly around and they say that you get a distress call.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you go and you fight some Klingon birds of prey in the ship combat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then you beamed it down to the planet, which was kind of like the city on the edge of forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Klingons are trying to take over the forever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so you had to...
[SPEAKER_08]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and we'll be giving more details on that a little later on in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's one of our stories coming up a little later.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my question about Star Trek Online, was it fun?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun, the little bit that they showed.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they even said that, you know, this was a very small episode.
[SPEAKER_08]: What they're basically doing is their missions are scheduled to be
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Trek writers.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were basically just showing the combat portion, but they said there's going to be puzzles and other things to do that aren't just fight, fight, fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here at PAX, they were just showing the fighting.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of a nice little taste.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: and it was kind of interesting watching like going through the line of people and basically in Heavy Rain it reminds me a lot of Shenmue like I really didn't understand or get what Heavy Rain was but it's basically you know quick time action sequences along with tank driving in terms of moving your character but it's basically there's a gunpoint heist in a grocery store or serve a quickie mark and basically you can actually
[SPEAKER_08]: determine how it ends up and the guy before me actually convinced the guy to leave the store and I had to punch him in the face but it was very interesting mechanic and just interesting the way that it went down and it's not a game I haven't seen this kind of gameplay all that much in terms of a full game I've seen it in mini games like God of War and Shenmue and things like that but it's going to be kind of interesting to see how this game really turns out longer than a five minute demo
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're monitoring our chat room at chat.orangelonsradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting some questions for you, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft wants to know about Scribblenauts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you go to the Scribblenauts panel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it there on the show floor?
[SPEAKER_08]: I did not go to the panel, but they were once again on the corner of the show floor where they belong, apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they brought six kiosks, and the lines were long the entire time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I actually did talk to them and even talked to some of the developers and said,
[SPEAKER_08]: and for people who've listened to my show for a long time know that when I went to GDC in 2007 one of the student competition IGS winners I interviewed was a group that made a game called Toblo and during that interview I met up with the guy that I interviewed then and he said I was one of the three people that wanted to talk to them at GDC and they thought it was really cool and apparently I announced their first game, Drawn to Life
[SPEAKER_08]: because he had talked about it on our show, gave us a rundown well before they had even done any kind of formal announcements or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: He didn't get in trouble, but it was kind of neat to hear him talk about it and how he remembered me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was kind of cool to talk to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did get to play one level, just getting one of the stars, but that was about all I could do because it was near the end of the show and the lines were just so long the entire show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ryan, what a turnaround from E3 because we walked right up to the kiosk at E3, so apparently word of mouth is spreading.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've been very happy with all the coverage and surprised.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't think they would get the kind of coverage that they got.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so they came a little bit more prepared this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like WB, their little booth, they were showing Fear 2 and Scribblenauts.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they had six Scribblenauts kiosks and two cave kiosks for Fear 2 or a Fear thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, why would they show Fear 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been out forever now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, it was a fear something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't look at it because Scribblenauts was next to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it was a new platform.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe a new expansion or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby, what about other... Oh, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, there were some games that were already out, like Metroid Prime, the trilogy, was in Nintendo's booth, and it's already out in stores, but they were bribing people with t-shirts if they came up and played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were some stuff that's already out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: No, because I was able to get into a lot of the parties, a lot of the company parties, so I didn't really do any panels or anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, I'm very happy because I've been a fan of like Paul and Storm and Jonathan Colton for a long time, and you know they're coming to Rock Band this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the PAX pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've actually referenced Paul and Storm several times on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every time I reference myself as an opening band, that's the song that's going to be in Rock Band too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So once again, we're showcasing artists that people are going to know very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: CCP People Are Freaky
[SPEAKER_08]: that was probably the most hilarious one just because it's not my scene CCP bought White Wolf which is World of Darkness and they did usually at Dragon Con they do the Succubus Club which is at like this golf night club or whatever and you know just a lot of weird things happen from that scene I think we got an invite to something like that at E3 I saw pictures of that
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there's probably pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, we saw, like, when I was there, it was just, the comedy was great, where they had a guy doing, like, this whole routine with a lightsaber to techno music, and actually the techno music was actually going with, he was timing the lightsaber moves with the bass and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, seeing people use iPhones as glow sticks because they didn't have their own, you know, I mean... They have an app for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, yeah, the glow stick app's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, they weren't even doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They just had the screen on, the home screen on, and they were just waving them around.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Bobby, before we let you go, because I know you want to get a flight and all that fun stuff, I want to know what was the best thing about PAX and what was the worst thing about PAX?
[SPEAKER_08]: The best thing about PAX is that it started, and the worst thing is that it ended.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a tricky response.
[SPEAKER_04]: How did it compare to E3 this year?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you can't really compare it to E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, basically, I can actually compare PAX to last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were 70,000 people here.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the badges were sold out.
[SPEAKER_08]: My girlfriend actually bought a badge.
[SPEAKER_08]: She thought she was coming out, and she didn't, and she wound up being able to sell it for $170.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I thought it was going to be very crowded.
[SPEAKER_08]: I say I thought, but the difference between PAX with 70,000 people and, say, E3 2006 with 68,000 people is that PAX is spread out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not all 70,000 people are trying to be on the expo hall at the same time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whereas at E3, pretty much you could say 60,000 of the 68,000 were all trying to be in the exhibit hall so you couldn't move around.
[SPEAKER_08]: Other than when they were throwing t-shirts and giving away raffles, I could still walk around just fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, the big games, I had to wait in line to play, but it was pretty manageable.
[SPEAKER_08]: You didn't think that there were 70,000 people here this weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess a lot go for the live gaming events, too, and I bet those rooms take away quite a few people.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think when they say 70,000, that's spread out through the three days.
[SPEAKER_04]: PAX sells a lot of individual day badges, too, and it's never really, I think, accounted for just how many they're selling of those Friday, Saturday, Sunday badges.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, well, I mean, they have the numbers because the convention center actually let them sell 1,000 of the one-day passes for Saturday and Sunday at the last minute, and they were very surprised about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I mean, so people who did come up here hoping to get a badge were actually able to get badges at the last minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that was really nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: But basically, the thing is, there's only two or three events at this convention center that
[SPEAKER_08]: that take up the entire center.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually they double book.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a Jewish convention last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you ever remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Way up on the sixth floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: PAX actually had the entire building this time and they're like one of two events in the entire year that actually need the entire building.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's also why they're on Labor Day weekend because that's the only time they can schedule just one event.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Red Dead Redemption
[SPEAKER_08]: was Rockstar's big game that they were trying to show off here, and it's basically GTA meets Wild West.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you thought Liberty City was big, or not Liberty, yeah, Liberty City, if you thought GTA 4 was big, this one is huge, open world, it's basically GTA Wild West, and it actually looked really good from the demo they showed.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that shows that they can make a good demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll see, eventually.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Split Seconds guys were there, people were playing Split Seconds,
[SPEAKER_04]: and they say that's probably going to be in spring of 2010 or summer they say it's kind of been pushed back which means they have even more time to work on it from what we saw at E3 awesome well that was definitely one of the all stars at E3 so I'm hoping it got a lot of air time I guess you could say out there on the show floor sounds like a lot of fun stuff was DJ Hero playable there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Activision was not here Activision apparently did an invite only event Thursday night and that's when they showed off some stuff but I was not invited to that so I didn't get to go to that but no, Activision themselves were not physically here at the show this year
[SPEAKER_04]: Pax East, Pax West, Pax East
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: And even, like, the enforcers don't know if they're working Pax East.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I was talking to the media guy, because I want to start doing broadcasting again.
[SPEAKER_08]: They couldn't fit us in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, the space that we were in last year for All Games Radio was taken up by other tables.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, like, there was, like, tabletop gaming going on in that area, and that's why we couldn't have that area, and they didn't want to run the network all the way across.
[SPEAKER_08]: But...
[SPEAKER_08]: I asked him, I'm like, are you the new guy that's running the media?
[SPEAKER_08]: He said, I asked him, are you running the media at Boston?
[SPEAKER_08]: So we can go ahead and kind of start talking about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he's like, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Basically, here's the thing that he did tell me is that TaxEase has been outsourced to another company.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's not the same people running it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't know if that's going to change how it feels or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, I mean, the guys that run tax are just a little bit too overwhelmed with this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they've kind of had to farm it out and outsource it to another company while still having the reins on it, but we don't know if it's going to be...
[SPEAKER_08]: The same as this.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, and I'll be up there too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this Friday we're actually going to be running a show on my TV show, Friday Night Gaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're actually going to be running one of the games that's here that comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you've heard of Darkest of Days.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a time-traveling first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's actually by the same guys that make the Real Deal Casino game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it looked funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming out on PC and 360, and we're going to be running it on fnglive.net this Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for interrupting your show flow to get me in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby Blackwolf, live on Orange Lounge Radio, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: He always gives us like five minutes on his show every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can give him 15 on our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of great... I had no idea that PAX East was being run by a different company.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's huge news, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know if it's like huge news, but it's a huge interesting thing I didn't think about before.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game Darkest of Days looks funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically you can time travel to the past like the Civil War with giant weapons that you could totally hit everyone's ass with.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is intriguing, so I may have to try that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I shook my butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Parapara First Mix and played a lot of 2DX Distorted.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what was that weird trippy-ass game that you told me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here, play!
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Max Technica, the new arcade game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really my thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a little too K-pop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that was pretty.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did have a good time playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just very K-pop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like, wow, is this Andamiro?
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Dan played the new Hydro Thunder spiritual successor.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it called?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember the name, but it was a big machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Hydro something or Hydra something.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a cool little game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big, big machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan was like, give me the card I want to play, give me the card I want to play, give me the card I want to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, and I played that punching bag game, which was stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it was in the corner and I was bored.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I played lots of Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I played some Ragnarok Online before I got completely just fed up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fed up!
[SPEAKER_06]: And I have a guilty admission.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm downloading... Well, I downloaded... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not an addict.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't touched it in two years.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, my last date of playing was October in 2007.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why were you playing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you're going to play... I'm just downloading World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: My gaming week was alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm having a love-hate relationship right now with Rockstar, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love the new trailer for The Battle of the Gay Tony.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really making me excited for the next expansion they're going to have because it's now more over-the-top stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did play more Grand Theft Auto this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, they did patch Grand Theft Auto so that we can't run our modded games anymore, which is very... We were completely depressed for the remainder of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's absolute crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I am not letting that stop me, and I will get by this one way or another.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'll find a way around it eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm already kind of working on a way, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, it's kind of annoying, but I understand they did it for the greater good because there's assholes out there that like to ruin everybody's games by doing all these different cheat things and stuff and not exactly in the closed environments that we're playing in, but, hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still, though, it sucks that, you know, some people have to ruin it for everybody else.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other game I played, not that I got an early media copy, but I did get an early copy of The Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: And honestly, you know, I think one of the things you gotta consider when you're planning on buying The Beatles Rock Band is you better damn well be a Beatles fan, because if you're not, then you're not gonna enjoy it too much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm okay with The Beatles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't hate their music.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like some of their songs, but it kind of lost...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, it's... So you're saying the presentation, as somebody who's not as into the Beatles, kind of the presentation and the new packaging of Rock Band kind of wore off on you really quick?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I don't... It's not a bad game by any means, it's just, you know, for me, I can't see myself playing this for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if I could...
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: And I don't sing either A lot of reviews, I guess the embargo or whatever was lifted the other day Because all of a sudden there was just a ton of reviews that all hit the internet at once And I'm seeing a lot of positive about the presentation The way it looks, the way that it really feels like the Beatles It's kind of interesting, you're one of the first negative things I've heard Not so much negative, but just the fact that as someone who's not as into the Beatles It wore off on me Interesting
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd be less satisfied with a Guitar Hero release that is basically just re-skinned.
[SPEAKER_02]: They didn't put any effort into the presentation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still love the intro to the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't really played much of the story.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's mainly been just the quick play stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, for me, I wasn't, you know, I don't, like, listen to Beatles music that much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I recognize their songs, but I don't really, like, go seek out Beatles music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me ask you one more question.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you were, let's say, imagine that you were, like, a hardcore Beatles fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you think this game would compare to other artists' solitary games, such as Guitar Hero Aerosmith or the ACDC expansion for Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, this would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they totally nailed the Beatles and just the whole feel of the game and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really dig that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's just, I'm not a huge fan of the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, if they put that amount of effort into other artist games, yeah, then I would still be likely to check them out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, because even though I'm not a big fan of the Beatles, I still bought a copy of it, you know, because it looked really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I don't think I wasted my money on it it's just I'm not going to enjoy it as much as Rock Band where if I don't like a track in it or whatever it doesn't really matter because I can just always get different artists and stuff later on whereas the Beatles stuff if I don't like the tracks in it I can't really buy more tracks because there's just more Beatles music
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to our chat room, chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Certainly a lot of comments going on about the Beatles rock band.
[SPEAKER_04]: J-Rod in chat says, so because rock band Beatles has an opening cutscene, it's not a reskin version and, quote, better than the Guitar Hero Artist games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God, my brain is raging so hard.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's not forget, this is not the first rock band artist-dedicated game.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was an ACDC game that a lot of people forget came out last year that was, I mean, it was probably even worse than the Guitar Hero games, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was something they did for Walmart.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a cash-in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just straight-up cash-in.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, it's not like they've always done perfect releases, but to, I guess, kind of defend it a little bit, what do you think makes this a step above
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero Aerosmith, Guitar Hero Van Halen
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero, Metallica, Van Halen, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lego Rock Band is pretty much going to be the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing with Lego Rock Band, though, is it's also more like the other Telltale games where they have the little cut scenes there with the Lego characters and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the Lego games kind of feel the same as far as that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have a little bit of different elements into there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it's really not that much different than, say, Guitar Hero Van Halen or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have gone a little bit further in the presentation, but not enough to where I'm going to say it's amazing or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, see, I'm not feeling Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though I appreciate the Beatles, I'm all about Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think the music games I'll probably buy this holiday season are the Beatles Rock Band and guitar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero 5
[SPEAKER_06]: But, um, I'm still more looking forward to rock band Beatles, you know, Beatles rock band myself.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because I am a fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, not as big a fan as some people I know, but, you know, I'm a pretty, I love it and I'm actually looking forward to the overall experience of it, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not feeling it with Lego.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know enough about Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_06]: It seems like Band Hero is going to be a little bit... Band Hero should have marching band.
[SPEAKER_02]: Band Hero is basically just the same thing as Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically their E10 Plus game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got a bunch of different artists.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know who they have pimping it out?
[SPEAKER_02]: I found out the last artist that they haven't announced yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: No doubt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero 5 Guitar Hero 5 Guitar Hero 5
[SPEAKER_04]: So, but, I don't know, like, I'm okay with the re-skinnings if the song lists are really, really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it sounds like Band Hero might have a pretty good song list.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enough of the music game, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anything else in your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: TheDanceManiacs manual first sent to me because I would like to know how to wire this thing up.
[SPEAKER_02]: DanceManiacs sensors come in top and bottom.
[SPEAKER_02]: The bottom have two sensors, one on top, one on bottom, I think, or two on the bottom, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the top sensors only have one sensor.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so I got two top sensors, unfortunately, and now I have to do something or create my own sensors or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Talk to the guy that sold them to me and see if he has any bottom sensors, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: If there was a Guitar Hero No Doubt game, even if it was just a re-skinning or whatever, I'd probably buy it, because I really like No Doubt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought that whole album and rock band and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Call me a sucker, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of people, if their favorite band came out in whatever game, would feel the same way.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, I don't want to get into too much more talking about music games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you heard that Lego Rock Band, the rumor is that you're going to import those tracks into...
[SPEAKER_02]: Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope that's the case because I'm going to rent it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just rent it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Import those tracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shame on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do what I can.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Seg is in chat and wants to correct Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Telltale Games does not make any of the Lego games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you botched the company name when you were talking about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I'm thinking of... It's Traveler or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Traveler's Tales.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's T.T.
[SPEAKER_13]: Close, close, but very different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Traveler's Tales.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, same initials.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, at least we got that clarified.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on, My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good lord, I played a lot of games this week, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to talk about DJ Max Technica real quick, because I know DarkSakura was kind of eh about it, but I really enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was like Elite Beat Agents, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine if Elite Beat Agents were an arcade game, where you tap the screen with your finger to hit the buttons.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically what happens, you see a bar going across the top, and then it goes back down to the bottom.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like running a track around the screen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then as it passes these dots, you have to tap the dots to play the music.
[SPEAKER_04]: or you can drag your finger for some of them and some dots you have to hit over and over again to hit with the beat of the music I really like the way it was set up I had a really good time playing the game, the only problem I had with the game the music was completely uninspiring and not memorable to me and I know that's going to piss a lot of people off that I said that, some of the music game fans especially if you like the Korean pop, but I'm sorry it just was not, like I didn't wasn't able to distinguish one song from another that I was playing, like I can't put my finger on it, like
[SPEAKER_04]: 2DX just has such a variety and such cool songs in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of it is so memorable, at least in the past.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would almost say the same is true about Beatmania 2DX now, ever since 13th style about there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too bad they don't have a Ubi machine there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the game itself I thought was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would play it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe the music will grow on me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the game itself I had a lot of fun with.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm seeing frowns in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess maybe it's a personal preference thing, but the game itself, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, some other stuff I played this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Zen Pinball.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a pinball game that's available on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you check this out yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not yet, but I saw one of the games in action.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: so unfortunately that makes the display a little difficult in a pinball game but you know they do the best job they can you have different view modes you can use in this game to look at the table from different angles it really reminds me of a lot of the pinball games I played on the PC in the 90s but obviously you know with the high def graphics and all that I hear there's multiplayer too but I haven't tested that mode out online so I can't really review that component of it yet
[SPEAKER_04]: Things I'm Learning About Sony
[SPEAKER_04]: and there's so much functionality in the PSP that I don't think Sony does a really good job at advertising because I was really surprised.
[SPEAKER_04]: As I was looking at this, I was like, oh yeah, I think we've talked about this on this show but damn, I don't really hear about this a lot and it's actually a really cool feature of the PSP and that is that if you have a PSP, let's say I was here at Jamie's right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could, if I connected to her internet, I could power on my PlayStation 3 from home
[SPEAKER_04]: Go into my crossbar, see my crossbar on the PSP as I would see it on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go to like a movie that I have downloaded on the PS3 or even a data disk full of movies that's in my PS3 right now and I can play them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stream them over the internet to my PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: and you know it's kind of one of those things where it's like oh yeah I think I remember hearing about this but damn they should be shoving this down my throat that's really cool functionality that's way better than anything the DS and the Wii could ever do that makes the PS3 PSP combo in my opinion that much more awesome it's not just the movies thing or the data disc thing sorry you can't do blu-rays or DVDs but um
[SPEAKER_04]: you can do some of the games too like especially the PS1 classics and some of the I don't want to say arcade games but the PSN downloadable games you can also play on the PSP from anywhere by turning on your PS3 from somewhere else that's like kind of neat so that's remote play of course is the feature there they call that
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else did I play this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to say there were more games, but I can't think of anything right now, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess I will just leave it at that so we can continue on with the show because I know we want to get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, we have some housekeeping news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a whole lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to let you guys know I am going to be out in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll be here next week, but I'll be out in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know if there will be a show or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll keep you posted.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm going to be in LA, so I won't be here.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going on a personal trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what happens in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we will be back next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as other housekeeping goes, you can always follow us on Twitter, www.twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be getting into Twitter topics a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, you can always send us emails, mailbag at orangelounge.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget to join us on Facebook at the OL Army or on LiveJournal at username Orangelounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, how about some gaming news?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, start us off tonight with some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, lots of gaming news this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, let's start off with the rumor, and this wasn't exactly a complete rumor, but we knew it was coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know if it was going to be coming this soon, but there are DSi only games coming this fall, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, of course, no official announcements have been made yet about...
[SPEAKER_02]: DSi exclusive games will be out this fall
[SPEAKER_02]: DSi Exclusive
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, alternative reality, or I guess an alternative reality game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Augmentive reality game, that's the word I'm thinking about.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you find monsters and then you collect them and put them against each other.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of like Monster Rancher, but with a camera.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, sort of like the barcode scanner games back when.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, yes, very similar to that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: So this is one of the first DSi-only games.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I remember correctly, I think from...
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't remember if those are DSi exclusive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they do use the DSi, but I don't remember if they were exclusive or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said they were, but the sell sheet said not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: There might be more coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: So interesting that Nintendo is kind of letting the third parties do this first.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of torn on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is one of those things where I'm a little bit disappointed because I really didn't see the point in getting a DSi because the DS honestly has everything I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really need the camera or any of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I don't think you need this game either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just a lot of these games are going to be DSI only.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're obviously going to be using the gimmicks of it, the camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's basically it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: How long, Loki, and you know this is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: How long?
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, let's take bets here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: How long until Nintendo puts out...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's almost I think how they plan it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know they may not care, but here's the thing though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their audience, the people that buy Nintendo products, are a lot different than your normal consumer that buys any other console franchise.
[SPEAKER_02]: For example, with the Wii and the DS owners, I think that they're pretty content with what they've got on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: or the Wii and they're not gonna exactly like if the Wii HD comes out your normal mom and pop is not gonna upgrade to a Wii HD because they could care less because they have Wii Sports and they don't really care about upgrading to another system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same with the DSi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Until Wii Sports 3 is Wii HD only.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I think
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see how they're going to convince people that they need to buy a DSi because, oh, this game uses a camera now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Question from your distribution perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are the regular DSs being phased out?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Takeo Ray in chat says, That's why I never got the DSi.
[SPEAKER_04]: My DS Lite is perfectly fine for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much the same camp I'm in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I rarely play the DS as it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've listened to the show before, you know kind of my little rant on handhelds.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I will say, the PSP is quickly gaining a lot of favor in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily as a gaming device, but as a multifunctional media device.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is quickly gaining popularity with me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm sorry, but if they come out with a new Zelda game or something that requires a camera...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: I won't buy it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to buy another system for one fucking game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: When your library plays on my system except for this one game, boo fucking hoo, I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will make do.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're expecting these hardcore players to go, okay, let me buy a new system for this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the audience that buys the DS, they aren't really hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just the wrong expectation for their market.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you already have a DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanna play the new stuff that comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew it was gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what if it sucks?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's another thing we have to remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if I don't care?
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's a little different, because she's a system collection whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's not your typical gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, anything new that comes out, I pretty much want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we pretty much end up getting it.
[SPEAKER_04]: She owns some fucking Dreamcast game that came with a dish, for heaven's sake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, she's just a video game collector.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah, you're not exactly going to want my opinion on that because mine's going to be, well, why shouldn't it be in my collection?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's move on to another story that maybe we will get your opinion on then, and that's about the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's interesting is that there's always been that rumor that's been going around probably as long as we've been podcasting that Apple's going to get into gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apple's gonna get into gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're gonna do something.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're gonna get into gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apple kind of just got into gaming when everybody was kind of looking everywhere else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, Apple is into gaming now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they have a lot of users using their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, I'm talking about the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't believe me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, guess what they announced this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Grand Theft Auto Chinatown Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the game that was the DS exclusive.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were so excited about it at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember, they came out and, ooh, GTA Chinatown Wars is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is right after they announced that a PSP version was coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, that is on its way as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's also coming to the iPhone, and of course, that would mean the iPod Touch as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not a whole lot of other details at this time, but only just that they're calling it a perfect match for the iPhone and iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of iffy on this because I don't think... Some games just don't run well on the iPhone and iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's a very...
[SPEAKER_04]: Peggle
[SPEAKER_04]: or any PopCap game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Certain games that are optimized for the iPhone and iPod Touch run pretty darn good.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I see the iPhone and iPod Touch basically the app store that they have it's just the most successful mobile gaming platform is basically it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other phones and stuff like that don't really work well with gaming whereas this
[SPEAKER_02]: They built this phone around the apps that you can make in these programs, which is good.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as it being a gaming platform, yeah, sure, I guess it could be.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can put lots of games on it, but you're not going to see the same functionality as some of these games that are on the DS and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: but I would just see that they could do something like that that would just add a lot of oomph to the iPhone and iPod Touch and make it that much more.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't you think it still is competition for the DS?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_04]: To an extent, the PSP?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's always competition for them because their app store right now is definitely working a lot better than what they have for DSiWare or the PlayStation Network stuff and obviously the PlayStation Go is going to try to
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Like one story that I don't think we are covering tonight, I think, but it was in the thread.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just ran out of room tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, there was a game on the iPhone that just came out this week that is like a PP simulation game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's what it's called.
[SPEAKER_04]: IPP was the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you literally are like aiming at a urinal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is stupid, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my point.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of crap out there on the iPhone and iPod Touch.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one person's trash is another person's treasure.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, then couldn't the same be said about whatever Sony's planning with their mini bar and the DSi to an extent?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't have a problem with Sony's minis.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have a problem with the DSiware because it's a lot of calculators and clocks, which, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just doesn't really add anything to the DSi.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get to release dates here in just a little bit, but first, over to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, you sound so enthusiastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: But first, over to the one and only fabulous DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know, Splatterhouse was being developed by Bottle Rocket Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they don't exist anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: They clung to life as long as they could, but the plug was pulled.
[SPEAKER_06]: So guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Their house got splattered.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I really don't know what that means for Splatterhouse, except that it's not going to be coming out anytime soon unless someone else picks that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just let it die.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a neat idea, but just let it die.
[SPEAKER_04]: Might as well come out at this point.
[SPEAKER_06]: They say that they're actually working on another company that they're going to start from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think it's sad, though, that although it seems like there's a silver lining here that for every door closes, another opens, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I seriously feel like this is, again, we had a lot of this at the end of the year last year, but this is like the fourth story I think we've had in the scope of two months about some studio closing down.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's because they're way behind in schedule.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game was supposed to be out at the end of last year, and then they pushed it back to, you know, June, and then it still wasn't done.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, time to close.
[SPEAKER_04]: WhatUpG in our chatroom at chat.orangeonestradio.com asked a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't Namco take Splatterhouse internally?
[SPEAKER_04]: I seem to remember hearing that at one point, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, yeah, there's nothing about what exactly is going to happen with it, but Namco pulled the development of Splatterhouse back in.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right, but there hasn't been anything else said about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, hopefully those guys, you know, as much as we're making silly jokes about Splatter and House, you know, it does suck when people lose their jobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I hope this whole starting a studio from the ground up works out for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, just try to get stuff out there as soon as you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get the public experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a really tricky balance, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to spend enough time on the products to have a quality product, but at the same time,
[SPEAKER_04]: If you spend too much time on it, you go the way of Duke Nukem Forever and the guys behind that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am confident that that game will be super epic when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever you say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm completely lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get your expectations too high.
[SPEAKER_02]: My expectations are incredibly low.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, lo, then fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, never mind then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was like in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember the 90s.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: So... Yes, it's when No Doubt was popular.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Speaking of something from a long time ago, God of War and God of War 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I guess that wasn't that long ago, but hey, it was a few years.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's ancient.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember how we were talking about backwards compatibility and how they probably could do it, but they're not?
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's why they're not doing it, because now we can sell every game that we've made over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm okay with it, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because how is this different than what Nintendo's doing in Metroid Prime Trilogy?
[SPEAKER_04]: It isn't different.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't... I think it's kind of cool, because then I can... You know, yeah, and why I'm okay with this, Loki, is because they're going back and they're making the games HD, they're giving them trophies.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, they might be old games, but they're giving them new treatment.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it was still a trend before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go back to the PlayStation 1, you would see Super Nintendo games, the Final Fantasy and Chrono Trigger re-release.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not like this is anything new, but what I think makes this kind of special and kind of cool is that the games are being souped up a little bit to match the times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I miss the God of War boat back on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: This actually really interests me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, God of War 2 actually did output at 720p because there were a handful of games that were on the PlayStation 2 and on the Xbox that would both either output at 720p or they would do 1080i, which was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But God of War 2 was one of the ones that actually did the 720p, so it wouldn't be that much of a stretch for them to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't there like a secret code or something you had to put in to do that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's so weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey...
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely a good way to get ramped up for the new game coming out, obviously, in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: And true, that is the price.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're going to buy them both new right now on the PlayStation 2, that is the price that it would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's $40.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think I'm going to wait a little bit for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because again, I never played God of War 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I played it at a friend's house for a little bit, but I never bought it myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played through 1, never played through 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw makes a comment about Metroid Prime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Metroid Prime 3 in Metroid Prime Trilogy was censored a tad.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the cutscenes had a character say, damn, it was redubbed with a no.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: So listen, I told you not to climb up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the... And then it pauses and says, do you want him to say fuck or do you want him to not use any... Fudge!
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fudge?
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it just censors the rest of the game like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think that's kind of funny, the way that they give that option to you.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's an interesting way to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: J-Rod in chat gives his quick reviews these are like twitter reviews of these games it's very short but maybe help you out Loki God of War 1 I think has a better story but God of War 2 was overall better yeah I really wish I had played God of War 2 but the thing with God of War 1 is I got so frustrated at the end of the game because the last boss was really hard oh
[SPEAKER_02]: and the last boss glitched out so it didn't quite work right so I beat the crap out of them just over and over and over again even though I know what I was supposed to do in the game but it still wouldn't work because the game glitched out so I just got pissed off with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's go back over to the Nintendo Wii for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we were talking about Metroid Prime Trilogy.
[SPEAKER_04]: One other thing you might be  which actually, by the way, the Metroid Prime games are pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm even thinking  I have Metroid Prime 3, but I'm thinking about getting the trilogy because I never had Metroid Prime 1 or 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: My roommate had them around that time.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how you can't get, obviously, the Metroid game downloaded to your Game Boy Advance with Metroid Prime Trilogy, but you can get the costume.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was in that game as well to kind of download to the Fusion costume or whatever in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That unlocks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious what other kind of synergy between the three games there is, if any.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, anyway, speaking of Nintendo, you know how they had a web browser?
[SPEAKER_04]: They had their Nintendo Internet channel that you could download for a $5 fee?
[SPEAKER_04]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Earlier this week in Japan and Europe, that fee went away.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then just a couple days later it also went away in North America.
[SPEAKER_04]: The internet channel is now free to download.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you have a Wii but you never got the internet channel, you can go ahead and download it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's free.
[SPEAKER_04]: It used to cost 500 Wii points to download.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I should take a step back.
[SPEAKER_04]: When it first came out, you might remember, if you were an early Wii owner like myself and I think the others in studio here,
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: and if you were one of the people that paid 500 Wii points for this sadly Nintendo isn't going to give you the 500 points back but what they are going to do is they're going to give you a 500 point credit towards a virtual console game so at least you get a little something although I don't know if I was one of the people that paid 500 points for it I might be a little sad but then again it's only 5 bucks I don't know 5 bucks is still a lot I guess
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, I'm also kind of like, as much as I think that's cool they're making it free again, unless this new remastered internet channel somehow made it a lot faster to browse the internet on the Wii, I don't think it's going to be that great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Browsing the internet on the Wii is kind of slow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what did you do when you were only dial-up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: or Phantasmagoria, which was on seven CDs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used to download overnight, and I used to have a download accelerator to basically queue up a bunch of stuff to download.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some folks in chat want to clarify, X-Link says the credit was only for Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, no, it did open up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go check out Nintendo.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is now.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is just a NES virtual console download credit that you can get now.
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's not 500 points clarifies Deke Bandit as a free NES game that's right it's basically a credit towards a free NES virtual console game which of course is 500 points but you can't like take the 500 points and apply it towards a Sega game or something else has to be an NES game so there you go alright let's move on with some more news it would help if my brain worked yes it would it's kind of required to do a show
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, you know that the new Halo 3 ODST is supposed to be coming out and it has a launch date of September 22nd for, of course, Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there are people out there who are playing illegitimate copies, meaning they either have a burn of some kind or received a copy that they weren't supposed to receive.
[SPEAKER_06]: and um so uh the uh big Microsoft enforcer dude went on Twitter and said and I quote I spy with my little eye some illegitimate ODST players no early play for you commencing permabans and except for those who actually have legit copies like early um you know actual true early copies for reviewers and that type of thing they're okay um
[SPEAKER_02]: Or if you have an actual legit copy of the game that you happen to get early, then that's okay too apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand why people are playing the one that's out there now because the leaked one that's out there is actually in French.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people know French.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we import Japanese games even though we can't read Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of curious, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are they able to spot the difference?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is that some type of secret they're not saying?
[SPEAKER_02]: They're claiming that's a secret.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're just going after whomever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what if they get it wrong?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that they know.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a way they can tell the difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're basically... Or is this a scare tactic?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's a scare tactic.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other thing I think is, if you want to think the real conspiracy theory to it, is that people are thinking that this is actually a copy that they leaked out that's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Modified in a way that they can flag people that have played it or something like that, which would be entrapment, but I don't see how they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm guessing that it's because you're going to see a bunch of people all playing this French-English version of it, like in the United States or something like that, and people are going to be like, Huh, I'm pretty sure that they didn't buy that from wherever it was released at.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably going to be a hacked version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need a weapon, I'm Mr. Chef
[SPEAKER_04]: Master Chef.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, he put Chef, but it's supposed to be Chief.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why I read Chef.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I would like a game called Master Chef to come out next to Cooking Mama.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Deekman in chat says it's the same way they tell if people are playing burn games on live.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of the new stuff that's out there now makes it very difficult for them to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're really stealth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would know, I played modified Grand Theft Auto 4's for like, what, how many months now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's still risky, you know it's risky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go around the globe and explore some upcoming release dates from around the globe.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Darkest of Days, PC, Xbox 360
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what Bob was talking about earlier, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awesome, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Trine coming to PC this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Disgaea 2, Dark Hero Days on PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: War Leader, Clash of Nations on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, Fallen Earth, Welcome to the Apocalypse on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Go Play City Sports on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had another sports game collection.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this one has rooftop hockey, so I kind of had to think of a little bit of clerks there.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cubed, the Q Games collection coming to Xbox 360 with your resin Every Extend Extra Extreme.
[SPEAKER_02]: Time of Shadows on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dirt 2 coming to PlayStation 3, DS, Xbox 360, and Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I thought PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine Detectives on DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: Isle 2 Strumovic, Birds of Prey coming to Xbox 360, PS3, DS, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Capcom Platinum Hits Triple Pack that wonderful collection of three games including Dead Rising, Lost Planet, and Devil May Cry 4 coming to the 360 this week Ant Nation on the DS kind of I guess your kids first real time strategy game
[SPEAKER_02]: LittleBigPlanet Game of the Year Edition coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course the big one, the Beatles Rock Band coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, the Wii, as well as the standalone instruments and your two different bundles that are available for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Finally, if you have little kids that want to learn to read, they have three different games for you for the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Virtual Tutor Reading K-1, Pre-K-K, and 1-2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also coming out...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Mario & Luigi Bowser's Inside Story Xbox 360 Elite
[SPEAKER_04]: The Last Remnant, speaking of price reductions, is getting one this week on the 360, as is Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both of those games moving into the Platinum Collection, as well as Call of Duty 4, Modern Warfare, and Bioshock.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I wouldn't be surprised if Microsoft's doing a little push in Japan right now with all these recent price drops.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all happening on...
[SPEAKER_04]: The 10th of this month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also happening on the 10th of this month, Sid Meier's Civilization Revolution, the Japanese localized version, is out on the PlayStation 3, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: As well as, of course, a price drop as well for Call of Duty 4 over there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to the Nintendo Wii, nothing this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forever Blue 2 next week, but not this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: also another House of the Dead game but we'll cover that next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2 nothing this week either.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all on the 17th of September.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not much coming out on PlayStation 2 right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Engagement on Desert
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you got for Japanese releases this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, for the UK, we have some, I mean, pretty much the standard stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the 9th is Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: On the 11th, we have Championship Manager 2010, Colin McRae Dirt 2, yay, Guitar Hero 5, Mini Ninjas, NHL 2K10, and Section 8.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, Rob, there's something on the 15th that you might be interested in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Zuma's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this has a similar release date here in the US if it's not out already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's kind of like a sequel to Zuma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not my favorite PopCap game.
[SPEAKER_04]: My problem with Zuma is it's not something you can sit down and play quickly, like a game of Bejeweled or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zuma takes a long time to get through a game because not only does it take a little while to beat each level, but then you have three lives.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not as big on Zuma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: But there are other PopCap games I really enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know I still got a copy of Bookworm Adventures 2 I need to play.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, don't laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm laughing because I've played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Final Fantasy meets Boggle.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I do want to check out the sequel.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, Rob, I have to say, I like your shirt and all of its Helvetica-ness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You and your font hornus.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's Helvetic, I swear.
[SPEAKER_06]: Once you see it, you can't unsee it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple more stories for you before we get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, this week we had the debut of the new trailer for the new expansion for Grand Theft Auto 4, The Ballad of Gay Tony.
[SPEAKER_02]: And with that, it looks like it's going to be returning back to the over-the-top Grand Theft Auto fun that you can expect from the rest of the series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some new stuff to note in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some new weapons that they did kind of show off in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: A new...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Subway Car, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a golf cart in there as well, and some new sports cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's going to be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you notice what the song in the trailer was?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was quite... Those that listen to the Orange Laundry after birth that we only do live for a little bit after we tape live will understand why that's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then also they had...
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there was some other stuff rumored that there's a FIB tank in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like their SWAT tank or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm looking forward to this because they ruined my modded games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now, I'm seriously... It's like we're coming out of depression or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Going back to playing the normal game is just wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: There are some pretty cool stuff coming for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, also out of the trailer, though, of course they had a lot of different cutscenes in there and they recognized some of the characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them I was kind of interested by is Gracie, which was actually one of the missions in Grand Theft Auto IV.
[SPEAKER_02]: You had to kidnap her, which is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she's in there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Overall, it looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not as big of a Grand Theft Auto IV player as you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who is Gay Tony?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like a mom boss?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he's a mob boss.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's Tony Prince, is the guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: He basically owns nightclubs, and he's a member of the Ancelotti Crime Syndicate.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically, he owns the biggest gay and straight nightclubs in Algonquin.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's who you play...
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't play him, but you play a guy that kind of helps him out, Luis Fernando Lopez, which is like this Dominican guy that you play as.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's his bodyguard.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the games, all three episodes, including the main game, all kind of culminate around this diamond deal that goes down and goes wrong, and that's the Impossible Trinity is each one of their...
[SPEAKER_02]: Rolls in this diamond deal And if I remember correctly, I think Louise comes in And actually breaks up the diamond deal And tries to steal the diamonds So that's definitely going to be part of the game
[SPEAKER_04]: I got a weird question for you, but as kind of like the gay guy on the program, and who isn't as familiar with Grand Theft Auto 4, I'm kind of curious, not to get all glad on you, but I'm curious, like, is this like a step forward for gay rights, or is this going to be a bunch of stereotypes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, does gay Tony go around going, that's super!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, he didn't really do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a character, though, in Grand Theft Auto 4 that was like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember his name, but yeah, he was very flamboyant.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he didn't seem flamboyant in the trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, he wasn't talking much, but I don't think he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, I'm totally cool with it if it's like, you know, hey, you have a gay character who's like a cool mob boss and all this stuff, just like anybody else.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, if it's just going to be stereotype after stereotype, then I'm just going to facepalm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I don't think it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they're usually pretty, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rockstar's pretty good about that stuff, usually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm hopeful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just hoping they don't add any more full frontal penis again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that was enough in the last game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't need full frontal penis in this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you wouldn't have any problem with full boobage and everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, because they haven't done that in this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: It being an emirated game and stuff, for nudity and that kind of stuff, there's no...
[SPEAKER_06]: It's establishment of a double standard.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't want to see cock, but you don't want to see boobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't want to see more cock.
[SPEAKER_02]: There already is cock in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I want to see boobs that go along with the cock so we have an equal representation.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want equal opportunity nudity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually support his statement.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can go for equal opportunity nudity.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying that they need to, like, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, but whatever
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a game.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the hell do I care?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just funny how there's a lot of people out there that says, Oh, because it's gay Tony.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope we don't have to see more cock.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I hope just for that you get beaver shot in this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for that kind of ignorant comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: This game is going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm just hoping, though, that they bring back the tank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because the tanks are awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: The minigun, the flamethrower, and the chainsaw.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But already I like where they're going with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can't wait to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more story for you guys, and then we're going to go to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this story has to actually do with the 360, where this download content is.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, random-ass question.
[SPEAKER_04]: When they announced the Grand Theft Auto 4 exclusive content, it is never coming to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: As far as we're aware.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe someday they might say, okay, Windows over, we're going to release this disc now on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: It could be ported in a heartbeat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, since all the formats are basically the same, it's just recoding the textures and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: If the system is in HD mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: And apparently anti-aliasing is also out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Full screen anti-aliasing you do not have to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Those requirements are now out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Microsoft kind of was lenient on these rules before, and one very, very notable game that got around these rules is Halo 3, because you might remember, and I remember some stories on this when Halo 3 first came out, it's not running in true 720p, it's running at 1152 by 640, so it's 100 pixels short on either side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently Call of Duty 4 is also 600p also.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think this is a huge deal because I'm all about frame rate a little more than resolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, a great game should have both great resolution and good frame rate, something like Oblivion or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But some of the games that get really busy online, they have to scale back the resolution a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So why now, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of wondering if they decided to get rid of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this because maybe 360 has enough penetration in the marketplace now so they don't need to be advertising all this HD, HD, HD?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe there's a big game coming out that didn't have this or something and they figured that, hey, let's make this available so that it's fair for everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it makes it easier to develop on the system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alpha Cananogram has an interesting thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe it's for the indie games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if the indie games were ever held to the same standard.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't think so either.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a good thought, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because I don't think a lot of the indie games I've played have full-screen anti-aliasing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm trying to think if that actually... Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The technical certifications are changing, so we'll see what games come of that a little later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for now, let's go to a classic video game in a little segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like to call it the classic video game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the part of the show where DarkSakura likes to browse the gaming vault and find a game that she says, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: You kids should be playing this game this week, or at least check it out and show this game a little respect.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what game did you pick for the kids this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic Team Sonic Team
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, tell us a little bit about Choo Choo Rocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just out of curiosity, does this have to do with the fact that it's 9-9 of 0-9 this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, actually, it has to do with Dan fussing because I don't put in games he suggests, or I already have put in games that he suggested.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cat Mania So yeah, I put in Choo Choo Rocket So this was one of the first of the online games that came on the Dreamcast And then they just started giving it away with the Dreamcast as an online demo And it was also given away free in Europe When you would order a copy Well, you could order your copy by connecting to the Dream Arena service
[SPEAKER_06]: The whole point of the game is to get mice, as in choo-choo, because in Japanese that's the sound a mouse makes, it's choo.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get them onto a rocket while avoiding the cats, or the kapu-kapu, that roam around the board.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to place down arrows to determine the path the mice are going to take, because they just keep going in a straight line until they run into a wall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: and you can get special colored mice like a gold mouse will give you 50 extra mice a pink mouse gives you those events like we were talking about the cat mania, the mouse mania
[SPEAKER_06]: But the single-player mode is actually, I think, my favorite because it's really... It's really... It gets super complex.
[SPEAKER_06]: It really turns into a matter of figuring out how you're gonna get from point A to point B when you've got all these obstacles in your path and all you have is a limited number of arrows.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game is fucking fast-paced, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, that was my biggest problem with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was too fast for me to keep up with.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need, like, choo-choo slow...
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you also got a challenge mode where you have to get all the mice into rockets or get a cat to eat all the mice or put the cat into a guarded rocket or other stuff and you had a time limit on it and it had 25 levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could do that actually one or two player or two.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a Game Boy Advance version that's really the same as the Dreamcast version, but you can actually play with one cartridge multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, y'all said a level editor in it, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, the Game Boy Advance version wasn't made by Sega.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also in Sonic Battle, Tails has a choo-choo for his landmine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, it's a pretty fun little game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's just fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Choo-choo rocket.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which Jamie swears has nothing to do with the 9909 or 99, whatever you want to call it, anniversary of the Dreamcast this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chew, chew.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to go ahead and take a break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We always like to take a break in the middle of the show to just kind of stretch, you know, refill our drinks or go to the restroom or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we suggest taking an opportunity to do the same because there is plenty more to come in Part B of our show tonight, including Twitter topics, rapid fire news tonight, and more long discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about Blur, which is a racing game I am really looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Damon Auburn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blur!
[SPEAKER_04]: Blur the racing game, silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk about a brand new reality show coming to Sony, PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds kind of interesting would be the word for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And 3D, possibly on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some interesting developments with that this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to do all that right after a quick break here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned!
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back, everybody, to Part B of our podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're taping live on this Sunday evening, September 6, 2009.
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy Labor Day to all of our American listeners who get tomorrow off of work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, you know, if it's not America that you're from, then just have a happy Monday or happy week wherever you're at.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get into some more gaming news as we tape live on this Sunday evening at www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we have Bobby Blackwolf joining us earlier in the show, live from Seattle, where he had just wrapped up Penny Arcade Expo, which just came to a close earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any word on what the final game was in their little PAX... What do they call that?
[SPEAKER_04]: The little PAX... Megathon, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any word on what the final game was yet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Has that hit the internet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I've seen it on the internet, but I will look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Props.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mega props to you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_04]: No pressure or anything, but can you imagine the amount of pressure that it all comes down to skee-ball?
[SPEAKER_04]: That reminds me, though, there was a pricing game on The Price is Right, because your shirt reminds me of this, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's wearing a Price is Right shirt today, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a skee-ball game that, like, if you could hit the target on the skee-ball, you'd win, like, a new car.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, that's almost as much pressure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's, like, okay, so the rounds as it went, the first round was Mario Kart Wii, the second round was Bookworm Adventures, round three was Halo 3 ODST, round four was the Beatles Rock Band, round five was Kinect 4, and then, of course, the final round being skee-ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting, because you have, like, some new games mixed with some board games...
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good mix at the Omegathon this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to get back into our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to start off with some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we have theme song now for Twitter topics, don't we?
[SPEAKER_04]: I totally forgot to queue it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a bad host tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fired!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on a minute, let me get the theme song here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only if we get to use fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any exciting plans for Labor Day, you guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to sleep.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, we have to do something tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of want to just stay in and play WoW all day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I know what's going on tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Becky's going to come over tonight and we're going to watch My Fair Lady.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fun!
[SPEAKER_04]: Any reason why you were just deciding to get into old school musicals?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for the fun of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't remember how to except that it was very random.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing wrong with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But we're thinking about going to Yog-Yog after the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: FNANDO
[SPEAKER_04]: asked the very first question.
[SPEAKER_04]: What if there was a mariachi band as a game?
[SPEAKER_04]: It might sound a little like our background music.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd play a mariachi game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would totally play one, but I think the novelty would honestly wear off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was that tambourine game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you've ever seen this, but the makers of Samba de Amigo, at least in the arcade, also made a tambourine game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I forget the name of this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is the gayest game I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I use that term to mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw305 says, there's a story here he's linking us to.
[SPEAKER_04]: The creator of Mobile Suit Gundam says that video games are evil and links us to a story that ran on Gamasutra earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, Yoshiuki Tomino gave a keynote speech at the CEDEC game conference and said, quote, I think that video games are evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gaming is not a type of activity that provides any support to our daily lives and all these consoles are just consuming electricity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's say we have about 3 billion people on this planet wasting their time bringing no productivity at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Add 10 billion more people and what would happen to our planet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Video games are assisting the death of our planet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, crazy man.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to bite the hand that feeds you, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would he say something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Gundam is unlike every fucking game platform ever in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Redertainment wants us to talk about this topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Most people complain that early adopters are getting screwed over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does the PS3 Slim mean it the other way around?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of been true of Sony for a long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do find the whole lack of even software emulation and the removal of Linux, I do find that odd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the rest of it I get.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get why they take out USB slots.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get some of this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get that the Slim might have a slightly longer loading time.
[SPEAKER_04]: The rest of this I don't think I get.
[SPEAKER_03]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_03]: It makes sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't understand why they removed Linux.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I understand that maybe no one's using that function, but I don't see how that function really did anything unless people found a way to hack the PS3 through Linux.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't heard of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It actually would be fairly easy using Linux, I would think.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I think they keep everything separated.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want more information, I urge you to follow them on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're at twitter.com slash fundarazor I just linked it in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: F-U-N-D-E-R-A-Z-O-R They only have 10 followers right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for charity.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should have 10,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out that event near you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to try and go to the one in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'm pretty sure I will be going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I kind of told Seg I would, so I'm going to go and then probably take the next day off work so I can go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to go?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll cover it for OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: and once more fans on Facebook I don't think I'm following them on Facebook yet so I will go add them myself a little later in the show but again that's F-U-N-D-E-R-A-Z-O-R and K.O.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ray is reminding us about Extra Life which is the marathon that's also happening on October 17th that we talked about last week Extra Life SG is their Twitter so two great events one in October one in December do them both think of the children damn you and how crunchy they are shush
[SPEAKER_04]: and Spazinator says PlayStation 3 firmware 3.0 unannounced or hidden feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: The addition of print screen and screenshot to the web browser.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was not aware.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, nothing you can't already do on a PC, but I guess it's kind of nice to have that on the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know that screenshotting is coming to home as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're going to do like a first person view so you can screenshot there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I think that is going to do it for Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I'll do one more.
[SPEAKER_04]: TKL Ray says, uh, just beat Batman Arkham Asylum.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you guys think of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That game was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Dan was playing a lot of it while Misty was here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_06]: and of course, and who's also here right now, our other friend Mystique.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we had Misty and Misty and me making commentary the entire time.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were doing the MST3K version of Batman Arkham Asylum and it was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then every time Harley came out, I was like, Harley!
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty good, but I wish it had more of an ending.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you're a fangirl of the comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the comic series.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like DC Comics.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you would like the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, I meant the comic book show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I watch some of the animated series.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not the world's biggest Batman fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan loves it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan loves it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mystique just came in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Has Mystique ever been on the show?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come here, Mystique.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, come here, come here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's end Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk to Mystique for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Mystique.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just talk loud and strong in that microphone because it's kind of sensitive.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't want me to be that loud.
[SPEAKER_04]: You hold in your hand a bunch of DC, what is this, DVDs of movies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is Superman, the animated series, and Justice League Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you guys going to Mystery Science 3000, like the movie you were watching last week when I was here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there might be fighting going on over the TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be a throwdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there's going to be a throwdown.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of Batman Arkham Asylum?
[SPEAKER_07]: I cannot wait to play that game, even though I watched a lot of it with Dan, although I'm really upset that I can't play the Joker in the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, because he has the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_04]: He has the 360 version.
[SPEAKER_07]: He just had to tell me after I made a decision of which one I was gonna buy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, hmm, both of them went down in price.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I think I'm gonna get the 360 since I have Netflix and all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Dan had to go and tell me, you know, on the PS3, you can play the Joker.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, you're a bastard.
[SPEAKER_04]: We need to get a bigger room!
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we need a bigger box.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's time to get a bigger boat.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a shark.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're done with that for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So thank you guys very much for contributing to Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, Rapid Fire News is up next.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some quick gaming news starting from Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uncharted 2, of course, is getting a collector's edition, which will be coming out with the game in October.
[SPEAKER_02]: And with the collector's edition, you will be able to get a replica knife.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, because that's what gamers need things to stab stuff with.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want a knife.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that's a knife.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, it's the Fortune Hunter edition, and it does come with the replica of the game's mysterious ancient artifact.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it is going to be very limited, and I guess apparently only available through GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, you know, they get all the limited editions nowadays.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Konami, in kind of a strange turn of events, is publishing the new 99 Nights game, 99 Nights 2, which, judging by the screenshot, looks way better than the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero 5
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And the week after that, they're going to be getting the AFI Track Pack, which is going to include Beautiful Thieves, Girls Not Grey, and The Missing Frame, also available for $2 each or 160 Microsoft Points.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, of course, the Track Packs as a whole you can buy in a bundle for $5.49.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then finally...
[SPEAKER_02]: September 24th we'll be getting another track pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: No name for this track pack, but apparently it includes the editors with Munich, Faint with Geeks Were Right, and the Yayayas with Dull Life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also available for $2 each or $5.49 for the pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bit.Trip.Void
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: The Bit.Trip games are actually a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wonder if they'll release a compilation of this a little later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That could be a very fun game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think there is a release date yet announced for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just say later this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, it was playable at PAX.
[SPEAKER_04]: So some folks already got to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Arcade Attack is coming to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently it's a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has the arcade style controls like you see in Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you are going up against Shredder.
[SPEAKER_04]: by the way this was also shown at PAX
[SPEAKER_04]: You lucky PAX attendees getting your hands on some early stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another game that's coming out onto Xbox Live Arcade, Puzzle Bobble Live coming out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will probably make its way over here as Bust a Move Live or something like that over here in America because there's that whole fact that Bust a Move over here is actually Puzzle Bobble.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why they call it Bust a Move and then ruined the name of the actual Bust a Move game as Bust a Groove over here, I will never understand that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have an answer for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do they call Puzzle Bobble Bust a Move here?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because they're stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, the game's coming out in Japan on September 30th for 800 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_04]: No comment yet on North America or Europe release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure the games will be ported soon enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a pretty standard game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember on the PlayStation 2, Bust a Move was one of the first games that came out for it?
[SPEAKER_04]: And on the cover, it had a baby wearing sunglasses and had a big bubble that said Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: It made no sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: It made no sense at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was Bust a Move 2 that had the baby, I think, on the cover.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, what the hell was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That just sums up in a nutshell the transition of Puzzle Bobble to Bust a Move.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just never understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bochikawa says it's copyright infringement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Forget on what, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_06]: I have some stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, some kind of interesting news in looking at almost an international point of view.
[SPEAKER_06]: First of all, as in Japan, the PlayStation 3 sales have plummeted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_06]: With, you know, my bad sound effects.
[SPEAKER_06]: That actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: is going ahead of the PS3 Slim launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've gone for the regular PS3.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's only sold 1,040 units with last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, the Xbox 360 rose to sell 7,254 units.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course...
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a little bit of Nintendo sale drop but they're still pushing a lot of the DSi and DS Lite.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as other stuff going on, for some rock band news, there's a new PAX track that's going to be Freeze Pop, Jonathan Colton, MC Frontalot, and Paul and Storm.
[SPEAKER_06]: And each song will be $1 a piece.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you've got that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A whole dollar?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but it's Freeze Pop and Jonathan Colton and other bands that are pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to have both of those at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the last thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: This gets the facepalm award of the night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other than those idiot people wanting to pull their children out of school so they can't see Obama's speech.
[SPEAKER_06]: So stupid.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, there's a special function for the six axis in Ninja Gaiden Sigma 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to have six axis support.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what it's going to do?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Boob jiggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can control boob jiggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is the next likely progression.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like I was telling Sauce earlier today.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, yeah, I bet the developers are sitting around going, we should do something with the six axis.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: What should we do?
[SPEAKER_06]: We could wiggle their boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, that works.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet the conversation went just like that, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get back into some longer news that we'll talk a little more about, and then soon your calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I'm not sure if I'm going to be happy about this or not, and we know that with the new updates, especially coming in the fall, that they're going to be having some support for Facebook support and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know with the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, what's interesting, though, is apparently the game Blur coming out is going to have Twitter support.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope they can turn that off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you don't give it your login.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how you turn it off.
[SPEAKER_04]: This sounds like a horrible idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a horrible, horrible idea that is just contributing to the problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: And don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Blur is an amazing-looking game, and I really enjoy the demo at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of my favorites.
[SPEAKER_04]: That being said, the plug needs to be pulled on this immediately.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you spam this shit to your Twitter and I'm following you right now, you will be dropped.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because unfortunately, and here's the problem with Twitter...
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate Raptor!
[SPEAKER_04]: and it's nothing personal I just you know here's the thing it is personal with me by the way there's a finite amount of tweets that my iPhone Apple download at a time it's 200 tweets and if 20 of those tweets are your fucking friend feed or something I'm sorry that's gonna piss me off because that's 20 things I could have read about somebody else you know that might be like actually about their day or something interesting you know I just I am not a fan of these auto tweets at all and kind of and think they're gonna destroy Twitter
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless something is done about them very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I know this is not going to be the first or last thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, Activision destroy something?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't know, a beloved guitar franchise?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just so strange, though, because, you know, usually Bizarre Creations is... We've had them on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're a great studio.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I understand, you know, they're just trying to be on the cutting edge of technology.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should do it really with Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we're misinterpreting this.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'll give credit there maybe we need clarification on how exactly this is going to work and I think it's pretty obvious to say if you don't give this game your Twitter login it can't do it so to some extent you're going to have to want it to post to Twitter for you but why?
[SPEAKER_04]: that's the part I failed to see why is this useful?
[SPEAKER_02]: and the other thing too is apparently it's going to feature like a faux social networking site like InnerTube I guess it's their bizarre version of YouTube or something
[SPEAKER_02]: It will have real Twitter support as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's fine if you have updates and stuff like that, but that's something more like Facebook because at least then you can filter it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Twitter, I don't want to see updates about stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or maybe it gives you the option, like say you won first place and you get the option, do you want to tweet this or not?
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be a little more tolerable depending on how often people do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a little iffy on it, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just don't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just don't bother with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If my Twitter gets filled up with blur race updates, then I can't read that so-and-so just took a big poop.
[SPEAKER_04]: on Twitter, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: And isn't that what Twitter's really about is what you ate for breakfast this morning?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly, with the new action or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am actually starting to get really annoyed with Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a love-hate thing with Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of dumb shit on Twitter, but at the same time, I found it to be really good for networking and getting the information out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been really good for the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I use it for.
[SPEAKER_06]: I use it for a lot of my networking now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I use it for OLR Foodio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, now there's a new hashtag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki invented a new hashtag, and the thing is, people are using it that listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not just me, but I saw three other people using the new OLR Foodio tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm somewhere torn between this is really funny, and I just think Twitter needs to take some cues from Facebook and give us better ways to filter content.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's really what they need.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've actually been using my Facebook a whole lot more than Twitter now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, simply because of a lot of the reasons that you just mentioned.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Bochikawa in chat makes a very good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Poop is greater than race win.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyhow, Blur getting Twitter support.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see exactly how that plays out a little later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Meantime, one game that's not going to have Twitter support, but it'll have support for your balance board is, of course, Wii Fit+.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a release date has been announced for Wii Fit+.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming out on October 4th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the great thing about Wii Fit Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember how a lot of us were thinking that Nintendo's just going to price gouge on this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to cost $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wii Fit Plus is only going to set you back $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now keep in mind that's if you already have a balance board.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they figure if you have a balance board, then they got you once already with Wii Fit because they don't sell the balance board separately, do they?
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're going to get rid of the SKU that is the Wii Fit...
[SPEAKER_04]: The bad news, which you forgot to mention, was now they also raised the price of that bundle by $10.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and I'll be $99.99 for that bundle.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if you didn't get in on the ground floor of Wii Fit, which I'm going to tell you this much, if you didn't get in on the ground floor of that, you're not missing out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you're dumb enough to buy the game by itself, no offense, but it's almost the same game again.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why you'd buy the same game again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, because there are some extra things in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the little mini-games were kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if you're going to buy that Wii Play or whatever...
[SPEAKER_04]: You spend an extra $10 to get Wii Play and none of those games are good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think the same way as you about Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get the point behind Wii Fit and I actually kind of like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think if you actually make it a point to play the game every day, some exercise is better than none.
[SPEAKER_04]: you know granted it's not the best thing you could be doing you could be lifting weights or you could be running or jogging but you know if it's kind of a nice meet you in the middle type of thing and I think that's what Wii Fit's always been about right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess it's trying to make exercising more fun for kids and non-kids who are just not as motivated they should just have you bench press the board and make it way more I'll have to put D cell batteries in it to make it a little heavier
[SPEAKER_06]: No, just put in big old 9 volts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually considering picking it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not that bad considering.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it supposed to have some internet stuff too where you're going to be able to compare with friends around the globe?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wait for the peer used.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it will.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Takeo Ray in our chat room, chat.orangelongeradio.com, says, My friend's aunt lost 40 pounds using Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_04]: She swears by it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loomies in chat says, It's all about your diet and how consistent you are.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that's kind of true, too, is that you can't expect that you play Wii Fit by itself for like 10 minutes a day and that anything major is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It kind of has to be part of a greater lifestyle adjustment.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's why and I also noticed that xlink in chat says I'll play my EA active you know one thing about EA active is that EA active kind of encourages you as well to be eating and doing other stuff you know doing exercises besides just EA active I don't think it implements it very well but at least it kind of makes it a point to emphasize that as a part of the game as well yeah because I mean it's you can't just do one or I mean you could do one or the other but they're more effective done together
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you what, I mean, to be honest, I think one website I think has been very good for this, you know, when I was kind of trying to lose weight and I still am to an extent.
[SPEAKER_04]: One website I found that I really enjoyed was Spark People, which is actually a pretty good website where you can monitor your food intake and you monitor your exercise and how many glasses of water you drink a day and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, I really liked the way Spark People was set up.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I, and it has an iPhone app, which was the other big thing about that that was cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I would definitely recommend that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a lot of people like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of one of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll go out and run.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not a gym person at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I have a friend really, really trying to get me to go to the gym.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of on the fence.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't mind going to the gym, but I usually hide myself in the weight room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is sometimes kind of really nerve-wracking, especially when you have all the guys there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not that I have a problem with all the guys there or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just that I don't like going out.
[SPEAKER_06]: with all the guys there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and it's probably some people listen to us like, come on, you pussies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, if I'm the only girl there and there's like 10 guys that just got off the basketball court all pumping away, so I'm like, yeah, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I could take them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bench press them.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: So they can see who has the best mental, physical, their best knowledge too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they get a job as a game tester with the PlayStation QA department in San Diego.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel completely different from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think all reality TV is trash.
[SPEAKER_04]: You watch Big Brother.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think some of it is trash.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I like reality shows that are basically modern game shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, in my opinion, Big Brother is a game show as is Survivor is a game show of sorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I've always liked game shows of all different types.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm not bothered by those shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even to an extent, I can tolerate some of those like VH1 and Bravo shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Project Runway is pretty good too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Project Runway though is...
[SPEAKER_06]: More like a design contest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, see, you can't say you hate reality shows and then say, but this one's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, this to me, though, is like, what was the Trump one?
[SPEAKER_06]: The Apprentice?
[SPEAKER_06]: I hated that show.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, The Apprentice is okay, but my biggest problem with it is that it basically came down to one dude's opinion.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it would have been better if there was a board.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, I don't want to get into diagnosing all these reality shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I don't like is like...
[SPEAKER_04]: This VH1 is getting so saturated with these shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: I turned on the other day, it was like the Terrell Owens reality show or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's just a lot of these types of shows, like the dating shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want unreality.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much, too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Give me back my unreality.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want sitcoms.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, here's the funniest part about this reality show, is we've known game testers, and it's not as glamorous as you would think.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I actually wanted to get to, is that the prize here...
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate to say it, is not very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no offense to the game testers I know out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of you work very hard for very little money.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's why I don't understand this whole glamorization of the gaming testing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not that hard to get into, I don't think, either.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't be offended, but it's kind of an entry-level position.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's how you get your foot in the door at gaming companies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of people take that and work up to something a lot bigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shouldn't a prize on a reality game show be something bigger?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what this is going to be?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is just going to be a holiday tie-in.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a free download on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be product placement after product placement of all these Sony upcoming games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's a terrible idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, especially if it's a free show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll enter.
[SPEAKER_06]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't I enter?
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to enter?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't quit my day job, but if you want to enter and move to San Diego...
[SPEAKER_04]: I like San Diego, but I sure as hell don't want to live there
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think this show is really about giving someone a once-in-a-lifetime dream opportunity.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this show is going to be nothing but non-stop product placement for holiday Sony games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But granted, it's a pretty clever way to do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Patty said something funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's what I was... Yeah, go ahead and read it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a great suggestion for reality TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: Life with my grandma.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't know how compelling that would be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless your grandma competes in the X Games, then I would watch a show like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: or she was like a serial killer grandma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would watch a show called Serial Killer Grandma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they have that on Discovery Channel?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will check out an episode of this and see if it's any good, but I just kind of have a feeling it's just going to be product placement and trailers I can download somewhere else on PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something that this winner might be testing out is the brand new 3D support for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, this is kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's neat, but at the same time, it's not that special because in order for you to be able to use it, you need one of those brand new TVs that can refresh at over 200 hertz.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: that is a problem and not a lot of people have those TVs right now but if you happen to do and you have the special stereoscopic glasses for that then you can actually play some of the games one of them of course Wipeout in 3D and that will be coming out in 2010 I know actually sooner than that they're going to be doing that with Avatar but once again you need that really high end TV and right now there's like maybe 5 different TVs out there that have that kind of feature for them
[SPEAKER_02]: you think this might be the future of gaming though because when we see things like this I kind of go okay well maybe it's for a certain group of people right now but could it be the future of gaming it's cutting edge yes but it might be too cutting edge like you know it's too early because you know people aren't going to upgrade their TV just to get one of these TVs that does you know 200 hertz until they start coming out with like a lot of 3D movies and stuff and this stuff comes down in price but right now I mean I guess they can claim that they were the first to do this or something I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: But actually, they can't claim it as their first disc, because now that I think of it, because if Avatar is coming out on both the 360 and PS3, then they will be doing it at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't, like, Rad Racer on the NES in 3D?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but that was, like, with those, you know, the red-blue glasses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't the Virtual Boy in 3D?
[SPEAKER_04]: The amazing migraine machine?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, see, that was actually true 3D, but this, though, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a neat...
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of don't want to see gaming go all 3D like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went and saw Up in 3D, which don't get me wrong, great movie, had a great time, but I kind of had a little bit of a headache after for watching that for like 90 minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even though they say you're supposed to take a break every hour when you play video games, you guys know that's not how it goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll sit there and play a video game for four hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: Until you gotta pee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, HD and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just because people... It's the progression that's going to go in.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's what their push is for cinema right now is more 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, you know, eventually that's going to move to the home market.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it makes sense that games are going to go in that direction.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially since, you know, hey, 3D might come in handy when, like, Project Intel comes out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or, you know, these games are going to be using the, you know, Sony motion capture thing that they're going to have.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, you might need to see stuff in 3D space in that sense.
[SPEAKER_02]: But...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not cheap right now, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want to buy a monitor for your PC and the stereoscopic glasses, it's going to set you back $500.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's pretty cheap, you know, compared to an HDTV.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but technology is going to come down in price eventually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, it will.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like, remember when HDTVDs, or sorry, I just, I can't talk anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: HDTVs, remember when those were like thousands of dollars to get an HDTV?
[SPEAKER_04]: And now, like this Christmas, I think you're going to see those things.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, the Vega.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flying off the shelves, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the big deal?
[SPEAKER_06]: They were like $5,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh, I have two DX and a Vega.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a lot of that was faux HD, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of those Vegas didn't even really do HD.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, yeah, I mean, technology's going to come down in price.
[SPEAKER_04]: It always does, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: And if it doesn't, it kills the thing, too, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, because, you know, not everybody's rich.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something to keep in mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to go back to our chat room, chat.orangelandreda.com and read some comments.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a comment on the last story about the whole reality television from Salacious Pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Says, if I recall correctly, the Penny Arcade guys were doing something reality based at Penny Arcade Expo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's a mini doc for the DVD or a standalone thing or what.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, being a person that hates all reality television, would you hate a Penny Arcade documentary as well?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a difference between a reality TV show and a documentary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is the difference?
[SPEAKER_06]: The documentary being that it's set for an informative purpose.
[SPEAKER_06]: Its purpose is not necessarily entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is to give you the information regarding a particular situation, a historical event, or an individual.
[SPEAKER_04]: Couldn't a documentary be entertaining?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why I said not necessarily just for entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Reality TV is supposed to be, oh, here's your slice of how other people live.
[SPEAKER_06]: For example, if you took a documentary to Somalia to see about the results of the war and their own little mafia thing going on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you get unfiltered information or if it's filtered it's just to make it slightly more palatable but it's not scripted.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what's going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's inquisitive.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's editorial.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is what is going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whereas reality TV is in the end a manufactured reality.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just was kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that's a pretty...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what that has me kind of thinking about, though, is that, you know, I bet there would be a lot of people that would be interested in watching something like that, kind of a behind-the-scenes thing at PAX, and even though, you know, it was commented that it's probably going to be for a DVD, wouldn't it be kind of neat if this was a downloadable exclusive on PlayStation Network or Xbox 360?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it's done a lot of work with Penny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or even, like, you know what might be a really cool tie-in?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have it be something that's on Xbox 360 Netflix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put it on Netflix as an instant queue title, and then people could watch it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I think that is something that if PlayStation Network is going to make up this reality show or whatever, that should also be an avenue that they should think about doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe Microsoft will beat them to the punch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: Creating these shows about behind-the-scenes development of games or fandom, I guess you could say in this case, or expos, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like what I was watching today, Dan, because you know pretty much my favorite type of sports car is the Bugatti Veyron, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Dan was showing me the video for Forza 2 about how they got the Bugatti license and were mapping out the car, how it was done, the meat of how they...
[SPEAKER_06]: That type of stuff is always interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love behind the scenes stuff in movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like watching the how they do that type thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did love watching Ripley's Believe It or Not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unwrapped on the Food Network
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't hate it, I just don't love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially when you've seen the same episode over and over and they start reusing some of their segments on other episodes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll give you that, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do need to make some new stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, this episode's the stuff that's packaged in plastic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, this episode's about baskets.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, this episode's about Cheez Whiz.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was an episode on Cheez Whiz?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, there was not an episode on Cheez Whiz.
[SPEAKER_12]: But there's been like three episodes about picnics and there's like...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they show how they make picnic baskets.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care, that has nothing to do with food.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about those little, don't they call those picnics?
[SPEAKER_04]: Those little potato fried things you can buy and then forget it?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what is a weird show that's kind of along the lines of Unwrapped?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's how it's made or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have the most random stuff put together.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, this episode you're going to learn how they make galvanized steel, doorknobs, bowling balls, and mayonnaise.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, what the fuck is that?
It's like...
[SPEAKER_06]: I like those.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's so random.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, ooh, steel.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, doorknobs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I was just out of high school, there was a show that used to come on, and I don't think, I think this was before the day of the Food Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: It used to come on where they would show you how to make snacks that you buy in the grocery store, like they showed how to make Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Better than Scat before it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to remember, when our buddy Keith worked at Scandia, we ran that fucking joint when we wanted to do a tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we did the most random things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know the employees there must have hated us.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so did all the customers, which is...
[SPEAKER_06]: But we stayed and helped cleaned up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We did.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we did a really awesome tournament there and probably brought up some new business.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we did the most random stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We turned the birthday party room into a station where you could buy fried Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, we did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deep fried Twinkies.
[SPEAKER_04]: What the hell that has to do with video games?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Irene.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was Irene.
[SPEAKER_04]: I, I, I, I, I
[SPEAKER_06]: We should just have RandomCon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki presents the Baconator station or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We are seriously kicking around an idea of doing an all-bacon party for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't your birthday already happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, it's coming up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next Friday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you should do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have some bacon fried bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're not bacon frying bacon.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just redundant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look, look.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to get to some more comments because we had some funny stuff on Unwrapped.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had two fans of Unwrapped in chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Takeo Ray says, Unwrapped is the best show on Food Network.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says, Unwrapped is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Salacious Pop says, that show makes me lull because I'm like, oh, go jump in some Gak Mark Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: He couldn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's got that whole OCD thing going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see this documentary?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about Double Dare.
[SPEAKER_04]: It scared him.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, yeah, because he's... What type of phobia is it where you're afraid of messes?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Ranma in chat simply says, fuck Unwrapped, Good Eats is better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alton Brown is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, look.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do agree, Good Eats is better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enough food, let's get to emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't eat emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure if you could, DarkSakura would have eaten one by now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope, nope, you're wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have thrown them up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could print out emails on that paper that they use to print photos on a cake, then you could eat emails.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true!
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to have a contest where we eat somebody's email one night live on air.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have your email eaten by a castle.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't have the printer for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'd have to take it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: How much does that cost?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: People are sick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag!
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at OrangeLaunchRadio.com DarkSakura, dive into the email bag and read us some emails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, the first one comes from DeathWishing, which is actually the last email I received.
[SPEAKER_06]: I will have wrote, it's written, this message from a place called Howie's Game Shack.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I went to Guitar Hero 5 and it is fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's probably the best one in the franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Weird, but seriously, you gotta try it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just skip Smash Hits Van Halen and Metallica and any other weird, or weird, I should say, because he spelled it the same way twice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, any other weird, weird tie in games, they will make.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what he said, weird tie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cyber Cafe loved Death Wishing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think he meant weird tie in game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um,
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey OLR, I was looking on the net and I heard if you have a PSP Go and a PS3, you can pair up the PS3 controller with the PSP Go to have dual analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_02]: A half-assed way to solve that problem, analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_06]: and make you buy more stuff from them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Problem solved.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: I recently bought a UMID AM1, a 4-inch netbook, and it can play high-def games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, it looks stupid with the USB hub, external CD-ROM, and a controller sticking out of it, but it is a good thing to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, that feature isn't any good unless your PSP games actually support it, but I guess maybe it's a trend that'll be starting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you have a PS3, and you're near your PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, but I was talking about earlier in the show, there's a lot of hidden functionality between the PS3 and the PSP that Sony does a really poor job at advertising that is very cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like playing the PSP on your TV, like if you did that DualShock thing, you could put your Resistance game on your TV and play with the DualShock controller.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed DarkSakura was looking at a little thing for Dissida.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried the download demo of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is part of the soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't get a grasp on the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just couldn't figure out what the hell I was doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just was button mashing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that all the game is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Button mashing with Final Fantasy characters?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: I couldn't figure out the strategy behind it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think the demo was set up very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It needed a tutorial or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or maybe I'm just stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's fine too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is from Dragon, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have been listening to your podcast for a few weeks now and really enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to say I don't know why so many people are complaining about the cost of the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I live in Toronto, Canada and a PSP 3000 costs $167 and a 16GB memory stick costs $139 so the PSP Go is a good deal for a new player.
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the great work on your podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: A 6 gigabyte memory stick, he said?
16.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, get the bundle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how much it would cost Canadian, but it can't be much more than it is here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got a bundle, because my old PSP was kind of dying, so I actually just picked up a PSP 3000 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought a $199 bundle that came with the PSP 3000, a 4 gig memory stick, School of Rock little code you can use, which whatever, I don't really care for Jack Black, but I'll just download it because it was free, and then Rock Band Unplugged all came with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, that wasn't a bad deal at all for the PS3 3000.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is, the PSP Go is, what, $50 cheaper than a PlayStation 3 is now?
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's got, like, less features than a PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't... That's where the logic fails me.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're going to go PSP, go PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And to be honest, you can find memory sticks pretty cheap.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if you really need 16GB of storage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if you're buying games on there, I mean, I don't think you need that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, hell, when I was putting ISOs on there, I didn't need that amount of space.
[SPEAKER_02]: 4GB at the most, maybe, and then... I mean, how many games do you plan on storing on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they need 16GB on a PSP Go because that's all you can do is download stuff, but you're going to be playing a lot of your games off UMDs anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's really no reason to get the Go other than, ooh, look, it slides.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, my comments on Final Fantasy Dissida kind of got the chatroom talking about that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: AlphaCananagram says, the demo doesn't do it justice, and he puts demo in caps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Geovadea says, Dissida is fucking amazing, I heart it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And AlphaCananagram wants you to know he is playing Dissida right now, a level 100 Onion Knight on hardcore play mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess maybe I'll have to check out the full game at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the last email, and I'm kind of not going to say who it's coming from, but he also didn't say who he got it from, but it's an email that was sent out to Disney cast members.
[SPEAKER_03]: Huh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Marvel's business meshes perfectly with ours and what we've all been doing to maximize the value of Disney's creative properties across our business, media platforms, and geographical markets.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then goes on to talk about Pixar.
[SPEAKER_06]: But here's the other line.
[SPEAKER_06]: The acquisition of Marvel offers us a similar opportunity to advance that strategy, meaning putting out things all over the world for using it for marketing purposes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sort of, maybe I'm reading a bit more into this, but since they've been talking about use of the Marvel brand and, you know, the consumer market, I have a feeling we're going to start seeing actual, especially since this was sent out to cast members, meaning I think it's the park.
[SPEAKER_06]: That means that we might start seeing characters in the parks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, that's also going to mean games.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to mean movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to mean more things.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not going to happen tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not tomorrow, but I'm saying down the line.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me put it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their licenses aren't going to run until 2015, 2017.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's that long.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, and what else is interesting, and for some reason, the whole story about Disney buying Marvel didn't make tonight's show roll, but I'm sure everybody read about it somewhere on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You couldn't get away from it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought what was very interesting about when that story hit is that you just saw all this, like, frickin' cross-fanboy wank all over the internet all at once about, like, OMG, there's gonna be Kingdom Hearts with Marvel characters, and, like, just all this stuff that ain't happenin'.
[SPEAKER_06]: Run my ass if Spider-Man was going to be in Toy Story 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: We got a cool 3D thing at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so maybe we'll get a cool Marvel ride at California Adventure or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they'll bring back the 7th Portal.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's going to be a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't Marvel have an agreement with other theme parks?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know DC does.
[SPEAKER_04]: DC is what you see all over Magic Mountain and the Six Flags.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see the 7th Portal come back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: You went on that with me at Great America.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't think Disney is going to mean that Marvel is going to run the same way Disney does.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think a lot of people are jumping to conclusions.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma also said Darkwing Duck and the Avengers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Disney, fund it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Actdeft says The Incredibles vs. Fantastic Four.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, this is the best.
[SPEAKER_06]: Salacious Pop.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd be on board for a Deadpool-Hannah-Montana crossover.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would totally be down for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not happening.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would be so down for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, hey, the Kingdom Hearts with Marvel characters is kind of a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just not going to happen right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hell, we don't even know when Kingdom Hearts 3 is going to happen, if anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ranma says, Rob Roberts, yeah, but Disney already pulled the old budget cuts on one of their publishing arms.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't really have anything to inspire the FUs tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have a story.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what about that guy that said that video games were poison or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll dedicate the FUs tonight to him.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Gundam guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had something, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Already.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, they're supposed to be doing Obama's speech in public schools on the 8th.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how I feel about this whole political, but okay, go for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's really, it's an encouragement to stay in school.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's great that, you know, that this is going out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a sign that, you know, our president does care about children instead of, you know, Bush going, how do you read?
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, what really pisses me off are all those people who say, oh, well...
[SPEAKER_06]: This is going to interrupt my kids' school day, so I'm going to not let them go to school that day.
[SPEAKER_06]: That makes no sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: It makes my brain go, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why?
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, especially when all the schools are making arrangements for parents who don't want their children to see the...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: My whole thing with the people just need to stop thinking in one extreme or the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet you when all is said and done, nobody is blue and nobody is red.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody's a little bit purple.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just the whole like taking kids out of school as some type of political statement or whatever is just too extreme.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying that they're doing it not so that their education isn't interrupted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Watch the speech.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let your children watch the speech and then talk about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, be a fucking parent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Part of being a parent, yeah, true.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to make sure that your child's not going to see anything harmful.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, you can't protect them from every damn little thing that you don't want them to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what the real world is.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've met people who've grown up sheltered, and they're frightening people.
[SPEAKER_04]: I also think that...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you Rockstar for getting rid of my modded Grand Theft Auto games and it's absolutely ruined the whole Grand Theft Auto experience for the two of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I will find a way around it like I always do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to say something that's a total inside joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's maybe like two or three people listening that would understand this.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm just going to give a big F you this week to exclamation points.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all I'm going to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you exclamation points.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and also the ability to sync up your voice with the player's mouth movements, so it actually makes it look like they're talking.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, yeah, it's really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently, they do have an animation system, I guess that's intelligent enough to turn your audio stream into lip-syncing for the on-screen characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, I guess it's neat that they're offering all these things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if we will actually see a lot of Makima videos for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of interesting when gaming companies kind of really embrace the whole Makima thing, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I liked about this story was that they're really kind of showing that off and leaving it to people's creativity to make whatever they're going to make.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's really interesting how more and more gaming companies really embrace it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: XTAL Corporation XTAL Corporation XTAL Corporation XTAL Corporation
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, Sexbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this company, they're going to be making a video game system that only plays interactive adult only rated video game titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew,
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, as well as specializing in the adult-only games, the Sexbox will also give its owners access to adult-only content and entertainment in all sorts of other digital forms.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming this means like streaming movies and video and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Audio, video, HDTV, DVD, online, gaming, social networking, webcams, video on demand, downloading, movie rentals, purchases, etc., etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything but real fucking games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only because the technology doesn't exist yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, you seem to be a big advocate for this Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, is this something legit or is this just teehee?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the way they're going to approach it is going to be teehee, but I'm all about a system that will allow publishers, assuming that they actually want to put out stuff on this system, the opportunity to put out games uncensored.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, we're probably going to see a lot of porno games that are probably going to be crap, but at the same time, if they want to release a really fucking crazy version of Manhunt 2 or something like that,
[SPEAKER_02]: They can do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know, I applaud that, but at the same time, I think it's going to be kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, that being said, assuming that the games on there look pretty decent, I will probably pick one of these up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it will be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can go, hee hee, I have a sex box.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all for...
[SPEAKER_04]: I've gotten into this rant a long time ago on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm all for sexier video games and all this and just downloading porn on your PlayStation 3 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: I understand why the companies don't want to open Pandora's Box and that whole thing, but why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it's just because we have this whole stigma in our society where the violence is okay, Manhunt 2 is okay, and a lot of these games and the Saw movies are fine, but heaven forbid we show a cock or some bush, and I'm not talking about a president,
[SPEAKER_04]: On the television, you know, it's just, I'll never get it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But granted, how can you make a serious game out of sex?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, a lot of these AO games we've seen, like the Three Feel and stuff, those are all a little silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they are a little silly, but also some of the games that do get an AO rating, it's really silly what they're getting it for.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would be fine with seeing legitimate games, just maybe push...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they put some real time and investment into making a serious game out of it to just really wow everybody instead of all these cheap games that just have titties and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Make an epic fuck quest or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not necessarily with sex, but over-the-top violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something absolutely crazy where you can just rip parts off of people and it's gruesomely detailed and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't want violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want cock and titty.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like violence.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like, I want violence.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine, you'll play a cock and a titty that goes around ripping your limbs off of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Deekman in chat says, rip parts off of people and fuck them with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ew, you're dirty.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is wrong with you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Make a game called Naked Slayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Naked Slayer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Naked Slayer.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can play either a guy or a girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can choose, you know, whatever their orientation is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they run around naked, killing people.
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Salacious Pop in chat says, apparently they're still making Leisure Suit Larry games, though Sierra and the dude who originally made them have nothing to do with it, and they're terrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, that last one had an AO-rated version, and it was pretty bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they are making still a new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had that Magna Cum Laude or whatever that was a little stupid, and they have a new one coming out, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember hearing a story on that earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a new one that came out a while ago that was kind of eh.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that idea by Salacious Pop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Professor Layton goes to Bonertown.
[SPEAKER_02]: Professor Layton.
[SPEAKER_04]: Layton, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the whole social networking thing, though, could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of people really unleash their sexuality when they're hiding behind a computer monitor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you might be able to find people that are into the same freaky shit you might be into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for example, let me think of a fetish that not a lot of people are into that's not completely disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's actually, you can actually quote Patton Oswalt on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Talking about that there's a magazine for, you know, for every fetish that you think is so dirty and awful, there's a magazine about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Piss drinkers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, God, bleh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I'm sure there's people into that, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm saying that's the perfect... I'm trying to think of something that's not totally disgusting that I can use as an example.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here's one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people have a food fight fetish.
[SPEAKER_04]: They want to have sex after a food fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like getting really dirty, just rubbing around in pies and salads and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have a food fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one has a salad food fight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard about this on the radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you have a food fight fetish or whatever, you could go onto this sex box console, find somebody else with the same fetish as you, and then have some safe fun together.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's wrong with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: As long as these consoles preach safety and not things that are illegal like ripping parts off of dead people and fucking them with them, that's not legal.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as long as this encourages safe, legal things within boundaries with consenting adults that have to prove that they are adults in order to even be able to log into this service, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Leo Shannon Chat says, Rob, you should give Angel's Feather a try.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's basically a game with Final Fantasy type story and battles plus some porn on the side.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to check this game out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, please do.
[SPEAKER_04]: That again is called Angel's Feather.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it actually has anime too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Salacious Poppet Chat says, I don't think ants should be a possible consequence of sex.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, People Have Balloon Fetishes
[SPEAKER_02]: Why isn't there any, like, Pie Pod fetishes?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the Pie Pod from, like, Nickelodeon?
[SPEAKER_02]: They should seriously have them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be like, you know, the people that make those sex machines.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's the sex machine stuff with a food fetish in there as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could be the interactive game on the sex box.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Pie Pod.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, this show has just gone to shit tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a yowie game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, is it a Yaoi game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks like.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_06]: All male cast.
[SPEAKER_04]: Skype line time, 1-877-GAME-OLR if you'd like to give us a call, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go ahead and feel free to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the meantime, we are going to go to Loki for some last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming he has some.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku Legend of Zaku
[SPEAKER_10]: Nah, I'm just like at a hookah bar right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just figured I'd drop in, just say what's up.
[SPEAKER_10]: You at a hookah bar?
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have never guessed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like hookah too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you having fun?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I've already, you know, I've already gotten in some cheap hookah right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just like had my first cider, my first hard cider.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, just like been keeping up on what's been going on in PAX.
[SPEAKER_10]: especially the fact that one of the guys in Xbox Live had this little quote-unquote sermon about the Banhammer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually called on Kotaku earlier today.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did not hear about this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us a little bit about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't hear about this whole spiel, what happened there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us a little bit about what happened.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it was basically one of the guys who works for Microsoft for Xbox Live who's in charge of maintaining order within there and the one that wields the Banhammer and he was basically just
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, you know, giving a speech in the form of an actual, like, religious sermon.
[SPEAKER_10]: The way he's using, like, a lot of religious terms in terms of how he managed to wield the, you know, in other words, like, the name, like, the gamer tags, and how, you know, they get banned, and then he's saying, like, but this god is merciful, even though, you know, and he'll give you a second chance if you use any banned term in your gamer tags.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then the other one, and then this other thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on a sec.
[SPEAKER_00]: I already did it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sure, we can hold.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, he was basically saying stuff about, like, um, the...
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm still here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we're about to head out, but I'm actually still good for talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, give us any final thoughts, quickly, because we do want to get some other calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, basically, I heard that the new WiiWare game, that Contra game, that's supposed to be really hard to tell, that you can't even get through.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it was already out in Japan earlier this year, but I figured that it might present a challenge to folks.
[SPEAKER_10]: The original Contra was hard as hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you know anybody that can beat it without the up, up, down, down, left, right code?
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan can.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan's a freak.
[SPEAKER_10]: You got the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_10]: But even then, he's just shrugging it off because he's pretty much a classic gamer in that sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: A challenge like that wouldn't be a no-brainer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Weird that they haven't released that over here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: yet, though, but I guess soon enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's supposed to come out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: It only came out in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they dumb it down for us Americans like they usually do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope they dumbed it down for the Americans like they usually do then.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard the folks in Kotaku were complaining about the fact that it was pretty damn hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Zaku, we gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have fun at the hookah bar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Smoke one for us, alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a good day, Rudy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Light another one, dude!
[SPEAKER_06]: The hookah bar does not get you high, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I know it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: However, it's really fun to blow smoke bubbles.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I had hookah once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so back to the Data East collection here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the games are going to be included with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Magical Drop 3, Bad Dudes vs. Dragon Ninja, Burger Time, Caveman Ninja, Street Slam, and Secret Agent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Too many ninjas, as if there was such a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, I'm DSMaster25.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, DSMaster25.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, scratch that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm 26.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I aged.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, I've been playing a whole lot of old school titles.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like what?
[SPEAKER_11]: For the past few weeks now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been trying my best at trying to beat Contra for the Super C, for the Super NES.
[SPEAKER_11]: I swear to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is with all the Contra revival tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's two Contra calls in a row.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is some strange anomaly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a rite of passage, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: For the life of any young gamer, the rite of passage is making it to Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Super C on the Super Nintendo was badass, and everybody should play it once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those Mode 7 stages were pretty awesome, but I just find it very strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've had two calls about Contra back-to-back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is every caller going to ask about Contra tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not just Contra I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, this homebrew version of DDR for the Nintendo DS I came across called DSDS Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I would hope you don't dance on your DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might break it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's like... Did you guys ever come across the old Game Boy...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I played the Game Boy Color ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were hideous.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a way to memorize step charts on the go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really the only reason I have it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, basically, okay, the controls seem to do multiple arrows and everything with using A and B for the up and right arrows.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently, DSDS Revolution seems to do the same exact thing, which is weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: and of course I got the new R4i so I can play my homebrew stuff on my DSi and I'll say here it sounds a whole lot better than it did on my DS Lite but other than that I've mostly been trying to play some of my old Genesis games my Genesis doesn't work anymore which sucks what was that on Genesis?
[SPEAKER_11]: My Genesis does not work anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Period.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, get that freaking collection on the 360 or PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's like tons of games on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, but here's the cool thing, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I found a really easy to use, easy to install emulator for the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been using that now.
[SPEAKER_11]: because I also had this thought of trying to play Genesis games on the go.
[SPEAKER_11]: And most of my collection was as follows.
[SPEAKER_11]: Outrun, King of Fighters, I had Monopoly, but... Look, I'm just saying if you want to do it legitimately, the Mega Collection's not a bad deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I mean, it... You know, it...
[SPEAKER_11]: Even though, like, you know, granted, I'm 17, you know, and I was never around when these games originally came out, but I'm like, you know, it's great every once in a while to, you know, have an old-school jig every once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a very important question.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said at the top, you introduced yourself as DSMaster25 and then said, no, wait, I'm DSMaster26 because I age, and now you just said you're 17.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm totally lost.
[SPEAKER_04]: How old are you?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I'm 17.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so where's the 26 come from?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, because all the DS Master Tales are tooken up, and 25 is the only one available at the time, so it took that, um, and so now it's 26.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, I had, no, I, this was important!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very important!
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, and plus I have a review, um,
[SPEAKER_11]: For a bit on a new DS, well, semi-new DS title that I came across, Chinatown Wars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, make it quick, because we've got to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, I've got to say here, it looks exactly like the old PlayStation 1 GTA renditions.
[SPEAKER_11]: It actually runs quite well on the DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: And...
[SPEAKER_11]: And then our quickie, which I give that one of five stars.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then my last quickie review, Quake Live.
[SPEAKER_11]: Recommended, you have a pretty decent hardware because it was getting a little bit shaky when there was multiple explosions on screen.
[SPEAKER_11]: And don't try to play it with a trackpad mouse on a laptop, because I'll tell you this, this is murder on my hands beyond belief.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I had my index finger and all the rest of my fingers up to the WSAD keys, my thumb all the way stretched down to the left mouse button to shoot, and used my right hand to try to aim.
[SPEAKER_04]: I definitely don't play Quake Live on the netbook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, DSMaster, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Peace out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you see, DS Master 1 through 24 was taken, so I just went for 25.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have you know that someone linked me in chat to a listing on eBay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, for $235 plus shipping, we can own our own edible ink cake printer that will allow us to print emails and eat them.
[SPEAKER_04]: for $235.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do have a challenge though on a future show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would like to hear from DS Masters 1 through 23 at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to know where they are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or 1 through 24.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would love to hear from DS Master 2 or someone with a lot of seniority in the DS Master chain.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Featuring a cool roster of characters including Pyramid Head, Robbie the Rabbit, and of course characters from Rumble Roses, Frogger, Goemon, they even have Taco from Parodius it looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: They even have Pyramid Head in this shot, it's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Phone's ringing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, this is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, you know, a couple things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, yeah, I just caught one of your little stories about an adults-only console that's about to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what are your thoughts on the adults-only console?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of iffy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would have to get some more information, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: about before I fully form my opinion one way or the other, but, Mike, you know, at least for the moment, you know, the question is, even though the game's going to be adults only, you know, are they going to be actually any good?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you know, you can almost draw a parallel to a lot of the mature titles that came out at least last generation.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, for example, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: BMX XXX was awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesomely bad, but in a so-bad-it-was-good kind of way.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need to carry a hose around on your bike.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to derail this conversation for a minute, Spazinator, because I have a topic I need to hear about from you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we just had DS Master on the show talking about where his name comes from.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to know where Spazinator comes from.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, it's kind of a weird story.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I assume you're familiar with, uh, the American Pie movies, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you know how there's, uh, the, you know, there's a character on there, you know, that goes by the name of the Shivernator?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah, well, you know, when I meet a Spazinator, I, you know, this is back in the PS2 days, I literally just got down watching, uh,
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, the first American Pie movie.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I also had those kinds of Network Adapter and, you know, and SOCOM 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I went to create a screen name and I thought, there's a Sherman here, I like the American Pie movies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Changed the name up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the first thing that came to mind was Batmanator, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: and eventually the name kind of stuck.
[SPEAKER_10]: I started using his name on all the games and, you know, just to be a little consistent.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yeah, it kind of stuck.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so glad I asked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, what else do I want to ask you about?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us one more thing that's on your mind, then we're going to take another call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you know, right at the top of the show, after you got off the pole with Bobby, you had mentioned during your gaming week that you picked up that Zen Pinball game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I actually just got there a couple days ago, and by looking at it, I figured what table it's on by, and I actually beat one of your scores so far, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here's a good one.
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's playing Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Part of my soul died just in the last... 1-877-GAME-OLR if you'd like to give us a call or Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, did you have some more last minutes?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry I tore apart your grammar earlier.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to have to talk loud so I can barely hear you.
[SPEAKER_09]: About my name, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Counterstrike.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's just say I died a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, we had to ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't everybody have a story like that?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where did your name come from?
[SPEAKER_06]: Your mom.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since your story was so short, I'll let you... What did you want to call in about tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: The sex box and... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's pretty... It's kind of stupid in a way.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_09]: One, it's kind of a rip-off of internet meme name stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do we really need a porn game console?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a lolcat console.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not a two girls, one cup console.
[SPEAKER_04]: It probably is a lolcat fetish, so it probably will be a lolcat console.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lolcat fetish.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, there's something I hadn't thought of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Would you be interested in meeting people on the internet with a lolcat fetish, Deathwishing?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I have a girlfriend, so I don't need it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can has fucking.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is there any low-cat cosplay is what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll just walk around in cat ears with a sign that says, I can has, and then insert random items.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has to have been done.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it has been done.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had someone go around as low-cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, your thoughts on the sex box, sir.
[SPEAKER_09]: You guys were following PAX coverage, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had Bobby calling in for PAX.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, apparently there was a Street Fighter 6 they had for sale there, like limited edition for PAX only.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the girl one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, well, you, Frank, gave one away for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lucky.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless they didn't get a thousand viewers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure they might have, all I know is they gave away a lot of swag and stuff But they would only give it away if they got a thousand viewers, you said?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, they try to give away anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, God, they heard about the sticks off and they just want to buy two.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a shameless promotion.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is completely shameless.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We used to do Orange Laundry for 12 people and loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I don't understand this whole, like, we're not going to pay attention to you until we get 500.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think it's disrespectful to others.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a tangent you probably weren't intending on, but you got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I really think no one really cared about the new track thing either.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think so and so they posted the link to it on...
[SPEAKER_09]: and Chan.com and nothing happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw a user tell I was watching up to like from 197 to 200 and then went back down lower than before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe everybody was at PAX.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Deathwishing, is there a fight breaking out behind you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's these people playing some game called... Oh, well, they stopped playing...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hero of New Earth, which is kind of like Dota, and they're all playing Star Cry 2 now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to let you go, Deathwishing, so we can wrap up the show, but thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm now shutting off the skyline.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: No more calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry to those folks that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, did you have anything else for us before we close out shop tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: The ESRB has rated more games coming to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_02]: These are PlayStation 1 download titles, including Blood Omen, Legacy of Kain, Cool Boarders 3, International Track and Field, Oddworld Apes Exodus, and Oddworld Apes Odyssey, Pandemonium, Syphon Filter 2, and Um Jammer Lammy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't some of those already come out this week?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought I heard some of those came out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, well, Um, Jimmerlammy came out, um, in Japan, and actually, um, Blood Omen and Pandemonium were rated before previously in March.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think any of them actually came out this week, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, it's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: and we talked a little bit I think before about how Guitar Hero World Tour is going to have an option to or Guitar Hero 5 is going to have an option to import some tracks from Guitar Hero World Tour however it's actually quite pathetic only 35 of World Tour's 86 tracks are actually going to be available to import and it's going to cost you $3.50 to do so
[SPEAKER_02]: and also Smash Hits is only going to have a few tracks to import as well I believe they're going to have oh let's see here 21 songs from Smash Hits available to import and with an undisclosed price on that one and that's coming out later this fall but it's still pathetic if you ask me since Rock Band you can import everything except for three tracks well it depends what the songs are too maybe they weren't willing to pony up the money I don't know
[SPEAKER_02]: And then finally, apparently there's new versions of Bonk, Bomberman, and I think maybe some other games coming as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And these were discovered on Hudson's website.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently there's a Bonk update coming, a Bomberman live sequel, and a Wii and DS version of a game called Rooms the Main Building.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bunk Brink of Extinction 2.5D Action Platformer
[SPEAKER_02]: Bobberman Live Battlefest New Arenas, Game Types, Team Play
[SPEAKER_02]: interesting and I guess now I guess Bonk and Barman have been officially announced by Hudson with screenshots and it looks like Bonk and Barman so not much to report there that's it alright sounds awesome Bonk is though one of those things that's a little better left in my memory I think but I don't know if they soup it up a little bit it might be cool
[SPEAKER_02]: Frozen Yogurt
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is, sounds amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I thought this show would be shorter tonight, but it was actually kind of long tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes you just never know how long the show's gonna go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I have a toy for my cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a laser pointer.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the thing is, the laser pointer is shaped like a cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: So does that make it a laser cat?
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a cat that fires a laser, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least you don't have a laser cat fetish.
[SPEAKER_04]: And on that note, thank you guys so much for downloading and tuning into Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We really appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, if you like what you've heard, all we ask, tell a friend or two about the station because you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have a big magazine promoting us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have zillions of followers on Twitter, and we're never going to have a contest that we'll only do if so many people follow us or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just help us get the word out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all we ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, you can do it through an iTunes review, through anything, and we'll try to keep it free for you guys for another seven years, all right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be back next week with even more of the latest and greatest in video gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, we're starting to get to the start of that fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just going to have games after games after games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So our reviews and yours sitting around talking smack about what we love, video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!
Thanks for watching!