Orange Lounge Radio
There's a host, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Tonight, May 11th, 2014, we're joined by the Grammy Award winning Christopher Tin, composer of Baba Yetu on Civilization IV.
As if that wasn't enough, it's been a very busy week in gaming. From Tomodachi to Amplitude, we've got everyone's opinions on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
It is Orange Lounge Radio live for this episode number 552 on May the 11th of 2014.
Happy Mother's Day to all you moms out there or motherly figures. Pets need moms too and so forth.
Step moms and god moms and all those moms. Happy Mother's Day to all you guys.
We are here to talk about video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle with you guys live as we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com.
My name is Rob Roberts here in studio with our co-hosts. Say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
Hi.
Hi, how are you?
I'm alright.
You're alright?
We've been having some tech problems here in studio tonight. We're on take two of the show but these things happen.
Yeah.
Hopefully your tablet will stay connected throughout the show this time.
I'm considering taking a narcotic.
A narcotic? Is that how you cope with the program?
Cause my hip still hurts.
How'd you hurt your hip if you don't mind me asking?
It was already sore and a little bit out of alignment and then I reached over to pick up something and ended up pulling, it's called iliotibial syndrome.
Meaning that it's the muscle band going from the very top of the hip down to the knee.
Mine's on my right leg. It's not sciatica. Completely different thing.
Getting old sucks.
No, it has nothing to do with getting old. It has something to do with having, no.
It had to do with my old car accident and since my hip already goes out of alignment, bending over with my hip out of alignment.
Just sorta, and so I was told not to drive for the three days.
Are you able to sit for long periods and play video games at least?
No.
Uh oh.
I still have to get up and move it around or else it's a little good stuff.
Are you able to play some DDR once in a while?
No.
But today is the first time in two weeks I've done squats.
Oh, there you go.
And so that's fine. I'm back to doing yoga and squats. It just still hurts.
Alright. Well, hopefully you got to play some games. We'll check in with you on that a little bit later.
I'll play something.
But we also have, say hello in studio to Tech Master, Loki.
Hi.
Hi, Loki. How are you doing?
Doing alright.
Yeah? What's new with you?
Um, not too much.
So how goes the coding of Project Loki or whatever you're calling your game that you're making?
Um, okay. I kinda took a break from what I was doing because I have to make assets for things.
But, you know, I'll get into that later on.
But so I've been working on a, I don't know, editor if you will, I guess, to make my own 3D models.
Wow.
And it's coming along good.
Yeah? And that's like all you do now, right?
That's all I do in my free time, yeah.
Awesome, awesome.
You know, I tried to play Call of Duty, but people don't seem to line up as far as, you know, when they're online.
We have a scheduled time each week that we play and no one was there.
And they're like, well, I can't play until like 10. I'm like, well, I'm not waiting.
That's my problem too is one of the games, and I'll get into this a little more when we get into our gaming weeks later.
But one game I've been playing is the Heroes of the Storm Technical Alpha that Blizzard has out there.
And I have some friends that play it, but we can never seem to line up at the same time.
And a lot of that has to do with the fact that, you know, I have a lot of friends on the East Coast and I'm here on the West Coast.
And that screws things up more than you'd think.
So it can be tricky trying to schedule up that time to do things with friends.
Yeah.
So, all right.
We also have here in studio joining us, he's back, guys, after a few months break.
Say hello, everybody, to Jason.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Well, then where is your voice at the top of the show?
I'm just kidding. I'm giving you a hard time.
One of those things where you pack everything except for one thing.
Because my mic is XLR, I have a converter to actually plug into my computer via USB.
And I'm pretty sure I put it in its case and then decided not to bring it with me because I didn't think I would need it for another audio obligation that I had as a part of this trip.
And I completely forgot about passphrase show roll.
It's fine.
Well...
Which is I had to dispel the rumors last week when he didn't do the intro.
It was like, was Jason sacked?
It's like, no, no, no.
Sometimes the kid needs a break.
So he's been working hard on the YouTubes and all that other stuff.
Last week I was driving and I didn't wake up early enough to take care of it before I had to check out of the hotel.
And I wasn't going to pull over on the side of the road.
And...
The signal on the radio...
Yeah, it wasn't going to happen.
Plus, I didn't have my converter.
Oh, geez.
Sorry, guys, and all of your speakers and possibly eardrums.
Yeah, last week I was driving out to Portland initially.
Today, like I said, I went to do it and realized I didn't have a required piece of audio gear.
So...
Well, that settles that one pretty quick.
Hopefully I'll have a solution for weekends going forward, though.
Well, going to our chat room, because we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern, right after the Bobby Black Wolf show.
The now deaf chat room.
You can join us at live.vognetwork.com.
Oh, please, they're used to it by now.
Yeah, I know, they've heard Loki rant before, come on.
And we've got lots of Nintendo news tonight, so just you wait, y'all.
Just you wait.
In all seriousness, going to our chat room, we do have people welcoming Jason to the show.
Bobby Black Wolf, our buddy, saying Jason destroyed the internet.
Which could be the possibility for some of the internet...
I bring additional devices into the house.
For some of the internet issues we've been having in the studio tonight.
Can you believe that?
The destroyer of tech.
25 devices on our router, but it makes sense.
I mean, we have three nerds that live here now, and then you bring three more nerds in here on Sunday night.
I'm not surprised at all when you consider laptops and some phones and all that.
3DSs, and phones, and iPads, and multiple computers to a single person.
Exactly.
And gaming consoles.
We are a connected world, my friend.
Ain't we ever.
Oh my gosh.
Alright, let's get into, before we get into our gaming weeks, and our interview with Christopher Tin, as you heard in the intro.
We do have Christopher Tin on the show tonight.
He'll be joining us live in about 15 minutes to talk about his new album, The Drop That Contained the Sea.
As well as classic songs of his, including the one I think y'all know as Gamers Baba Yetu, which he won the Grammy for, from Civilization IV.
Our chatroom also asking, how many Final Fantasy XIV clients were online?
Just two. So I had to ask them both to take a little break.
Only two.
I feel bad.
Christopher Tin has one night off of work this week in celebration of Mother's Day.
And he can't play the game he wants to play because of his boyfriend's show, but it is what it is.
Anyway, before we get to our interview with Christopher Tin, before we get to our gaming weeks, I want to get into tonight's kickoff topic.
I'm actually kind of glad the time we get to spend on this topic is limited.
So I think this is a good reason that we bring this up first.
Jamie, if you wouldn't mind, let us know one of the big controversial things going on in the news this week.
Oh, yeah, it's a pretty big one. And it involves Pokémon. No, it doesn't.
But it does involve the...
That news was controversial too, actually. We'll get into that later.
But it does involve Nintendo.
Nintendo basically says that when Tomodachi Life comes out in the US, it is going to still not have same-sex relationships in them.
Because, as they say, and they are recognizing that it's not the best step, but they're saying that because of the programming of the game,
that it's not something they can patch out before it ships, that they're going to leave it intact.
But for future versions of it that come out, that they're going to, as they say, strive to design gameplay experience from the ground up.
That is more inclusive.
So basically they know, we done fucked up, but we're going to fix it.
Which, good on them for making the statement they needed to make.
And again, I don't want to dwell too much on this, so thank you to Christopher Tin for limiting our time tonight on this topic.
But I do want to make clear that there was two distinct statements that came out.
And, you know, what you're talking about here is kind of where we're at now, where all is kind of calmed down a little bit because Nintendo has acknowledged,
you know what, maybe this was not the best course of action for us and in the future we should consider this.
But what's going on is that the first time they put something out, it was really just tacky, like what they said.
And to back up even further, I think many of you that listen to this show are probably astute on what's going on because this has been everywhere.
This was one of those stories that had wheels that made it onto the local news in various places.
Like, does Nintendo hate gay people? That's like, you know, that's what the media does when it blows these things, you know, sky high and so forth.
And what happened is that in Japan, Tomodachi Life is out and it's kind of like, it's like a life simulator type game.
Like, think The Sims meets Animal Crossing meets Mii Plaza.
There's kind of all those things kind of thrown in a blender, a very Japanese twist.
Well, in the game, you can, you know, have a baby and all this, but you will have to enter in a relationship with somebody of the opposite gender, you know, in order to start that family.
Which, you know, as far as Japan goes and Japanese culture and so forth, and again, a big key word here is perception.
Remember that word, folks, perception.
The perception in Japan and everything, it's, you know, it's just accepted as this is the way the game is and it doesn't cause a lot of social ruffling
until a bug is found in the game allowing folks to get into same-sex relationships by basically registering the same-sex partner as somebody of the opposite sex the game thinks they are or whatever.
And so you get into a relationship and actually there was kind of a subculture in Japan.
Think like Japan's Tumblr blew up with these pictures and fans everywhere of like, look, I've got this same-sex couple in Tomodachi Life, isn't that rad and so forth, you know.
But then, because this bug also broke the game, Nintendo said, we gotta patch it out.
And I truly don't think Nintendo was trying to make a, oh, we gotta patch out the gay.
No, they had to patch out a mistake for something that truly wasn't intended.
You say that like it's also, you say the patch out the gay like the pray away the gay.
Kind of.
But I think, I think what really happened is that, you know, it was just ignorance, people.
That's what it was.
When the game was created, it was kind of ignorant in a way to a lot of the people that wanted to play it.
Now, I made the mistake when this, when this story went big, I made the mistake of logging onto websites and reading the comments.
Will people please remind me not to do that?
Hey, Rob, don't do that.
I can't fucking help myself.
I always want to go on and see, gosh, I wonder what the commenters on Joystiq have to say about this.
Gosh, I wonder what the YouTube comments have to say on this.
And I know what I'm going to fucking get and I get so angry.
Just do what I do.
Stop giving a fuck.
It's hard.
It's, Dark Sakura, it's so hard.
Run out of fucks to give. Use them up.
It's hard when on one hand you're really, really-
I said fucks and you said it's hard.
It's really difficult when on one hand you're really, really rooting for Nintendo and then on the other hand you're like,
God damn it, stop making it worse for yourself.
And I've used this comparison a lot in my broadcast days,
but one of my favorite television moments ever was on America's Next Top Model
when Tyra Banks started yelling at one of the contestants,
Be quiet, Tiffany!
Be quiet! We were rooting for you!
We were all rooting for you!
That's how I felt about Nintendo this week.
I just wanted to put my finger out and be like, be quiet, Nintendo!
Be quiet!
You're not listening to what the people are really saying.
And they put out this comment about the whole, oh well it's just this whimsy,
we're not trying to make social commentary, it's a whimsical world.
And I'm like, oh my God, be quiet, you're making it worse.
Because now you're basically saying, in our whimsical, magical world,
we've made a place where gays don't exist.
Perception-
Boy play girl!
Perception is everything.
The porn game.
And whether that's how they meant it or not,
that's how their statement came across,
is that, don't you want to buy this game where gays don't exist?
And you may not want to make social commentary,
but you can't sit there and say,
I'm Switzerland, I'm not making social commentary, I'm not being involved.
You don't get to say that.
By making a video game, which haven't we argued time and time again,
video games are art, right?
Haven't we tried to convince Roger Ebert and other critics out there,
haven't we tried to convince video games are art?
What is art supposed to do?
Provoke.
Provoke what?
Just provoke.
Provoke.
And one of those things it provokes?
Emo.
Social commentary.
Yeah.
So you can't come out and say a video game does not get into social commentary,
because it did.
And that's the problem, guys.
I'm telling you, like, I know many of you are out there listening to Orange on the Star.
Maybe we have some new listeners tonight, thanks to Christopher Tin being on,
and just everything else going on.
I just need to tell you something.
As a gay gamer, okay?
And I've made no secret about that over the time.
I'm not the type of guy that goes out there and is like,
I'm gay, I'm gay, I'm gay, and I play video games.
I'm not really that type of person.
I'm not ashamed of who I am, absolutely.
I put myself out there as, this is how I am, deal with it.
This is the way my creator made me, right?
And so I am a video game fan who happens to be gay.
And let me tell you what kind of goes through your mind when you see something like this,
is that it's...
Imagine if you're playing this game that's supposed to be fun.
Imagine you're a heterosexual male out there, because, you know, that's a big demographic,
and you're playing this game that's just whimsical commentary.
But that game forces you to enter into a relationship that maybe you don't want to get into.
And if you're trying to create a me that looks like yourself,
and you're trying to play a character with good values because that's how you feel about yourself,
and you're trying to create a character in a life simulation game that's a reflection on yourself,
but you hit a wall that you thought in many parts of society we've climbed over time and time again,
and you can't actually accurately reflect yourself, it's very frustrating.
And it's a huge setback, like emotionally.
Like, I play video games to escape this shit.
Now, some of you guys might bring up, well, in Mass Effect I can do this,
and, you know, in these other games, you know, in Dragon Age there's that one character who, you know,
maybe I didn't want to romance the same gender, but I have to.
There's a difference. Those games are storytelling.
You're not playing a reflection of yourself in a life simulator game or a reflection of a character you want to be.
You're playing somebody else's narrative.
There is a huge difference whether Nintendo wants to say there is or not.
Anyway, sorry, I'm hogging the conversation, but obviously I had a lot to say on that.
I do want to just say kudos to Nintendo. They realized the mistake.
They came out and they said exactly what they needed to say the first time.
They came out and said it was an oversight not to do this in the game.
We realize we made a mistake. In the future we'll try to do better.
Thank you. That's all I wanted the first time.
That's all I wanted was, like, you know, just acknowledge.
Don't put all this smoke and mirrors shit of it's a social whimsy world.
Just come out and say we are too lazy to reprogram the game because that's essentially what it is.
It's a port. They don't want to go back and recode the whole damn thing.
I accept that.
And I would believe that.
I do.
Too lazy to reprogram a game? Hmm, virtual console? Yeah.
Yeah.
It seems to have an accurate...
Going to our chat room. I'm sure the chat room is lighting up over at live.vognetwork.com.
And I apologize because I wasn't reading as I was ranting there.
So I'm kind of looking at some stuff now.
Bochikawa in chat says,
Regardless of this news and outcry of this, I would have really liked to see this bug not affect the game in drastic ways.
Because that community that would have been born of this would be quite an interesting force to add to our gaming culture.
Might even be a subset of gamer, but we will never know.
Well, it could be the sequel. We'll see what happens.
Eric RPG says,
That's a really tough topic for me to get into.
And I am going to say I am not the most well educated when it comes to Japanese culture because I've never lived there.
So I'm not going to try to make a statement on that.
But I will just say from what I've gathered,
Japan is not as progressed as we are at this point.
But change is coming, folks.
Because more and more people are beginning to know somebody who is gay.
And the more you know people that are gay, you start to realize they're really not different.
Know what you know and know what you don't know.
Kinda. Kinda, right?
Anyhow, let's see.
Going to our chatroom as well.
ActDeft says,
I truly believe Nintendo did have the best intentions at heart, but it was just ignorance that came into play.
So let's use this to educate them a little bit.
But when they came out and released that first statement, it was like, it was kinda just gross and ignorant and so on.
Here's why I'm going to stick with Animal Crossing for my fun little cutesy sim.
And the actual sims for the adult angle.
For the maturity angle. How's that sound?
Because I can have alien babies.
What if Animal Crossing had forced you to get into a relationship with Ed?
That the only way you could have a baby in that game is to make a baby with Ed. How would you feel?
Well, that's what I feel about the only way to make a baby in Tomodachi Life is to get married.
It's the same thing to me.
Interesting perspective.
Marriage and having children have nothing to do with each other. I'm just saying this.
I've been married for almost nine years with my husband for almost 17 years.
And yeah, maybe I wanted a baby for a little while, but it wasn't the sole basis of our marriage.
You know, I see those assholes, oh my wife won't give me a baby, I'm leaving her.
Fuck you! You marry someone because you love them.
And that's the whole point. If you have the game and you have the ability to get married,
it should be because you are playing a relationship in that game, not just to fucking breed.
And sometimes difficulties come into play where mom or dad may not be able to have a child.
Exactly.
And so, you know, that's why I always get, like, I don't mean to get on a political tangent,
I'm going to take this tangent train on a very quick trip, okay?
That's why I always get really, like, my feathers get really ruffled when I hear the arguments about,
it takes a man and a woman to raise a baby and that's a proper family is to have a man and a woman.
What about that family where mom passed away during childbirth?
How offensive is a statement like that to that family where the dad is doing everything to raise that child appropriately?
Yeah.
Think before you open your fucking mouth. Why don't you just say, I think gay people are gross?
Because that's what I hear. Again, perception, folks.
They've got the cooties.
When you make a comment like that, Loki, you and I lived together for what, two and a half years?
Did you catch gay living with me?
Did you catch it?
No. But then again, you throw like a girl, so.
So do you.
Well, what about this too? I mean, I'll just talk about my, you know, my mom left my dad when I was a baby
because at the time my dad was not a very stable individual.
You know, she left because of domestic abuse.
Would we have all rather than that my mom had stayed with my dad and have him not get any better,
beat on her, beat on me and have that kind of a broken childhood as opposed to her,
you know, raising me with my grandmother and having me raised.
I was raised in a matriarchal house.
You're not, you know, I'm just saying, you know, look at these people who have to make tough decisions like this.
What about women or women who are raped and decide that, you know, because of moral reasons or whatever,
they're going to have that kid.
Do you want them to hunt down their rapist and say, help me raise this baby?
Well, I got to, we're getting, I mean, these, these are all very tough social questions.
Obviously, you're asking some very uncomfortable questions.
But I think what people have to realize is that, yeah, it might be just a video game,
but when it's supposed to be a life reflection, there's, life is a little more complicated than that.
It's a lot more complicated. Yeah.
So, and sometimes we play video games to escape life.
But then when the game sets down all these rules that seem very arbitrary, it can be very difficult.
That's actually why I really like the whole approach of The Sims to it.
Because you can, you can, you know, bang somebody, get knocked up and kick them out of the house if you want to.
You know, you can raise the baby by yourself if you want to.
I have had a character do it.
You know, I, you can have, you know, same sex parents, opposite sex parents, and aliens and vampires.
Basically, no one looks at you weird because no one gives a shit. It's not their business.
I like that approach. Don't make it anything that's, oh, weird. Just make no one care.
Because really, no one should care. It's no one else's business.
All right. Well, we've got to move on because it is about half past six, and I've got to move into our interview tonight.
You know, we've been talking a lot in this opening about how Civilization has changed.
And, you know, there is another simulator out there, one of my favorites of all time, Civilization, that is, that has existed through, through five different games.
And the third Civilization game, I'm going to be honest y'all, Civ III, not my favorite in the series.
It's still a good game. It's like, it's like ice cream. Even a bad flavor is still ice cream. It's still pretty good.
That's how I feel about Civ III. But then, you know, when I first played Civ IV for the first time, and I fired up that, you know, loading screen and saw that opening movie,
it was very much like, yes, this is a new, this is the rebirth of Civilization. This is a new game. This is going to be awesome.
And so Civ IV, you know, a lot of that is credited to the soundtrack of the game.
And one of the most influential songs in the game that had such an impact was a song called Baba Yetu.
And we are going to be welcoming the composer of Baba Yetu to the show tonight, Christopher Tin.
Before we give him a call, let's take a listen to a clip because it is an audio download.
I can't play the entire song for you because you got to, you got to go to Christophertin.com and get this album for yourself.
But we're going to play a clip here to set the mood of Baba Yetu from Civilization IV here on Orange Lounge Radio before we welcome Christopher Tin.
And we're going to play the song called Baba Yetu.
Baba Yetu
I still get chills listening to that. I don't know about you guys, but that's like such a great song there.
Again, that's a clip of Baba Yetu from Civilization IV.
And we are going to get the composer of Baba Yetu on the line right now.
We're going to do this live here. We're going to give Christopher a call and get him on the show to talk about Baba Yetu as well as his brand new album.
Hi there, is this Christopher?
Yes it is.
Hey Christopher, how you doing? It's Rob from Orange Lounge Radio. You're on the air. How's it going?
Hi Rob.
Hi.
Welcome.
Welcome to the show. Congratulations. You just released your brand new album, The Drop That Contained the Sea this week, right?
Yes I did. This Thursday in fact.
Wow, that's awesome. Now if people want to pick up a copy of The Drop That Contained the Sea, where's the best place to go to pick that up?
Well the best place is my own website, ChristopherTin.com. You can also get it at iTunes and Amazon.
But they take a big cut, so my website is definitely the best place to do it.
So if you want to make sure that Christopher is actually the one getting your money, because he deserves it for this soundtrack, check out ChristopherTin.com.
We see some folks in our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com. Tigerclaw is asking, will you take questions from the chat room?
Absolutely. If you have a question for Christopher Tin, head on over to our chat room. Live.vognetwork.com.
I've also got some questions from social media we will get to in just a little bit.
But Christopher, if you don't mind, I want to take a step back, because we are a show primarily about video games and gaming culture.
So you have an awesome title by your name. You are the first person to win a Grammy for a song that was composed for a video game.
How does that feel when you hear that?
It's kind of cool. The history of video games is littered with all sorts of trivia, and it's kind of cool that I get to be a little footnote in that history.
So it's cool. I really enjoy it.
You might end up a Jeopardy question someday. That's pretty awesome.
That would be hilarious if that happened. I would love that.
Which would feel better? The Grammy or the Jeopardy question? No, don't answer that.
I don't know. That's a tough one, you know? Yeah.
Don't answer that. That was a dumb question. All right. Let's take a step back. Since we are a video game show, I want to talk about Civilization IV, obviously.
I'm a huge fan of the Civ series, and I just talked about how Civ III, for me, was not the strongest Civ game.
But Civ IV, that was such a rebirth for the series for me, and a huge part of that was the music.
When you fire up that game for the first time and you hear Baba Yetu and you see the full motion video of Civilization is being created,
it really sets the mood for this epic rebirth for Civilization.
I know you've probably been asked this question a million times, but for the sake of our audience, how did you end up being asked to do Baba Yetu for Civ IV?
It's a pretty funny story, actually. The lead designer of Civilization IV is a guy named Soren Johnson, who happened to be my roommate back in college.
I went to my five-year college reunion and I ran into Soren and I said,
Soren, what are you up to? He said, I'm a video game designer now. I was like, oh yeah, that's cool.
He said, I'm working on a game. Actually, he said he just finished a game. It was Civilization III.
I said, oh, fantastic. I love the Civ series. I grew up playing it. He said, that's great.
Well, I'm working on Civ IV. Have you ever considered writing music for video games?
I hadn't at the time, but obviously it was a thrilling idea for me because, like I said, I grew up playing Civilization.
Like many other people, I logged hundreds of hours playing that game.
A few months later, I got a call from him saying, hey, Chris, we took some of the music that you produced in college and we stuck it on the game and we really like it.
We were wondering if we could hire you to write a new piece of music that had an African influence as well as an orchestral influence with lots of big taiko drums.
I said, yeah, I'd love to do it. That was kind of my version of the breaking into the business story.
Just a pure chance encounter with my old college roommate, which led to pretty much the biggest break of my life.
It seems so crazy that they talk about sometimes, and I was just having a conversation with a colleague before the show tonight,
that a lot of the gaming industry sometimes is about who you know.
It's so interesting that, yeah, it was this chance encounter or whatever, but it worked out so perfectly.
You can't imagine Civ IV without that soundtrack now.
Yeah, it's kind of weird, isn't it? You think about it.
This was like 10 years ago that I ran into him at our reunion, maybe 11 years, something like that.
It's almost one of these things where it almost never happened for me.
My life would be very different now if I hadn't run into Soren.
It's a cool thing, I gotta say.
Well, congratulations. Your music is incredible, and you're very deserving of the success, so congratulations to you.
Thanks, Rob. I appreciate that.
No worries. Baba Yetu, it's had a lasting presence.
Here we are still talking about, they're on Civ V and talking about Civ V and a half now with the After Earth and all this or whatever they're making this year.
Yet, here we are talking about Baba Yetu. This song's had such a lasting presence.
How did it feel to win a Grammy for a song that you'd written years ago?
It was a great feeling. It was kind of surreal, and it actually didn't sink in for about a year until the following year when I went to the Grammys as a spectator.
I knew some people at that time who were nominated for Grammys, and one by one I saw them all not win.
At that point, I was just like, oh my god, I can't believe I managed to get through. I can't believe it happened for me.
That's when it really sank in. It was kind of a surreal experience when I actually got it, though.
Baba Yetu is really a staple of the Video Games Live Tour. I'm sure you're probably familiar with the Video Games Live Tour that Tommy Tallarico puts on, and he's still touring the world with this.
I was actually just telling a story to Bobby on the show prior to us tonight that when I went and saw Video Games Live, I remember them playing Baba Yetu.
That was one of the memorable pieces in the show for me. Have you seen or participated in Video Games Live, and how do you feel about your song being such a staple of the tour?
I love it. I'm very heavily involved in the show. I conducted it from time to time. I conducted the Canada Tour last year.
We went coast to coast in Canada and did the show for a number of different audiences.
I'm going to be conducting Baba Yetu again this June at the LA E3 Video Games Live Show.
I love it. They were the ones who premiered the song live. They performed it at the Hollywood Bowl back in, I think, 2006.
I got to give credit to Tommy and Jack Wall as well, who is conducting it. They really brought that song out of purely the video game world and into this new world that I'm connected to, which is the classical world.
Because of Video Games Live, the sheet music got published by Alfred Publishing, which is a large sheet music publisher.
Alfred issued it, and it became a hit amongst high school choirs. Suddenly, thousands of choirs around the world were singing this song, just for their spring concerts and whatever.
It introduced my music to a brand new audience. I like to think that this was a big step in me. I think it's kind of difficult for video game composers to hop over to the mainstream.
I think this was my particular way of doing so. It was purely through the fact that my music got performed so much, and the sheet music, that I found an audience outside of video games.
Wow, that's amazing. Do you still plan to work with video games composed for future video games? Now you're on this different path where you're able to express the world music on your own through these albums. Do you see yourself working with video games again in the future?
I actually have a new song coming out in a game that I can't tell you the game, but I can tell you that it'll be announced in a few days, actually. But if people like Baba Yetu, it's similar in terms of the style of it.
The game itself that it's coming out in, let's just say it's in that same world. There'll be an announcement pretty soon, within the next week, I think.
Well, I have a guess what that might be, but we'll see. That'd be awesome. I'm hoping it's true. I'm sure whatever it is will be awesome. Let's continue to talk about the future. I know that you have a new album that's out there, so I definitely want to let you talk about that new album.
So what do your fans have to look forward to from your new release, The Drop That Contained the Sea?
Well, it's a lot more epic, world-influenced, orchestral, choral music, I guess is the way to describe it. If people like Baba Yetu, then there's a lot of tracks on there that I think blow Baba Yetu away, but we'll see what other people think.
But I'm really proud of it, actually. I think it's been my way of maturing over the last couple of years as a composer. I think the level of writing is a lot deeper. My level of expression is a lot more personal and a lot more grandiose, I think.
I feel really good about it on a purely artistic level. So far, the response that I've gotten from people has been very positive as well. People have been saying that it's like the evolution of my writing. A lot of people have said it surpasses my previous album, so I feel really good about it, I gotta say.
That's a great point, because when you talk about that this is where you're at now and things have evolved and so forth, I think everybody always asks me, how can I go listen to Orange Lawn's radio episode 1? I don't know if you know, we're on episode 552 now, so we've been doing this a very long time.
And I'm kind of like, don't worry about episode 1, guys, it's not even as good as what we're doing now.
Yeah, totally. You always want to push yourself as an artist and you always want to evolve, right? And what's a little difficult sometimes is some people, especially if you're an artist that releases an album once every five years or something, they're kind of locked into a time capsule in terms of who you were five years ago and what you were writing then.
But you always do want to push yourself as a writer because you want to grow, right? And if people just want to listen to the stuff I was writing five years ago, there's already an album for that, but I do sort of want to bring people along for a ride and of course I hope to reward their participation on this journey by delivering a good product and I hope that I've done that.
I think you have. I think when people listen to The Drop That Contained the Sea, they will not be disappointed. We're going to play a track from that in a little bit at the end of the interview so people can get a little taste of that. But if you want to hear more of it, check out The Drop That Contained the Sea at ChristopherTinn.com.
Christopher, our chat room is lighting up with questions. In fact, I'm not even going to be able to get to all these. I feel awful. But I do want to ask you some of these questions that are coming from our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com.
I'm going to go with this one from Dark Tetsuya who asks, is there a particular genre of game you've always wanted to compose music for?
Hmm, interesting. A particular genre. I think it's a role-playing game of some sort. I think that would be great. Or an MMO actually. You know what, I love the idea of working on an MMO. Something where people give me kind of a world to populate with my ideas, so to speak.
Yeah, something like that. I'm not so drawn to things like first-person shooters. Whatever gives me the opportunity to write good music. But honestly, I just love working on games anyway. Whatever people ask me to do, I'm probably thrilled to do it.
Well, I was going to say, if Blizzard is out there listening, Christopher is waiting for your call. So just know that.
Yeah, I know all those Blizzard guys. And one of these days, maybe I'll come begging at their doorstep or something.
I don't think they'd mind.
No, I love them. They're a really talented bunch of guys. I have a lot of respect for them.
Let me do a question from Dungeonbuster, who saw your AMA recently on Reddit. Dungeonbuster asks, can he share what about Katamari Damacy's sound makes it amazing to him? I love the soundtrack too, but I'm curious to know what excites him about it.
Yeah, I gotta admit, Christopher, when I hear your music, I don't necessarily see Katamari Damacy influence. What's that about?
But it's so good. I don't know, I can't explain it, but I just love the energy and the zaniness of it.
We're not just talking about the main theme, which is fantastic, of course, but in my mind, the entire soundtrack to all the Katamari games is genius.
I second that.
There's a wide diversity of styles in there. I mean, some great vocal performances, some great tracks being produced by a number of different DJs and producers and so forth. I think it's just really, really cool.
And I think it takes a special, really quirky game like Katamari to pull off a soundtrack like that. You're never going to hear that in any other game. And I don't know, I think it's just fantastic writing.
And I kind of miss that series myself.
I have to say, though, it combines anything from old swing to jazz to the whole crooner style. My two favorite tracks are completely, stylistically different from each other. The Moon and the Prince and then Que Sera Sera.
Totally, right? I mean, it's all over the place. And I think that's why it's so fun, too, because it's like this giant amalgamation. It's like a Katamari in musical form.
It is. It really is.
It's like a giant amalgamation of random songs thrown together. And I just think it's fantastic.
Let's go to another question from our chat room from Gamer Girl, who asks, is there an influence outside of video games that you get your inspiration for the music you compose?
There's got to be plenty, right?
Oh, there's a lot. I mean, I'll tell you what inspired me to write the latest album is I got really turned on to the band Florence and the Machine a couple of years ago.
Oh, yes.
I totally dig her. And I, you know, this album was kind of inspired by that feeling that I got when I first listened to her debut album Lungs.
I mean, I was just, I just loved the rocket-ness of it. And I loved the lyrics and I loved her vocal performance and sort of the gospel influence.
She was, I mean, that album, you know, really, you know, there's absolutely no direct influence on any of the songs. I mean, they're so stylistically different.
But the energy that I got from her really made me want to create an album like my latest one.
And then, you know, there's all the other sort of influences that I have from being a classically trained composer and playing jazz and, you know, doing all these other different things growing up and listening to world music and performing in world music groups.
But honestly, the influence comes from all over the place.
That's amazing to hear because Florence is one of my favorites. I got to say Shake It Out is probably one of my 10 favorite songs ever written.
Oh, I know, right? Oh, my God, yeah.
She wrote it in like 15 minutes, apparently. She's like, like, she just literally-
I have one that I like better, though, and that's My Boy Builds Coffins.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That one I can just sing.
Yeah, so good.
But she's very diverse in her styles, too, if you really think about it. And I know on your albums, you have all these songs in different languages and it's very diverse as well.
I just, it's, I would have never made that connection to Florence. That's so funny.
Yeah, I mean, it's purely on a fan level that I'm connected to her. I mean, there's no sort of like, it's not like our music is related in any sort of level, but I just, I'm just a huge fan.
I understand the feeling very well.
If I may, actually, one tiny question for me.
Of course.
I did happen to notice it sounded like you had a little bit of a minimalist influence as well, like Philip Glass.
Hmm, actually, I was a big John Adams fan all through college, actually. That's well spotted. I'm not sure where you spotted that, but you know, that's woven into my DNA musically. So I mean, it's all this sort of stuff surfaces at one point or another, so good catch.
I just sort of got the feeling across the board, you know, it's like, you know, how there's just that, it'll start with one thing and then build and build and build, but it's so subtle that you don't notice it until one point.
Well, what were we talking about a minute ago? Art always provokes response, and it's always interesting how that response comes in all these different ways.
I actually, when I'm a designer, as my hobby now, I do it only for volunteer work now, but when I listen to you, actually, when I draw, I listen to Philip Glass.
And depending on the style of what I'm doing, depends the style of music I'm going to listen to. It's like, I will fully throw on, you know, Ella Fitzgerald if I'm doing, you know, 30s and 40s style, so.
All right, well, I just, I don't want to take up too much of Christopher's time. I just have a couple more questions from our chatters and our listeners. One more question from chat here, Christopher, from Tiger Claw, who asks, have you ever thought of composing, speaking of diversity, have you ever thought of composing for feature films or TV?
Yeah, you know, I've never really given TV much of a thought until recent years, and I think that's because, like, I think TV's gotten really good recently, and, you know, I've started to become more of a fan of TV.
Films, my original intent was to write for movies, but along the way, I sort of got sidetracked by commercials, games, and, you know, this career that I have now. I would love to write for films. I think collaborative work is a lot of fun, and films are a great medium to work in.
So, I mean, I have done a number of films, and I'd certainly like to do more. So, I mean, I'm just, you know, I'm keeping all my options open at this point.
All right, I'm going to go to one more question. This one's actually from Facebook, and I know this guy is a huge fan of yours, so he'd be so devastated if I didn't ask his question, and I'm going to.
So, Awesome Unicorn is on our Facebook and asked you this question earlier this week, who said, I'd like to hear about the process of selecting vocalists for the songs.
Some of your work seems very tailored to a specific type of performance or singing style, and then others seem like a wider range of vocalists would be able to perform the songs.
Do you tend to write songs with specific performers in mind to sing them, or do the songs come first and the quest for the vocalists later?
Well, hello, Awesome Unicorn, first of all. Yes, I do actually write specifically with vocalists in mind.
I mean, usually what will happen is I'll listen to a bunch of records, and I'll identify who I want to work with, and then I'll just track them down on the internet and write to them.
If they're game, I will write with them in mind. With a lot of the singers I've reached out to, they've totally been game, and so the songs were pretty much tailored to them.
I think there's a real advance to doing that. First of all, if you have a specific singer in mind, you can write to their strengths.
When you write to their strengths, they'll perform the hell out of it. When they perform the hell out of it, you get an immensely dramatic and gratifying performance.
You maybe won't always get that when you write something in the abstract and have someone else come in and sing it later.
There are times when I've done that as well, and it works some of the times, but generally speaking, I prefer to have someone in mind when I'm writing for them.
When I'm writing a song, I prefer to have a particular voice in mind. Let me put it that way.
Good to know. I'm glad we could resolve Awesome Unicorn's inquiry there.
Before we let Christopher go and get to the other song preview, Jamie, you mentioned you had one other quick question you wanted to sneak in.
What is your favorite non-standard time signature?
Probably, I don't know, maybe 7-8 or 5-8, something like that. I'm going to start exploring more and more complex ones as I get further and further into Bulgarian music and Bulgarian rhythms, which are very complicated.
7-8, 9-8, 11-8, 13-8, things like that. I'm just going to start exploring a little more.
But I think there's plenty of great music that can be written in 4-4, I gotta say.
I agree with that. I just keep thinking about the first time I ever, I was a band nerd, the first time I ever played Mars Bringer of War, and learning how to do 5-8, and I was like, I want more of this.
Yeah, right? Totally. There's a little bit of a Mars Bringer of War influence on one of the songs on my new album, too, actually.
Ooh, I'm excited, because that's like my favorite in the planets.
Oh my god, yeah, it's fantastic. Actually, the ninth track of my album, it's called Has Gengor Fridum, which is a sort of setting of an Old Norse Viking text.
I mean, that's one, there's a piece where, you know, there's a little bit of Mars Bringer of War, there's a little bit of Carmina Burana, there's a little bit of Nobuo Amatus, Liberi Fatali, you know, there's all these influences.
And, you know, I'm speaking to a gamer crowd here, but, and this is why I feel comfortable saying this, like, there's a lot of game soundtracks out there which have this sort of bombastic, you know, Gustav Holst, Mars Bringer of War sound to them, you know, these gothic choirs and things like that.
And I've never really had the opportunity to write for a game like that. And I sort of resisted writing a piece like that, sort of for my own projects.
So after I conducted Video Games Live, and after I conducted Liberi Fatali a number of times, I was just like, I want to write a piece like this, I, you know, screw it, I just want to do this, you know, I don't care, you know, if it's been done 1000 times, I'm gonna write my own version of this type of gothic bombastic thing.
And so, you know, I channel Stravinsky and Karl Orff and you know, all these other guys and, and, you know, crank up this big old Viking tune, which I was a lot of fun to do, you know,
Well, I'm sitting here excited now.
Well, only Dark Sakura would go there and take it to a whole nother music nerd level. But the chat room is eating it up. Just so you know, Christopher, chat room is Bobby Black Wolf saying 7-8 is my favorite too.
And kind of causing to a music nerd high five and they're they're they're music nerding out there. So that's
High five guys, high five.
My first major in college was a music major. So
Fantastic.
I was a band nerd and I was a clarinet player in high school myself.
Oh, fantastic. I was a trumpet player.
I was sax and contra alto clarinet just to be different.
All right.
Wow.
Music nerds and band nerds and video game nerds everywhere have a reason to check out Christopher Tin.
You can check check him out on his website, Christophertin.com.
And you can check out the new album, The Drop That Contained the Sea, which I'm sure many of you haven't heard yet because it just came out this week.
So no excuses. Go check that out at Christophertin.com.
Christopher, as we say goodbye to you, we're going to check out one of these songs from the new album.
This is track four. And I apologize if I horribly butchered the name, but it's Eza
Nomso, I believe.
It's Eza Nomso, which means come tomorrow.
And this is also performed by the Soweto Gospel Choir who performed Baba Yetu and a little bit of trivia about this song.
I wrote this at the last minute. I was on a plane to Johannesburg.
And it's a long story, but I was being flown around for this commercial project I was doing for Emirates Airlines and they're flying me all around the world business class.
So I had a very cushy seat and I was on my way to Johannesburg and I thought I need to write another song for these guys to sing.
And so I wrote this song and it's about clouds, which is kind of a fitting thing to write about when you're flying.
So it's got a sort of a brisk sort of breezy feel like you're sort of flying through the clouds.
And the lyrics are about, you know, the lyrics translate to things like, like a bird, I fly, I sing, like a bird, I'm holding on to the wind.
Very sort of poetic stuff about, you know, clouds and flying through the air.
Well, we're going to check this out right after I say goodbye.
Christopher, thank you so much for taking the time out today with us.
I know today is a big day for a lot of people with Mother's Day and everything.
So thank you for spending time with us and best of luck with the new album.
And I really encourage people everywhere to check it out on your website.
Thanks, guys. It was a lot of fun.
And I look forward to the surprise announcement this week.
Yeah, yeah. Keep an eye out.
All right. Take care, Christopher. It was a real honor.
Likewise.
All right. Bye bye.
Bye.
That was Christopher Tin, everybody. And you can check out his new album, The Drop That Contained the Sea, at ChristopherTin.com.
And in the meantime, here is a clip.
Again, I can't play the whole thing for you guys, but I think it's on his website if you want to check it out over at ChristopherTin.com.
This is a clip of track four from the album, Iza Nomso.
I think I said that right. Come tomorrow is what it means.
Nyomso.
Nyomso. Here it is. Come tomorrow. I'll just say come tomorrow.
Here it is, guys, at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
Oh,
oh,
beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
This is a real game, people, only in Japan.
Omega Quintet, coming to you September.
It's Idol Master meets the beep.
Drop that beep.
All right, lastly but not leastly,
this made me exclaim a lot of excited things
that had to get beeped, because I was excited to hear that Tetsuya Mizuguchi
is back in game development.
That's right.
We thought he was taking a break
or was going long-term or whatever to focus on the college stuff,
but in the new issue of Edge,
which is available in print form and so on,
he talks about how he left Q Entertainment.
He took up a role as a lecturer,
but he is not giving up on video games.
So he's right now, quote, helping with a few games,
but they are not like his previous work,
like Res or Space Channel 5.
He says, I'm helping with some social games in Japan.
I'm just helping.
I want to start a new project on my own,
maybe this year or next year.
Yes.
Very excited, because I'm a Mizuguchi fanboy.
That you are.
I am, very much.
All right, Dark Sakura.
Well, there is a new comerage for the Left 4 Dead franchise,
and it is an arcade game that's planned for Japan
that basically it's going to,
I don't know if this is going to be something like
the Gun Survivor series,
if it's going to be one of those,
but it looks like Taito is working with Valve
to put this out,
and it's been thought of,
announced before as Project Z,
but now it's Left 4 Dead.
Next up, Shaq Fu, a Legend Reborn.
It got funded.
Next.
What an interesting world we live in,
where Amplitude probably won't get,
on its current path anyway,
won't get funded,
yet Shaq Fu got funded.
Just let that sink in for a minute.
But.
And then have a drink.
There is something good coming out of this.
Okay.
Five percent of all the profits will be donated
to the Boys and Girls Clubs of America.
Okay.
Better than five percent going to Kickstarter,
but that's a great thing to hear.
Last but not least, we have,
you know how there's just two new tracks for Outrun?
Well, now there are going to be three
Outrun soundtracks coming out.
You can get them for $9.49 for each soundtrack
on Amazon or $9.99 on the iTunes store,
or you can just get them individual
in case you're like me
and only care about Magical Sound Shower.
Fair enough.
And don't already have other Outrun soundtracks.
Alright, fair enough.
Alright, we're going to move on.
There is no frugal question.
I was going to say, for the record,
one of my horses in Derby Owners Club
was called Magical Sound.
I remember that.
I think because there wasn't enough characters
to be Magical Sound Shower.
But you did have Beat Politary.
Just Politary.
No, Politary, so that you could whip Politary.
Yes.
And that Politary would cry.
Although it's kind of tasteless in retrospect,
but I don't really wish harm upon this individual,
but it was just a running gag with Bamani music
because her songs were really bad.
I had one called Just a Horse
that ended up being awesome.
Didn't you have one called Glue?
Yeah, I did have one called Glue,
and Glue ended up being my best sire.
I remember I think I had one called Briton Spears.
Yeah.
And then...
I missed Derby Owners Club.
That was the day.
I know it's still around, but it's not the same.
I found my folder.
Did you really?
It has my horses in it.
Anyway.
Alright, anyway.
No frugal question of the week this week
because I knew we would be running along
because of the interview
and I wanted everybody to ask our guest questions,
but it'll return next week.
So Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio
or Google.com slash plus Orange Launch Radio.
There is a game Sega should bring
to the Wii U.
What?
Derby Owners Club.
Hey, now you're talking.
Because then you can whip the horses
with the Wii remotes.
Yeah.
And Sega's in bed with Nintendo now.
And you'd use your little sub screen for training.
This is a good idea.
Why isn't this happening?
I don't understand.
Because licensing everything that goes into that game
is actually kind of fucking expensive.
That's why the cabinets are premium.
That's true.
Aren't those like six digits for those cabinets?
I would not doubt it,
especially for that main screen that always shows the running race.
Crazy.
That alone is easily high fives.
All right, let's move on to some other
Take the card with you.
longer gaming news stories.
We'll get into maybe a little bit more in depth.
Loki.
All right.
So once again we're talking about Nintendo here.
They're planning to approach emerging markets,
you know, like China and stuff,
a little differently than they do the rest of the world,
including that they are going to actually target those markets
with different hardware or new hardware, I guess.
They're basically saying, you know,
we want to make new things,
you know, thinking rather a cheaper version of what we currently have.
The product and price balance must be made from scratch.
So if you kind of take it like, you know,
how they made the Wii mini, you know,
doing something like that for maybe like the Wii U or something.
Or, you know, 2DS or something like that.
Where it's slightly cheaper than the stuff that's out there,
you know, to help drive sales, I guess.
I don't know.
I mean, I guess that's a good idea.
I just, I can't imagine what they would strip out feature wise for like a Wii U.
You know, the 3DS obviously, the 2DS works.
NFC.
Yeah, I think with the handhelds it would be really easy to get.
The gamepad might be tethered.
Yeah, it would be really easy to get a lower cost console for the handhelds.
The other consoles, I mean, what about just a Wii?
Like, why the Wii U? Why not just a Wii?
Well, they have the Wii mini, so they could do that.
This is for other markets that don't have video games
as much as they do in Japan, USA, Europe as it is.
Well, as of recently, they haven't had any consoles because they were banned.
It's an interesting change in strategy for Nintendo,
especially considering a lot of the crap that we use getting here in the States and in Japan and so forth.
It's an interesting way to try to turn things around by taking a proven success and launching it in other places.
I mean, it's not like China is a small country, you know.
Something like the Wii has the potential to do very well there, so it's a very interesting strategy.
Maybe a good way to cut the losses in the home department.
I don't like that term.
What?
Proven success.
Well, what would you call the Wii in that regard?
It is. Come on, Wii Sports. Best video game ever, sales-wise.
I've, you know, saved the argument that I've made at least three times on the show previously.
I call it a lightning bolt.
It came, it landed, it's done.
Other markets, I don't know.
I truly don't know how could I know the state of gaming in China.
I really don't want to make any claims to that, but it's one of those things like,
it was truly media fervor.
It wasn't technically, low barrier to entry, gaming, games, games from real life that we all know,
and you can do, you can put to use with less investment.
It was a lightning bolt.
You are not guaranteed the success if you give it to somebody else with cultural differences.
Bowling isn't a worldwide thing.
Soccer, you probably know.
I don't know. I just, like that term has a place that we use, not it, in my opinion.
Alright, well, we will see what happens.
I think we'll get more information of this at E3.
Maybe, maybe.
In the meantime, as far as the Wii U is concerned, you know, I mentioned that one of the other markets,
besides just the US, is Japan, and Japan, some information for what they're going to be getting Wii U-wise.
Bayonetta 2 and Hyrule Warriors set for summer debuts in Japan.
This surprised me. I figured Hyrule Warriors was probably a summer, like, early fall game,
but the fact that Bayonetta 2, it's fucking happening this year, OMG, and it might even be summer,
especially in Japan, that's pretty exciting to hear.
So, yeah, finally we'll get to see what this, you know, hype with Bayonetta 2 is all about,
because the first game was pretty awesome.
Of course, Bayonetta 2 bringing a two-player mode into the game, analog and touch-based controls,
and, of course, new hair for Bayonetta, very important.
Yeah, that's really exciting.
The only other Wii U games confirmed for this year for the West, those games, Mario Kart 8, Smash Brothers,
X by Monolith Soft, which I'm actually very curious about that one, that looks like it could be a winner as well,
and whatever else they announce at E3.
So I'm fully expecting at E3, we're going to get release dates for Bayonetta 2 and Hyrule Warriors here in the US.
That's pretty exciting, so some things to get excited about on the Wii U.
Is it going to be enough to really push sales of that system?
I don't know, I think another price cut would go a long way in helping that, but we shall see.
Meanwhile, Dark Soccer are going to talk about a game that should be on the Wii U, but probably won't.
That isn't. Alas, Minecraft, specifically the PS4 and Xbox One versions,
they are not going to have the infinite world size that the PC version does.
It will have borders. You will find the end of the world, and then you'll fall off of it.
Basically, they are constrained for size limits so that you can't...
I mean, they have bigger worlds than the PS3 and 360 versions,
but they still are limited because there's only so much memory, only so much space.
Not infinite.
People make a big deal about the PC worlds being infinite and so forth, but it's really infinite in theory.
You get the equivalent of a kill screen, where the data starts...
Yeah, at some point you're going to run out of server space.
It's going to be forever. You would be challenged to ever be able to run from one end of the world to the end.
Well, people do actually make that look up. I think it's called the Endlands.
It's a thing in Minecraft where people basically go until the game starts having corrupted data,
and the calculations won't apply anymore because they've already used up what they can.
Wow. Has anybody found that on the VoG server yet?
Everybody stays in one little area on the VoG server.
Everybody stays in one area, and also...
I tried to go out a ways when I built my house, and to come to find out, it really wasn't that far.
That's why you fly.
The other thing, too, is I occasionally...
Well, I don't anymore, because I haven't really messed with the server in a while,
but I'd occasionally cut all the area that's around...
Because I did that so that new terrain would generate, because when we upgraded,
there's new biomes and stuff that weren't generating, so I did that.
And so I clamped it all down to where we were just at.
So if some idiot goes straight for a long ways away, I'm just going to probably...
Unless there's some interesting stuff over there, I'm probably just going to erase that terrain and...
Clip it out, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, fair enough.
It's really boring, though. There's not a lot of terrain that's interesting over there.
There's a lot of great stuff on the VoG server, though.
I know we haven't talked about it in a while, but there have been people working hard on there
to connect everything with trains everywhere.
Seattle said it best, the Farlands. That was it.
Well, yeah, the problem right now is when they upgraded Bucket,
it's because they've added all this new stuff now,
because they're giving you the ability where you're going to be able to change your username,
and so they're tied into IDs now, and so all the systems that are based off usernames are all broken,
and so it's just a big ol' mess. The whole infrastructure is kind of being rewritten,
so a lot of those plugins aren't available.
And I've spent all my time programming, so I haven't really messed with...
Because honestly, I looked at the server logs and there's nobody on there, so whatever.
How do you guys feel about the limited space on PlayStation 4 and Xbox One?
I kind of feel that even though it's limited, it's going to be very hard to push the boundaries of it.
It's going to be a lot of space to work with. I don't think it's a big deal.
Well, they're saying it was because of save file limitations, so how big of a save file are we talking?
Because save files aren't normally that big, at least on consoles.
I would imagine, even with a couple megs, which some games have 30-meg save files.
I mean, they're huge, some of them.
I'm surprised you couldn't just make an exception. I mean, come on, it's Minecraft.
They're like, nope, nope, nope, sorry, we have this rule in place here that we can't do this.
We're not flexible at all.
It might have something to do with the RAM or something. I don't know.
But I'm pretty sure those save files are going to be able to be pretty big.
You know, I was just thinking. Remember when 30 megs were hard drive limits?
Yes, right?
When we moved out here, we had a 60-meg hard drive.
Yeah. My first PC had a 40-megabyte hard drive. Like, that couldn't even fit an episode of this show.
The day the gigabyte was standard, I was like, ahhh.
Exactly.
My first computer had a 0-megabyte hard drive.
My first computer, mine, it actually was in my bedroom. It had no hard drive and two 5.25-inch flash drives.
Yeah, I remember when those 5.25-inch disks could hold, what, 720 kilobytes?
And when you measured your hard drive by height?
Yeah.
I used to use a full-height hard drive as a paperweight.
We're reminiscing again. Let's go do more news.
Because we're old.
I know. Low-key.
Alright. So, this is kind of, I don't know.
Everyone's been kind of wondering since they announced Unreal Engine 4.
Hey, so when do we get in the next Unreal Tournament game?
Because it's been like, what, six years since Unreal Tournament came out?
Maybe even more than that.
So, now Epic is going to put out an Unreal Tournament game, but they're kind of going a different route with it.
They're actually making it open source.
And so, they're going to be creating the game.
It's going to be on, I want to say it was going to be on GitHub or something like that.
Oh, that was fun.
Well, maybe not GitHub. I don't know.
Oh, it is on GitHub.
But it's going to be available to the people that actually pay for the Unreal Engine.
I don't know if I trust those crazy people at GitHub anyway.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
And apparently, there's going to be discussion with people that work at Epic developing the game and fans of the game.
And you're actually going to be kind of helping mold how the game is.
And they're going to have Twitch streams showing stuff like that.
Also, like I said, all the code that's created during the development of the game will be available on GitHub if you're an Unreal Engine 4 developer.
So, you need to pay that $19.99 a month or whatever it is.
So, that's kind of neat.
And when the game does come out, it will be free to play.
Interesting.
I'm sorry. Yeah. And not free to play as in you buy stuff. It's free.
Which is a shocking...
I really don't want to do Unreal a disservice because they have been a mainstay for so many important things for as long as they have.
And so, I really...
Very specific, the point that I'm trying to make.
I've always considered Unreal to be kind of second.
More engine, less game.
Exactly as Loki just finished saying.
Unreal Tournament, not so prolific.
But the games that have been built on Unreal Engine, far and wide.
Phenomenal. That's where their strength is and they make a good game on top of it.
The fact that they're going in the same direction that Valve has with Steam.
Steamworks and mods for their game aren't new.
But items and all of these other community-driven things that generate interest, revenue for everybody.
It's the right choice for them. It's the way the gaming has gone.
It enables them to do new things and open up Unreal to plenty more players that may not have been able to play it in the past.
Not condescendingly, welcome to this generation.
It seems like they did it right. They're here. Everything that they've done has been interesting.
The pool of available, capable games has only gotten bigger and it's exciting.
Some comments from our chatroom over at live.vognetwork.com.
Dark Tetsuya says, not gonna lie, super stoked for the new, free Unreal Tournament.
Tiger Claw says, Unreal Tournament had a huge mod community behind it.
It's where you can download lots of custom maps, skins, and all sorts of mods for it.
SHG100Matt says, I still have Unreal Tournament 2004.
Still my favorite Unreal Tournament game and I still play it occasionally.
Live.vognetwork.com. Those comments.
Yeah, they recreated the whole end of Hypercube in Gary's mod.
Yeah, you mentioned that. Crazy. Mod communities are something else.
But I mean that in the nicest way.
Anyhow, let's move on. One community that's on hold for a little bit.
Need for Speed. After 13 years of a new Need for Speed every year.
Really? I didn't realize that. My god.
Well, they took a year off this year.
It will be back in 2015 and this news was broken during an EA conference call about earnings.
Ghost Games in Gothenburg is working on an innovative new chapter of the Storied franchise.
We've planned an extended development window to ensure we're delivering a high quality experience for Need for Speed players next year.
That quote from CEO Andrew Wilson.
So, no other reasons outside of that, but you know what? That's alright.
Take the time to get it right, folks. There's nothing wrong with that.
And I look forward to playing this new Need for Speed game.
So, alright. Let us take a moment to go to our email bag.
You know, every week you guys email us.
Participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send your emails.
Yeah, boy.
Oops. Not that one. Sorry about that.
This is the song that we use for the emails every week when you guys email us.
Dark Soccer's gonna dive into the mailbag head first and find some emails worthy of reading on tonight's program.
All one of them.
Just one?
Yeah.
Hey OrangeLounge PokeMasters.
Let's create our own Pokemon on this week's show.
With exclamation points.
What would your custom Pokemon look like?
What are his or her powers?
Example, fire, ice, electricity, etc.
Don't forget to name it.
Great show as always.
Keep gaming dudes and dudette.
EA skeezy.
I would have a dark type that would be female and based kind of off of a fox.
Kind of.
Named Bob.
I don't even know where to go with this question.
I would want a kitty named Sanrio.
Like my kitty.
Well, Alan's kitty, but mine by association.
Do you have a Pokemon you would have, Jason?
I don't have the imagination for this anymore.
It's really strange to say, but like I said earlier, I've owned maybe three of them.
And I really appreciate the universe.
It's interesting, it's beautiful, and I love what they continue to do.
But Jason would like a brain for his Pokemon.
That's it.
Jason's Pokemon is going to be Mother Brain.
I don't have the courage.
I need a heart.
I want to go home.
Jason's is going to be Mother Brain.
Well that makes that battle very interesting.
That was a great Facebook meme I saw, by the way.
Happy Mother's Day with Mother Brain.
Did you see the Cubone one?
I forgot what side it was, but someone said,
Cubone's having the worst Mother's Day ever.
Because Cubone wears his mother's skull.
Awful.
I think it was Geekology or something.
Loki, do you have a Pokemon in mind?
I don't fucking know anything about Pokemon.
I don't care.
We have to do our various shows as Pokemon.
Where we only say our names the entire show.
Rah rah!?
Thank you for the email.
Team America. World police to me.
No. We love the random questions.
If you have some random questions for us.
Participate at Orangelawandtrady.com
I would think with the new-
I'm a Digimon fan anyway.
I would think with the new stories we've had this week
You all have some things to say, so participate at Orangelawandtrady.com
Why did you just make crossed fingers at Dark Soccer
when she said she liked Digimon
You don't even know Pokemon anymore
I know Pokemon a hell of a lot more than I know Digimon
Did you ever watch any of the Japanese Digimon?
No, definitely not
Digimon Zero 2 is like the best anime in the universe
I'm just going to say this
This guy I dated once
This is years before Alan obviously
This guy I dated once had me watch the Digimon movie
I thought you said Disgaea
Needless to say it didn't work out
No no no no
We have to have you
Whomp whomp whomp
You need to watch it in Japanese
It's actually a true story
But anyway
I am disappointed Rob, my heart is break
I'm just giving you shit
Although that is a true story
But that wasn't the reason
I won't go into the reasons here on this show
Because I'm classy
Let's get into the FUs of the week
Speaking of classy
It's time for us to say fuck you
To things that are pissing us off
Why do we do this on a video game talk show?
It's called tradition, deal with it
Dark soccer
This one is private
I'm leaving it at that
I actually know I have another one
Fuck you to my grandmother's doctor
Who thinks that people give a shit that he used to play
For the University of Alabama football team
And isn't actually taking care of her needs
So fuck you
With a sandpapery giant three foot dildo
Ouch
Uh, Jason
You wanna follow that?
No
I don't wanna come anywhere close to that
Uh
FU to highway construction
Oh god
Oh yeah
Oh you had to come through highway 50 to get here didn't you
Yup
Oh you poor bastard
You didn't warn me
That's my drive home from work every day
I forgot
It wasn't that bad
The good news is you don't have to go through it all the way back
Eh, I got more traffic in Berkeley
Shocking me on the way out here than that
Whatever, minor driver
I'm enjoying my time in San Francisco
Thank you France
Low key
I'm not a big fan of cyclists
And I'm really not a big fan of cyclists racing
And the fact that you know
They're shutting down Folsom
At least most of Folsom
For a fucking bike race
Yes we could have done this on the weekend
But no fuck you guys we're gonna do it on a Monday
And we're gonna shut down most of you know
The part that people actually drive through
Oh and it's gonna be during business hours
Wait they're shutting down Folsom on Monday?
Yeah they're shutting down like a good section
Of like Folsom Boulevard and stuff like that
So it's just like
I fucking hate you guys
So much
And now you know it's now they're doing it
Thankfully I don't
I'm not going to work right now so it's not a big deal
I just don't drive through Folsom that day
But you know it's still fucking annoying
I have to see if that's gonna impact my work tomorrow
I was just about to give an FU to the fact
I have to be up and in work early tomorrow
But now I'm worried about this
Stupid thing that Low key's talking about
Well it's just in like old Folsom
So I don't think it is
As long as it doesn't stretch out to
Rancho Cordova
Alright
Then in that case
My FU of the week would go to
I don't know I guess things have been
Mostly well this week
I've actually had a pretty good week all things considered
So my FU of the week would go to
Just the fact that
The year is going by so fast
Where did it go?
I know it's May 11th
It's crazy
Alright
FU to the fact that frappy hour is over
It's actually probably a good thing
Those things are a lot of calories
Alright that's it for the FU of the week
Just a couple more stories for you guys
And then we're going to open up the phones
At 1877 Game OLR
Our username on skype
Orange Lounge Radio
But a few more stories for you guys
I saw this news and I kind of giggled
Because I was like
Damn
But yes Elder Scrolls Online has been delayed
On consoles
Six months later
So uh
That's gotta suck
Considering that I don't think that MMO's
Done too well as far as like people being
Impressed by it or anything
The fact that now the
Console versions aren't coming out until
November or December
That's gotta hurt
Especially now that they're coming out instead of a dead period
Of releases it's
In the middle of the fucking 4th quarter
When no one's going to give a shit about your fucking game
That can have positives and negatives
Because it could come up on Christmas lists
And so forth
But Bethesda probably would have another game coming out
And it's either going to be maybe like
Doom 4 or a new Fallout game
So who's going to give a fuck about an Elder Scrolls Online game
Eh we'll see
I don't know
Unless it's Dishonored 2 maybe
I agree that the reception of uh
Prey 2 finally
I agree the reception of Elder Scrolls Online
Hasn't been the greatest
I know we're really into it but
It does seem like the other MMO's out there
Kind of eclipse it like nobody's really
Going after Elder Scrolls the hardest
People are playing it because WoW's boring right now
Or because WildStar's not out yet
You know I kind of fear for Elder Scrolls
Once everything else kind of gets up and going
But we'll see
It's not like there's not going to be
New MMO's coming out
Like there's going to be this game that's coming out from
I don't know just some no name company
Named Bungie that's
You know Destiny and
Oh I'm sure that game will affect the
Sales of that at all
Dungeon Buster in chat says
Delayed hopefully to fix all the broken
Stuff that should have been fixed in the beta
Welcome to the wide wonderful world of
Online games where they never work
To be fair though
It is an Elder Scrolls title so
A vast majority of bugs
Are to be expected usually with hilarious
Results but you know it is an MMO
Correct yeah and an MMO though
Things are different it's one thing to screw up your world
It's one thing to another to screw up everybody else's
Anyhow
Some news on Disney
Infinity which yes Disney
Infinity there of course there's the new ones
Coming out and it is a success
How much of a success?
Well Disney Interactive's decision
Had revenues increase 38%
During the second quarter
This means they have an operating income
Of 14 million this compared to a
54 million lost last
Year this business grew quote
Driven by the strength of Disney Infinity
And there's also growth in Japanese
Mobile markets
Unfortunately this isn't
All good news because they also
Had to cut 26% of the staff
And a 50% reduction in game
Development so they didn't just get
Those numbers at the strength of the game
Because they're not developing any other games other than
Disney Infinity yeah that's kind of the
Well I think that there's some mobile
Stuff too but yeah it's not quite
What it used to be so yeah Disney
Infinity sales over 3
Million starter packs and an
Estimated 500 million in global retail
Sales to date Disney
Infinity 2.0 this
September of course with the Marvel characters
Well yeah and then here's the other thing too
That Disney's doing why they
Probably laid off people is that
They are now outsourcing
Their games to be developed
You know for their movie titles
So like for example
They're not developing
Disney planes the sequel game
That's coming out the Disney planes 2
Or whatever Majesco's doing that now
Or I
Want to say like Tangled had like a
Third party doing that one
Harmonix is doing that Disney
Fantasia eventually
Someday yeah
I wish it was sooner than later but
Things happen
So well I mean
I'm glad to hear you know I'd like to
Hear about profitability in the gaming industry
Although I'm a little sad it
Came at the loss of jobs but
Hopefully it will lead to
Job creation in a year or two
So that would be some good news
Speaking of good news I
Can't think of a better thing to end
The show on than talk about
Free games right Dark Sakura? Yep
Plants vs Zombies is free on Origin this month
Go get it Well that's good
And bad news Bad
You have to get Origin good
Brains I don't know it wasn't so bad
I got it for the Titanfall thing
And you know it hasn't eaten my computer live
So whatever The good news about
All that despite all the shit we've given Origin
Over the years it has gotten
Better you know it's still
Kind of I don't think you really need it but
It's not quite the pain in the
Ass it used to be so
I'll pick up free games on it I'm not gonna
Buy games on it but I'll pick up
Free games Well actually I got
Dead Space for free on there too
I got Dead Space a long ass time ago for free
They've been giving away
They've been trying to entice people to come to Origin
By giving away free games in their catalog
So hey I'm not gonna complain
I got Populous for free too
I have quite the library there
Free games that they put out every now and then
I haven't played any of them but hey
What else is new? Steam
See but then you get that client on your desktop
And then good old games
Come out of nowhere and says hey we've got
Covert action available for five bucks
You know that Sid Myers game that you're like the only
Person on the planet that likes it Rob
So I had to buy it
I had to buy it it's covert action
You guys awesome
And I don't know
Maybe I'll end up getting Titanfall
Too cause I kinda want it
But I'm trying to hold out for a sale
Trying really hard
We'll see Just wait
I'm trying Loki I'm trying
It's difficult
Alright that is it for our
Stories tonight but we are
Gonna go to the phones
The Skype line is open
1877 game OLR or a username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio if you wanna give us a call to talk about
Anything we've talked about tonight
Or possibly something else
Maybe there's a story we didn't hit that you wanna talk about
Go ahead and give us a call right now
While we wait for some calls to come in
With a delay I'll ask Loki if there's any
Last minute stories and I'm gonna bring up our
Twitter at twitter.com slash OLR
Well real quickly we talked about a really
Expensive HD NES
Console that was supposed to be coming out
Yes
So now they're finally selling it
It's $500
And it will up- $599
US dollars
$599 US dollars
And it will up scale games to 1080p
Your old
Nintendo classics in 1080p
Of course you have to buy
Controllers if you don't have controllers
And it's
One solid piece of aluminum but
Fuck that
I don't need it to up scale that
And I think if you even
If you bought an NES and bought an
Upscaler it would probably be way
Cheaper than buying this thing so
I don't know
Some people
And just as reliable as it was back in the day
Do I have to blow in the cartridges to get them to work
For that authentic feel
Yeah actually you would probably
It's those cartridges still
Going to our Twitter
Twitter.com slash OLR
Some interesting tweets coming in
SSG100Matt sends a tweet
This is sure to be polarizing
But I'm going to read it
SSG100Matt sends a tweet that says
According to a study and survey
This is from Reason.com
More gamers politically align themselves with libertarian
I'm not super
Even though that's not where I personally necessarily go
I'm not super surprised to hear that
Could that potentially be because
Whenever we talk about these politics
About violent video games
They're trying to ban them
Does it drive people away from the two parties
That everybody talks about most of all
Well the two party system is shit anyway
So maybe people are actually just getting smart
You think?
Although I am actually turning my interest
Toward the after party
That's real
That's basically what's evolved out of the Occupy movement
Interesting
As long as it's not
A pee party
Anyway
Let's go to the phones
We do have a call coming in
Hi you're on Orange Lawns Radio who's this?
It's the one and only Ronma
How is everybody in the studio tonight?
It would just not be Orange Lawns Radio without Ronma calling in
What's up buddy? We're doing great
We had a great interview tonight
And Jason's here, it's a full house tonight
We have 25 devices on the internet
It's great
Well there's 5 more devices I have wired up right now
Not much, couple of quick things
Number 1, I meant to mention last week
Where you were talking about that
Waffle place in New York City that we took you to
Yes
It was called Waffle and Dingles I believe
I think that's the name of it but the place is so good
So good, still there?
Yes, yes it is
So there's a possibility
I will be in New York very soon
We're going for Poutine
Gee I wonder what announcement this is related to
Because we may also go a weekend without a show
Potentially yes
I will know next week
Stay tuned
Rob you don't have to worry about not doing a show
I have a small studio here
We will jury rig something
We'll do an
OLR Unauthorized or something
There you go
Yeah there's a lot of interesting things that could be coming up
I don't want to say too much
But I will know for sure in 7 days
You can call it Marmalade Radio
Because it's Orange Jam
Tune in for next week's show
I'll definitely tune in for next week
The second thing
Not gaming related
Something I meant to ask you
I don't remember if I did
How do you feel knowing
That there's going to be Dunkin Donuts
In your neighborhood and if it's already there
Have you been there yet?
I'm so fucking excited I'm shaking and crying and screaming and convulsing
I'm just like
You guys don't understand
I know the rest of the US probably looks at me and goes
It's just Dunkin Donuts
Fucking shut up
Live in California and have no Dunkin Donuts
People even ask me
Where do you get donuts if you don't have Dunkin Donuts?
And I go
That's a great question
I want to see Tim Hortons
Yes
But for the record the grocery store and there's lots of mom and pop stores
There's no Winchells anymore
There's Winchells in LA
One Krispy Kreme
Actually I've found four Krispy Kremes in town
In the area
There's a couple in Roseville and one in Atomas
Everybody finally got off Atkins
But anyway
As far as Dunkin Donuts goes
There is one in California now
And I haven't been there yet
Because it's in Barstow
Barstow is between Los Angeles and Las Vegas
Known as Death Valley
Um
Yeah
So I'm not going there to get a coffee
However it is coming to
Our neck of the woods
I think they said 2015
So I think we're going to start seeing them next year
Which I'm excited
Their coffee is so flipping good
I have a reason I don't care
So terrible for you
I am not going to care because I can't
So you still need me to ship you
A few batches of coffee
I would love that
Yeah however we can get the K cups
But I'm going to be honest the K cups are not
Even as good as the real thing
We also can get the bags of coffee
Yeah I think there's better K cups out there
I thought it was really horrible when they had like apple
Whatever flavored fucking coffee
I was like what the hell were they eating but the coconut was really good
It does not compare to
That drink that they give you
That's like a little bit of coffee and then
Creamer and sugar
Amazing
Anyway
I guess you could bring the discussion on our video game show
To food but you know what donuts
Are a great
Great snack to game too
Not healthy but
Unless you're me you sit there and you
Make a batch of popcorn and you sit there and you
Eat it while you're playing Kingdom Hearts 1.5
Remix
Yeah something like that I'll usually play
Final Fantasy 14
And sob quietly to myself
Into my bowl of potato chips
But you know
Alright anything else you want to talk about tonight
Last thing I'm getting out of here
So yesterday I picked up my
Glorious Playstation 3 from the shop
And the guy told me that
It's working
I had it burn in for about 4 hours
So you're good to go
But I recommend getting a new one cause this one's going to
Die on you, may die on you soon
He pretty much told me don't use it for
Streaming of anything
Play a couple of games on it
Movies but don't use it
As a streaming device
He's like get an Apple TV and I'm like
What?
Was there a reasoning behind that?
Well
I took my PS3 in the first time because
When I was watching my Ronlef Blu-rays
It would lock up after about 10 minutes
And then
It would not read Blu-rays
Now it's working fine. The guy told me
I brought it in just in time before it started to
To yellow light out
He pretty much said he had to disassemble it
Clean all the thermal paste off
Put fresh thermal paste on it, reassemble it
And get it up and running
Wow
He said that the Playstation 3's were never designed for streaming
And I'm like
I've been streaming on this device for maybe about
2-3 years and I haven't had an issue with it
Maybe you should just flip it upside down
Like we used to do with the Playstation 2's
I fixed everything
We used to put them on their side
With my PS1
That's what I did
When this first started acting up I flipped it
Horizontal, vertical
I'm like, okay, let's see if it works
Still nothing
I always thought mine was going to be full of cat hair
Because it was like super hot
Heat coming out of that thing
And I took it apart and it was actually completely clean
If that Playstation 3 gets hot enough
Perfect for grilling chicken
Mmm, if I ever had one
It knows
And I remember
When you get the PS2's
Don't use it for playing DVD's
The drive was not designed for normal DVD's
Spinning, I'm like, well, let me go out and drop
50 bucks on a DVD player, you know
We used ours for years
Most of America used theirs for DVD players
That's why that thing sold so well
I don't understand how a DVD drive isn't used
For DVD's
You know how it is, somebody says something
And everybody follows along with it
But I think it was more of a heat issue
Because when I moved it to this new place
My PS3 sits on a little platform
Under the table
It's getting intercooler
I mean, my friend had a friend who had an uncle
Who told me that, you know, they buried
ET in the desert in the middle of New Mexico
So
And lo and behold
Alright, Rama, I gotta let you go to get more calls
But thanks so much for the call, buddy
Uh oh
Internet connection problem
We're losing Rama anyway
So thanks for calling, Rama
If you hear this and your internet didn't cut out
Boy, that was weird
Oddly timed
Alright, we're still connected
It looks like
So I'm hoping we're not having those same issues that we were having earlier
Rama's problem
Northeast problems
Oh look, and Rama just left IRC
So that's, well, there you go
He had to make an exit
He was just like, I'm out of here, bye
He was all, fuck it, pull the cord
Yeah, he just said, fuck it, and pulled the plug
But we do have another call coming in
Hey, one man's loss is another man's gain
Let's get to it, hi, we're just launching
Who is it?
Hey, you're lucky
That Rama just pulled the plug out of anger
Or something
What's up, buddy?
Well, I could talk about
A lot of stuff that happened
During the week and especially on Twitter
But I want to talk about
Team Fortress 2
Don't know why
Can we talk about Kirby Triple Deluxe
And you're gonna have to come up here and kick her butt
And by kick her butt, meaning give her a hug
And go out for Mexican food together
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Dark Sakura hates Kirby Triple Deluxe?
Not really
I haven't played it yet
It was a joke earlier in the show
Yeah, me neither
FedEx screwed up my order
It pretty much got lost
And I have to wait until Wednesday
To report it back to Amazon
And say it got lost
I'm kind of sad
I would be playing
I would be talking right now about Kirby
I am surprised you are not over there right now
Beating down the door
Showing your anger
It's very reserved of you
Anyway, I'm sorry
That's not what you called in to talk about
What did you want to talk about?
You want to talk about Team Fortress 2?
Yeah, basically
I got back into Team Fortress 2
After months of not playing
And still the game is pretty much the same
It hasn't changed that much
At least from what I've noticed
Aside from new hats
And some new stuff for the weapons
But
I don't know
I found a new enjoyment on it again
And pretty much
Where I'm going
Is if you have
Played a game recently
Or maybe not recently
But
That's a reason
That you haven't played
For many months or many years
Before
I actually do have an answer to this
But you guys are going to roll your eyes so hard
You can see your fucking brain
But it's my honest to god answer
And that is because I had the new computer
And all the new graphics and everything
The one game I had to go back and see
Was Mass Effect 3 multiplayer
And play that again
I totally did do that this week too
It was so sexy
The graphics were about the same
Because Mass Effect 3 was only set for a certain bench level of graphics
And I wasn't using HD textures or anything
So not to be all Jamie about my gaming week
But I definitely played some Mass Effect 3 multiplayer
And that was a sexy thing to revisit
I'm trying to think
Because I've had the new computer
There's been other things I've been revisiting too
Getting to go back and play
Some of the games I've had
Diablo and stuff was pretty cool too
But what about you guys?
Is there a game?
You've played for the first time in a very long time
You just kind of went back and revisited
It wasn't a long time
But I've had the conversation a couple times
About comparing Titanfall on the 360
Versus the Xbox One
And they're not terribly different
I think more of the differences that I see
Are the fact that I sit closer to the TV
At work than I do at home
And I think it may have those
120, 240 hertz features on
And not on game mode
Flat 60, etc.
I played
I don't know if this actually counts
But I did download Jetmoto 2
Onto my PSP
Not Vita
The other day
I bought it a while back
Graphically I don't remember anything
But not having all of the shoulder buttons
Completely fucks that game up
Because the R1, L1, and R2, L2
Do very distinct things
I really wish they'd bring that game series back
Jetmoto?
I saw what they did with 3 though
I played Fairy Solitaire
Fairy Solitaire?
Can't get it old school
I was bored
So I played Fairy Solitaire
Especially when you have some of those free games
I played Portal 2 not that long ago
And that was the first time since probably the game came out
It was kind of fun to relive that one
I should just give you my Portal 2 shirt that I don't wear
Cool, free clothes
I played
While I was restocking my 360
I downloaded and played Discs of Tron
That didn't look any different
My 360 hasn't been hooked up for like 6 months
I had so many downloadable games it was disgusting
So I should plug that in and play some of that old school stuff
I did have the Tron
They released that
The arcade Tron
4 minigames
The Overworld is a game
Although it's not
I can travel in 4 directions
Hey in the 80's that was modern stuff
Well there you go Act Deaf
There's some of our walks down memory lane
Yeah those are pretty cool games
Especially like Portal
It's a game I usually try to play at least a few times a year
Even I played Portal the first one a few weeks ago
I did a stream on it too
Good times
When these companies give away games for free
Even though they might be a few years old
They're always worth picking up
Let's say Plants vs Zombies being given away free
Right now on Origin
As long as you're cool and have an Origin on your computer
Most of you probably already have it
I would say go grab it while it's free
Because maybe you haven't played Plants vs Zombies
Since it was first out on the
IOS or Android devices
Or when it was first out on Xbox 360
It might be a whole different experience on PC
Definitely worth picking up
Especially if you don't have it
Because it's a really great game
Absolutely
I already have it on Steam
Act Deaf I'm going to let you go so we can get a couple more calls
Thank you very much for the call
Good question trip down memory lane
Hey thanks for having me
And I hope you get your copy of Kirby already
I can't have Kirby's number one fan here on OLR
Being robbed of his Kirby
It's not cool
It's sad
Oh FedEx we're coming after them too if they don't get it worked out
Alright
Take care
1877 Game OLR or username on Skype
OrangeLoungeRadio
We can probably squeeze in one more call if someone can get in here pretty quick
DarkTetsuya sends us a note that Fistful of Potions
Was taping from a comic shop during free comic book day
That was last week
But yes I read that one last week
That was during the
Wait did you?
If they tweet during the show I usually get to it
Jason if you let me do my segment
I'm just kidding
Well we are being invited to Concord Ontario
Being a Catholic school board trustee
What the hell is that?
We get all these random ass tweets that are like
Oh I went to church and I saw the
OLR and I'm like what the fuck is this
I've been trying to figure out who they are
I don't know who OLR is
It's a church I just don't remember what it was
I remember seeing that one time
Probably Ontario something
That's fine
But it just cracks me up
Because I'll see these random tweets
It's like somebody tweeting god dammit
I heard you talking shit about me on air
That was an actual tweet from Gemet this week
Or hey read only memories
Is on Steam Greenlight
Like Reddertainment tweeted us which is true
And then it'll be like oh the worship this Sunday
Was so good
It's Our Lady of Rosary Church
In Union City
Thank you
It's like my story that I've told
My coworker who has the Twitter name Dice
And he retweets
Everybody who bitches at him
For Battlefield
There's one it's www.OLR.net
And then
OLRSD.org
For the San Diego one
I think it's just a church there
Who owns OLR.com
Online residential New York source for real estate
Listings
I looked into that some time ago
But you know whatever
Anyway
Moving on to another tweet
Again this is the last chance to get called in
Or to call in 1877 game OLR
username on Skype
Orange Lounge Radio
I see some people talking about civilization in chat
Which ties into the interview we had earlier
And it just kind of makes me laugh
Because Civ is that game you can go back and revisit once in a while
But it's going to be a very long while
All night long
And it's going to look exactly the same
And play exactly the same
As long as you have the time to spend on it
With Civ they have the expansions and everything
I kind of hope
I have a funny feeling
When Christopher Tin was on the show earlier
Talking about that song of his
It might be for that new Civ game
Is that the impression you got?
Because that's the impression I got
I didn't
I was leaning towards some new title
I was going to make a tongue in cheek
Joke about Civ 6
Civ 5.5, Civ Next DLC
Well there's the whole don't call it alpha centari
Civilization game that's on its way
Not my world
That was going to be my
Tongue in cheek joke
I would kind of expect it to be a new game personally
A different company at least
I was surprised
It was next week because I would have thought
E3, but now is the time of year
Where all the companies are getting a jump on E3
To say here's the games to get excited
About E3
As big as some other companies
Right, yeah I know about that one
Or even just need to shove some of the news out of the way
Before what they're going to announce there
All these companies that weren't cool enough to get in the door
Anyway, going to another tweet
From 13X forever
Or cross forever, 13 forever
Who tweets us and says
Did you know that Kiro Blaster
A new game from Pixel from Cave Story fame
Is available right now
And tweets us a link to playism-games.com
I did not know that, but you have educated me
I've checked that out because
Pixel games, like all the
That stuff was great
With Cave Story and all that
So, excited
Hooray hooray
Unfortunately, Shane's not in the room right now
But I had to read this tweet from Andy Scout
Who tweeted at us saying
I can't trust game recommendations from someone who doesn't like
Ni No Kuni
Me neither, Andy, me neither
Alright, I guess that's it for tweets
How about any other last minute stories?
No
Well, I guess that means we're out of here
Because the phone is not ringing
So I'm going to go ahead and close that on up
And we're well past 9 o'clock anyway
I want to thank you guys for staying up late with us tonight
Really appreciate it
What a great show, thank you guys all for being a part of it
If you like what you heard here at Orange L'Antrado
Please, all we ask, tell a friend or two
About the show, help spread the word
Of the show, that's all we've got
Is word of mouth
We really appreciate a nice review
On a website where you found this show
Those reviews go a long, long way in helping us be visible
So please, help us out
Really appreciate it
Jason, I want to thank you for being here
Absolutely
I know we didn't get to talk as much tonight
Because I didn't get to budget you any stories
And we had another guest on tonight
Who, you know, with all due respect, Jason, you didn't win a Grammy
That's a tough act to follow
Maybe next year
I give him all of the accolations and lauds I possibly can
But it's a pleasure to have you here
And come back again sometime
You said you might be here next week?
Make a weekend of Scandia next week
And I can stick around here for the weekend
Then we can hear that schmexy voice of yours all over again next week
It'll be fun
I'll be here
We'll give you some stories
I can be here
It's like Jason the sequel
That'd make it sound like a Friday the 13th movie
Wasn't it?
The funny slash sad thing
That may turn out to be more accurate
Not the Jason movie part
You're going to be here for months and months again?
It's fucking possible
Oh boy
Keep that fourth chair nice and warm for Jason
Alright
Moving on, DarkSakura
Thanks for being here
As you always are
You're welcome
Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
I really want a burrito
A burrito?
I may go to Adelbertos
Do you want to get me a burrito?
I'm going in the opposite direction
I'm going that way, far away
Well, poop
Well, if you eat a big enough burrito
Jason, I didn't properly give you a chance to give your final thought
Did you have a final thought?
No, actually
I really don't
I have literally nothing left in my mind right now
Besides maybe telling your dryer to hurry up
Hey, it's got a timer on it
It'll tell you when it's done
Alright, my final thought
I love the fact too that you are literally on your last clean thing you own
It's a radio show
He can wear whatever he wants
But he's got pajama pants with little chilis on them right now
It's hilarious
This was a very explicit plan
I have more than a week's worth of pants
But I like having all of them just in case for some reason
I don't get a chance to do laundry
Because doubling up
Yeah, pajama life
Exactly, that's alright
It's radio, they don't look at us
The audience is lucky I'm wearing any pants at all
But you know
We're lucky you're wearing pants at all
I do that out of respect to you guys who come here in the studio
But trust me, the minute you guys leave
I did
Sorry, Jason
I did say as soon as I walked in here
That lounge has gotten more appropriate
Because we're not all crammed around a dining room table
And we're actually spread out
What do you think of Studio N7?
It's fucking open, there's space to move
And not have to shift and get out of people's way and contort
Most families would have a dining room
Well you do have a dining room, it's literally right there
You remember what we did with our dining room
Pinball
We called it Pinball Alley
I'm just saying, wouldn't a baby Pac-Man machine fit right here?
Just saying
Wouldn't it be great?
I'm gonna turn into Dark Sakura's house
Get a table, I have a freaking bar top cabinet that could go right there
Where's that in my video capture card?
You know, I thought about it before I came here
And I thought about it after I came here
And I was like, oh, forgot it
I'm messing with you
N7 is wonderful, that is my final thought
Alright, fantastic
My final thought tonight is
It is really stupid to drink a cup of coffee
At 8 o'clock in the evening
When you realize, oh yeah, I have to go to bed early tonight
Cause I gotta be up at 6.30 in the morning
That's not true, you have awesome dreams
When you're caffeinated
And they're weird
That's a good way of looking at it
Alright, last but not least, Loki, your final thought tonight
My final thought is I hate my fucking touchpad
For some reason it keeps clicking the right button
Even though I'm not touching the right button at all
It's really annoying
And it's just some stupid
Aces gesture garbage
Which I disabled, but it's still doing it
You have a rough life
Yeah, and I'm trying to figure out
How to fucking do texture atlases correctly
Cause I don't want to buy this one program to do it
And it's just a pain in the ass
Alright, well that's gonna do it for another week
At Orange Lounge Radio
Thanks to Christopher Tin for being here
Thanks to all of you for listening
Those of you that were here live and on the podcast
And Stitcher and all that good stuff
Thank you very much, we'll be back to do it all again next week
Happy Mother's Day once again
To all you guys out there
Have a great week, we'll see you next time
We've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio
Is a production of OLR Studios
To join us for a live show
Tune into vognetwork.com
Sunday nights
At 6pm Pacific
9pm Eastern
The views and opinions expressed in this program
Do not necessarily reflect those
Of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio
Or VOG Network
But you know they were all still true
See you next week
Thanks for watching!