Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Repeat after me, I will not believe everything I read on the internet
Nintendo hardware, Smash Brothers rosters, the time to fake is high before E3
But could a relationship between EA and Comcast per video games on your cable box be true?
Find out this week on the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio
Live on this May the 4th of 2014
With the 551st episode of our show
And yes, let me get it out of the way right now
May the 4th be with you, blah-di-blah-di-blah
But, for me, as a fan of Arrested Development
Maybe not as hardcore as some other people I know
I would say it's actually Happy Cinco de Cuatro
And yes, I know it's totally wrong Spanish
If you see Arrested Development, you kn-
Ah, forget it
Alright, anyway, my name is Rob Roberts
And I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about video games, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
With my co-host, sadly not here tonight, DarkSakura
She has the night off tonight
But we do have here in studio, Loki
Hi
Hey, Loki, how you doing?
Doing okay
Hi
Good, good to hear
What's new with you?
Not much, just looking at pictures of Legos
Pictures of Legos? Why, are you planning on investing a bunch of money on Legos or something?
No, just ideas
I see
Have you ever fiddled around with that program that allows you to build your own things offline
And then order the exact right Legos to make the thing?
No, I'd be afraid of how expensive it is
I mean, I just, yeah, it's gonna be expensive
We actually have a local Legos shop over here
That they sell cut, you know, pieces and whatever
So I haven't really gone in there because once again I'm afraid of how expensive it is
It's an expensive hobby from what I understand, so
There you go, good luck
And I noticed to the show tonight you brought your very own pizza
But you got your pizza well done
Yeah, I always do
Why is that?
I don't know, I like it well done
Fair enough
Alright, well since we don't have Dark Soccer here tonight
We do have another friend of the show here in studio to fill in and help host tonight
It's always good to see him and we might be seeing him a lot more often in the coming weeks
Say hello everybody to Shane
Hello
Shane Olinko here with us tonight, how you doing?
I'm good
Yeah?
Yes
So you live here now?
I do
You do, you're back in Northern California, welcome back
Thank you
And so we might be seeing more of you on OLR in the coming weeks?
Depends on if I'm awake or not
How's your rock and roll lifestyle going?
Do you sleep all day and party all night or what?
Yeah, partying is trying to catch Pokemon all night till like 5 in the morning, yeah
Well how was the experience in Northern California?
You came here from Kansas, for the listeners that didn't know
And you've been on the show on and off literally over
Like a decade
All the whole years, yeah
I think I first met you, my god, when you were like 19 years old I think
And it was when I was living with Loki, when we had that first, like, episode numbers less than 100
Was it 19?
No
I think so
No it was because we did episode 69 from the apartment
Yeah, no, Shane was only like 19
Oh I was 19, I thought you said you were 19
Oh god no, no I was 24 when the show started, actually technically 23
Cause the show started like 3 days longer
Yeah it was probably like 19
Yeah, so crazy stuff
So you're back from Kansas, and how does Northern California compare to Kansas?
It's better
In what ways?
Name one and I'll agree
The weather
Yes, it was 100 today, where I'm from back there, and they had humidity which makes it like 743
And let's see, how about the arcade scene, the games
Well there's not really one here either
We can go to Golfland and have some sadness
Oh my friend has his own DDR machines
I hear it's not so bad anymore because it's like one of the local Bimani enthusiasts actually runs a lot of that
See, when
Scandia had Pump It Up, so I was happy about that
They also have the new Beat Media 2DX
Okay I don't get that because when we went there, Shane and I went there when he was visiting like a couple months ago
None of that
Yeah it wasn't there a couple months ago
Shane we gotta take a trip
We can go play Spada
That's what it is
Alright, I want to say hi to our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
We are at The Voice of Geeks Network, and we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Blackwell show at The Voice of Geeks Network
www.vognetwork.com
Alan Alchemy in our chat room says, Shane likes California better because Del Taco
Yeah, it's actually pretty good
Okay, true story you guys, true story
First off, the first part of the true story
Shane, as long as I've known him, has been like addicted to Taco Bell
Like he's eaten a lot of Taco Bell
A lot
Why do you like Taco Bell of all places?
I don't know
I really don't
I've had Jim Boys
I've not had Jim Boys
What a convincing answer
But their breakfast is really good at Taco Bell now
So I have to vouch for that
Again, I've known you since you were 19, and to put things into perspective you're 30 now
So I've known you a long time
And in that entire time, I've always said when you come to visit California, I'm like we should go to Del Taco
You like Taco Bell, you're gonna like Del Taco
It's a very California thing, it's even better
And you're like, no, Del Taco sucks, Del Taco's stupid
I'm like, oh, he must have had it once and he never liked it
Well come to find out, I just found out this past week
You never had Del Taco, so you wouldn't have had it
Nope
And you were like, oh, this is so good
Yes, except for their french fries
Which, one, you're a Mexican restaurant, you shouldn't have french fries
You're stupid
Two, refer back to one
And three, they were way too salty
There might have been some french fries under that salt somewhere, but I couldn't find them
People are gonna think we're on their payroll
Their french fries are terrible
I think they're good, but people are gonna think we're on their payroll, we're not
And they have a hamburger, what the crap
I'm not gonna eat your hamburger
No more free advertising
Now the bacon double del is pretty good though
No more free advertising, they want more advertising, they don't have to pay for it
Alright
I haven't been there in like
There's one right by
There's one, not to give away where I live
But I mean, there's a few Del Tacos in Sac
I'm just gonna say, there's one like right near us
So it's like, probably less than a mile
So it's painfully addicting
I haven't been there since the first studio
Oh wow, that was a long time ago
Yeah, so like, you know
Alright
Also, I wanted to say, cause some people are asking
Like, where was Jason in the intro? Is Jason gone?
No, Jason's not gone, gone
He's just gone for the week
Jason's traveling right now, so he had to drive a lot today
And we actually do all the shows production on Sunday
Like I do the show roll on Sunday
Because we want to make sure we get as much news as possible
And sometimes still there's breaking news during the show
So he wasn't able to do the production schedule today
So that was my voice in the intro
And doing the passphrase this week
But Jason will be back
I think next week, but he's on a road trip
So I just didn't want everybody to go like
Oh my god, is Jason gone? No, he's still around
He's still helping with the YouTube
Which by the way, if you haven't checked out our YouTube channel
Jason does archive all of our episodes on YouTube
And you might be like, well, why would I want to watch something on YouTube?
Because it's really convenient
Like, you can do YouTube on your 3DS
You can do YouTube on all of the consoles
Sometimes it's a little more convenient than the MP3 files
And we want people to be able to listen to the show
As easily as possible
So if you want to listen to Orange Dance Radio on your 3DS
You can do that via YouTube
The only catch is that it is delayed by one week
The reason why we do that
We want to draw people to our site
To get the viewers and the numbers and all that
Yes, I'm fully opening and admitting it is kind of a trick
To actually retain our listenership
Because we don't want to lose everything to YouTube
But YouTube is an option
For especially the archive stuff
And Jason works very hard on that
So we thank him for all that
And yeah, DarkTitsUya says he just saw that
Episode 550 went up on YouTube
It sure did, it sure did
So that was Jason that did that
He also likes to sync
When we're talking about the Classic Game of the Week
He'll actually put the video of the Classic Game of the Week
He does little things like that too
For those that are actually watching
So as I mentioned, remember on Twitter
I saw this thing about that they're going to be
Marathoning all the episodes of The Simpsons
And 552 episodes of The Simpsons
So we have
Recorded, including the E3 specials
Because they don't really number those
More episodes than there are of The Simpsons
That's scary
Well that's because most TV shows only do
Hey, hey, hey, don't belittle what we're doing here
No, no, no, no
We've been doing this way too freaking long
But I mean, most
TV shows only do
What, 22 to 26
Episodes in a year? If that
I mean a lot of them are only like 12
But you think of a show like 24 is a great example
24 is coming back
They're having a shorter run this year with 12 episodes
But usually 24 was 24 episodes
Right? One for each hour
So most shows do that, but we
Produce something like
At least in a year
It varies depending on how many weeks
We have off in the year, because obviously if you do one every week
You get 52, but real life happens
We don't always have one every week, so we do about 46
Or so a year, so it's pretty
Pretty crazy, a lot of hardworking
Podcasters out there crank that out
There's probably, I know
Some that were on a daily basis
Got even more than that
That is dedication, folks
That do the daily shows, that is a lot
So, alright
Anyhow
I want to get to the gaming news
And our kickoff topic and our gaming weeks and everything
But I do want to kind of address
This in our kickoff topic tonight, because E3
Is right around the corner
We're getting to be about one
Month from E3, a little over a month
From E3, no word as of
Yet if VOG Network will be represented
At E3 yet, we
Put in our request about two and a half weeks
And still haven't heard back, so Bobby
And I are getting a little nervous, because we don't know
Where to do a hotel or any of that if we do get in
But we're hopeful
But regardless of that
Situation, E3 is happening
In about five weeks
And all the big gaming news
A lot of it's being sat on until then
You're going to see some of it trickle out
As people want to get the jump on E3
And people want to build the E3 hype
You saw Nintendo do some of that this week
We're going to get into that in the news
But speaking of Nintendo, a lot of lies
Start to come out around this time
About what companies are going to show
And one of the big ones that's been gaining a lot
Of steam out there is
Nintendo is going to release new hardware
At E3
Well, in a statement to website
Computerandvideogames.com
Nintendo came out, and this was posted on Friday
Nintendo came out and said, not happening
Okay, they basically said
Reps told this
CVG site on Friday
This reveal is not under consideration
So that's on record
They are not revealing new hardware at E3
Now, I don't know if that necessarily means
It's not a new console
Or anything like that
Because I still kind of go
It would not be outside of the realm of all possibility
For them to do another DS
Type of remake
I'm not necessarily saying
Like a new, like a 4DS
Or, I mean, right
Or a DS that has new powers
But I would think maybe like
What about like a reconfigured 2DS
That would not be outside the realm of all possibility
To me
But it's like them putting out something
To trump Wii U or whatever
Not happening
That's reverse
Fanboy wank
Yeah, I don't even see them redesigning the Wii U
Because you don't really need to make that
Console smaller, I mean, it's pretty small as it is
And maybe tweaking
The gamepad or something
But I just don't see them doing really
And why would you want to do that anyways
With everything out there
I think it would be, I mean, for Nintendo
To put out a new Wii U this soon
I mean, they can tweak the Wii U
The Game Boy Micro Micro
They can tweak the Wii U they have
I mean, I wouldn't think it's outside the realm
Of possibility that they somehow figure a way
To make the technology cheaper
Maybe they reduce the size of the gamepad
I don't know, I mean, again
Or increase the storage space or something
They reconfigure the Wii U that's out there
For like a Wii U
I don't even know what they'd call it
Super Wii U or Wii U 2
I don't even know what you would call this thing
Wii U Lite, Wii U
I don't know, yeah, just Wii U New
Or something, whatever they call it
I mean, they could slightly reconfigure it
But they're not going to throw everything out
Where none of the games are going to be playable anymore
We know Mario Kart 8, they're hedging a lot on that
And the new Smash Brothers
You know, I just
I don't know why people believe
That this is really going to be true
I don't know if the rumor is that they're saying
They're launching a system that's called the Fusion
That's going to play all these 3DS games
And stuff like that
Well, I don't think it's outside the realm of possibility
That Nintendo is going to look to marry
Their handheld console
And their home console
I don't think that's
Like, outside the realm of what is possible
And you see them moving closer and closer
To that with, what, the GBA games
You can play now on your
Wii U, right?
And you even said a long time ago
They're going to do DS or 3DS games on Wii U
And then they did, they're going to do DS games on Wii U
Yeah, it's going to happen
And I even think they're going to do it with the 3DS
Because they don't really care about 3D too much in those games
And they have the right aspect ratios
With your TV and your gamepad
To where you could do it
I mean, they say they can't emulate it
But, come on
They have emulators on PC that can run 3DS stuff
So, I don't buy that
Here's my other question
Why do people feel the need to lie about this shit
Going into E3?
Because they want hits
Because they want, you know, people
Some people get off on tricking people
And some people just want, you know
Page hits or something
Well, I mean, as far as page hits goes
I've seen some real cheap ass stunts for pages
Like, just even this week, on Twitter
There was a site that, and I'm not going to name the site
Because I'm not going to contribute to their
Cheap grab for hits
I didn't look to see if they ever apologized for it
But there was a website that a lot of World of Warcraft
Players kind of visited a lot
Because I think their roots were kind of in that
Or whatever, I see a lot of people in that community
That I follow because of Horde House
This site ran an article that was like
The top 15
Sexy girls wearing
Sexy girls holding controllers
Was the article
And it was literally like one of those
You click one for each picture
And it's just, it's sexy girls holding controllers
And sometimes provocatively
Sometimes wearing not so much clothing
Or whatever
It was just, it was a really gross way to try to like
Get hits, because a lot of these pictures
That were put up were from like charity
Events and so forth
And you know, it wasn't
It wasn't a super diverse
Group of women either
It's just, you know
It kind of reinforces certain
Stereotypes that I don't think are good
For gaming, so obviously
This is a really stupid thing that they did
That's the types of stuff that you see people do
For cheap hits
I mean, Buzzfeed has made an industry out of this
Right?
And sharing stuff on Facebook
Like, we could do more of that
On VOG if we wanted to, but there's just
There's certain lines I'm not gonna cross
You know what I mean?
So, that's that
Fifth dream in chat
Over at live.vognetwork.com says
Those sites seem to finally be dying
I don't know about that
Unfortunately, you know
It got a lot of people talking about it
And people checked out the article out of curiosity
I wouldn't be surprised at all if they didn't
But it just, I don't know, it really kind of
It irks me to know that
You know, E3 is looking for
Websites of a certain volume
And that's all they're looking for is a traffic volume
And they use these really archaic methods
Of measuring that traffic
That's what they're looking at to see who is media
And who's not for their site
And knowing that somebody is going to reach
These folks by putting pictures
That they don't even own in the first place
I mean, other debate aside
Of whether the pictures are appropriate or not
They don't even own these pictures in the first place
Of 15 sexy women with controllers
Like, knowing that that's how you do it
I don't know, this is kind of gross to me
Like, and it's like
I'm not willing to go there
Just to feel
Special
In going to the show or whatever
Like, I am proud of the work that we do here at
And the
The commitment
That all of us, myself, Loki, DarkSakra
Have to it and having done it
For weeks and weeks and weeks and so forth
Like, I'm not going to stoop to those kind of levels
To meet these archaic
Qualification things
If it doesn't work out, it doesn't work out, fine
I won't get to tell you stories from E3
We won't get to do the interactive stuff
You can be spoon fed the same press release crap
That every other site is going to be running, whatever
But, you know, anyway
Sorry about that
Anyhow
Shane, you've been awfully quiet
Why do you think people
Want to lie about E3 stories?
Why do people lie about this stuff?
Because they want
Hits for their crappy sites
They just hide behind that
It's not always crappy websites
Yeah, it is
And a lot of times
They may be just trying to
Not even say educate guesses
But just try to take guesses about things
And that way if they're right, they can say
Hey look, we said that first
And that's supposed to give you some sort of credit
Oh yeah, the next call of duty
Is going to be on the Golden Gate Bridge, you guys
Now I'll just pull that out of my ass
And take a gamble
See what happens, right?
Yeah
Is that?
Anyway
I had to, I'm sorry
I know that's a sensitive subject, but I had to
Alright, anyhow
It's water under the bridge now
You know, you thought the usual suspects
Would be reporting on this news, but it is what it is
Alright, anyway
Let's get into our gaming weeks
The types of video games that we have been playing this week
And then we'll get into some more gaming news
I'll start with Shane
Dark Soccer's not here tonight, she usually goes first
But Shane, you're our guest
What types of video games have you been playing this week?
I've been playing, and I'm currently playing
A lot of Pokemon
I am trying to complete my
Pokedex
That I've been technically working on for years now
I am 12
Pokemon short of the 718
needed
And I
Have been playing it way too much
Way, way, way, way, way, way, way
Too much
Now, why do you have to collect all
718 Pokemon?
Because the theme song said so
Way back in the day
And you gotta
You can't go against that
And B, you get this item
That makes it so you can find
Shinies easier
And that is what I want to do
And what does shiny Pokemon do?
They look shiny
They look different
What does shiny Pikachu look like?
Dark or yellow
That's it?
I get blue
And that is enough for me to want that
You make a big
It's not just you, but the Pokemon fandom in general
Makes this big stinking deal out of these shinies
And that's it. They look slightly different
That's it. Yep.
They used to have better stats back in the day
When they were first introduced
And now, no, it's just
That one might be slightly differently colored
Or sometimes they look really different because of their color
I was doing a livestream the other night
On Twitch of Final Fantasy 14
And this person was in the living room with me
And he was playing Pokemon
And he caught a shiny while I was on the stream
I was so happy
And he took over the stream with Pokemon talk
He's literally walking up to the camera
You told me to do it!
Because I wanted to know what the big freaking deal was
Because you're sitting over there going
I got a shiny!
And it was uglier
It's like some Pokemon look a lot better as shinies
But this one did not
It looked like somebody threw it in an oven
And took it out
Oh my god. What shiny did you get?
Swirlix
I don't even know what that is
It's the cotton candy Pokemon
Sounds like laundry detergent
So you are a Pokemon nerd
Of the highest caliber
Yes, I really am
You're 30 and playing Pokemon
Which is fine
I know a lot of folks that play Pokemon
But why after all these years are you still addicted to it?
It's still a fun game
It's a little bit like gameplay structure
That works every generation
Now it looks better on the 3DS
So I'm not going to give it up
It's fun to collect them all
Or frustrating
It's both of those F words
Alright
Anything else?
I played Final Fantasy 14
Skylanders
I'm a little bit infamous
And that's it
What have you been doing in Final Fantasy 14?
Playing Leviathan
Over and over
And that's the new fight
They patched in about 3 weeks ago
No, we're almost to 3 months
Is this the Leviathan patch really?
Holy crap
2.2 was Leviathan
2.3 is coming out in June
2.2 came out in April
End of March
Oh my gosh
Wow
Time flies
So I've been doing that
And getting my items from there
I want my water donkey
And some things to upgrade my items
That's it
Alright
We'll come back to Skylanders in a little bit
But we'll go over to Loki first
How was your gaming week?
I played nothing
Nothing?
What's up?
I've been coding
Oh that's right
Oh I've been putting stuff up on YouTube
Every now and then
Because I get bored of just looking at code
And I wanted to see some actual progress
So I'll take breaks from stuff
I was working on
I'm using this program
Called Cubicle
Which does voxels
To do the graphics
So I made some test stuff
It's hard looking at a box
And a box firing more boxes
Than another box
I wanted it to look like something
So I was just messing around
Learning the program a little bit
I made a ship
Just a really stupid looking missile
But I have video of it
Firing the missiles
Into big ol' volley
So you haven't been disconnected
From video gaming all together
It's just that you are right now obsessed
With this making your own game
I'm absolutely obsessed with it
That's what I've been spending all my time on
I was trying to play some Call of Duty this week
But unfortunately I missed
The people I play with
By a few minutes
Baby took longer to
Rock the sleep than
They normally did
So they didn't see me on
So they just said oh we're gonna call it
And I was like ahhhh I missed you
I checked a few minutes late
Unfortunately it didn't sync up there
So that's what I've been working on
And I actually got in touch with
Because my music that I've been
Picking and stuff I have no budget
So I have to pick free music
And that involves
A lot of Creative Commons songs
And so I've been spending
A lot of hours searching for Creative Commons
Work and I actually found
One that's gonna work perfectly for
The theme song
For the whole game
But the problem was it had some anime
Samples in there so I got in touch with the artist
Who actually is a huge fan of Shmups
And like that type of thing and he actually
Wants to score Shmups and stuff
So I'm like hey
Is there any way that you can make me a version of that
Song without the stuff in there? He's like
Yeah hell yeah! So I'm like
Sweet so that was the big
Exciting news today. I was gonna say you should put a call
You never know we might have listeners out there who are
Kinda musically like they might be
Amateur music just like your amateur
It's hard because I actually had someone
Hit me up on Twitter and I don't even think that they
Like knew anything they just was doing
Like a general search for like people
Making games or something
Just like some of that music just didn't work
It was like a lot of hip hop stuff
And it's hard to say like what
Exactly I'm looking for because it's basically
I have to listen to the song and if I can imagine
Like okay this is gonna
It just has the right feel to it
Didn't you try to say like pendulum meets
Daft Punk meets or anything? No that's not even
That and actually you know it's funny because I was looking
For you know that kind of
Pendulum drum
Drum and bass stuff and I actually found a lot of it
Just recently
It's actually I think it's another genre
Of drum step so it's a cross between
Drum and bass and dubstep they have a lot of that
So I did find a lot of that stuff
It's just a lot of it
This creative common stuff
Especially the electronic music and
Even there's a ton of dubstep for
One and two like
All the dance songs sound
Very similar like they use
Almost the same it's not like the same
Instrument but the way that they
Are structured is just like
Oh my god I'm just like listening to the same
Fucking song for 50 times
It's just ridiculous but that
Yeah it's what I've been working on is just that I've been
I'm trying to get to
Well I'm at a point now where I need to start making some
Of the assets because
You know try not to explain too much
About the game because I wanted to you know
I'm still working out stuff but
Basically it's like if you
Crossed a shmup with
Borderlands so you've got you know
It's a 2D shmup but your
Ships are customizable in every
Way so you can customize what weapons
Are on it the way it looks and all that stuff
And each thing has different features and
Stuff so you can literally play this game like
You can't almost any other shmup
You can play it like
In Igaruga or you can play it like Gradius
Or you can play it like whatever and so it's kind of catering
It towards you know however you want
Now I know that sounds absolutely complicated Bobby's always
Saying you know don't do something complicated
But you know what fucking simple games
Are fucking boring to me so
I'm going to do something complicated and you know what
It's actually worked out fine I've had no problems figuring out
How to code anything it's just it takes
A lot of time and just like right now
It's interesting to me too to hear about
All this little shit that goes into games that
Sometimes people forget like like the soundtrack
You might want to make a game and you
Might want to but you might not know the first thing
You have no budget that's hard because
You got it you know otherwise you're going to
Find free music that people want to have in
You know they use their music and then
On top of that like if you want to have a big soundtrack
You got to pay someone to make that music
Or you have to pay artists to do that kind of stuff
Alright you know Bobby is talking
About this in our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Live on this Sunday night Bobby
Says Loki is being Peter Molyneux
Right now you will be able to plant a tree on the
Ship and it will grow and Dungeon
Buster says will the ship have a dog
The ship is
Not going to have a dog and no
I hate to be compared to Peter Molyneux
But no seriously
That's what I'm you know I have set up
That's what I've been building is just this customization
Through where you can
Well I'm trying to do all the framework and then when I'm done
I can basically okay create a model
And put stats on it and that's it that's all I have to do
Is create models and stats
And be done with it
So that's why I'm trying to do all the coding
First but I'm getting to the point now where I need
I have where it creates
The ship from the parts and I don't have
Parts yet I just have this like stand in
Ship model and a bunch of blank stuff
And so I'm running into
Errors because it can't find these
Generic parts so I need to create a set of generic
Parts first so I can do more testing on that
And then finish what I'm coding
So I'm taking breaks now to
You know well last night like I was like
I'm too tired to actually code on stuff I'm just gonna listen
To some music so I listen to
About 200 Creative Commons tracks
And so I've been picking out
Stuff and just
You know like okay this works because
Creative Commons you know what was it
CC by is basically
All you have to do is attribute
The artist and you can use it in a
Commercial product you don't have to pay
Them you don't have to do anything they just that's it
There's not a lot of that out there and you have to
Also know where to look and it's hard like
I
It's a lot of searching and a lot of it's
Just like ugh
Maybe there's some artists out there who might
Want to help so hit Loki up on Twitter
Sure I mean in the mean time like I said
I'm gonna post stuff on my YouTube page
And I'm posting stuff on
You know Twitter
And like I'm not going into really any details
Like I know what the title of the game is but I'm not
Gonna say and I'm not gonna go into really
More details about anything else cause
I just
I don't want it like I just feel like I'll
Jinx it if I do that yeah so
I like hearing how you're
It helps too because you
Sometimes are a big critic of video games
So having to feel the pain of making one a little bit
I think it's gonna be very good for you well there's a lot of stuff like you know
It's like I made a save file
I'm like holy crap I made a save file
It's amazing you know it's like
It's like stupid
It doesn't even do anything right now
Other than yeah okay what's it saving
I don't know well it's saving nothing right now
It's a bunch of blank you know data but
You know it's made a save file
It's a save file it's so amazing
Going to the chat room
Bob Blackwolf is saying to be fair Loki
Who did give up multiple times already
But he says in parenthesis I'm actually
Really proud of Loki I just don't want to admit it because
Then I'd be a softy
I was working on a complete different game
And I'll even tell you what it was cause
Unfortunately it was you know it got
Lost when my computer crashed last time
I was working on another like F-Zero
Racer type game I was like what should my first
Game be I don't know I'll make a game that someone else
Wants to play okay Rob likes F-Zero okay I'm gonna
Get an F-Zero game so
I was gonna make an F-Zero game
That wasn't quite F-Zero but you know whatever
And funny enough actually I was looking at some stuff
The other day G1
No someone actually first off someone made a game that has
The title that I was originally gonna call it
And then there was another person that made another game that
Looks exactly like the game I was gonna
Make I was like ah well whatever you know
I started over and this was the concept that I'm
Doing now was actually one I had
Like about four or five different things I was throwing around
And at first it was like okay
This is gonna be way too hard I'm not gonna be able to do this
So I gave up on it went to the F-Zero thing
And then when I lost it all I'm like well crap
I don't even remember how I got on to doing a 2D
Shmoop again but um
Somehow I got on to doing that and then
That's where I stuck with it and so
It's been fun it's just
It's a lot of work and a lot of like
I have to be in the right mindset to be able to
Code stuff cause like you know I'll stay
Up late I'll be really tired you know
A lot of Red Bull so uh
It's just getting in the right mindset
And I wish I had more to show
It's just you know right now it looks very plain
Alright well good luck to you
We'll be looking for updates in the coming weeks
And now we'll understand why you're not playing as many
Of other people's games so good luck
Um alright let me uh
Talk about my gaming week cause I've played a variety
A variety of new games this week actually
Um I played and Shane
Brought this up earlier so I'll get right into this
I played Skylanders for the first time
I had never played these games before
And it was kinda like Shane with Del Taco
As we were talking about earlier in the show
I was kinda like I don't like Skylanders
And I haven't played it I just know I don't like it
Because uh you know they want to sell you all these figures
It's a cash grab and da da da da da
So Shane set it up for me and he's like
I don't own too many Skylanders
I don't
And he dumps 16 of them out on the table
That's 16 across 3 games
Were any of them Spyro?
No
Care about Spyro
Neither does Skylanders
So yeah so I played Skylanders which specifically
I played the new one that's on Playstation 4
So Skylanders Swap Force right which is the third game
On the Playstation 4 so you and I played that
And there's actually we caught
The whole thing on a livestream and I even put it up on my
Youtube channel at Rob Roberts Plays
If you want to see like us playing it for the first time
I gotta admit it was a pretty good
Looking game like you know it's on
Playstation 4 so the graphics were good and there's like
These scenes
Which is why I specifically got it on PS4
There's these scenes where you're like racing down
A tree branch and around that looks like
Something out of like a Sonic game or something
It actually looks really good
And the quality of that's pretty good
It's geared towards kids so you get a lot of loud colors
Cartoony vibe, big text, short
Sentences, things like that, the game is really
Geared towards kids
The gameplay itself is very platformy
Like you know
Somebody had called it Diablo
Asked to me but that's
I think the earlier games are more like that
Probably
It wasn't so platformy back then
It reminded me like a lot of like
A kiddie version of
Gauntlet which is fine cause that
Like you smash pots
To find gold and you use the gold
To upgrade your characters you know
It's pretty basic platforming stuff
And you know as a basic platformer
It works pretty well you know Shane and I
There were some neat little co-op games in it like to unlock doors
You go through these little puzzles
Where you try to join the green box
And the blue box but you want to collect
Little bolts on the way like it's a little puzzle thing
And they're fun to play co-op so
Yeah it's a fun little platformer
I will admit overall I liked
Skylanders more than I thought I would
That being said
It is completely obvious
There's a huge cash grab
Going on here
Especially with the in-game advertisements
Yeah tell us about this Shane
Tell us about the in-game advertisements
So to get like the final power for each character
There's these soul gems and they're littered throughout the levels
You go and collect one and
It'll be one for some random character
And like the one we saw was for Popthorn
Well I don't have Popthorn
Thankfully they let you preview
A video of Popthorn so you can see what
You're missing out on
Mommy mommy mommy
So that's kind of dumb but
Yeah and
There's these little gates in the levels
And some of them will be like fire doors
So you have to have a fire guy to get through the door
Or you'll have an ice leaf door
Where you have to have one ice guy
And one leaf guy or cause it's swap force
You have an ice top and a leaf bottom
Or whatever you have to be both elements
To get through that door
Here's the thing though and this is very important
It's not like those rooms
Lead to full fledged levels
They really don't
It's like one room
But the thing is that room's gonna have
What? More coins
Maybe a hat which is their version of armor
Basically that changes your stats
If you want to really collect them all
So to speak you're gonna have to have one
Skylander of each element
Now thanks to swap force
Not only are there elements
But there's powers
Oh and don't forget the giant boxes too
Oh yeah and the giants
You only need one giant
So now you have to have a
Fire railroad or whatever
You have to get a railroad guy
What the hell else was there?
There's stealth, there's the tornado ones
And you were giving me such crap
For not being able to go to so many places
I was cause I was like why can't we go through that door
You're like I don't have the figure
You don't have the right figure
No you were missing a lot of them
Yeah because I do not buy all of them
I buy the ones I like
And that's not always a whole bunch
So if you're the type that's OCD
And has to complete everything
Do yourself a favor
Stay the fuck away from Skylanders
Stay the fuck away because
It's gonna drive your OCD bonkers
Yeah cause they already announced what was in the new game
It has 60 new characters to collect
Collect
Like it's in Pokemon
Yeah 60 new characters
Each character is about 10 bucks
So that's $600 worth of characters
Right there
And I bet the trap team
The bigger ones are gonna be more expensive
And then 40 new enemies
To capture which means
I'm sure that each one of those gems
Maybe you're gonna only be able to store
One enemy per gem or something
And maybe they'll be cheap and be like $5 each
That's how they get you
That all being said
As far as like a platforming experience
I actually had a decent time
I would go so far as to say
I might buy the game for myself
If I can find a deal on it
That's what I do like
I didn't buy Swap Force when it first came out
I waited until it was like
On sale for 35 bucks
Which is 40 off the original price
But I'm gonna repeat to myself over and over and over
I don't have to open every door
Only buy the ones you think that are cool
And then you can always go back
Cause the figures work up through the series
So if you have an old figure
You can always bring it into the new game
Find an old figure
Remember we were at that place you hate yesterday
And they had like the triple packs
They had ones that were on sale for like
10 bucks so that was 3 characters
From an older game that you could use in the new one
For 10 bucks
But they don't level up power wise up to the same as the newer characters
That's true but who
Like I think that falls along the same lines
With the people that collect all of them
I like that little air bird I was playing as
I know that was one of the newer characters
I just need him
Yeah free ranger
It just depends
Having played Disney Infinity is just as bad
They do advertise the same thing
And a lot of times you have to have a full set of characters
In order to be able to unlock
Like stupid things
Oh yeah and the blind packs are fucking terrible
I bought a lot of those
But yeah it was
It was not worth it
But the blind pack thing is not so bad
Those are really only for the toy box stuff
And you don't really need them
Now let me say this
The one thing I didn't say about Skylanders
Is the figures themselves
I have to admit
I'm going to call something out when it's bad
But I'm going to call something out when it's good
And I've got to admit
Those figures like the 12 year old boy and me
Really love the figures that light up
When you put them on the portal
They're more expensive
Well whatever they're cool
When you put them on the thing
Like the one guy with his little jewel
The prism
Is that it?
His little arms light up and I was like
That's fucking cool
That's fucking magic man
I was like that's cool
And do they change the portal
The only time you're going to see it light up
Is when you're playing the game
The prism dude
The only time you see him
Is when he's on the portal right
When it lights up
Or is there other ways to get him to light up
Not when you're playing the game
No no that's the only way
But it's also like those light core ones
In the game they light up more than the regular ones
Like you could get a regular one
And a light core one
And the light core one will play slightly differently
Because it's a light core one
Which is neat
So the bottom line on Skylanders for me
Is it's not awful
It's not even bad
It's a decent platformer
It's a fine platformer
But know what you're getting into with this crap
And don't feel OCD about it
And realize that there really isn't that much
Behind all those doors
And there's a great resale market too
Yeah I mean can you tell the story about that one figure
Yeah I have one that I
Picked up while I was working one time
And I knew that it was rare
It's just an ugly variant of a figure
It's not painted right
It's stoned
It looks like granite
And that's a legit
Variant that they put out in packs sometimes
And that thing
Can sell up to according to what I saw
$750 unopened
Which is how I have it
Yeah that's because of those OCD people
Like oh I've got to get every single variant
Like your ex right?
Yeah exactly
And he didn't get that one
There's like one that they did
For the holidays for Activision
Blizzard employees too
I mean I thought it looked pretty cool
And I know that one sells for a lot also
And that was the only way you could get it was if you were an employee at that party
And Bobby says he got one at E3
That apparently is an early good seller too
So yeah
Alright so anyway there you go
That's Skylanders
Not as horrible as some people think
But yes it's a cheap cash grab
Be very careful
Just wait for your kids
I'm really surprised they have it
Well there was the
Rumble blast
That wasn't done
They didn't execute that well at all
No
The figures were like
An inch tall
They were really crappy figures
I don't know what the hell they were thinking
They didn't do it right
If they were to do it right
I'm trying to get 718
In a stupid game right now
It's so futile they release a new game every year
And then it's just you know you have more
Pokemon you gotta you know
Yeah but at least now they have that bank feature
In this game where I can put all these guys into
The Pokemon bank and when the new game comes out
I can bring them back in so I never have to
Find them again
Hope that save doesn't corrupt
Oh don't say that
They all go to the cloud
All my Pokemon are in the cloud
As long as the cloud doesn't burst
Or you get hacked
Chinese or Russian hackers take all your Pokemon
They took my Pokemon
I would declare war on that over country
Alright
Other games I played this week
I played a demo for a game called Child of Light
That's brand new
I did that one too I forgot about that one
You played it? I did the demo
You turned it off after like 5 minutes
I liked it I actually liked it quite a bit
The thing I liked about it a lot
Is that it did a lot of
Different stuff I don't see in RPGs
Very often like you know a lot of RPGs
Kind of the same
Same thing over and over
But Child of Light did some really neat stuff where
The right stick controls this
Extra little monster that can float around
The battle, well I say monster but it's really an ally
But this extra little fairy or whatever
They can float around the battlefield and like
Freeze monsters or
Heal your people
I thought that was like a really neat mechanic
It was a really stupidly simple thing but
I can't think of another RPG I've seen that in
Which I really liked that
Yeah that was neat but
The gameplay like the actual
Combat system I thought was crap
Well it's very basic RPG
You know either you like it or you don't
They really should have just made it a platforming game
Everything else about the game was great I can't deny that
It's a really gorgeous game Music is great
Music is great and
Everything rhymes which is interesting
Just a little way to do it but
Yeah and that's cool but
It's a decent combat system if you're gonna do that
See now here's what I disagree with
Actdeft in chat says
Child of Light reminds me of Bravely Default but better
And by better I mean could
Wow
I do not think Child of Light was better than Bravely Default at all
Bravely Default is amazing and Child of Light
Is a piece of crap
A really pretty sounding and pretty looking piece of crap
I did not think that rhymes
I didn't think it was a piece of crap at all but Bravely Default
Bravely Default on one hand was a very familiar game
Bravely Default had a very familiar sense about it
And it did do some new things within that
With the whole street passing and some of that stuff that Bravely Default does
Bravely Default
Bravely Default was like
Bravely Default was like going to see
A new Harry Potter movie
That comes out in the series
Like you know what you're gonna get
You've read the book already
It's kind of the standard stuff
Whereas Child of Light was different
It was more of an art house indie film
It's doing some new things
You don't necessarily know what to suspect
People respond differently to it
Shane hated it
Are we saying that Bravely Default would be like Labyrinth
Whereas Child of Light is like Pan's Labyrinth
But did you hate Pan's Labyrinth?
I didn't really care for it
It was very visually pretty
Ok then yes
That is actually a really good example
Labyrinth is my favorite movie of all time
Pan's Labyrinth
They're the people that like
Stupid Child of Light
And probably Ni No Kuni
So they're awful people
Whatever
So yeah Child of Light I played that
I did not actually get the full game yet
But I probably will to be honest
Other than that I've been playing a lot of the same stuff I talked about last week
Shane really enjoys watching me play NES Remix 2
It's over now though so I'm very sad
He says it's over because I beat all the
Well I didn't beat all the stages
I will not fucking play Wario's Woods
I will not
I tried with Wario's Woods
What the fuck is that game seriously?
And I like puzzlers
But Wario's Woods has got to be one of the worst
ones I've ever played
I would put that up there with Tetris on the Playstation
If you've ever played the Playstation port
PS1 port of Tetris
It's god awful
And I would put Wario's Woods up there with that
It's that bad
So I refuse to play those stages
Shane watched me get really frustrated
It was so funny
The Kirby stages
Were the worst to me
Where he had to float up and not get hit
By the spikey things
And it was like 20 minutes of him getting hit by the spikey things
And I was laughing so hard
It's a bummer you can't
Live stream that gameplay
And the whole internet could have had a lull at that
But it's so frustrating
Just remind me seriously
To bring my
Capture thing
I have a capture thing too
But it's delayed
Oh my god bring it over
And he can play that stage
Over and over again
What was another one that you sucked at?
There were a lot of them
ActDeft is screaming at me in chat
Wario's Woods is awesome
It's different but it's good
Now I'm talking about Kirby
I don't dislike Kirby though
I like Kirby
I dislike what they did in NES Remix 2
But no it was fun
I gotta say
Spoiler alert for NES Remix 2
I don't think this is a big deal
But the very last stage
In the second set of remixes
The very last stage is
You save the princess as the princess
Meaning you beat Bowser
In Mario Brothers 3
With Super Mario Brothers 2 princess
They showed them the trailer
Well then it's not that big of a spoiler
But you know where she does the floaty
And you can't get hit because if you get hit she dies
She's a one hit kill or whatever
She's a woman
Stop it, not cool
But the frog Mario thing
Was the same way
You get hit one hit and they die
But anyway with the princess you get hit once
And she dies
But what's really funny is that when you beat it
She goes through the door
And gets to the castle
And it's the princess meets the princess
Sorry but you are in another castle
Or something like that
It changes the words
So that it's an old play on that joke
I'm sorry but our princess is in another castle
But then it's like sorry but you are in another castle
Ha ha ha just kidding
And then that's the end of the stage
You know what would have been a good remix
Is something to do with the part in Punch-Out
Where you're on the bike and your trainer is running after you
That could have been a fun stage
They didn't do enough with Punch-Out in that game
They didn't do enough with Punch-Out
I don't think there was a single remix stage that you just punched out
No I think it was like
You know one of the last remixes
Where it was like eight different stages
The lights went out
Silly
That would be funny to have Punch-Out where he's just
Punching other things in the air
Punch the
Well they did like Mario 2 is in there
So why couldn't they have put
Wart in there instead of King Hippo
So you'd have to punch Wart or something
That would have been cool
Punching the eggs from Birdo or something
Yeah
Or punching ducks from Duck Hunt
That would be hilarious
Go to our chat room
As soon as Shane cracked that joke
Rama's like no Jamie tonight
Where's Dark Soccer to smack him into place
No Jamie is off for the night
She wouldn't smack me
She would give me a look
And I would say I'm sorry
Made a huff yes
And then I've been like let's go play Final Fantasy 14
Alright
She might be listening be careful
No I just said my apologies
I know I know
He's not serious guys
Anyhow
I think that's really all I have for my gaming week
I mean otherwise Final Fantasy 14, Diablo 3
All the same stuff I always play
So yeah
I will give a cheap plug for my Twitch channel though
Because ever since I got my new computer
I've been doing a lot more with it
And your PS4 you've been doing a lot more with
And my PS4 yeah I've been streaming on both
Rob Roberts
Oh that's something that you should have said
When we were doing Skylanders you could not see chat
And I wonder if that's something to do with the game
I don't know
Yeah they updated because the Playstation update
Changed some things like the Share Factory is really cool
I gotta say
If you haven't checked out Share Factory
Check it out because it makes movie making really easy
That was a great move on Sony's part
To really get people to share more of their
Gameplay footage that's being saved
It's really a powerful little program
But they also upgraded the Twitch functionality
Now I don't like the new layout
Because they put chat on the side
So you could I guess see more of it
Instead of more than two lines
You could see a little more
But it word wraps
It doesn't word wrap at all really
And then in the bottom it's just elapsed time
I liked it better with the scrolling messages at the bottom
And the elapsed time
But you can get rid of those borders completely
And just have the camera
You couldn't do that before
So that's pretty cool
That's the one feature I would like to see
Because in Final Fantasy XIV I could put the camera
Over the chat box so that
The people in my free company
When I'm live streaming
They don't feel like they have to censor themselves
Because what's being said is broadcast on the internet
Or whatever so
Bobby Blackwolf in the chat says
I'm on Raw TV
On a new line
That's what it looks like when you're chatting on the
Twitch TV now
Quick housekeeping
I don't have a whole lot to add
I will say follow us on Twitter
Twitter.com slash O-L-R
Also Facebook, facebook.com slash
OrangeLoungeRadio and Google Plus
Google.com slash plus OrangeLoungeRadio
I do want to mention a few things with VOG Network
Again our show tapes live
The Voice of the Geeks Network
That's vognetwork.com
If you haven't checked out the new TV reviews section
TV reviews by Critical Myth
I really urge you guys to check it out
Because the crew over at that show
Critical Myth has been really diligently every week
Like they're pushing like 10 to 15
New reviews of TV shows to our site
It's like all this new content, it's great
And you can interact with it
And when you interact with it you might receive some
Loot and the loot helps you
Get raffle tickets
And the raffle tickets
We do have a raffle, the raffle's been on hiatus
For a few months just because you know we fund it
Completely out of pocket so
Sometimes we would rather
Pay to keep the site running than pay for a new raffle
But we do have a raffle this month and it is
I believe season 1 of Arrow
The new series on the CW on Blu-ray
So if you want to win that
You're curious to check it out, you want to win it
Or maybe you're a fan of Arrow and you just want to get it for free
Because you don't want to buy it because I don't think it's a cheap Blu-ray
Go enter the raffle
And you can get participation points at VOG Network
Just for listening to this program
Somewhere in the show you're going to hear
If you're listening live you can check in on the site
As the show is broadcasting live
But if you're listening on the podcast at some point during the show
You're going to hear that little doodle-a-doo
And then it will say to register participation
The pass phrase is and then you type in that phrase
You get your five points and that's five tickets into the raffle
Really cool stuff
And that's just a little something we give our
Fans and participators
Just to try and increase awareness of the site
And all the cool things that we have there
So check that out once again
vognetwork.com
Alright, do remember though
The raffle is opt-in
You have to go say
Yes, I want to enter the raffle
You are not entered automatically
So you're going to want to check that out at vognetwork.com
Slash raffle
You are not entered automatically
And I believe this particular contest is US residents only
I am so sorry to our overseas listeners
It's just that the cost of mailing
And all that, we can't do everything
But we do try once in a while to have something
Digital or something
That is much more lightweight
That we can send overseas
We have done some overseas
Unbelievable ones
So I just want to make sure you guys know
It's not that we don't like our overseas listeners
Because we love them very much
But the reality is the cost to include you guys
Is a lot more
So check that out, vognetwork.com
Slash raffle
Alright, now let's get into some gaming news
There's plenty of it
Despite the fact that we're only a few weeks away from E3
There's still lots coming
So Loki, start us off
Yes, if you thought that Comcast
Well, EA is looking to Comcast to sign a deal
That would make EA published games available on Comcast
This doesn't make it confusing enough
X1 television operating system
Yes, there's the X1 Comcast box
And the Xbox One
And both now play games
Wow, confusing
I guess they're saying that
The X1 is an HTML5 based streaming platform
And I guess it has
Now, I thought that was only a DVR
But I guess they're saying it's gonna have
Internet cloud support
Apps and that kind of stuff
But now you'll be able to stream
Games to it
The lineup so far is probably gonna include
A new FIFA, Madden, Monopoly
And Plants vs. Zombies
So not necessarily like
Battlefield 4 or anything like that
But more of kind of a
Not casual, but just kind of for everybody type stuff
Of course, they're still figuring out revenue share
And release date stuff
But yeah, so you'll be able to
Another platform you'll be able to stream games to
I just think, man, the name of that is just fucking
X1 and Xbox One
And now they both do games
I wonder if that will cause some legal ruffles
But it's Xfinity
I think Xfinity had the X1
Before the Xbox One
Wow, okay, that's gonna be interesting
Yeah, the newer Comcast boxes
Are pretty powerful little things
They're basically Apple TV type units
They're little computer things
They're really powerful
The old clunker we have
Was one of the first HD units
So that's what it does, but that's about it
And I think it does DVR too
But we don't pay for it
I think these do the room to room DVRs
And that kind of stuff
So they have all that functionality
But I wouldn't imagine
Oh yeah, the new ones do everything
I'm surprised
I don't think you're gonna find a Netflix app on this thing
Or anything like that
You might in the future
For money, yeah
What doesn't have Netflix nowadays?
Well, I would think though
Comcast, a pay-per-view content provider
Would probably be less likely to want to include
A service that you can get same content
No, Comcast and Netflix are playing nice nice now
Thanks to Net Neutrality being fucked over
Netflix is paying Comcast money
Which is bull, absolute bull
But what can we do right now
Besides petition our lawmakers
Which is what people are trying to do
And need to do a little more of
To push the importance of this issue
That we need Net Neutrality
Or this type of wheeling and dealing
We're gonna be the losers in it
And when you guys bitch about
It costs too much
Or Comcast sucks because they limit
And I can't do it
Then maybe you should have complained about it before
How long until we see someone streaming a game
To an Xbox One through an Xbox One
Well, if we are able to stream games at all anymore
That aren't, you know, Comcast approved
Who knows
Hey, that's why EA's getting into the ground floor of that, right?
Yeah
I guess
They know evil when they see it
So they're attracted to it
Both, of course, winners of the worst company in America
Yeah, right
A few times over
So, you know, they're in good company
Oh boy
So, alright, you know, I'm all for more games
Getting out there and everything
But this is just kind of one of those things where it's like
This is why I need Net Neutrality
Because I don't want this to be the only way to play games
That makes sense
So
Yeah, I
This is all still rumor status, though, right?
Although it's one of those things that seems very plausible
I don't think it's rumor status
I think that they're actually working on it
It's just, I don't think it's gonna be that big of a thing
It's just because they're gonna be streaming games
It doesn't mean a lot of people are gonna take advantage of it
Because I think people that are gonna play like, you know, Plants vs. Zombies or something
Aren't probably gonna do it through a cable box
They're probably gonna do it on a PC or tablet or whatever
I think it's just
It's more exposure to those games, I guess
And, you know, exposure's not terrible
It's just, you know, they have to weigh the cost and benefit, I guess
Going to our chat room over at live.vognetwork.com
Rama says, just what we need, a multimedia cable box, pass
Well, that's kind of already here, I think
But Rama also says
I think that was a joke
The X1 box was made by Motorola, which is now ARIS
That sounds like Yaris
Um, Loki, here's an FAQ
And links you to something there about more information
ARIS won survivor one year
No, this one's spelled A-R-R-I-S
Oh, okay
Alright
And let's see, Kaijuto says, Netflix sounds like they want to become a cable network
And not what people love about it
I don't know, I mean, I sort of saw the Netflix originals not really wanting to be their own network
Just so much as, you know, I always thought it was kind of a way to kind of compete with cable
I think that's, it's just, you know, why do I need to get Netflix
You know, save contents on TV
Well, it's because you can get this other stuff
You know, they want to, it's like, why do I want to subscribe to HBO
Because there's a show I want to watch on it
Or there's a couple shows I want to watch on it
It's not like a ton of
I want to see Game of Thrones boobies
You know, they have tons of movies on there
But they're trying to be like, you know, an HBO or Showtime
And yes, the way they can do that is more boobies, more skinimax
So that's what they need on Netflix
They do have the women in prison show
That's not entirely skinimax, but yeah, I understand what you're saying, but
Alright, well speaking of television and so forth
You know what, Netflix isn't the only one that wants to put their own programming out there
I think you guys remember, Xbox is getting into this
We talked at length last week about the whole, they dug up ET in the desert
That was all for an Xbox original
Xbox wants to do original television
Somewhere in between major game releases
They're talking about premium television experiences
And you know, they hired some big TV executives to kind of do all this stuff
And yeah, they want to do these Xbox originals
And things out of the Xbox entertainment studios to hold you over between major game releases
And see, that's another thing that they're trying to do
Like this, you know, they want to be an HBO or something
So that you would buy their system so you can watch this content
I just don't see that happening
By the way, they are going to be bringing to the Xbox originals
The Halo television series
Every Street United, which is an unscripted, so reality show
Series of eight 30 minute episodes and a one hour finale
It's soccer, soccer players
Bonnaroo, which is the music and arts festival
They're doing something with that
And then Signal to Noise, Atari Game Over
These are a film documentary series
And Atari Game Over is about the whole stuff in the ground
And then something called Humans
Which is produced with UK broadcaster Channel 4
And it's going to be an hour long eight episode series
So, hmm
So yeah, they're going to start cranking these out
By the way, they say that everything is fair game for these TV shows
Talking at a press event in San Francisco
The Vice President of Xbox Entertainment Studios, Jordan Levin
Said that games like Forza Motorsport, Fable, Gears of War
Not off the table when it comes to making TV shows
I thought you meant when you said everything is fair game
I was like, okay, so it's going to have Halo porn and Forza porn
No, if they really wanted to make money
Isn't Forza kind of car porn already?
Well, there are a lot of exhaust pipes you can do things with
What?
Gas tanks
I'm just giving them ideas
You have issues
For free, dang it
So are you guys going to be turning to your TV to watch
Or are you turning to your Xbox to watch TV shows pretty soon?
Let me go get an Xbox
Oh wait, no, I don't care for an Xbox
I think they're coming to 360 as well
I don't have a 360
Oh, you got rid of it?
Long time ago, I don't care about Xbox
We have to
Am I going to my Xbox to watch TV shows?
Maybe if my boxie dies
And then I'll watch Netflix on it
But I don't think
It's just like that Halo movie
The Ford on the Don and stuff
They're like, oh, Halo movie
But it looks like a sci-fi original movie
I'd be curious about this
I want to see the documentaries
Gaming documentaries might be really interesting
Especially this Atari one
Even though I gave my thoughts last week
About what's the biggest one
When it leaks out to YouTube or whatever
But you were just talking about piracy
I could do that with the TV shows today too
But that's not how you're supposed to do it, Logie
But I have a 360
I can get up to the TV and watch the Atari documentary
I'm sure they'll all be on Windows 8 too
Because they're trying to get people to buy Windows 8
Yeah, I know all about that
Let's move on with some more news
Shane, what do you have for us tonight?
Since I just said how big a fan of Microsoft I am
Let's talk about how they are committed
To making more interactive programs
You can't accurately finger quote when you're on the radio
Interactive programming
In the same vein as 1 vs 100
Like they did on the Xbox 360
What's her name?
This is ads
Nancy Tellum, the president of entertainment and digital media
Said that there is now infrastructure there
I think it was just Xbox One, right?
Every time I hear her name I think of Soulja Boy
Why?
Because it wasn't one of his songs like you tell him
Or something like that
Oh my god
I don't know
Please be seated
Shane
Anyway, I guess the infrastructure there for the 1 and the 360
It's there so they know now how to accurately make these style games
They're looking into not remaking 1 vs 100
But a game in the similar vein that you can get a lot of people together and have fun
I never got to play it
I don't know how much fun it was
I hear it was great
I loved it
That was like the best thing that ever happened on the 360
When they got rid of it I was so pissed
If they said 1 vs 100
And I know they're saying not that specifically
But if they said for whatever reason 1 vs 100
Is coming out to the Xbox One
And it's going to be out on such and such date
And here are the screenshots
I would go out and buy an Xbox One
I love the game that much
And that would push me over the edge
Because there's already things on Xbox One
I'm kind of like
I'm kind of on the edge
I know there's some of the stuff coming
But I'm not ready to put down the credit card just yet
But if 1 vs 100 was coming out
You know I would
Didn't they have a poker game that came out that flopped?
I don't think it flopped
It flopped with me
It flopped in terms of the same sort of buzz that 1 vs 100
I think it has its fans
I know there are people that play it
There's also fans of Ni No Kuni
But I don't think it's necessarily as huge as 1 vs 100 was
I love the idea of game shows
But I don't know what other game shows could they do
But then again when we first heard about 1 vs 100
It was like what are they going to do?
It's going to be a lot of miming stuff
So like Wheel of Fortune
So you have to like spin the wheel
Or Price is Right
And you go like this
Like you're spinning the big wheel
Price is Right would legit be a lot of fun actually
That would be a good one
Family Feud
That could be one
Survey says
Press your luck you just go like this
However many people said the answer
Don't they have like a live version of You Don't Know Jack
Yeah a long time ago they had with Paul Rubens
It was okay
Just go back to the old night
I always fucking bring this up on the show
Whenever we talk about 1 vs 100
This was the highlight in PC gaming for me
Was when Berkley Systems was around doing stuff like Acrophobia
Acrophobia I used to play the crap out of that
Just put Acrophobia on Xbox One
I would be happy
I don't think I'd play it now
I'd play it now
Especially if you could still have the After Dark Rooms
Where every acronym was just like
Fuck, Cunt, Cock
Like it's just every dirty word acronym you could think of
I miss the After Dark Rooms
And they had other games too
Like there was the one where you went up and down the tower
I don't know that one
Yeah there was other stuff too
So there's ideas out there
Just jack all the old Berkley Systems games
They can do it
Alright
Anyway
Let's move on
Loki what do you have
Let's go to another company
Alright
So
Nintendo
Of course
They're not doing the stage presentation like they did a couple years ago
They're going to be doing a livestream press event
Or a Nintendo Direct type thing
That's scheduled I guess to air on
Was it 9 AM Pacific Time 12 PM Eastern
On June 10th
And the Nintendo Treehouse will be
I guess conducting that
And they're also going to have livestream unscripted game demos
From their E3 booth during the show as well
And I hope to hell they're using multiple providers
And not just Ustream
Because that was the worst part of E3 last year
Was Ustream's Nintendo Direct was awful
I thought I did
Didn't they have YouTube as well
I think they did later
Yeah YouTube and then I think now they're using Twitch
Twitch can handle that crap
So they need to just use Twitch
YouTube I think they also do livestream YouTube at the same time
Well here's an idea
Let's check the press release
Because it might say if they're going to be doing
Twitch or whatever
No
It might be too early for those specifics
They did say though
One of the things that was kind of a little teaser video
Is that they're going to be doing this Super Smash Brothers thing
At Best Buy
Remember like last year you could test out stuff from Best Buy
You know play different games and things
For the Wii U
Well now they're going to be doing that with Smash Brothers U
Or Smash Brothers for the Wii U
At certain Best Buys
So you can check that out as well
And they go along with that
They're going to be hosting a tournament at E3 for Smash Brothers
So
I wonder how much of the final roster
Will get for Smash Brothers by E3
Because the 3DS one comes out this summer
Whenever that time period really is
So the rosters are supposed to be the same
So
I would imagine the final roster
Is out at E3
If the game is coming out in the summer
Final roster at E3 with maybe one or two surprises
Probably not hidden characters if there are any
Yeah
So
I think that's
That's what you expect at E3 I think
Interesting they're putting so much focus on Smash Brothers
It's their big game
Mario Kart 8 is out at that point
I'm wondering if Zelda is not coming out this year
Because of the lack of focus so far
Because of the fact that they pushed Smash Brothers to fall
I'm wondering if Zelda is coming out this year
Because they're expecting Smash Brothers to fall
I'm wondering if that was the original
I'm wondering if they were expecting
Smash Brothers to be released in the summer
And have Zelda for quarter 4
I don't think
Zelda was ever going to be this year
Or do you think maybe because those are
Two separate genres that they might not really care
They could still release both because they did that
With Wind Waker and the new Mario
I think Zelda's
Holiday 2015 people
I think you guys are being way too optimistic
About how fast they're going to crank that out
Zelda's Holiday 2015
I'm sure they'll put out Bayonetta 2
I was going to say
That's the other big thing they've been talking about
That's not going to sell systems I'm sorry
It won't
I love the game but I would not buy a Wii U
For that game
But will you buy the game if you already have a Wii U?
No
Well I bet a lot of people disagree with you and will
I'll buy it
And I think Nintendo needs to not just sell systems
They need to be able to sell games
And especially a game that wasn't
Necessarily made in house by Nintendo
I mean kinda, sorta
Well they also have their Dicey Warriors
Zelda game too that's supposed to be coming out
At some point, that'll probably be summer as well
I don't know, we'll see
But yeah, so
Invitational tournament that's going to run
From June 10th through 12th
During E3
Alright well we mentioned there
That before E3 happens Mario Kart 8
Will be happening and a big
Nintendo Direct came out this week that
Talked pretty much all about what we can
Expect with the launch including a $330
Wii U bundle that will
Come with Mario Kart 8
It will have the 32 gig
Black Wii U and a red
Wii U wheel and a Mario Wii remote plus
As we mentioned a little bit about
Earlier in the show
Here's the part that I don't think anybody was expecting
All copies of Mario
Kart 8, this is how big this game is
To Nintendo and they want to make sure it succeeds
No matter what they have to do
And this is huge
All copies of Mario Kart 8
Come with a free download code
For one of four Wii U
Games, if you register the game
On Club Nintendo before July 31st
Which anybody with an internet's gonna do
You're gonna get a code for a
Free copy of New Super Mario Brothers U
Wind Waker HD
Peekman 3
Or Wii Party U
Here's a pro tip
Don't pick Wii Party U
It's not a bad game
But like the
Box one comes with a little attachment
For your controller that makes it a lot more fun
To play
Well I think a lot of Nintendo fans I know
Already own the other three
Even I already own New Super Mario Brothers U
So I'm probably gonna do Wind Waker
Just because Peekman doesn't
I've never really been super interested in that game
Sorry I know some people are really into it
Even though
But in Europe by the way
They have more choices
I don't know why they got more but they did
Because in Europe you can get Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate
Nintendo Land, Wonderful 101
Sonic Lost World
Which would have been the one I would get if I could get it here
Mario and Sonic the Olympic Winter Games
And Game and Wario
All those extra ones in Europe
In addition to?
It's like ten choices in Europe
That was Game and Wario
It's a really decent game
But it won't last you very long
Like most WarioWare games
Multiplayer information coming out of the Direct
Twelve people can play at once
Voice chat will be available
Good job Nintendo
You did it!
Finally!
You can choose from four modes
Worldwide, Regional, Friends, and Tournament
Does that mean voice chat
Is going to be in the public matches?
I could have sworn
Hey Nintendo!
Like I watched that Direct
I thought the voice chat was really only for lobby stuff
I don't think it was for
When you're actually racing
It doesn't matter even if it's just lobby
Oh my gosh
I really hope you can mute people
Also some new items revealed
The Super Horn
And the Crazy Eight
Which will whirl eight different items that you unleash
Awesome, it's protection against blue shells
You're right
That is pretty cool
I think you could just make them as rare as they were in Mario Kart 64
Also
Last but not least
More characters announced
Baby Rosalina will be a character as well
And
Pink Gold Peach
What the fuck is a Pink Gold Peach?
I've heard of rose gold
Pink Gold Peach
I can't help
But I can't help but think of that scene
From Project Runway
Where she's like
I'm going to use this blood orange
And it cuts to the scene of the guy going
She's so pretentious, that blood orange
Shut up, it's fucking red
I can't help but think of that
When we talk about Pink Gold Peach
Which in reality
Pink Gold Peach is like
Metal Mario
But instead of metal peach, it's Pink Gold Peach
It's the heavyweight peach
It's terrible is what it is
All these baby characters
And all this metal Mario
Metal Mario is not a fucking character
It's a texture swap
It's not a fucking new character
Come on
Branch out a little bit
Yes, I understand it's called Mario Kart
But throw in a Zelda level
And have two Link or something like that
I was a little pissed there's no Birdo
It looks like Birdo got cut
Or Birdo
Fuck, there's a ton of different things
I would have much rather had Birdo than
Blood Orange Peach
They should have gone back and picked random enemies
Mouser would have been cool
I do love the fact
They put all the Koopa kids in there
But it makes it hard for me to pick between
Lemmy, Larry or Toad
What about a Goomba?
What about a Goomba, why not?
They have no arms
How are they supposed to drive?
They could use their feet but then what's pushing
The gas pedal
Is it two Goombas?
Nope, it's tank style
Despite all this crap we're giving it
I am so there and I am so playing
Wendy O Koopa
On fucking Toad's Highway
The day this thing comes out
Oh, and thank you
For mentioning Toad's Highway
Because I would like to say
While Nintendo has done all this fantastic shit
Making the game look awesome
And they brought back Battle Mode
What the fuck did they do to Battle Mode?
Hey guys, you know
We could totally take all these really kick ass
Battle Mode tracks that we had
But no, instead we're gonna take
Just the regular tracks
They're all fucking loops that they slightly tweaked
And that's what they are
That you play Battle Mode on a fucking track
Because god forbid
It would be so damn hard to
Bring Block Fortress in or something
I'm gonna take a wait and see approach
I'm not ready to get low key
No, it's just
They don't get it, they tried the same shit with
Like, what is it?
It was either Double Dash or
The 3DS one
We don't talk about Double Dash
Rama in chat says
Calling it now, DLC for older tracks
With all due respect Rama
I think everybody is calling that
This is such an obvious extension
There are some tracks I would pay for
Half the tracks in the game are older tracks
But that's not out of character
For a Mario Kart game
Besides, of course, the first one
Yeah, it's not out of character
It is out of character though
To completely ignore any regular
Battle Mode track for Battle Mode
That makes no sense
That's the DLC
That's stupid
Hey, we broke this on purpose
So that we can fix it with paid content
That's dumb
They said they needed more third party ideas
Make the model a fucking Battle Mode track
Calm down
Mario Kart 8 is gonna
Be the bomb and you know it
Stop it
Like two hours tops
To do all four of them
Have a seat
I also wanted to say
That means 30 characters playable
Also, you can play as your Mii
Which is all you're ever gonna see online, probably
I just really hope they change the Mii voices
Cause
Like the voices
Those Miis have is scary
Maybe they'll just have you
They should have you record
Only with friends
But
I fully
I still hope
Like they did with Mario Kart Wii
And I don't remember if they did with the 3DS version
But I hope they actually have your Miis in the background
Love this idea from Tigerclaw
And I think even Loki has to like this one
Tigerclaw says, what if they do
DLC tracks based on other games
You remember how Sonic Lost World
Had levels based on some classic Nintendo games
What if Nintendo made a deal and made
DLC tracks based on Sonic
So, what if somebody
Got your Sonic Mega All-Stars
Racing courses in my Mario Kart 8
No
How about a Bayonetta 2 course
Come on
Come on, Loki
What would that be? I mean, driving up the hair
No, you'd just basically drive into her vagina
That's a Bayonetta 2
I was trying to hint at that, but you know, whatever
That's fine
Just go for the direct approach
On a serious thought, you're driving around
These mountains that are just her boobs
On a serious note
What about like a Hyrule level
You laugh at that, but actually one time I did have a concept
For a kart racing game, and that was gonna be
You know, that was gonna be my level
Battle of Ariola Mountain
It's gonna be all bacon
And fucking giant breasts
Like, bounce on like those
You know, mushrooms and shit
What was the name of the game, Bacon and Boobs?
Oh, it was VoG Kart Racing, of course
Did you run that by Bobby?
No, I didn't, I don't really care
This was a long time ago
Ah, the ideas
I had for that
Alright, now what about like
A Hyrule level
Like, that would be rad
What did they just say a second ago?
Yeah, it'd be awesome if they had a Zelda level and
Finally, that was
Either here or there
Alright, moving on, Shane
We gotta keep it moving, we're like at an hour twenty
And we're not even halfway through the show
Okay, well
There are some Mega Man games headed to Virtual Console
Thanks to the votes of fans
Capcom posted a poll
Asking
When you want to see
Select Mega Man games show up on the Virtual Console
That poll is over
How'd Mega Man Legends 3 do?
It got first place
I'm glad that Capcom's listening to
User feedback now
But you know
Back when we wanted a new Mega Man game
Well, fuck you guys, we know better
That's awesome
Thanks, Capcom
Sorry, Shane
Anyway, so
The votes are in
Capcom has announced the schedule
For release
On the week of May 1st
Which has already happened
Mega Man Xtreme will be available
The following week
5-8
Both Mega Man 2 and Mega Man 3 will be available
Week of the 15th
Mega Man 4
Week of the 22nd
Mega Man 5
And then the week of the 29th
Mega Man Xtreme 2
Now, these are for
I believe the 3DS Virtual Console
Yeah, they are
The Game Boy versions
The end
The games were all coming anyway
That vote meant nothing
All it was was the order that you wanted them in
Which it looks pretty much like
Numerical order is what we went with
Apparently
There you go
Oh my gosh
Some people in chat
Capcom needs to lose that IP
I don't think they're letting go of it that easy
Well, let's travel around the world
That are coming out a little sooner than Mega Man Legends 3
Loki, US
Yes, well this week
There's a few things coming out
Starting off with Bound by Flame
Which is actually coming out on
PlayStation 3, Xbox 360
And on PS4
Sorry, Xbox One
You don't get that game
It looks pretty cool though
The PlayStation 4 version of
MLB 14, the show
Will be making it out this week as well
Today, actually we had a couple
3DS games
There was Mario Golf
World Tour
So that came out on 3DS and
Kirby Triple Deluxe
Let's see
What else was coming out later this week here
We also have
There's so much stuff
Smooth dates
Hakuoki Stories of the Shinsu
Goomy on PlayStation 3
If you like your visual novel games
For the Vita, God of War
Collection
That's coming out on the Vita
Also the amazing
Spider-Man 2 which kind of got delayed
A little bit
That's coming out on Xbox One
And this is pretty sweet
Borderlands 2
Going to be coming out
Later this week
Actually, that might be next week
13th, is that a Friday?
13th is a Tuesday
I'm sorry, that's the following week
It was originally supposed to come out this week
Anyways, that's it
Alright, well moving to Japanese
Release dates, there is nothing on the schedule
For this week, literally nothing
It probably has to do with Golden Week going on right now in Japan
So there is nothing
Sales, I need to take advantage of still on PlayStation
There are the sales stuff
And some other little tie-ins like that
But as far as official releases go, nothing this week in Japan
How about the UK?
The UK has a few games
Starting with May 7th
You get Peggle 2 on
Xbox 360
Titan Attacks on PS4, Vita
And PS3
On May 8th, Age of Mythology's
Extended Edition for PC
And the God of War collection on Vita
May 9th brings Bound by Flame
For PS3, PC
PlayStation 4
And Xbox 360
And then last on here, and I don't think this is right anymore
But Killer is Dead on PC
Didn't that get pushed back by a couple weeks?
I believe, everywhere
Yeah, I want to see, I just saw
I think it was my birthday, I think
On the 23rd, so Killer is Dead
On my birthday
Well maybe you can get Killer is Dead for free
No, I don't even know what that is, I don't want it
Killer is Dead is the, I can't remember the guy's name
It's the guy that does the new Killer 7
And No More Heroes and stuff like that
It was there, they came out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
I think about a year ago
Last August, I want to say
Kajudo in chat says
Japan has stopped making games
No, that's not what happened
I will say this, May 15th, it's going to pick up again
And I'll tell you what, guess what's coming out on May 15th
A new Idolmaster game in Japan
So those are huge
Yeah, we should be getting a new
Not Idolmaster, but
Hatsune Miku? Yeah, maybe this year
Hatsune Miku is opening for Lady Gaga, did we talk about that on the show?
That is some crazy shit
Lady Gaga is having Hatsune Miku
Yes, the video game character
Well, it's more than a video game character in Japan
But with the holograms and shit
Is actually opening for the art pop
Whatever they're calling it in select cities
I don't think on this coast, but on the east coast
Hatsune Miku is opening for Lady Gaga
I feel like that would be this coast
Not the east coast
You would think, right?
You would think that she could just call herself Gem
And she could have the hologram
Alright, just a couple more news stories for you guys
And then the classic game of the week
Which, look out guys
Because Shane's filling in for Jamie tonight
Guess who I picked for the classic game of the week
But I'm going to tell you what, Loki, I already know
Is going to love this pick
Let's get to those other
I will tell my first pick before we go with that
Okay, well let's get these other stories out of the way real quick
This was actually kind of a surprise
I mean, I knew that they were teasing that they're going to have
Marvel Super Heroes as part of the new
Disney Infinity, but I just figured
Hey, it's going to be another pack
Or something like that, it's not necessarily
Going to be the whole game, but guess what
Disney Infinity 2.0, Marvel Super Heroes
Is going to be announced
Or it was announced
And it is full of Marvel Super Heroes
So, yeah, it's going to be pretty sweet
Launching with the game
They said it's going to be Iron Man
Thor and Black Widow, but along with that
Hulk, Captain America
And Hawkeye will also be
Launching alongside it
And of course
With it, they're saying that, you know
You can have higher levels in your characters
New skill trees
Also, the toy box mode is coming back
And all the old characters will be supported by it
So you'll be able to play as the old characters
In toy box mode only
And they kind of
Showed some more
Well, they showed some other things
They have the Avengers characters in there
They've got Spider-Man
They showed off a lot of different
The characters from
Guardians of the Galaxy
Are going to be in there, so obviously
They'll have that toy box come out
Maybe when the movie comes out or something
Although that's a summer movie, I want to say
It's interesting to see these worlds
Coming together, though
We know what Disney Infinity 3.0 is then
Yeah, right, with the Star Wars, absolutely
Or maybe it's 3PO
Oh, God
You just wrote their entire
Advertising campaign
Patent pending, quick
It's not surprising
Infinity 3.0 is going to be Star Wars stuff
I'll be pretty
Exciting, too
There's some
Characters that were in the
Trailer as well
Stitch, although that could have been
Maybe a different playable character
Or not necessarily
Merida
Maleficent
Nick Fury
Loki
It's not only Avengers
Some of the newer
The chick from Brave and the
Frozen characters
The Frozen characters were from
The last pack that came out
Frozen characters are already out
But they're only in the toy box mode
It's kind of lame
Is Brave out, too?
No, no
They have
What's-her-name from Tangled
Rapunzel
Miss Tangled?
Yeah, from Tangled
And then they have
Green Goblin, MODOK
And they showed off
Rocket Raccoon and Groot
Kind of mimicking the scene that they had in the trailer
Well, I can see where Marvel nerds are going to be really happy about this
I don't know how I feel about the whole
Old characters only work in toy locks mode
Let's put it this way
I think what the problem was before is with Disney Infinity
It kind of skewed too much
Too young, maybe
And so now that they've got all this Marvel stuff
They're trying to capitalize on
Skylanders, young boys
And honestly
I think they've got a stronger license
Because people that are just getting into it
Who the fuck are the Skylanders?
I know who the Avengers are
I don't know who the fuck the Skylanders are
Well, Skylanders is getting more and more
They've been around for a few years now
So I think it's getting more and more out there
I understand that, but I'm just saying
Marvel's been around a lot longer than
Skylanders
I think that they stand a little bit better of a chance
But I'll be interested to see
It's supposed to be coming out in September
And on this also
There are going to be
Last Gen and
PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
So you can step up
To the PlayStation 4 with this cycle
Yes
Moving on to one other story here
We're about to get into the Classic Game of the Week
So it's appropriate that I talk about some free classic games
That are available
And they're actually coming from Blizzard
Now you may or may not know, over at Battle.net
If you have an account over there, you can download
Blackthorn for free, that's one of their old games
From the Super Nintendo days
That's been out for a while
Well, Blizzard decided to add a little more to that
By putting out some of the other classic Blizzard games
I think this goes all the way back to when they were
A different named company
The Lost Vikings
There's actually some Lost Vikings
Jokes in World of Warcraft
You actually see them in one of the dungeons
So the Lost Vikings, you can actually now play that
Free via Battle.net
You can go download it, it's completely legal and all that stuff
You play it through Battle.net, it's pretty cool
Also available, Rock and Roll Racing
Although they say that Rock and Roll Racing
Might actually be just the demo
Because there's only three songs
Available in Rock and Roll Racing
There's some issues with the licensing
That game was awesome
Rock and Roll Racing had all these
Actual Rock and Roll songs
They fear the licensing may have screwed that up
Because they say, the reports are
That if you download the game
It's really only the three tracks from the demo
Put new music in there
Yeah, you would think, or something
But yeah, unfortunately
So Rock and Roll Racing has hobbled a little bit
But you still can get that for free
And Lost Vikings
Those, again, are available at Battle.net
Pretty cool way to convince people to go get
A Battle.net account
To register participation
For this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
At vognetwork.com
Anyways, Squash
Alright, well speaking of
Classic games, it's time to take
A journey to the past
As we open up the gaming vault
And step in and find a game
That we think, hey, you should
Check out this classic game this week
Now usually Dark Sakura dives into the vault
And finds a game for y'all
But with Shane filling in tonight, we thought
Alright, let's let our guests have the honor
Of selecting the classic game of the week
What were the rules that Jamie set?
You said it was ten years old
That's what she said, she wanted to do Kingdom Hearts
At one point, I think
So it has to be ten years or older
So Shane, you stepped into the vault
And what game did you find for us tonight?
Well, first I found Power Rangers the movie The Game
And I was like, I love that game
I should talk about that
But then, I had a much more
Better idea to pick
And I picked Final Fantasy XI
So
This game is amazing
Final Fantasy XI meets this criteria
Because it came out
Actually on PC in America
In 2003
So we are well past that
Final Fantasy XI is
Square's online entry
Their first online entry into the Final Fantasy
For the Final Fantasy series
Oh my god, I'm sorry
This music brings back so many memories for me
I remember when this game came out
I was living with
Because this show was on
I was living with Loki
I stayed home from work the day this came out
I requested that day off from work to get the game
I remember I was the first one on the server
And I had to get everybody else
You kept deleting and re-rolling until you got it
Yeah, we had to get the world pass
I got world passes for everybody
I had to go out and kill a million sprouts
Or whatever to go get the stupid passes
I'm going to actually switch to
Some gameplay noises here
From the theme song
That theme song takes me back
So this is a standard
MMORPG
You fight things
You get experience
You level up
The game, which launched in Japan a little bit before we got it
Launched with six jobs
And then when the game came out in America
We not only got the original game
But we also got the first expansion
Which added
Oh my god, so many more jobs
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight
Nine, ten
Or eight, what?
All the advanced jobs
Except for, I'm sorry
The game did launch with the advanced jobs
Paladin, Dark Knight, Beastmaster, Ranger, Bard
And Summoner
The expansion, which was the base game for us
Also gave us Samurai Ninja Dragoon
And that's it
The game had
Let's see, one, two, three
Four main expansions
It's still going strong
Had an expansion last year
The Seekers of Adulin
Which added two more jobs
Bringing to a total of
I believe twenty-four jobs
The President of Square-
Oh my god, this video is of the Rama fight
Sorry
I just got excited
These Primal fights were so hard
Oh my god
We only did them as the solo ones
You can get a full party to do them as well
But we always did the babier versions
Where it's just you and carbuncle
In 2012, Yoichi Wada
Announced that Final Fantasy 11
Had become the most profitable title
In the Final Fantasy series
Probably because of all the monthly fees
And the cost for extra characters
And stuff like that
Yeah
This game has an amazing story
It spans across, you know, the four
Expansions, the little mini scenario
Expansions they put out as well
I couldn't tell you anything about that story either
No, it's really good
I've gone on the wiki and just read
The story at times
The game has changed
So much from when it launched to what it is now
Used to be everything required a party
Nowadays
Everything does not require a party
In fact, a party is a hindrance
Up until the very end of the game
Which is level 99
And you can increase your character's
Skills and stats
Beyond level 99 too
Through various means
It's awesome
Yeah, these guys are just duoing the fight
That used to take six people
I recently went back and played this game
Like two months ago to see
What all was different and it's
Still really fun
I got to level
65 or something like that
I was fully AF'd as a dancer
I played this game for fucking three years
I never got anywhere
Did I play that last January
Or was it this January
I think it was last January
I bought everything
Up to the last
The very last piece of
DLC and the expansion for it
It was like
It must have been like $8
I was like, dude, how can I not
Play this for another month
This was also the game that introduced
The hard drive to the PS2
That used
Or that was used for so many games like
Resident Evil Outbreak
And Resident Evil Outbreak 2
I think that was probably it
Oh, EverQuest
Yeah, EverQuest as well
Which is another online game
But yeah, this game still goes strong
The servers are a little bit more dead
Than they used to be
Because of Final Fantasy 14
A lot of the online Final Fantasy people moved over into that game
Is what you would think
But the people I was playing with
Were like, we went to 14, we didn't like it
We came back to 11
I love 14
I don't need to look back to 11 myself
I do, because it has so many amazing jobs
Blue Mage, Dancer
Geomancer, Rune Fencer
Puppet Master
Alright
Well there it is, your classic game of the week
Final Fantasy 11
It's constantly on sale on Steam
If you ever want to just pick it up for a little bit
For a month
And Xbox 360
I wish it would go free to play
Free to play, free to play
Come on, free to play
Never
I still get the emails, newsletters
Like, come check out what you're missing
Well, another good thing is that they update the game monthly now
So there's always a content patch of some sort every month
Whether it be job adjustments
Or quality of life changes
It's pretty nice
Square is pouring a lot into their MMOs
Meaning that they won't release Dragon Quest X here
Don't get me started
I'm about to get started
Alright
A classic near and dear to my heart
Many years of my life wasted on Final Fantasy 11
And soon to be 14
And Loki as well
And Shane
Actually, Shane and I probably became better friends
Because of Final Fantasy 11
I mean, we knew each other through LiveJournal and stuff
We really talked everyday through Final Fantasy 11
Pretty much, pretty much
Alright, well there it is
A classic game of the week, Final Fantasy 11
Let us take a break, when we come back
We've got the FUGL question of the week
Rapid fire news to come
Some shifting and so forth going on at some game companies
And email bag
Participate at orangelandtrady.com
A follow up to last week's email
Did we tell our listener
What game they were looking for
We're gonna find out
They wrote back this week
So we will get that follow up coming up next
On Orange Lounge Radio after this break
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
Live on this
May the 4th of 2014
With episode 551 of our show
And yes
If you're just joining us live at the Voice of Geeks Network
VoGnetwork.com
Yes, we got the May the 4th jokes
Out of the way, I'm sure your Facebook feed already
Blew up with them earlier today
So there you go, done
As far as Star Wars and video games goes
We must talk about that a little bit
We kind of already talked
During the last segment about Disney
Infinity
3.0 is most likely gonna be Star Wars
Bank on it for Disney Infinity 3.0
Otherwise, anybody played a Star Wars game
Recently?
They don't make them like Super Star Wars
Star Wars is a crappy IP anyway
Oh be quiet, that's not true
I don't like Star Wars
I don't like them, the movies are crap
The new ones are
Well all of them that I've seen which are 4, 5, and 6
You're wrong, they're not that bad
But the old republic keeps doing stuff
So that's still going
There's a Star Wars game
Yoda and Darth Vader were cool in Soul Calibur 4
By the way, if you listen to my little rant
Last week on Soul Calibur Lost Swords
I tried
I tried again this week, I booted
I think there was even a comment on VOG
But I saw that they fixed it
There was an article on a blog site
That said they fixed everything
Nope, it's getting deleted tonight
I tried, I'd win it one more time
I brought up the thing and it's still loading, loading, loading, loading, loading, loading
I want to see it before you delete it
I got to the, well here's the thing
I get to the menu screen, can't move up or down
Can't hit the button, can't do anything
Saya said, I'm out
I didn't even get into the full game, I said I'm done with this garbage
But I tried
I tried
Tigerclaw says
You think Shane is going to hate Star Wars Episode 7?
Yes I do, he will hate Star Wars
Most likely
Unless the series gets a decent story
And not terrible acting
Which I don't have high hopes for
Bobby Blackwolf says
Shanehateseverything.com
That's not true
Just things that are awful
He loves Power Rangers, Pokemon, and
Skylanders in the color blue
And Taco Bell and
Del Taco
Alright
Anyhow, let's get into some
rapid fire news because there is
a lot of other stuff going on in gaming
Loki
So finally
After months of wondering
Where's Drive Club? Isn't that supposed to be out by now?
They have
Made it official that
Drive Club will be out October 7th
In North America, October 8th
In Europe
And of course
They had planned for the game to come out early
But they ran into
A problem being able to deliver
On their ambitious
Yeah ambitious promise
And apparently
The whole issue with it was
That they wanted it to be a
Socially connected game
And they were having trouble with
The social networking part of that
Wait, their ambitious promise
Is that the promise of releasing a game?
Is that the ambitious promise?
That is ambitious as far as
Socially connected
We need to make sure that all the connectivity
That surrounds the game
Whether it be joining clubs or sending challenges
Or even interacting with iOS and Android
Drive Club apps
That had to be slick
And that had to be absolutely seamless
And that was one of the areas that we need
To put extra time into
We were able to polish the cars
The tracks and stuff
Or just a fantastic byproduct
Part of me
Is wondering that maybe the reason why
They delayed it a little bit
Was because of all these launch
Issues that they've had with games
Like Soul Calibur and stuff
Where their servers were just fucked up
And they were worried that if they weren't able
To talk to each other that you may have some issues
And stuff
Also they were saying what we originally had
That was not necessarily as smooth or
Transactions
Or transitions
Where the way it connected you
Or other players weren't as intuitive as we
Intended them to be
So we had to go back and re-look at those areas
And kind of look at different ways
And new techniques to get people
Socially connect
And we changed that with a new
Dynamic menu system
So we really feel like we've solved
All those problems
Also
You may be wondering
Well are we still going to be getting
Drive Club for free as part of PlayStation Plus
Well yes that is still going to happen
It's actually going to be
Taking place in one country
With five tracks
And ten cars
So that's going to be the free portion of the game
And you'll be able to
Buy stuff a la carte
If you want
On top of that
So
It's pretty neat
Of course people are getting pissed off
It's 1080p and only 30 frames per second
Not 60 so there's that whole debate
But who gives a shit about that
I'm glad they're still doing the
PlayStation Plus free-ish mode
Definitely
And then
I'm a little disappointed about this
You may remember
Adam Sandler
Their studio
For pixels
Which was a kind of a short
That came out
A digital short that was on YouTube
Where it was a bunch of
This blob of pixels flying through the air
And then all of a sudden
Oh look Donkey Kong is there throwing barrels at people
And all sorts of pandemonium
The Tetris blocks are destroying buildings
And everything kind of went all pixely
Well
Now there's a little bit more information regarding this
It's supposed to be coming
In 2015
It's of course going to have Adam Sandler
And all those crew
Peter Dinklage is going to be in it as well
And apparently the plot
This is really weird
The plot centers around I guess
Aliens who discover video footage of classic arcade games
And apparently after seeing that
The aliens believe that Earth is
Trying to wage war with them
And
You know apparently the aliens
Invade Earth using the games
As bullets for their attack
Of course they're going to have some people
That are arcade aficionados
That are going to take them on
And defeat the aliens and save the day
But it sounds really weird
Originally it was like all these
Classic arcade characters
Are kind of waging war
Against everybody
And then to this really strange plot line
I don't know I think it's just going to sound kind of cheesy
But whatever
That's coming out next year
I sounded like the last star fighter almost
I just
It's just Adam Sandler
He's like poisoned for anything nowadays
Back in the day you know the Adam Sandler movie
Hell yeah I got to watch it because it's going to be hilarious
Nah it's just not so much
So I'm going to have to wait and see
Also this week
They announced the brand new Call of Duty
Game in
It's going to come out in November
Called Call of Duty Advanced Warfare
And it takes place in the year 2059
And following I guess a bunch of different
Private military contractors
One I know which is Atlas
And I don't know if they're supposed to be the
Good guys or the bad guys
But I know
That Kevin Spacey is going to be in
The game as well
He has a character that he's voicing
I guess
Parents kind of based off of
Apparently he has
Some sort of
I don't know if he's going to be the good guy
Or if he's trying to take over the United States
But anyways
Stuff happens
The Golden Gate Bridge gets destroyed
At one point and it's got a lot of the tech
That you see in some of these
Near sci-fi movies like Elysium
Or was that new one with
Tom Cruise coming out
The exoskeleton suits
And all sorts of
That kind of tech
Like the wearable armor type things
Oh and hoverbikes
That's kind of cool
So we're going to get our hovercars
In the next 30 or so years
But yeah that'll be coming out in November
Great! Bunch of information on Call of Duty
I didn't know about
Yeah that's completely new information
Alright let's move on
Talking about a game that I do know something about
Because I've played it before
I just haven't played it on the Wii U
But it's Giana Sisters, Twisted Dreams
There is a patch that will be hitting the Wii U
In off TV mode
Some of the in-game sounder music
Wouldn't come through to the Wii U gamepad
Oops! So that will be a
Patch that will hit so if you want to check out
Giana Sisters, Twisted Dreams
Which is a pretty solid platformer I gotta say
I've been playing it on PC
But if I didn't have a nice PC
I think the Wii U would be a great place
To check that out
Yeah check that out
Especially after that patch goes in
This is interesting, this game came out a while ago
With the Mortal Kombat HD arcade collection
I had no idea this was a thing
But thanks to some forum posts
This week some screenshots
Leaked of what was supposed to be
A full HD remake
Of the Mortal Kombat collection
Meaning new characters
I'm sorry, same characters
But new grabs
Like the sprites were all new
New actors dressed up in the costumes
That would be hilarious
And they actually have lots of screens
That people posed in
Luke Kang and Katana
Completely different people
And you see that they're grabbed
In HD
Kind of neat huh
But then they actually show some pictures
Behind the scenes of these actors on a green screen
In the costumes
They were ready to
They had the Mortal Kombat 3
Katana and the 2 and all that stuff
I'm imagining that's
Sonya in one of these pictures
Which I know makes for great radio
New actors
Stryker's
Kind of chubby isn't he
That's alright
No he just looks derpy
And it's so sad because the newest
Mortal Kombat game made Stryker almost
Cool and now they're just like
No we're gonna take that away from him
So I don't know what they changed
They cancelled this and just
Did it with the regular actors instead
Maybe it was too much of a shock
Maybe on playing it with new people
They were just like no this doesn't
Like this defeats the purpose, people are gonna hate this
No I imagine somewhere in testing
This fell out that like people were gonna
Reject it
I kinda think though they should've done it anyway
With both
Why not have the new and the old
Let people choose what they wanna play as
I think the new ones for the most part
Except for maybe Stryker and Kano
Look pretty decent
They should've kept it
It would've been weird that they would spend all that money
And then nope nevermind
Psych
Speaking of, nevermind, psych
We had a story last week I think on the show
About Silent Hill Origins and Shattered Memories
Coming to the Playstation Vita
Oh no that was a mistake
The Konami blog
That announced this apparently was some type of
Either a mistranslation
Or just plain wrong
Because now it's two Silent Hill
Titles headed to the Playstation Network
Even though Konami of the UK tweeted
That they're coming to the Vita
Oops
They made a follow up tweet
Regretfully the games aren't available on Playstation Vita
We're afraid
If this changes however we'll let you know
Well you can download them for the PSP
On Playstation Network and I'm thinking
That's where the error came from
Somewhere they said oh we need to run an announcement
That it's coming to the Playstation Portable
And somebody said oh that means the Vita
Totally forgot about the PSP
Like a lot of people did
Well don't the PSP games play on the Vita though?
Most do
So
It's not entirely unsure I guess
I guess not but yeah I think people
Had it in their minds that it was new ports or something
And that is not a period of games
So there you go
Oh well I don't think I mean last week when we
Talked about it people didn't seem to be too excited
About the idea anyway actually it was the week that
Flaco was here so it was two weeks ago
But anyway it turned out to be
Psych just kidding
Shane do you have some stuff for us?
Yeah DuckTales Remastered the soundtrack if you enjoyed
It from the recent release
Is now available on the
Amazon MP3 store
iTunes and Spotify
You can get the
47 track
I didn't realize there were that many songs
In it
You can get the 47 track album
For 949 on Amazon
Because they have the retro stuff on there too
So it's the original and the retro
That's what fills it up
And it's somehow $11.99
On iTunes I don't know
Why that's kind of
Really dumb
Also
Gran Turismo 5
They're pulling the plug on its
Online services so
They are holding a special event
To commemorate it
It will consist of two stages
With the first having a focus
On the Mazda
Roadster touring car
Of $11 I guess
And then the other
One is the Top Gear
Or sorry
Is the Nissan GTR N24
I don't know how to pronounce these car names
Scholes
Motorsports $11
I don't know whatever
Participating in the event will give players
It's alright Shane it's like me reading Japanese release dates
I could do that way better than I can read
Car things
Not during Golden Week
I could do that better too
I wouldn't say anything also
But better
Just playing in these events will give players
Five free vehicles in Gran Turismo 6
If they use the same PSN
ID as they did from
Gran Turismo 5
You will also earn
The
Golf Grande Punto 09
Wasn't
Barth the name of the burger chain
And you can't do that on television
This is a Barth
Yes you're right
The Renault Sport
RS
Trophy 11
The Nissan
Fairlady Z
Why don't you just say
A bunch of car stuff
You'll get cars does it really matter
And you get a car
It's just some stupid car
For Gran Turismo
You get five stupid cars
For Gran Turismo 6
There
In lighter news Bob Hoskins died
At age 71
That means no Mario 2
For anyone
Never coming now
It's alright you know what
They can just recast him with Danny DeVito
It's almost the same right
I guess
Bob Hoskins didn't care for the Mario Brothers movie
Oh god I hope not
Well nobody did well apparently John Lee
Was almost put out a tweet about the whole thing
And I think he even responded to somebody
That said like well didn't you guys hate the Mario
Movie and he kind of said something to the effect
Of and I'm paraphrasing here
It's grown on them over the years
Probably the fan response
And the fact that people care about it now
Probably has grown on at least John Leguizamo
It kind of sucks I mean imagine like you're
John Leguizamo back and you're kind of almost like
A no name actor at that point
And they're like hey we're gonna
Ok whatever yeah that's fine but he's a little bit more known
Now I mean he's more known now
He was in Moulin Rouge
And he was also in Kick-Ass 2 by the way
And they're like
Hey we're making a movie based on Super Mario
Brothers you want to be in it?
And it's like fuck yeah well he probably wasn't like that
He probably auditioned for it but you know hey we're making a movie
His agent was probably like fuck yeah
Yeah it's like seriously
You know probably the same thing happened when Double Dragon
Had a movie too and we know how that turned out so
It's just
It's just one of those things you know it's unfortunate
And now we'll never know if
You know a sequel really could have happened because they left
It wide open at the end
Or Tiger Claws has no
Sequel to who framed Roger Rabbit either
Yeah that movie scared the crap out of them
Well wasn't the end of like the Super Mario Brothers movie
Wasn't that kind of like the same premise that they can basically do
In the end of the new
Or the beginning of the new Tron movie you know
Where they invade Earth or whatever
Well but in the Mario movie it was like
Was it Daisy that was in there?
She just shows up at the end and she's like guys we got trouble
Or something stupid like that
And they're like okay Marty it's your kids
She had like plunger guns or something I don't remember
That movie was so awful
Rama in chat says in heaven right now
There's two Marios and a Luigi
I think Bowser, Koopa around
Yeah because Dennis Hopper's passed away
I didn't know that
You didn't know that? Yeah Dennis Hopper died a few years ago
It was while he was on that TV show Crash
That they made out of the movie
And then
Yeah Captain Lou Albano
Who played Mario on the TV show passed away
And the guy who played Luigi Danny Wells
Passed away
So yeah
John Leguizamo better watch out
Not to be crass but
Better watch out
Maybe we can get the pest too
No
My favorite Bob Hoskins
Role will always be Smee
In Hook
My favorite will always be Who Framed Roger Rabbit
There you go
I didn't like Who Framed Roger Rabbit actually
I know that's sacrilege
Actually that's my favorite Christopher Lloyd role
Oh yeah he was actually really good
Not even Back to the Future
Professor Plum in Clue
Never
Alright but Christopher Lloyd's still alive
Just for the record
And I gotta be honest
And I gotta be honest I'm absolutely surprised he's still alive
Because he looks older than dirt right now
Stop you guys are so
I mean no don't get me wrong
I hope he lives forever but
He looks old
I know he can't but
He looks fucking old but
That's why if we're gonna get another Back to the Future
Movie or something
Hurry up on that shit
He's not getting any younger
If they don't do a reboot isn't that what they do now?
It's a reboot
What happened to reboot the movie?
I thought that was coming at some point
What happened to reboot the show?
They really fucked that one up
That was cool for like the first season
We're gonna have all these characters in there
And now it's something weird
Fifth Dream says the only ones surviving
Are Princess and Toad that's suspicious
I don't even remember Toad in that movie
I don't either but
Alright let's move on let's get to the foogle question of the week
You take Facebook, you take Google
As in Google Plus you slam those
Together and you get foogle
And so that's why we go to our fan communities every week
And ask a question of our
Listeners and we read some of our favorite answers
Here on air
Maybe I'll read them all tonight
I'm gonna start on Google Plus
With the question which is about the whole Disney
Infinity, Skylanders
Because I knew we'd be talking about these games that come with figures
Tonight because of the Marvel news and the fact
That Shane made me play Skylanders
I will point out
That when you actually played it
You asked me to go get it
Like I've been saying we need to play this
We need to play this and then out of the blue you're like
Okay let's play this
I was ready to do the live stream
I was like if we're gonna do this let's do it
And then we asked you guys
Now that it's been a few years for Skylanders
And a year for Disney Infinity
It looks like these games are here to stay
How do you feel about these games
Involving sold separately figures
Do you really enjoy the games and collecting the figures
Or do you think these are cheap cash grabs
That aren't worth your time
We just kind of wanted to know generally what do the listeners think of these games
Retertainment on Google Plus says
I haven't given these games much thought
But I'm not a kid and I don't have any children of my own
Sure I could buy these video game or toy combinations
My sister's family has enough problems keeping themselves
In government subsidized housing
Does anyone else remember Captain Power
I do I do
Act Def says
I still think these type of games are really big cash grabs right now
But they're good ones at least for the most part
A lot of people both children and adults
Like both Skylanders and Disney Infinity
Collect the figurines and play the games
The only one that got close to getting me to buy
Figurines was Pokemon Rumble U
But I heard the game was crap and didn't do it
I'm still kind of tempted by them though
It was crap
Don't do it
Alright and going over to
Facebook I can probably read most of these
I might make some of them a little shorter though
Andy R says
In a way it doesn't seem all that different than DLC to me
Only your DLC nets you a collectible
You can put on a shelf
DLC is its own love it or hate it gaming trend
But getting physical collectibles with it
Is all upside I'd say
I've never been into Skylanders or Disney Infinity
But as someone who collects and plays Magic
People may get addicted to it
The only problem I have with that is that
DLC tends to be
Not always but tends to be more robust
Like when I think about Mass Effect 3
Story DLC
Great! Whole bunch of stuff I'm getting for my 10 or 15 bucks
But then I think about horse armor
In Oblivion
Not great right
The reason why I bring that up is that
When you get through these doors and things
It's not that much
It's like one room that has a hat in it
One puzzle to do
It's not like a whole bunch
Technically for the case of Skylanders
You buy the starter pack
Because that's what they're forcing you to do every single time
You get characters there
You don't need to buy anybody else
You can beat the entire game
Everything else would be optional
That is horse armor
That's all it is
Haseo Sumeruagawa responds
I can't I just can't
Rene our friend from the podcast
Killer Queens from Outer Space says
It's a great way to keep a game in players minds
By offering expansions
To keep replayability high
But it's just not my bag
Gamer Girl says
On one hand I think it's good for the collector in mind
But on the other hand I think it's a waste of money for parents
Whose kids lose interest rather quickly
Blood Drunk says
It's a giant cash grab gimmick to get children hooked
To make the parents buy figurines for the game
In my book at least
Critical Myth responds
And even though he's beat each of the three games
Many times over
There's still plenty of those damn figurines sitting unused
Their idea is neat
But there has to be a better way to implement it
To make it less of a cash grab
Ciala responds and says
If Nintendo ever does this with Pokemon
They'll become a leading world economy
Well again they started to do it
But they did it half-assed
They did it really half-assed
I'm not huge on this method myself
But I might collect some if they have cool figures
From something I enjoy
Shay C. replied
And agreed with the first answer I read from Andy R.
It's essentially DLC
And should be held to the same standard
It can be fine
But if you're shipping a full price game where say
Half or more of the content is gated
Oh the boss is behind a door you need a fire grind to open
Buy additional figures
That crosses the line
As long as the amount of gameplay provided for all combinations of purchases
Is in line with the cost
I've got no real problem with it
And if we're going to be fair
This is all on this DLC by the way
In my book
I did think it was cool
I did think it was really cool
That those figures save
Data in them
Through the little chips
I had never played the game on my Playstation 4 before
But when Shane put the little bird figure
It's like oh this is level 10
And you have all these abilities on it
So is your Wii remote but no one gives a shit about that
So I thought it was a neat use of that technology
For what it's worth
But I just want to say about the DLC question
Since Shane already answered it
You can beat the game with just what it comes with
In my opinion
Those figures are not worth it
Just for the DLC in the game
You really have to like it
You have to like the figure
Like that it lights up or whatever
And you get a little bit of an enhancement
A little bit of an incentive
You could eat a pizza that's just cheese
But really you want pepperoni
For some people
That's how it's going to be
Two more answers left
I hope I don't mispronounce this
It's either Felipe or Felipe
Felipe A replies and says
When I was a kid my parents bought me a lot of cheap toys
From the store that I would end up playing for maybe
Two to three hours and forget about them
I equate Skylanders and all other figures to those
They are cheap distractions that keep kids entertained
For a couple hours
I got my parents to use their money to give me a couple hours
Of entertainment back then
And then I gave the game to a couple more extra
Not for me since I'm in my twenties
But I'm not the addressable market for them either
Shane might disagree with you there
I think once you start putting like age restrictions on stuff
You get kind of ridiculous
Like you could say the same thing about any video game
Can we talk about your Power Rangers toy?
Yeah I don't care
Talk about my Power Rangers
You want me to go get it? I'll play it over the stupid thing
After I'm done, yes go get your Power Rangers toy
I brought all three
You didn't know I brought three
It's like a train
That's not even the series we have here
It's a train thing in Japan
And it makes choo choo noises
And you paid $60 for it
It's their Morpher in the new Japanese series
I love it, it's amazing
You know what though?
Everybody has their thing
I do this Rocky Horror thing
And you always look at me going
You are wasting all of your time
Don't tell me to tell you that too though
So I'll remind you
There's all that going on
But then you spend $60 on a Power Rangers toy
And I'm fine with it
People spend money on whatever makes them happy
Yes, now you can keep reading it all over our back
Alright
Well I only have one more answer so you better hurry
And again I'm probably going to mispronounce this
So I apologize
Amanojeko
I think is how I say that
Amanojeko says the idea of Skylanders
is a fun concept with a variety of
figures to choose from so you can play
the way you want. The only drawback is
the fact that some Skylanders giant figures
can't be used in Swap Force and vice versa
For the money people put in the game
they should be able to use them as they
see fit
Alright, I agree with that
Bobby Blackwolf in our chat room says
I'd be more interested in Disney Infinity because
of recognizable characters. I wouldn't
mind having a Tron action figure that also
works in a video game, but no, they didn't release
any Tron figures for Disney Infinity
Yeah, I'm a little
bitter about that
Yeah, I agree. They did have some Tron things in the
toy box, but yeah, no Tron figure
unfortunately
Best you could do is have these little
citizens or whatever
toy things running around
you can dress them up like Tron, that's about it
Whoopee
So answering the questions for ourselves here real quick
Loki, all the sass
and anger stuff aside, how do you really
feel about these games?
I mean, I tried Disney Infinity and
once again, it was
too young
of a demographic for me
You bought it and sold it on eBay, right?
It wasn't
It's cool, like the figurines
are pretty neat. I kind of wish that you could
do something with them, like that they actually were figurines
that you could pull off the base and
do stuff with
But as far as collecting them goes, I mean, they're not
bad. I mean, they're kind of cool looking
I just think though it is
pretty obvious in both games
of how much of a cash grab they are
and yeah, I know that people compare it to
DLC, but dude
there's 60 pieces of
DLC if you want to call it that
60 pieces plus
that are like 10 bucks each
You don't really have to buy
like as Shane said earlier, you need one of each
element or one of each power, you don't need all
You don't have to, but then why offer 60 pieces?
Because they want you to buy all of them
And there will be people that will buy all of them
And some of the figures are kind of neat, like they light up and shit
remember? Anyhow
Yeah, and those cost an extra $5
Here's the thing, after
finally getting my hands on Skylanders this week
it's not as bad of a game as I thought it would be
like the game itself, I was expecting it to be a lot worse
and a lot more in your face of a cash grab
No, it's pretty sweet, but it wouldn't be
just the same game if you just
played it and you unlocked characters via
progression or whatever, finding
them, I mean, that would be
I don't know, like a game that they released
years ago, but now they're like, hey we can make
an extra $600 off of that
Fuck you
I can hear you on that
And you know what? There's going to be stuff
when the Tron figures come out eventually for Disney
Phoenix, like
that's really cool, but nope
Alright, got to move on with the show, but quickly
Shane's back with his toys, remember it's a radio show
so help explain it for us a little bit
what you brought back. So, first of all I couldn't find one of my toys
but I have the original Dragonzord dagger
from like 1990 something here
and it still
still works
I haven't ever changed the batteries
I don't know how it works
But this other thing is
you put a train in
and it makes train noises, hold on
What do trains have to do with Power Rangers?
That's just the theme this time, is their train theme
Oh yeah
So he's putting this little train
in the, it looks like a rocket
launcher or something that has
Well no, these are like
the crossing signal things. Anyway, so like
you want to morph, so you hit this
That's train noises, and you put the
train in
You push the gates down
And because of the way
the train is molded at the bottom
and it hits certain sensors
and it knows which train you put in there
so it knows that this is the Red Rangers train
so it tells me that I just wanted to
The look on Loki's
face right now is priceless
He spent $60 on that
I was over at Flaco Jones' house
and I showed his kid this series
and he would not quit watching it
so watch out
And Flaco Jones isn't going to be inviting you back
anytime soon
You know what though?
I respect the fact that they can do that
straight face throughout the whole thing
even though it's kind of ridiculous
but I do want to see some really
I want them to kind of take that and run with it
Maybe next year they can do
household appliances
Well, toaster ranger
Yeah, mow the lawn ranger
It's Japan, they do crazy things
like last time was dinosaurs
but the other half of that was samba dancing
and they had guns that they would spin
and would make music and they had to dance to it
This is pretty awesome
You know what? That's the next one we get here
I'm excited
Syallen Chat says, you're not alone
because Syallen Chat says, Shane Alinko
I need that in my life
Yes, I see that
live.vognetwork.com
Alright, let us move on with more show
We've got more news to get into
and your emails to get to as well
I mean, I don't know
I've watched the Transformers
slash Thomas thing that they did
on YouTube, it's hilarious
and they have that
so maybe Power Rangers thing would be so bad
Anyways, ok
so
this is kind of
I don't know, it's kind of disappointing if you're a fan of
maybe Tony Hawk and stuff
Neversoft, a company that used to do
some pretty awesome games
Tony Hawk included
They are now being rolled into
Infinity Ward or what is now Infinity Ward
and
because I think Neversoft
actually did some Call of Duty
work before
I want to say that they worked on
either certain versions of the game or DLC
or something like that
a portion of the game
well now
they worked with them for
Call of Duty Ghost
so now they're actually going to be part of Infinity Ward
and Neversoft is no more
so
but it's
did I hear no layoffs?
the name is No More
Didn't they make the Guitar Hero 3 and after
and all that too?
I wanted to say that they did, yeah
well moving on, this is involving layoffs
this is Future
is going through some restructuring and
redundancies or layoffs
Future, they don't make games
but they make some gaming commentaries, magazines
things like OXM, PC Gamer, CVG
and Edge, so some of these magazines
and websites, they're going through
global restructuring, this means
layoffs and according to CEO
no part of the business will be unaffected
they also say that Future
will no longer, this is not from the CEO but from Media Week
Future will no longer be structured around
content types like technology
but instead a single content and marketing
team will produce all content
basically the whole move to digital
they say diluted focus and distracted
the talent, so interesting
all these brands range from
cars to tech, music, sports and so on
it sounds like they're probably going to combine
similar things and try to push out
similar content in both paper and
digital forms or something along those lines
kind of where it sounds like this is going
it doesn't totally surprise me
in this day and age we live in, it's so
much easier for people to make homegrown
media content, hi
how you doing?
so that's just the reality
of the industry, but still
no funding, and not get paid for it
well for us yeah, but
well yeah we do it for free
so it makes it that much harder for the people
and I'm not just saying we, but I mean there's tons
of websites and tons of even
homegrown mags and
video shows and so forth, it makes it that
much harder for the people that do want to get money to do it
but you know
that's the reality
but layoffs are never fun to talk about
so best of luck to those
folks that are affected, hope you can find
another job in the industry that you enjoy
Shane
oh sorry I was chatting
oh now the chat room wants to talk
Power Rangers, you're all in it right?
yeah I'll talk Power Rangers for days
so from software makers of
games like Otogi, because that's really the only one
I remember, but I guess
they also do like Dark Souls
or Armored Core
but Otogi
enchanted arms
like the first RPG on 360
Awful, that was such a bad game
yeah, that was from software
did From Software also do
or did they have a part in
what was it, ChromeHounds?
I think that was mostly Sega I think
I could be wrong
but they have published recently
they've done a lot more than what
Shane's leading on, but mostly Otogi
still, because that was a really good game
but they also published Killer's Dead
and the lollipop
chainsaw in Japan
they have been acquired by
Kadokawa Corporation
which is a
corporation
that publishes manga
like I guess
Gundam and Neon Genesis
Evangelion
Bobby says
From did do ChromeHounds, you're right
and I'm wrong
sorry Shane
no that's really it, they were acquired by a
manga publishing company
interesting, interesting combination
I hope they make Otogi 3
crossing your fingers and your toes
just my fingers, I don't want that
much
lowkey
let's see
so this is kind of cool
one of the games I want to see, I think this was
GameSpy, yeah it was GameSpy
so one of the games that was affected by GameSpy
was a PC version of Halo Combat Evolved
and you know
the Halo franchise
they were rabid fans when it comes to
multiplayer, you may remember Halo 2
multiplayer on Xbox, there's a ton of people
that stayed in after you know they kind of
closed off the matchmaking
servers and stuff and they stayed in as long as they could
and they kind of drug it out, well
thanks to a
third party matchmaking online gaming
company called
GameRanger, the multiplayer service
is actually going to still
be continuing
and they're going to be
taking over I guess handling
the multiplayer for that game
so
oh and also I guess the demo and
the custom edition of that
so that's pretty sweet
on top of that
there's also, and this is good news
for me because I'm a fan of you know a lot of these
the Rockstar games but
Grand Theft Auto 4
and Red Dead
what was it, Red Dead Redemption
the multiplayer for that is actually
being, Rockstar is going to
make sure that keeps continuing
at least for those two games
Midnight Club 3 dub edition, dub edition
remix, Grand Theft Auto, Chinatown
Wars and
Beta Raider though are going to have their multiplayer shut
off although I can't imagine a lot of people play
multiplayer for Chinatown Wars, I didn't even
realize they had multiplayer
and of course you know Grand Theft Auto 5 is not
effective because that was never 3 games by the first place
Max Payne 3 also
not being affected by that
we're seeing though that
oh I'm sorry
Mac users in Max Payne 3 are not going to be able to
play multiplayer anymore, PC though you're ok
Red Dead Redemption though
no problems there
and then the PS3 version of
Grand Theft Auto 4 is losing its
leaderboards as well
so
I don't know
I'm glad to see that some of these companies are
stepping in to make sure their games don't go dark
as far as multiplayer is concerned
so that's
pretty cool
alrighty
let us go into the mailbag
we're going to open up the mailbag and read some of our emails
participate at orangelawandtrady.com
the place to send those emails
and every week DarkSakura
suits up and dives into the emailbag and
picks some emails to read, however she's not here
she has the night off so
I will borrow the hazmat suit
and dive on in and pick out some emails to read
for y'all
we are going to start with this email from
Dee
Dee does not want to have their full name read
and so
can we just make up a name then?
sure, make up a name
but what if the name you make up
and you don't know because you can't see the email
what if it happens to be the same name
it's going to be awkward
this person's name is DuckSauce
DuckSauce?
this person's name is not DuckSauce
it's because they don't want their full name read
so DuckSauce emailed us
and
DuckSauce has some insider info for us
let's get to it
I'm not, I don't give a shit about grammar
and B, even if Jamie had been here
and I would have been like, look Jamie
he speaks two languages
and until you can speak
two languages fluently, you're going to cut him a break
so please don't ever
be afraid to email us just because English isn't your
first language. Jamie will give you a break
because, you know, she expects if you're going to
speak one language, speak it well
but if you're going to speak more than one, then you get
a little room for error, so don't worry about it
LDuckSauce? Is that what we're
calling him now? Yes, LDuckSauce
LDuckSauce, ok, act-def says that would be
El PatoSauce
but that doesn't have a D in it
alright
alright, anyway
however, I am too excited to not tell
anyone about this, I am currently a beta
tester for PlayStation Now
I wanted to hear your opinions, please
keep my name private so I don't get in trouble for
opening my big mouth, you've got it
LDuckSauce, alright, I finally
received the code to get into the private
beta of PlayStation Now
I want to know your opinions about the service
do you think it's going to be a great, great
service? What are the problems you see
with this service? What do you want this service
to be when all is said and done? Do you think
it can be a type of future for gaming?
That's a lot of questions, LDuckSauce
but I will try to kind of summarize
my thoughts on it
I think it's a very exciting and creative way
to get the PlayStation games
backwards compatible. I am not
too exciting at the prospect of paying
for games again. I really wish
that if I had a PlayStation 3 disc
I could just enable that in my library
I realize why that's probably not going to
be possible, even if the digital games
carry over, I'll be mostly happy
about that, so I'm hoping
I'm a little worried about the technology
sometimes with streaming games
it's not always perfect
the delay concerns
me quite a bit
but I commend
them for trying and I'm open
to it and again I'm really
curious to see how much they charge for some
of these games because it's very interesting
what LDuckSauce breaks down
here
BlackWolf says
I want to hear LDuckSauce's opinion because he's
actually used it
and BlackWolf says it's hard to answer these
questions without having used the service
so let's get into actually
you're lucky Bobby because LDuckSauce actually
answers these questions
my experience so far is as follows
I'm using a Playstation 3 and a wireless
connection, the beta only has about 20
games and so far in the beta
I believe it's a good selection, they have good games
like Saints Row 3, Luminous Supernova
Puppeteer, BlazBlue, Disgaea
Catherine Knights Grid, Fuel, and Skullgirls
as you can see they have a good selection
or choices for anyone
for now all the games are free
I was going to say those are all the Playstation Plus games
for the most part
not Luminous, I would have grabbed that
well some of these are, some of these are
not, maybe those are upcoming
free titles
alright, when you select a game
you need to pick how many days you want to
rent this game, you have three options
one day, seven, or thirty days
I will assume that these prices will eventually
show up after beta, the game
themselves ran great, I do have to admit that
I never had a problem with the actual gameplay, sounds
or frame rate, however I did have
trouble with the video quality, there's this weird
YouTube dream effect going on
I don't know how to explain it, it's like when you watch a
YouTube HD video on your iPhone
and the quality drops to 720 or lower
for a couple seconds, this happens sometimes
on Playstation 3 games that I was streaming
at first it was super distracting, but eventually
you got used to the video dip, when I plugged
in the connection, this problem was resolved
my second concern is that I am worried
about online gaming with this program
I haven't tried that part yet, but I love
fighting games and I can't truly see anyone
playing fighting games online with some
service like this, I'm really
impressed by this technology, I know
that there was something like this before
I think it was called OnLive, I feel
that this could become like a Netflix meets
RedBox and specifically if you mix it with
Playstation Network Plus, no need
to ask for demos, just pay 99 cents
and rent the game for a day, maybe
a program like this will also discourage game
companies to make short games, like a game
like the most recent Metal Gear, I would have
rented it for a day or week instead of buying a disc
version, I know there will be problems like
internet connections, licensing fees and other things
that Sony can't control, I truly
wish this is part of the future for gaming
I know I only test it for two days so far
but I'm loving it, I know we all want to know
what the future for gaming is, but this could be something
that Sony can release quietly and catch on
really good once we all give it a chance
Sorry for the long email, just wanted to hear
your opinions and give mine, keep up
the great podcast, love you guys
Lducksauce
There it is, so
thank you for the email and actually your English
is very good, I did correct some of your tense
as I was reading it, that's really
the only thing I see is that sometimes you have to put
the D at the end of the word because it's in the past
but otherwise you did a great job
and considering I can speak no Spanish
really, although that won't
stop me from trying to watch Telemundo because that
shit's great, I'm very impressed
and please do email us in the future
What did you guys think about, what do you have to say about PlayStation Now?
I just have to make, you know
as long as it works and the
pricing is right, because I mean honestly
with some of these older games and stuff, why am I
going to rent it if I can buy a used
copy of it for just about the same price
you know, like hell fuck, I just bought
Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2 for five bucks
I'm not going to rent it
Is this why GameStop
might think they're in trouble though, like they're thinking the opposite
you're thinking, that people will want to rent
because it's so convenient? No, because that's why rental
stores are around, I mean you can rent games if you want
to usually, I mean depending on your area
I guess, and those are kind of
gone by the wayside anyways, and they already have
they have games in Redbox so you can get
like for example Metal Gear Solid
or Metal Gear Solid 5, Ground Zeroes
you probably could have rented that for like two bucks
or whatever and
that's available to you
but it's just whether you want to do it or not
Shane, what are your thoughts on PlayStation Now?
Well as someone who may or may not
have played it
I may or may not agree
with what he said, especially
the parts about
it not being laggy
or
responsive, like
say for example, hypothetical
hypothetical
playing Luminesce
if I were in the beta
I may have problems
or may have had problems
playing Luminesce because
of the responsiveness
of the controller or
that stupid music
game shooter thing where you play
backwards and it's all based on the
retrograde which I liked. No, no
I'm saying based on a PlayStation
Now experience that I may or may not have had
yeah
that was ridiculously hard
because of that, or would have been
if I was playing it
but I think
otherwise I agree with what he said
I
worry about that delay between
input because it makes music
games hell, it makes a lot of action games or anything
especially a very demanding
platformer that you have to time
your jumps perfectly and shit
NES Remix which I know isn't a PlayStation
game but hear me out
that would be murder on that so they really need to
tighten that up. It's murder on any game
like maybe in the
past when they had Guacamelee up
to play and if I had been
playing it just normal jumps would
have been awful to get to
various parts in that game
making me turn off the system
alright
well I
really appreciate the email from
ElDuckSauce so please
who has a new nickname thanks
to Shane? You never had
one before but you do know. I can nickname everybody
that you have for the mailbag
so let's go with the next one
we'll get to it, hold on because in the chat TigerCaw
asks, Sky you tried watching
Sabado Higante, yes I have
that shit is amazing, it's like a
game show, variety show
that's the type of stuff that used to
be on the TV in the golden age here
in America and you don't see it anymore
but you're still doing that stuff on Sabado Higante
which Act F corrects
is on Univision
not Telemundo, yes it's the other
big Spanish network
so there you go
yes I do enjoy watching Sabado Higante
I have no idea what they're saying but some of the
sketches are still hilarious and I can
I can pick up enough words
you know
like if I'm watching a
telenovela
and one chick calls another
a peta, like I know what they're saying
no
alright, moving on
we have another email from
this one is from
Martin from
Belgium, Martin
from Belgium, he's emailed us before
I thought I was giving a nickname, well that's
that's the name, what should Martin
but there's no nickname, Martin is I think their real
name, like you know
Martin but Belgium, what you gonna give
a nickname or not, not now?
you're protesting? I'm protesting, I was going
to give it before
we, okay we'll assume I didn't say his
name, it's too late, I can't do that
cause now I'm like oh his nickname
will be Martin
alright
Dear Sky Dark Soccer and Loki, I wanted to email
you this week since you were kind enough to remember
on last week's show that you have listeners in Belgium
I got your back, I got your back
I remember, why are you laughing?
I just took that as a dig at you
yeah cause I usually forget
a lot of things, I really do
congratulations on your 550th episode
that's an impressive number, now on to
I listened to the show on my commute to work, a welcome
distraction, I've been playing FTL
faster than light this week, my god is it
addictive, again, they just released
a free expansion pack adding new ships, weapons
and events which made the game interesting again
since I got burned out on it last time
is it the kind of game that incites
it is the kind of game that incites comments
such as crap, it is that time already
I just played FTL for 5 hours and it felt like
5 minutes, it seems to make time move
around you faster than light
that came with a winky face, that's an apology
for that pun, definitely recommend
it, also wanted to share
something gaming hardware related, I just
got a new Retina MacBook Pro recently which
is pretty good hardware for gaming, an Nvidia
750M, but tends to get very hot
due to the thin form factor, I came
up with a cooling solution for when I'm using it at my desk
for gaming, I prop up the MacBook on
a giant heat sink and have a
120mm fan blowing
cool air through it, the heat at the
bottom of the aluminum case is conducted through the
heat sink and blown away, I attached a
picture, this lowers the system temperature
significantly while gaming
anyway, keep up the great show so I have something to do
on my commute to work, greetings from
Belgium, the land of beer and waffles
just one 120mm fan?
you forgot fries
by the way, I went to a place
in New York City once, it was nothing but Belgian fries
and dips, it was so fucking good
I went to a place that was just all fries
this weekend, it's called
Potato Corner, and they have
six types of fries and they're all different flavors
where is this at? This sounds amazing
Paladio, it's in the food court
I'm gonna have to check that out, I don't know what that is
alright, there's a PS
by the way before I get to the picture, PS I'm on my way
to go paintballing right now which I also recommend
it's like a real life video game and also good exercise
well that's something Loki used to do, the paintballing
I did airsoft
paintball's a little bit more honest because you can actually
see when you hit somebody and can't say
I didn't hit, what are you talking about?
and here's the picture
of the heat sink and the fan
against the laptop, that seems to be
pretty, I bet if Loki had
did that when he was doing Titanfall
his laptop would not have melted
I did not have my
heat sink or fan
when I was playing Titanfall because I was at work
and I don't bring it with me because it's fucking huge
and also requires an external
12 volt power supply in order to run
those fans, and I actually don't use those fans anymore
because my new laptop's pretty cool
I just have to
use that tray because it still gets warm
on the bottom, just not to the point where
it's gonna break
damn you aces
if I still buy you
alright
now onto our last
email tonight
which is a follow up to an email we got
last week, which Shane you let me know during the break
you don't listen to OLR so you didn't hear
of this email, you know I was asleep
alright, well
last week we had an email
from Dr. Noir
who emailed us from Lima, Peru
and said they could not remember the name
of a game, it was an 8 or 16
bit game where you place
so here's the description of the game for you Shane
cause you asked, so here it is, Shane
you gotta guess, you ready?
it's an 8 or 16 bit game
where you place mythical creatures
I remember unicorns and dragons
on a hex board to do battle
against monsters on a turn based
strategy system, the creatures
level up after they acquire kills
the name and platform for the game
is what I'm after, and a source
would be appreciated since I wanna play it
with my kids, Shane
can you name that game?
no
what is
crappy RTS on
the Genesis or Super Nintendo
and he wagered
one dollar, no I put
everything, it was like 30 million
alright, well
somebody last week got it right
Dr. Noir's emailing
us again, hi OL Army
greetings from Buenos Aires, Argentina
he's moving around
he explains why in the email
thanks for the answer
Master of Monsters it is
I played the Genesis version
oh I got some of that right
yeah Genesis or
Super Nintendo, yeah but it could've been
8 bit, so I was still
half right, so there it is Master of
Monsters it is, and somebody in chat had
yelled that out last week and I think Sega gave him a
free game for getting it, so
thank you chatters, you saved the date, that's why
I love doing this live show, and I fully
admit, sometimes I don't know it
when we're talking about video games, and Loki don't
know it, and Jamie doesn't know it, and Shane sure
don't know it, sorry I don't know all the obscure RTS
back from the 8 bit days, but we had
the chat room to save the day, and it was Master
of Monsters was the game, and
he goes on to say Sky, sorry for the
headache, it wasn't
really your question that was causing the headache
I had a lot going on during the show last week
there was a lot going on, everything's
better now, and
Dr. Noir wants to clarify, I'm Mexican
but I travel a lot for my
sales job, listen to you soon
we'll say hello to everybody in Argentina if you
haven't already left, so there it is
Dungeon Buster, taking a bow in
a victory lap in our chat room for remembering
Master of Monsters, and
all of our listeners as well can finally
go, finally
and it's funny because my buddy Jonko
from Koopa Club actually left
a comment on the Orange Launch Radio page
it was like, what if like
somebody just made something up that didn't exist
and sent it to your email bag, like how
I was like, I kind of thought that's what
happened, like not that I thought Dr. Noir would lie
I certainly wouldn't think he would lie, but you know
how like memory can change details
sometimes, like you think it was one
thing but it was- I know, there was
seriously, there was seriously
one of those fucking meditroid
energy tanks in one spot, and I wrote
down on like, cause back in the day I used
to have like a place I'd write down you know where stuff
was, and it wasn't fucking there
any other time I went back there, and I know
was there cause I got it one time
and it was never there again
damn anomalies
Well Dungeon Buster did not go away
unrewarded, he does clarify in chat
Seg gave away a copy of
Dominique Pamplemousse, which Seg was here
on the show promoting about a month or so
ago, which is available on Steam, check
it out, if you like kind of artsy
games that are kind of click adventures
that are musicals, check
that out, Dominique Pamplemousse, and thanks Seg
for giving that out
Black Wolf says master of monsters for classic game
of the week, I was trying to pressure
Jamie into doing that tonight actually
but then she ended up not being here and I was like
alright well, Shane doesn't always get to pick
so I'll let him pick, and I would not have agreed
with that, this
crappy RTS came out
in some stupid time
stop it
alright, anyhow
moving
on, that is
that is that, that's it for the mailbag
get to the FUs of the week, thank you guys very much
for emailing us, participate
at Orangeloungeradio.com
is the place where you can send us emails
if you want to try and stump
the hosts
or ask Shane for an answer, then he'll just
go, well it's maybe
black or white or kind of in between
it might be anything actually
no, I gave an answer, it was pretty
like the only thing I was wrong on
or you know, not sure if it was the Genesis
or Super Nintendo part
but it was stupid RTS with unicorns
or whatever
alright, alright
let's move on and
get into the FUs of the week
Loki, why don't you start us off tonight
because Jamie's not here
I guess FU2
or future FU2
I'm gonna have to make
actual levels for my game
and I was thinking about it today
I'm like, out of all the things I'm gonna have to do for this
that's gonna be the hardest
so, as fun as it will be
making stuff, that's not gonna be fun to
actually do because you have to
you know, find a
nice balance between detail
and optimization
little voxels
a little difficult
alright, Shane, do you have an FU of the week?
I sure don't
alright
I'm gonna take one that I think you wish
you would have thought of, my FU of the week
goes to PG&E
man, it was fun
who banged on my door at 9 o'clock this morning
that were like
we're here to shut off the gas because you don't have an account
through us
I'm like, because you remember, we just moved into this house
about 6 weeks ago at this point
and I'm like, da fuck?
I'm like, yes we do, I called in to get it arranged
I logged into the website and gave this lady my account number
and she was like, dumbstruck, like awestruck
like, how could this happen?
what is this internet that you've talked about?
I know, well she even admitted, she's like, I'm an older lady
I don't know anything about this internet
when she realized I wasn't
like, that I had the receipts
I'm like, here's the receipts, lady
here they are
I know, she backed off a lot
she became very apologetic, she's like
oh, something's going on, let me take that down
well yeah, it's like, god dammit, someone
all of us fucked up again
well first off, Shane was like, how do you even know that was real
and maybe I don't, like it could have been a fake truck
or something, but
well she was just so crazy in her knocking
and doorbell ringing
they didn't ask for my social security or anything
so I was like, alright, whatever
but yeah, I was like, that was a little weird
I think cops knock on like
criminals' doors nicer, because this is what she did
okay, etiquette dictates
that you ring the doorbell
you wait a couple moments
no answer, you knock politely
you may repeat these steps again
she was, knock, knock, knock
doorbell, doorbell, doorbell, doorbell
knock, knock, doorbell, doorbell
so she was my wife
this is what my wife does
whenever she goes to her parents' house
and they're like, yep, it's Nellie
it's 9 AM on a Sunday
and I have a rock and roll lifestyle
yes, I am still asleep
and Alan
obviously I made Alan
get up
I know, I'm poking Alan
get the door
Alan gets up and gets it and is like, the lawn
better be on fucking fire
so yeah, that's what it was
so
F you to PG&E for getting me up
early on a Sunday morning, and then I was up
you should complain
I did what people do in the year 2014
and I sent a passive aggressive tweet
that's what I did
I would have called them up and complained
because then you would be like, listen, they woke me up
you said that I didn't have an account
and you were threatening to shut off my stuff
I had to show you
this information that's available in your system
maybe they would have knocked off some money on your bill
we'll see what happens, I'm gonna see if I get a response on Monday
because then if I don't get a response
then that's two strikes
they knocked on my door
and didn't acknowledge my passive aggressive tweet
come on, check what year it is
I needed to get somebody that knew how to use a computer
that was my problem
alright, computer? what?
what is computer? there's no computer in this house
it's too small
how do you internet?
alright, which room do you have
dedicated to said computer?
couple more news stories for you guys
then we're gonna get to you guys at
where does the reel-to-reel tape go?
or our username on skype
orange lounge radio, all one word
let's get to a couple more stories, Loki
alright, so, talking about
like, really strange accusations
um
ZeniMax
they're claiming that
IPs were thefted
thefted
um, see
to el-duckface
verbs?
oh, sorry, el-duck-sauce
I couldn't remember the name
I hate, I did that on purpose
ok, that was purposefully mispronounced
alright, fine
because it was funny
tense is hard
it's for humor, ok
so yes, basically they claim that
when John Carmack left he took
some proprietary VR
information and now
they're pissed off and they think that
money should be owed
little do they realize that
oculus was around before he left
for oculus
so, I don't understand that
part of it, but whatever
um, basically
seeing as ZeniMax
um, you know
they send a formal notice
regarding its legal rights to oculus concerning
its ownership of key technology used by oculus
to develop and market the oculus rip
I just don't buy that, I mean
I don't know, I
maybe John Carmack was working on some
VR stuff separate to the oculus rip
but I don't think that, it's not like he
left, formed oculus
rift, and then that
all happened, you know, it was
he came and joined them after
they already kind of had a prototype and
everything, so I don't really understand what
the point is
um, I'm guessing that they just want a piece
of that 2 billion dollars maybe
maybe, now that Facebook's involved, the timing
of it is a little suspicious
of course, you know, John Carmack has, you know
responded saying, no work I have ever done
has been patented
ZeniMax owns the code that I wrote
but they don't own VR
ouch
you know, Bobby told a very, you know, as
I'm nice in promoting Bobby, even though he keeps
telling me tonight I'm wrong, and Loki's right
but Bobby told a very interesting story tonight
on his show, uh, Bobby Blackhole's show
that, uh, about getting hired
for tech companies, cause he's been job hunting lately
and, you know, some of the things that they
expect that they're gonna own of you if you go
for this company, and like, if you write any code
even if you're not on the clock, but you're with the company
they potentially own it, so
I'll let him tell the story, you can go listen to
his show for the full details, but uh, yeah
you know, it's kind of interesting how legally
that all works when you're on somebody's payroll
like that, so that's
what they're trying to make the case
they're trying to say that someone possibly owns the rights to flappy vog
they could
if Bobby did not put a clause
in his contract or whatever, that's like
vog is a pre-existing thing and you can't
touch it, basically, if he didn't do that
uh, which I think
if I remember, I'm probably gonna be wrong again
but I believe if I listen to his show correctly
one of the people he was talking to
and getting employed at was like, we will own everything
basically, and he said no
because he didn't want them owning vog
but he got another employer that was like
you know, willing to write out, you know
things that, they, like
who's interested in vog, the types of companies he was
working for shouldn't have an interest in vog, it's not
like, not the same industry or whatever
we're interesting, what the hell
I mean, they should be interested
we're just not worth it to you guys
we've only been on the internet forever
but you know, whatever, I guess we're just not good
we're not an IGN or Kotaku
we don't run, you know
Loki, you can't get a fucking NeoGaf account, okay?
we've been doing this for 12 years
I don't even fucking care anymore about NeoGaf
it's just like, seriously
it doesn't mean shit, unfortunately
if I write another forum thread about
what game should I buy
it's like, seriously, that is worthy of a friend
that person deserved an account
you know, to, you know
that was worth it
fuck it, I don't give a shit anymore
well, speaking of things
that have been on the internet forever and forever
yet a lot of people don't seem to care
Twin Galaxies made an announcement this week
I thought they were gone!
oh, hold on, let me sip my tea
I thought they were gone though, didn't they go under or something?
nope, they're back
I think they have a new owner or something
but Twin Galaxies has announced that there's a
24-7 internet channel
dubbed Twin Galaxies Live
using Skype and Twitch
to foster interaction between broadcasters and audience members
and there's also like a schedule
of all these things so they can see what's coming up next
the COO of Twitch said in a press release
that since records are constantly being set
and broken in real time on Twitch
having Twin Galaxies on our platform
is a perfect fit
we look forward to seeing great gaming content from the Twin Galaxies team
hmm, 24-7 internet channel
fully interactive
featuring things like Skype and video
never heard of it!
the only thing I'm kind of
worried about
is some of those records
especially when they're doing like these
high score records and stuff
require like 48 hours of playing
I'm not gonna fucking watch somebody play Donkey Kong
for 48 hours or however long it takes
it's several hours
I don't really mean to shade Twin Galaxies
because I do respect the site
and what it is an awful lot I do
but with all due respect
I have to go here, Logie
with all due respect
to our former home, All Games
All Games Radio, right?
I seem to remember back in the day
during All Games Interactive
somebody that he had on the show a lot
was Walter Day
from where?
Twin Galaxies
fully interactive content
I'm just an observation
I'm just...
just interesting
to be fair
there's a lot of people doing this
I think that they have now
because remember they have the awesome
games done quick type thing
where they had an event where they did that
I think they're actually continuing on with that
and that's still going
as its own channel now
where you can watch people do speedruns and stuff
it's more interesting than watching someone try to go for
the world record score in
some game
what's to say that they're actually
going to achieve that
score?
so all I'm doing is watching some person
who may not even be
a celebrity even in the gaming
scene or anything
making an attempt at a high score
so basically I'm just watching someone play a game
which is any channel on Twitch
any channel
and these people
who's giving commentary
we're in hour 46
of the
high score challenge
some people would make fun of the
Starcraft and League of Legends type of commentary
so whatever
what do you talk about at that point though
when it's gone on for several
hours you can't talk about the game
wow this part of the game is really interesting
he's gonna have to
not die in order to make sure that he
keeps a high score
that's why they have
those long videos that Twin Galaxy watches
so you don't have to watch
the 48 hour attempt to get
whatever it is high score
and granted yes I know not every high score is gonna take
48 hours but it's still several hours
usually
in all seriousness good luck to them
please tell me that they're gonna go for the records for the quickest times
finishing these games because
then they've totally ripped off the other channel
alright
yeah we're done moving to the Skype calls
1877 Game O.L.R. your chance to be
interactive through Skype with our stuff
1877 Game O.L.R. or a username
on Skype Orange Lounge Radio all one word
if you want to give us a call and talk about anything we've talked
about tonight or possibly something
else maybe there's something in the news we missed that you
want to talk to us about hey stay tuned until the
end of the show because I do have an announcement
regarding next week's show it's a
pretty good one so stay tuned for that
hey can we get like a world record
for like the most views in like
a what's
what's that uh the channel or whatever
that they have you know the PlayStation 4 thing with
the camera and playroom playroom
yes they should have a world record for the most
views consecutive
views of playroom you know whatever
it takes it would be pretty high from those
chicks who are taking their tops off I've seen
like up the ante I've seen 800
viewers in a channel sacrifice
alright well we got the phones ringing so let's get to it hi you're on
Orange Lounge Radio who's this the
residential convention whore Ranma
hey Ranma how's it going
good good good how
about you guys uh we are
doing very well
so I hear y'all kind of playing
around since Jamie's not there
guys night out I don't know if I call it
playing around you know Shane's
just running his mouth but what else is new
I'm not running my mouth I had my
microphone on mute
but uh
sure it can be it can be a bro down tonight
what do you want to um what do you want to chat with us about
alright I want to talk about something different
I don't know if you saw this but
last week you know
how Nintendo is releasing
the limited edition Mario
Kart 8 green
edition in Europe right
now I posted it on my
Facebook and I said that
they want $300 or I guess
$330 for this
fuck you Nintendo
wait till the price drops to $250 then
we can talk because I personally think
that it's overpriced for the technology
that's behind it and if you
saw it became a very interesting
conversation now a couple
days later I checked my I noticed
I have a message waiting for me on
Facebook in my other folder I go check it out
somebody was
really so butthurt
that they decided to write
a flame essay
to me about
why the Wii U
doesn't suck
and this is how Facebook
is ruining America to be
quite honest I just
sat there and I just laughed
and he's telling me
that I'm a moron for thinking
that and as he's
trying to tell me it's better he goes
into reviewing some
new Mario Brothers or something else
how it's so much better and I'm just like
if you're going
to flame me at least be a little bit
more precise
flame me straight forward
I understand everybody has their
consoles what they like and don't like
because when I first got my 360
I dealt with the same thing
I bought the 360 because at the time
it has more games
that I will play on it
now that I have a 360 and a PS3
if you look at my library
I think it's
3 to 1 of
360 games of PS3 games
some of the Nintendo fans
are extremely passionate
and you know
I understand
you know what's funny Rama
there's people that listen to this show that call me
a Nintendo fanboy and that I'm
blind to all this other stuff you know or whatever
and I kind of think
I usually think I'm pretty equally
critical and fanboy
you know there's things I love about
Nintendo but there's things that really bother me
about them too
I don't think you're being fanboy-ish at all
maybe you are but for every single
console that comes out
we rejoice
for a while and then we're like
wait what are you doing
we gotta call you out and just
play it down the middle
you know
so I mean personally
I just look at it from a technological
point of view I just personally feel
Nintendo is asking for too
much money but as we all know
Nintendo is probably the only company
that makes a profit off of their
consoles
right they do now
I don't think they used to but they do now
well from my understanding
from back as
8-bit NES they were making profit
over every single console till the 3DS
then they had to do the price
cut and I think they're
now making money off of that and
did they profit on GameCube? I thought GameCube
was one where they didn't profit I could be wrong
I think they made like between $15
to $20 off of every
GameCube sold
that's part of their strategy
like I said the power behind it
if Nintendo was to knock it down to $250
I
had no problem going to Nintendo World
or Best Buy whatever and giving them my money
and walking out with a system I'm just waiting
for the price to come down and I'm not gonna
make the same mistake I did with the N64
buying it for one game and realizing that I'm not
really liking this game
so
where are things now with you and this guy
like did you just end up banning him
or what? no no he sent the
message and he blocked me after
he sent it so I went to my personal
blog and I
just said my piece and walked away
I mean what did he hope to gain
from that whole thing I mean when you come out swinging
like that he's figured out that I'm right
and the fact that he's like
I'm wrong he's like
he also bought it for his kid I'm like
you are not setting a
proper precedent sir you need
to stop yeah like I don't know
like I just don't think that's the right way to win somebody's
opinion over going fuck you you
fucking fuck you know like I just don't think
that's the right way to do it like I think just kind of like
Rama are you considering this
or something like that might be like a better
way to do it right exactly
so if
only more people in the gaming industry could kind of think
that way not I shouldn't say the industry gaming fandom
really could think that way right
not just gaming fandom
ain't that the truth
alright Rama anything else to share
with our listeners tonight yes
I picked up yet another bumper for
the VoG network oh
wow what'd you get this time check
it out oh boy
my name is Voltaire and you are listening to
VoG on the VoG network
geek shows for
geeks by geeks I'm a geek are you a geek
I hope you are because if not don't hit me
not the face not Papa's money maker
that was
great alright
that was great that's awesome
Voltaire?
who's that Voltaire
Voltaire
Shane doesn't know who Voltaire is Rama
wait wait Shane doesn't know who
Voltaire is I don't know who Voltaire is should I know
GTFO
I
don't know who fucking Voltaire is
you know I
beaten around the bush who the fuck is this person
and why should I care I know thanks
to VoG network dot com but go ahead Rama
Voltaire is a
geek centric music composer
pretty much
he did a song that plays on VoG
from time to time called the USS makes
shit up
uh
he's named I keep finding the
classic one I'm trying to find the newer musician
there it is that's
what he looks like
there but usually he's dressed
up in more garb or whatever I don't use
yeah he kind of was he was also pretty
drunk and tipsy too
well go search VoG network
because I remember there was an I love
this song article yeah yep good job
alright good job
and now you've educated on who he is
and I forget tomorrow Brad says
he's a dragon caller actually his music's really good
it's kind of like it's like goth-y nerdy
stuff it's pretty cool so
alright Rama I'm going to let you go to get more
calls in but thanks so much for the call hey no problem
bro stay black alright I will
bye
alright
1877 game OLR our
username on Skype orange lounge radio
if you want to give us a call I'm not going to keep it open
too too long cause
we're running a little long tonight it's already
915 here on the west coast
our first part of the show was a little bit long
I'm actually trying to
go to the twitter right now I didn't see a whole lot of links
or anything come through but I think I saw some
like FYI
heads up types of things coming over
I see darkdetsuya sending us a tweet saying
apparently one of our other local indie
podcast Fistful of Potions
was taping at a local comic shop during
free comic book day that's pretty cool
cool yeah I wouldn't have thought to do that
but I know a lot of people getting out during
free com- excuse me
free comic book day so that's pretty awesome that they
participated I on the
other hand missed free comic book day
and I missed what was the other
free day they did not let it all go I'm missing
all the free days it's sad
but anyway we have another call coming in hi you're on
Orange Lounge Radio who's this?
Hey Zaku long time no chat how you
doing?
Yeah me too except without
Gran Turismo oh you got a little
rig look at that he can explain those cars
he explained all the car names
that Shane butchered earlier
are you saying your goodbyes to Gran Turismo 5
or are you on 6 now?
So I mean they're calling online multiplayer
so I kind of well I'm kind of
regretting the fact that I never partaken in it
so this kind of makes up for it
I kind of you know
after a while I had to
you know give in and buy 6
but at least I have a steering wheel for it though
so that's probably the only
good the only good thing about it
yes nice shiny
Logitech G27
yeah
let me see
yeah that whole
I guess that whole stick
with the you know
with call of duty
essentially like jumping the shark again
you know releasing the
trailer for the new version
and I'm just like wondering
whether or not like
Activision is repeating history in terms
of saturating the market with one particular
genre of video game to the point
where it's critical mass
and it basically
it just crashes
well it's only one a year right?
I mean this has been happening in sports games
since video games existed
so maybe not
sports games it's kind of expected
you know
you know players expect
an updated roster to reflect
the you know the current
state of the
Zaku you were a big time Bamani fan
you used to put out new DDR's every year
and I think it was very disappointing when they stopped
true but I got over it
and that's why I have 2DX to
fall back on
but even then you do have a point
in that you know they also release
arcade mixes every year
for certain of theirs
but I guess the point that I'm trying to make is that
everything that Activision
has pretty much you know
taken to the extreme ran with
has pretty much at some point
fizzled out for them
and so I'm just wondering whether or not
Call of Duty is the next one because
at this point Activision isn't really
doing anything other than
Call of Duty and Skylanders
wait a minute though
because Activision has Blizzard
which has a whole other thing going on there
Activision is partnered with Bungie
Activision is going to have Destiny
that has the potential to be huge
they also have Skylanders
yeah well he said Skylanders
aside from that it's just licenses
like you would expect
someone to be diversified
let's say like EA for example
which learned the hard way to not
really rest on
you know on a short thing
wait are you counting out Cabela's?
but that's like
that's a cash grab
that's what
I just mentioned
you know what EA did
what EA did to diversify their
portfolios they bought a bunch of other
companies with the cash on hand
they have the partnership with BioWare
they freaking own PopCap
and have just kind of ruined it
as we all knew they would and so on
who's more likely to take a chance
on something new?
them or Activision?
neither, what's going to end up happening
is that indies are going to be the ones
that take a chance on something new
the thing is the trend in the gaming industry
right now especially the big AAA publishers
you publish less titles
but better titles and that's what they're doing
they're sticking with titles that they're going to
have no problems with
although Activision occasionally will take like
a license like
Walking Dead or The Fast and the Fierce
and take a big pile of shit on top of it
I don't know how you fucking ruin
a Walking Dead game
the game of the year version
Zaku, Loki makes a great point about
the indies are going to be the ones that really innovate
EA and Activision are probably kicking
themselves that they didn't think of Minecraft
they probably tried to write
I bet you both those companies
have offered to write Notch a blank
check to get Minecraft
and you know as much as Notch's stubbornness
kind of drives us all bonkers in the industry
sometimes when it comes to things like Oculus Rift
you have to hand it to him that he has
not sold that out
true, that is true, he basically
I mean with the whole Facebook
deal he pretty much flat out
explained why he didn't want
why he didn't want to back that
horse anymore because it was pretty much
funded by a mega
corporation that started out small
but then it became
a lot larger than it
it just became something huge
and something critical in everyday lives
and that's not what he wants to happen to Mojang
exactly, they don't want to
jump the shark essentially in their own
corporate culture, they believe in terms
of not being
the man instead of
as opposed to just them going against
the man which is what they're doing and
so far I mean you know
Mojang's doing pretty damn well
especially for something that was essentially
a beta for most of its existence
I mean that was like one of the
best selling betas you know
long before DayZ
on Steam and that's not even out
yet and people are still paying
$30 just to try the game
that still might have
still rough around the edges
alright well
Zaku I've got to wrap things up because we're going to be
wrapping up the show but any other thoughts real quick
I guess
the only one I had that I was
trying to get to last week was the whole
Nintendo basically
doing everything
in their power to shoo away independent
developers meanwhile Sony
and Microsoft I would imagine
have like developer outreach divisions
just for independent developers
Sony sure does at this point
did you see this week on their blog
Sony was like on just some
random ass Wednesday or Thursday it was just
like hey guess what BAM
announcement BAM announcement
BAM Spelunky PlayStation 4
BAM I mean like it was like all these indie
announcements came out in advance of E3 this week
on Sony I mean not to mention
I even bought Guacamelee
like an hour ago
on PSN I was just
like trying to grab whatever you know
some of the flash sales some of the things selling this
weekend so I mean it
gives credence to the fact that
Sony and Microsoft
they you know they try to diversify
and not just AAA
games but just something that would give
you a reason to buy their platform even
if it's a small one. I would say
Nintendo's got a
has got an image problem in
the development community right now
both large and small both third party
and independent and people can argue with me
all they want on that I think we would be fighting
over the severity of that honestly but
I think no matter where you look at it Nintendo's got an image
problem they've got to fix.
And it goes it further
reinforces the point why developers
are running away from the Wii U it's like
it's like a redhead stepchild that
they don't want to talk about because it's
dated it's just
like a I use this expression
from the Simpsons of an episode
where you know they try to reinvent Malibu
Stacy but all they end up doing is just
repackaging her with a new hat
trying to get the Wii U
it's basically the Wii with just an
HDMI port
we'll see what happens come E3
and what Nintendo can do to fix that image problem
but Zaku I'm going to let you go so we wrap up the show
take care buddy. Have a good one. Alright you too.
Alright that is going to do it for the skype line
tonight because we're damn near 9.30
so I've got to wrap up the show I'm very sorry to those
that didn't get through if you wanted to get on
tonight's show and you weren't able to get through please consider
sending us an email participate at orangelandtrady.com
or you can send us a tweet
on twitter.com slash o-l-r
I'm going to check in with Loki real quick to see if he has
any last minute stories
yeah real quick there's a couple things
one there's this game
I actually saw on Kickstarter it's
sort of looks like Jet Set Radio
it's called
Hover Revolt of Gamers
and there's gameplay
they kind of describe it like
Mirror's Edge and Jet Set Radio
well to make it even
more like Jet Set Radio or
Grind Radio
they have a stretch goal of 60,000
which is going to add the
composer Hideki
Naganuma
which I hope I didn't mispronounce
that but he was the original producer
or the original composer for
that's right Jet Set Radio
oh interesting
so
that would be pretty cool
and then this is kind of
neat looking
this thing called Project Evo
and it's apparently an
iOS game made by this company
Akili Interactive Labs
and apparently playing this game
will be able to kind of
evaluate you to see if you might be
susceptible
for
what is it? Alzheimer's
so that's
kind of interesting and they're also saying that they're
attempting to use
the same research I guess to
diagnose ADHD, autism
and depression
kind of neat game that can
basically
evaluate your state of being
and
last but not least
this game actually I saw a while ago
Hat in Time
it was also another Kickstarter project and
what's kind of cool about it is it looks very much like
Wind Waker and
apparently now they're having the
alpha version of the game available if you
backed it or if you have it on pre-order
and it looks very very very pretty
so check that out if you like the
Wind Waker platformer type games
and your games look very very pretty
alright
well that is going to wrap up another episode of
Orange Lounge Radio but I do have one other
last minute story, this involves next week's
show, this is pretty cool, Loki I don't even
think I've had a chance to tell you about this yet
but next week on the show we're going to have a special guest
we are going to have a live interview
and this is pretty cool, we're going to have
a live interview here on the show with
Christopher Tin who is the
composer of
Baba Yetu the song that won a Grammy
the first song that ever won a Grammy
from a video game
so Christopher Tin is going to be on next week's show
he'll be here live to take your questions
so
make sure you're here next week
live Sunday night May 11th 6 o'clock Pacific
9 o'clock Eastern at the Voice Geeks Network
live.vognetwork.com
Christopher Tin is promoting a new album
and we'll talk of course about his experiences
winning the Grammy and composing
for SIV and I definitely want to get into some of the
questions about how video games kind of continue
to influence him if they do and all
that so he will be here live and your questions
as well in the chat room live.vognetwork.com
alright that is going to do
it for tonight's episode, we're going to go around and get everybody's
final thought here first
Shane, thanks for filling in tonight
appreciate it, I'm sure
in the coming weeks we'll see more of you
especially now that you're back here in Northern California
but do you have any final thoughts for listeners tonight?
no
unless you guys can give me some stuff in
Pokemon
what Pokemon do you need, what ones are left?
I don't know, I have their Dex numbers written down somewhere
I am like 7 away from being done
wow, you made progress tonight
you're 17 at the start of the show
go you, I know, I'm awesome
alright, my final thought tonight
is they
need to fix that freeway faster
because I'm not looking forward to getting Alan from work
with all that stupid freeway mess
stupid highway 50
what freeway mess?
highway fix 50, that whole thing
haven't you heard about that?
I saw, I keep seeing the things for it
with your commute and everything, you never really go through downtown
I have to do this
I fucking hate downtown
I know, I know, I like downtown
but I don't like driving there
I like the shops and stuff downtown but I fucking hate driving
I hate driving to any major city
well, Sacramento is a pre-major city
but it's not like San Francisco
but I hate metropolitan areas
I hate driving and that kind of stuff
alright, Loki, your final thought tonight
my final thought is hopefully I have enough
caffeine or consciousness
in me to get some more
coding done this weekend
hopefully I'm going to work a little bit more on
asset stuff so that the next video I do
will actually be interesting
and I have something to show
it was funny, the first video I recorded
the microphone from my webcam
was on, I'm like
why do I hear clicking?
oh, it's picking that up
and the second video, of course, I talk a little bit
but see, I talk really quietly
because I'm up at night
like at 11 o'clock at night
my wife's asleep, so I can't talk
loud because I didn't wake everybody up
be very quiet
alright, that does it for another episode of Orange Launch Radio
if you listen to the whole show
thank you very much for sticking with it tonight
we really appreciate it, you know
we don't ask for money for doing this show
I mean, we wouldn't necessarily turn it down either
but no, in all seriousness, all we ask
tell a friend or two about the show
help spread the word about Orange Launch Radio
and help grow our family, because like Loki said earlier
we've been doing this show for 12 years
and no one knows
so help us break that by
getting more people to listen to our show
we appreciate it, grow our family
thank you guys very much for supporting independent radio
and that's going to do it for this week
I should be back, Christopher Tin will be here
it's going to be a big show, so don't miss it
next week, we'll see you then, good night
but you know they were all still true
see you next week
thanks for watching!