[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, May 19, 2013, Nintendo makes a controversial move against Let's Play videos, virtual trading cards come to Steam, and a new Gran Turismo game is announced for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is Orange Lounge Radio for this May 19th, 2013, episode number 505 of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: My name is Rob Roberts and I'll be joining you over the next few hours to talk about games and gaming news with all you in our chat and listening on our podcast feed and my co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining us remotely tonight, say hello to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, how are you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a cold.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How'd you get that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's like, I just have allergies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's share a soda.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oops, sorry, it was cold.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought maybe he might have got something at that whole Pentagogo thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you go to that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which was this weekend?
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: There ain't shit in Dixon either.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a weird place for Pinagogo.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's stuff in Dixon.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's pollen and a really good ice cream parlor.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't even have a 24-hour Starbucks anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they do have a Mary's Pizza shack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, they do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they do have Pinagogo, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently this year was supposed to be totally bombed.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had every spot filled.
[SPEAKER_07]: They couldn't take any more people in because of power usage.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really wanted to go because they had all kinds of prototype machines and they had the new X-Men table and all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really wanted to go, but Dan was sick and I wasn't going to go without him because I have no other reason to go to Dixon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who can blame you?
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll also say hello to, here in studio, Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Techmaster Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm organizing Steam games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now what was this you were trying to figure out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe one of our listeners knows because we do have the live chat room at live.vognetwork.com when we are live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do have the chatters joining us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe one of them knows the answer to your question.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was just wondering if there's a way to... Oh, I guess there's different categories and stuff you could say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just seeing if there's a way to, like, you know... Oh, okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Categories.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can add categories to the games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, the folder sort some of the games I have, because I have now over 100 games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Amazon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they have a crazy sale recently or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's still going until the end of the month.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's their mega sale or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a whole bunch of games and bundles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some really good Sonic bundles.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you like Sonic the Hedgehog, you can get almost all the games that they have on PC, including the Genesis stuff, for like $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a Steam sale, but it's on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, actually, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been finding a lot of these sales on Steam games on other sites, like Green Man Gaming or Amazon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Amazon, for a lot of the stuff, even Gamefly has stuff, and it's all redeemable on Steam or Origin.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually have some games on Origin that I really wanted, but I am not installing Origin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't blame you, sir.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm passing on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Battlefield 3 was $10 on Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really wanted Battlefield 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel like I had to sell my soul to play Mass Effect 3 online on the PC.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I really wanted Command & Conquer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thankfully, I wanted Red Alert 3 because I forgot all about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I went back and I started playing some of the older games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I saw in the trailer for it that they have George the K's in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tim Curry is in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Tim Curry is in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they even have... Oh, who the hell is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see her face and I can't think of her name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jenny McCarthy is in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: She plays Tanya.
[SPEAKER_05]: Random.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, she plays like the assassin chick.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it's so awesome and just...
[SPEAKER_05]: and because they went back in the second game I don't know if they had the full motion video cutscenes but they went back to the way that the first game was where they had full motion video cutscenes and it's just awesome but it also has origin and I'm not I'm not doing that so I'm sorry going to the chat room at live.vognetwork.com Actdeft says you can sort your games in your Steam library so you can at least sort them differently
[SPEAKER_05]: XBOX 720, XBOX INFINITY
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki will do the one-man show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't you do that one year?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've done it a couple times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, those shows are really interesting, you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can discuss pizza and bacon.
[SPEAKER_05]: I might.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I've got stuff to talk about, it's not so bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But trying to stretch like, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: it's more fun when it's live and we have the chatters for that kind of instant feedback too even when we're wrong I can team up with Bobby I guess there you go you can team up with Bobby but I don't think Bobby's looking for a partner that would be hilarious but he's my only friend on multiple gaming services alright let's talk about final predictions for the new Xbox I guess I will start with our resident loud mouth Loki and I say that with love
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'll tell you, I'll just start with what we're not going to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not going to see a date other than holiday.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're not going to see a price.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're not going to hear anything about DRM, so you can just forget about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's going to have to come with press asking follow-up questions, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to say, oh, by the way, use games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think they're even going to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like I said, that's going to be really weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although there are some stories that make me wonder if there is something coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: But once again, everybody has to be on board.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not just them.
[SPEAKER_05]: All platforms have to be on board with it in order for it to work.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know what we're going to really see as far as new games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: Specs, they're going to show us specs.
[SPEAKER_05]: They may show us a box.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you think about it, how hard would it be for them to mock up something?
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't have to be exactly like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can change once it goes to retail, but they can mock up something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just have it there so that people can not bitch about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And things do change before retail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think about the PlayStation 3 boomerang.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be 1080p, 120 frames per second.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to have 20 USB ports in the back.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have a million USB ports and three HDMI ports or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you even need that for?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if you want to, like... A daisy chain.
[SPEAKER_05]: HDMI in, HDMI audio to your receiver, and HDMI to your TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll probably just talk specs.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll talk about, you know, I think they're going to focus a lot on, like, the entertainment stuff, you know, with the whole, you know, taking over your TV, being an entertainment hub.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hope there's something cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't want to see connect, connect, connect, connect, connect.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the new video game console, you want to say something cool?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's shocking.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say, though, I am going to get a new video game console this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am going to buy one of those at launch.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's either going to be the PlayStation 4 or the... My money's on Wii U. For you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: There could be a price cut at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm actually going to second a lot of what Loki said, just because I'm sure we're not going to get a specific date, we're not going to get a specific price point.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get a name, we'll get a few screen captures of video games that are actually PC screen captures.
[SPEAKER_07]: More about it being for entertainment, the multiple use, you get pictures of actor families together looking happy and waving their hands around looking stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stupid and happy, stupid and happy people.
[SPEAKER_07]: um you know the name confirmation just the you I mean I've seen so many Sega announcements and they've been the same I'm not saying what am I saying Sega um Xbox announcements and they've been the same type of thing every year I think it's just going to be their usual pattern I'm not going to be surprised by anything
[SPEAKER_04]: Cirque du Soleil this year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Space ponchos?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, the thing was that the... Information-wise.
[SPEAKER_05]: The actual tent is the space poncho.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like you're in the space poncho.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like meta space poncho.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anything else, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what it should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you guys like the hashtag so much, we now present the Xbox space poncho.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they'll have a...
[SPEAKER_07]: EA humping them in the background and it won't sell in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else you want to say about that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to our chat room, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some comments on Loki's possible solo podcast next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alan Alchemy in chat says, Loki's totally rational and not loud Nintendo critique and discussion hour.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am 100% rational, and I am only, I critique because I love.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya says, Loki's Bacon Pizza Podcast, where do I subscribe?
[SPEAKER_04]: at the hospital when you guys all have heart attacks.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where you subscribe.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: My turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do I predict for Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely you're going to have the name.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Finally, we can stop calling it the 720 and we'll know the real name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unless it is the 720, which would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please no.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please, Microsoft, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've spun around twice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still vote for the lube.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the name Xbox Salub.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Infinity seems probable, but I do think that's more internet wank.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just simply something you haven't heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: My money is on Fusion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Xbox Fusion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, you will get... I think they are going to one-up what Sony did, and I think they will show you what it looks like, even though it is, of course, subject to change.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely not on the date.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely not on the price.
[SPEAKER_04]: That will be E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I think one thing y'all need to be prepared is that there's not going to be a lot of games shown because they've already pretty much come out and said E3 is all about the games and I think that's a really risky move on Microsoft's part because I can just see the Twitter snark now
[SPEAKER_04]: Where are the games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they did say they're going to show the Call of Duty Ghost thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: That will be shown, but that's one game, and that's a game we already kind of knew was coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you're going to see any bang up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to Rumor Wankville.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the wankiest of wanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: If there's a new Killer Instinct game on this Xbox, you ain't seeing it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be an E3 surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be the end of the E3 presentation.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they're going to pull out that kind of wank, that's when that's coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see him do something like that and then just drop the mic at the end.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just drop the mic and walk off the stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or just fire a gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shots fired, Sony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bam.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be a lot I think it's a lot about trying to get the tech world kind of buzzed up a little bit and I think you're going to see much more on the if it's true that they want to replace your cable box which I think could be a likely thing I think we're going to see a lot more about that and definitely interaction between Windows 8
[SPEAKER_04]: and how you can interact with things on your PC and how the PC will work as you know pretty much what you've already seen with Windows Media Center but I think they're going to kind of bump it up a little bit and Windows Phone because you know it's all about the synergy between all those different Microsoft phones.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be all tablets and you know iOS and they come on they know that they're limiting themselves they're not no one is going to buy a Windows Phone for the next Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: But any of that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: The snark in you ought to be asking, will Microsoft let it last more than a year?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or is it going to be the next game room?
[SPEAKER_04]: The next smart glass?
[SPEAKER_04]: The next HD DVD drive?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or on top of that, is half the stuff they're even going to show actually going to be possible?
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, hey, I'm scanning the bottom of my skateboard to bring the artwork into the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Versus, hey, I'm scanning my pictures so that I can get a color for my car.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it always looks pink because the lighting in my room sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you will see some games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a limited amount.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be a lot of what we already know about.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe like a teaser reel of Stay Tuned E3 for more on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, like a full motion video that will make no sense at the very end.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like, you want to see what this is?
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned for E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how it'll end or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll end with Square Enix coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to have... We would like to announce...
[SPEAKER_05]: A game that we're going to announce at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_04]: EA will walk out on stage and go, we are going to give our full support to the next... We believe the next Xbox is the future of gaming and we are going to partner up with the... And we'll be all sitting here going...
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't we hear this before a couple years ago?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, you are correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: They will be out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do think that they're actually going to be in the presentation because one of the rumors was supposed to be that Titan game from the ex-Infinity Ward guys, their new company.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the actual Titan game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the actual Titan game.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you say Titan, my mind goes to Horde House, Blizzard, and all that, and I think of the Project Titan that Blizzard's doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, it's not that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that we can all agree, though, that no matter what Microsoft says, there is going to be a shitstorm on the internet immediately following.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely, which is really interesting because I'm actually going to be out of town.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not going to be able to watch it live or participate in the snark on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to watch it live and I'll participate in the snark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course you will.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should live blog it for us.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I already have my popcorn, so I'm all ready.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a little sad I'm going to be having to watch it late, but I'm going to be up in Reno.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not getting up at 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: to watch this crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be busy.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'll have to kind of wait and see it later and have to go rewind the snark over on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com and I'm kind of curious what you guys think is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says, I'm betting on Xbox Power 3 or X-Cube.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might be a little too close to GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow Next Gen says Xbox Infinity makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: Turn the Infinity symbol right side up and what do you get?
[SPEAKER_04]: The number 8, which can tie into Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my whole kind of like, hmm, with that though is that we had that news, was it this week or last week, that they're going to move on to Windows 8.1, which is that Windows Blue they've been talking about, which is going to be a free upgrade for Windows 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's basically like...
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they should call it the Texaract
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because a Tesseract is a fourth-dimensional cube, since they would have, if you were going by box to cube, the next step up would be a Tesseract.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then again, I watch way too much Cosmos, so just ignore me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are some of the chats from live.vognetwork.com because, again, we do tape live Sunday nights at 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern, and it is all about letting you guys have your voice in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know a lot of you are going to have some reactions after Tuesday, so please, we want them when they're fresh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Email us, mailbag at orangeloundtrader.com, or you can always tweet us at OLR, and we're also on Facebook and Google+.
[SPEAKER_04]: So interact with us and we'll read your comments here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to our gaming weeks and the types of video games that you've been playing this week while you wait for this next wave of game consoles to take off.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: My gaming week was kind of less eventful just because I've been getting ready to leave.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've played Ragnarok online too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm definitely going to quit WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just I'm trying to find a time to log on and finish up some stuff and give people some money if anyone ever went on the Alliance Guild again.
[SPEAKER_04]: For your money, I'll sign into my Paladin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me a dollar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a lot of money on my Alliance account, which makes me kind of want to transfer one of my toons over.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I've been playing some Ragnarok Online 2, and Gravity is doing this sort of drawing thing where you can win a prize.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your name is entered for every hour you're logged in, so there have been a lot of vendors.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of vendors in-game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been doing my weekly Mass Effect 3...
[SPEAKER_07]: I would call it my rant fest whilst playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been doing that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A let's play.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to come up later in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a let's play, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's more or less me just doing the MST3K thing with it and telling off characters and calling Udina asshole.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so a let's bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Mass Effect 3 Rocky Edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so I've been doing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I also bought Borderlands 2 because right now I think it's still on sale on Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: It went to some ridiculous price, like $13.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I went ahead and picked up Borderlands 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even if it's going to make me puke my brains out from motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan had such a good time playing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan also got a new racing rig.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw those pictures on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's got like three monitors, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And a little sit-down seat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, he had the monitors already.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're actually three TVs.
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: and the guy came and delivered it and it was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So he's got a lot of racing going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's looking forward to Grid 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so I've been indirectly participating in his racing addiction by watching him and commenting and going, that car sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's really been the extent of my gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I played something else.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for the life of me, I can't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: So just forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, Off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, I must not have made a big impression.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is Off?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I've heard of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a very, very weird little RPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Especially now that I can play it windowed.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like you are sort of like controlling an avatar and your avatar is called the batter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like a guy with bats.
[SPEAKER_07]: and you go around and do puzzles and talk to people and it's bizarre.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll put it that way.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's free.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was done by...
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to go, you're freaking out over no news, really, nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They haven't done anything, you're just, you know, Yahoo doesn't have the best track record, but still.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I made this comparison on Bobby Blackwell's show when we were doing the call at the end of his show, as we always do, but it's kind of like Grandma taking you to a One Direction concert.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what that buyout feels like.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's One Direction?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a British thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought you were up on all your Brit stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not up on things that suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you do know what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I played a whole bunch of different things this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Started off this week, we did VOG Gaming Night, Grand Theft Auto 3, or 3, Grand Theft Auto 4 free play.
[SPEAKER_04]: I promised I wanted to be there, but I drove to San Francisco to see Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you play the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we just kind of hung out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We were going to try to join other people's free mode games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just a big combat fest.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we didn't really want to shoot each other, which is kind of anti-Grand Theft Auto, but we were just messing around.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we went to the swing set of evil or death or whatever you want to call it, and we're launching cars out of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we messed around with that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then let's see what else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and for next week, I have no idea what we're going to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: So anyone has any suggestions on what you want to play?
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also I'm thinking about maybe toying with the idea of changing the night from Thursday to Friday because I know it gets kind of late, especially when we're starting at 8 o'clock on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, on Thursday night, it's a little odd.
[SPEAKER_05]: But maybe Friday, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also have video capture equipment finally.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got an Elgato Game Capture HD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, you have to tell me how that works, because I really want to get something for the living room here to do that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it looks pretty simple, so I'll have to mess with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, um, okay, so back to games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, so I had the urge this week to play Command & Conquer Red Alert, like, the first one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I was gonna go buy it from Amazon, because they have their sale going.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I was doing some searching and it's freeware!
[SPEAKER_05]: So I downloaded it for free, which is fantastic, that's the best price.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so I installed it, had to add some different patches to it to get it to work in Windows 7.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the first thing I had to do, mod it, because that's what I do, I play modded games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I messed with the rules I had filed to mod...
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of how I had it before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a really cool setup back in the day when I was playing it with all these custom units I made and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I kind of remembered some of that and put it back in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I played a skirmish game last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: It took about, like, two hours.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I was toying with the computer.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't, like, immediately going for the kill.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just letting them kind of, you know, live a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a lot of fun with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It still runs like shit, though, on my computer, which is weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's such an old game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd think with, you know, the...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, you gave it a very favorable review over at VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, my laptop is not very... I mean, the graphics card on it is not great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ran everything in that game on low visual settings, but I never noticed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it looked just like the console version.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, apparently it has really good visuals, but you have to have a pretty decent graphics card, and I'm kind of limited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't upgrade my graphics card in my laptop, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: You weren't the only one that seemed to enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm seeing a lot on the internet, a lot of good reviews for that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But yeah, it reminded me a lot of Bioshock Infinite, just with the different story elements.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very linear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bioshock was very linear.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a little bit of, okay, you can do this, you can do that differently.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do a lot of stealth in the game, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can take out lights and...
[SPEAKER_05]: and a lot of the lights thing plays into the stealth stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a mode that's pretty difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually play the whole game without killing anybody except for the mutants.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to kill the mutants because they'll just charge right at you.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't walk past them.
[SPEAKER_05]: but there's an achievement you get for doing that and I don't know I just enjoyed it I enjoyed the storyline I haven't played 2033 I have 2033 so I should probably check it out although now I've had the ending spoiled because you know they kind of give it away at the end of this game because it ties in with it
[SPEAKER_05]: but um yeah it was a really great great game i'm glad i got to play because i wasn't really familiar with the series at all and it's pretty awesome so definitely worth checking out and i know a lot of people might want to wait until a sale comes and if it's anything like the other deep silver games it'll be deeply discounted pretty soon because they really knock the prices off their games pretty quick
[SPEAKER_04]: And just a quick plug, since you did bring up the review that you did for this game, if you check out his review over at vognetwork.com, and I noticed for the live listeners, Bobby put that in chat, but it's really easy to find if you just go to vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: The really cool thing about the way the website is built over at VOG Network, or the Voice of Geeks Network, is that you can actually do a response review.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you also like the game, or maybe you didn't like the game and you want to have your say on that,
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually write a response review.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the way it's done is that we actually screen the reviews to make sure they're not trolly, to make sure they are thought out, to make sure they're worthy of posting right underneath the main review.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we never judge that on opinion, whether you love it or hate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just want to make sure it sounds like you've actually played it and that you're not just first.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like a Metacritic thing where you're like, one, ten.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has to be a little more thought out than that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, so we will, uh, of course approve those and, uh, you get your review right there, right underneath the main review.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's, it's, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the things that makes our site really unique, uh, which I like.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you only have a limited amount of time to do that though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I, I, I don't remember what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bobby, you'll have to remind me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's like two weeks or a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also do that on movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of you've been seeing Iron Man 3, Star Trek, uh, Into Darkness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Both those movies are also reviewed on our site and you can participate with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then the other things I played on the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been playing a lot of stuff on the Ouya.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've actually been playing a lot of the Pingo, Puzzle Poker.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like this cross between poker and bingo.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can't beat my high score though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she keeps extending, they have a high score contest going on right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And she keeps extending it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's now June 15th is when that expires because there's not a lot of people participating.
[SPEAKER_05]: But man, I have a 591,000 score that good luck anyone beating that because I've been playing every day and I can't beat that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got close.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got 491 the other day.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I believe that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was trying some other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've been doing a lot of these quick looks at different games on the Wii, and I've actually been posting quite a bit on my YouTube channel, which is just LokiOLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I've been noticing a lot of problems with those analog dead zones.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't noticing it originally, but man...
[SPEAKER_05]: They're bad on those early controllers.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just not... You try to turn diagonal and your character slows down because it's like you're not pushing very far and the analog's sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played this Amazing Frog or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: and the volume on it they have these boom boxes in the game and the audio is so fucking loud it's ridiculous i had to shut the game off like it's actually funny if you watch the video um i shut it off because it's so goddamn loud on the game and like i had the volume on tv wasn't that loud because i've been playing other games in it but the audio of those boom boxes is just so fucking ridiculous that i was like i'm gonna try to smash this thing but oh that's kind of fun
[SPEAKER_04]: Jeez, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check that out whenever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, our site is just so intricate and awesome that I forget things.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's too complicated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice save.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need a user manual.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else for your gaming week, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's it for this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yeah, seriously, though, there's a topic on the gaming section on the VOG forums.
[SPEAKER_05]: for the gaming night stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me know what games you guys want to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't have to be on Xbox 360, it's just it's been that way for the last couple times.
[SPEAKER_05]: PC, PS3, whatever you guys have, whatever you want to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Obviously pick a game or consider games that allow a lot of people to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like Saints Row the third multiplayer, not going to work because it's only two people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'd be fun, but you just can't really do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So something that preferably free, like Team Fortress 2 was one that I thought of because I haven't played that and it's free, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: So we can have a no-shame noob night on Team Fortress 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I would like to see something like that for League of Legends and Dota.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need a friendly, warm environment to help me learn some of those games as opposed to the mean assholes that make up a lot of the League of Legends community.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be my mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know one of the games I've been looking at, like one of the sale things that they have on Amazon right now, speaking of games to get into and stuff, Civ V. They have Civ V Gold with some other thing on there and then XCOM for like 20 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pull the trigger.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Civ V is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think Civ 4 is also in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Civ 4 was a great game too, but Civ 5 is awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that would also be a game that would make a great night sometime.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that is going to have to be an OLR weekend game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Star Trek Online 5 Minutes
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: So I made my guy and I had fun doing the little tutorial but I had to go somewhere else so I didn't get to play I didn't get to actually interact with other people so that was that
[SPEAKER_04]: Quinto does the tutorial battle, he's the EMH
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They changed so much in it, it's not fun anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know enough about the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They changed the skill trees.
[SPEAKER_07]: They completely redid the skill setup for how you assign and do your points and your various weapons that you can pick up for your different classes.
[SPEAKER_07]: My normal class is an engineer and I always do the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: and it just took forever to get everything and I also had like the middle level account because I had stopped paying my subscription but I had been paying a subscription so it was just all I did last time I played was hang out at Deep Space Nine and play Dabo seriously that's all I did
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com reminding us Star Trek Online has a new DLC pack called Legacy of Romulus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I did notice that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all over the splash screens when you log into the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other folks in chat, a variety of people talking about the Star Trek game that just came out on 360 PS3 and the negative reception it's getting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen Shadow Next Gen in chat saying stay away, far, far away.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Diablo III Diablo III Diablo III
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I read somewhere they were doing a 25% increased XP and magic gold find weekend Because this is the one year anniversary of Diablo 3 coming out So I was like, what the hell, I'll go take a look And I actually played enough, I finally beat the damn game A year later, finally beat Diablo 3 I killed Diablo, and I'll tell you what
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I had some really good gear, but when I got to the last act, when I got to the second half of Act 4, that game started kicking my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: It got a lot harder.
[SPEAKER_04]: And when I finally got to the Diablo fight, I think I had to fight him like seven times before I got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was as intricate as a raid fight in World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: a couple people on my friends list got a little butthurt that I didn't want to play Diablo 3 with them but I said a long time ago I was gonna do that and I was gonna play it through because one of my friends was like let me help you kill Diablo let me help you kill Diablo and I'm like no um but uh I did it so now I'm gonna explore some of the multiplayer stuff that's the next thing I want to do in Diablo and move on to the nightmare difficulty or whatever because
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it worth the blood pact?
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, because I played enough WoW and I got Diablo 3 for free, so it's hard to bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to be fair, maybe the ending gets better when you play it on the higher difficulties, because you can play it through four different difficulties, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And then hardcore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, because I never beat games, I thought y'all could appreciate I did finally, finally beat Diablo 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that was pretty much my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: We may not have a show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'm going to say right now it's very likely we will not have a show next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stay tuned to Twitter for updates though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will let you know mid-week because we do want to do something about the Xbox thing on Tuesday and getting some immediate reactions to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to plug our Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio and of course Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, I thought we would take an opportunity and plug some of the Twitch TV live streaming we've been doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been doing it all on the main OLR channel, Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to try to convince Loki to move there.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I only did it once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now you're streaming where?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's Loki OLR on Twitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now, Jamie, you do some more personal projects where you're doing sketching and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you do have your own Twitch channel for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's that at?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Kuro Tsubasa, K-U-R-O-U-T-S-U-B-A-S-A.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm actually thinking about making an actual live stream account just for the drawing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Twitch is more for gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be honest though, I'm probably going to be taking a little bit of a break from doing the hardcore projects because I finally, finally finished my FemShot project.
[SPEAKER_04]: How many FemShep drawings did you end up doing?
22.
[SPEAKER_04]: 22, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two of them were mine.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, they're all done and they are on Mass Effecting, my Tumblr for all things Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well then maybe we'll have to get your gaming stuff on the OLR channel as well and then we'll have all those subscribers still built in from the days we used to do the show over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'd be nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for now, because when we're off a week, the live streaming is a really good way to kind of keep tabs on us during the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do make sure that we're streaming when there is not other programming at the Voice Geeks Network, which we always try to promote the other great independent shows, everything from TVs to movies to anime to British stuff to American stuff to Australian stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all at the Voice Geeks Network, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, let's get into gaming news, of which there was a surprising amount of it this week, although I guess we are getting in those weeks leading up to E3, so more and more is going to come up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Only a couple weeks away, so.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, EA shockingly announced that they are putting an end to their online pass program, and basically saying, yes, we are discontinuing online pass, and none of our EA titles will feature, or include that feature.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Feature.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says many players didn't respond to the format, and we've listened to feedback and decided to do away with it moving forward.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which makes me think, what the hell is coming up that we don't know about that's going to take the place of this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of people had that reaction.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's that initial celebration, the Kermit flail.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: The EA got rid of the online pass.
[SPEAKER_04]: They realized it was a really off-putting idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then it's like, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: This can only get worse.
[SPEAKER_05]: EA is not a company to go, hey guys, we were wrong, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hey, you know that SimCity?
[SPEAKER_05]: We should have made it offline.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a patch to make it offline.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to have something that's being done by the console manufacturers to take the place of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: The money is going to come from somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I wonder, well, even if it's not necessarily that whole thing that it's... Microtransactions?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's increased DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's where they're going to make and remember this point because I'm going to bring it up again later in the show when we get into something else involving EA but I think the whole DLC and the microtransactions is how they're going to make up the money I think you're going to see more games that really rely on that
[SPEAKER_04]: you know that to make their why not it works for Facebook and free to play games and a lot of companies unfortunately are moving into that dangerous space where it's like oh well people the consumer wants to play Facebook game and they want to buy all these little free jewels and energy packs and I don't know there's a part of me that's like that's gotta be something I don't doubt that they're gonna charge you $60 for a game and have a bunch of crappy DLC for it
[SPEAKER_05]: or some good DLC, but probably a lot of crappy DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that possibly the relationship with GameStop came into this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think maybe GameStop maybe choked a bitch, so to speak, and GameStop might have been like, you know, our retail people don't really push your games because you don't get the same value out of that and we kind of like to push the 2K sports games that don't have the online passes and
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know if that would have really I think that maybe they just found that they weren't making a whole ton of money off of it maybe they think that their games are so awesome that people are just buying them new anyways although I don't know it's just
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, the only companies left would be Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Warner Games, they still might do that, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, their next big game coming out is Batman Arkham Origins, which doesn't have an online component, but last time with Arkham Asylum, they had the whole Catwoman DLC, which was the sort of online pass, pre-order bonus, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ubisoft and Sony, really, Sony First Party would be the other ones that have that in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you think about the whole EA getting rid of the online pass?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a smart move for one thing, but I think that they're going to replace it with something more nefarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I trust EA as far as I can pick up their entire headquarter building and push it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I think this is a good excuse to check in with the listeners here for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think we're going to do a live poll.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we're going to go to vognetwork.com, and specifically live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to ask our question of the live listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: And tonight's question is, why did EA get rid of the online pass?
[SPEAKER_04]: And here's some of the options collected from what the hosts have said so far.
[SPEAKER_04]: They are truly trying to look less evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something about the new consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to rely on increased DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameStop put them in a chokehold or something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Register participants at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see the poll up there on the site and can vote right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'll see that under the chat box at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go over those results there in just a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool thing is that once you vote, you can actually see the results come in live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so far, everybody is saying there's something about the new consoles, dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, there's nothing already.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've already talked about the PlayStation 4, and they've said that there's nothing preventing used games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I don't...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if there is going to be anything with new consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe they just decided, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're just not making a ton of money off of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although, I thought they said they were making quite a bit of money.
[SPEAKER_05]: So why would you just get rid of money or give up on that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, is it really that much of a trying to save face after what happened with SimCity?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because people are kind of expecting that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, maybe...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know what their thought process could be.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're definitely not going to find out on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to say, hey, by the way, we're going to have a feature that's going to prevent you from buying music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the negative stuff or anything that can be perceived as negative, that's not coming out on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're not going to come out on stage and say, oh, yeah, and this Xbox has to...
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would be cool if they did address all those.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they had actual responses that were positive, like, it's not always online.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've heard your worries, and it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the guy talking, all the talking head would have to do is get up there and say, you know, and don't worry if I lose my internet connection, I can still play the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stop tweeting about it, you know, or just make a little joke about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like that's all they would need to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And everybody could laugh it off like an old sitcom at the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to check the results here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Still 58% of the vote.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something about the new consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: No votes for GameStop putting them in a chokehold, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: People don't think that seems to be it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So a large amount of people as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: 30% they're going to rely on increased DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: About 8% right now saying they are truly trying to look less evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: So 8% giving them the benefit of the doubt there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll check in with that poll one more time after this story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give you guys a last chance to vote there at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is getting a little bit of controversy this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: The story that's going around about a game that isn't even out here in America, but a lot of people here have an opinion on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is in Japan only.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo of Japan makes this series called Tomodachi Collection New Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a game that's on the 3DS, and from my understanding of the game, I'm not going to confess to know a whole lot about this game, but it's kind of Nintendo's answer to The Sims slash Animal Crossing, and it uses Miis, and it's one of those life simulation type of games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, apparently there is a glitch in the game, and according to some people in Japan, what happens with the glitch is that the glitch enables same-sex marriages to appear.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what you do, you bring your Miis over to the 3DS using the Mii transfer tool, and somehow this glitch will allow your character to bathe with characters of the same gender, make babies...
[SPEAKER_04]: Defy the laws of science and everything and you know raise babies and all that stuff with the whole same gender and obviously places like Tumblr are very and the story actually says this hey it's true though places like Tumblr and some of the fan sites are very happy about this and posting their pictures of their happy little gay family and so forth and you know
[SPEAKER_04]: Obviously, as a gay guy myself, I like to see a lot of this stuff that's positive in games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love the way The Sims does it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Sims is a great model.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like one of those games where it's like, you know, The Sims just will like whatever they like, whatever you want them to like.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's just no...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Getting a notice on home menus notification that a child will be sent on a journey but no actual message is there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's clearly something in the game that I don't know much about because I don't know the series very well.
[SPEAKER_07]: But a lot of people... Instead of taking the Republican route, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a lot of people out there that are like... You know the way games journalism works where it's copy-paste, copy-paste, but make the headline more sensationalist each time is that Nintendo bans same-sex marriage from their game.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, maybe the way this really is, is that Nintendo didn't plan to put same-sex marriage in their game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It ended up there anyway through a bug, which will also cause save files to corrupt and so forth, so they've got to do something about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I don't think they're necessarily trying to patch out the gay marriage, but that wasn't supposed to be there in the first place.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not as upset about this as you might think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, again, I'm gay myself and I like to see this stuff in games, but I also realize a lot of Japanese games don't have gay marriage stuff in their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy XI, you could marry in that game, but they didn't do same-gender weddings.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was something they were thinking about or whatever, but they never did it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like that for Ragnarok Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did they do same-gender as in Ragnarok?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they did.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had like marriage skills.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like if you married your character, you could teleport to wherever your character was or do like healing stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they didn't have it to where it would be same gendered.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people who took private servers actually had to modify some of the programming in the game to enable it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya in chat says from what I read of the story the fix is only for the problems with the side effects caused by the glitch and that would be a great way to kind of resolve this scenario so that way it's like okay if people kind of figured out how to work the system and get two guys in there then whatever and I think that's that's a good way to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: and I think we are headed in the right direction folks culturally like I look at games like Mass Effect and yes I know here I am bringing up that game again but guys it's done so well in that series that I there's a reason why I really love Mass Effect and and games like The Sims and other games and you look at what's happening culturally is that what did we have three states that
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: will update to reflect that as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But for right now, I don't believe gay marriage is legal in Japan, so it's probably why they didn't think to really put it in there as a fully fleshed out thing, and why it is still kind of a bug that the two guys actually make the baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which, you know, you would...
[SPEAKER_04]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, but they actually are working on using cloning technology so that two people of the same gender can have a child together.
[SPEAKER_07]: So just saying, science.
[SPEAKER_04]: so I think generally culturally and I'm not trying to get too political on this show but obviously you know it's an issue it's kind of important to me it's one of those things where it's like you know it's it's more and more becoming not a big fucking deal and that's really what this should be is it's not a big fucking deal if two guys want to do something that doesn't affect your life whatsoever you know what I mean it's just
[SPEAKER_04]: yeah anyway I'll get off my soapbox so what do you think DarkSakura about this Tomodachi collection I think people are just I think unfortunately the sensationalism of certain gaming websites and so forth tended to make this story a bigger deal than it is but I think certainly there's got to be Nintendo kind of looking at this going oh well I guess if people are going to have these tumblers and so forth about it maybe this is something we should have thought of putting into their first place I don't know what do you think Jamie uh
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it should have been there from the get-go, and if it's possible, I mean, clearly the glitch is causing some problems, and I have no problem with them fixing those effects of the glitch, but I would want them to see them leave in the option to actually even make it, if they could incorporate some way to make that a regular feature in the game, instead of just it being a glitch, and using that to fix the problems, then that would be the way I would go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I would also request that they actually bring this game over to America or, you know, so I can feel like I know what the fuck I'm talking about with this game because I'm going to be honest, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can only really go off of screenshots and little YouTubes and things I see of the game and my assumptions.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, I would play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to know a little more about what this game is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomodachi means friend.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's a buddy game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well let's move on Oh, quickly, I'm going to close out the poll here Here's the final results of our poll The winner, why did EA get rid of the online pass?
[SPEAKER_04]: 57% of the vote, there's something about the new consoles Second place, they're going to rely on increased DLC So there you go, those are the results of the live poll Thank you guys for voting at live.vognetwork.com Let's move on to the next story, DarkSakra
[SPEAKER_07]: In other news, now this is probably why I've had Sega on the brain for a little while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sega is, well we've always known that Sega's been in bed with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have no idea what they're doing in this bed, but they're doing stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: In this case, Sega has announced that they are in an exclusive partnership with Nintendo of America.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are gay married to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: The third one is still to be announced, but these are Wii U and 3DS.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that it would be the ideal platform, that's a quote, to showcase Sonic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, though, since people aren't buying Wii U's, Sega is once again showing that their business sense is kind of in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is Sega of America and Sega Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't see the official Sega of Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this really a big deal, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, I mean, Sonic games, not known for their quality these days so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've had several Sonic games that have been exclusive to the Nintendo platform.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sonic Colors, Sonic and the Secret Rings.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mario and Sonic and the Olympics, which sells really well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those games sell very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is one of those three games they're doing, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, it sold well because the Wii sold well, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the Wii U's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's going to suck for Sega then, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because Sega's really had, especially Sega of America, had a great track record.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish they'd come out and said it's going to be Phantasy Star Online 2 that's going to be on the Wii U that would have given me something to get really excited about which I'm surprised something like that isn't happening well you never know E3 might be interesting speaking of which Rob you need to play that with me on PC is there an English patch yet for that?
[SPEAKER_07]: yeah it's mostly English it's English enough that you could be able to play it I might have to do that we'll see it's actually super fun it's exactly like the last one so it's good
[SPEAKER_04]: Shadow Next Gen in our chatroom with an interesting perspective saying, Rob, with Nintendo helping to work on Sonic now, though, maybe it will have that magic Nintendo polish that a lot of first-party Nintendo titles have.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could Nintendo's involvement make this sweeter?
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, I do have to make a slight rebuttal, which I've said in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic Generations was pretty damn good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it was also out on multiple platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got it on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fun on PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think it's going to make a difference.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just has to not be a turd of a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was the last really big turd in the Sonic franchise?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic Adventure 2?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Sonic Adventure 2 was okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first Sonic Adventure was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sonic 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a huge turd.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't even do much in the way of
[SPEAKER_07]: being fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, um, Tigerclaw theorizes in our chat room, what if part of the deal with Sega was that one of the Nintendo characters makes a cameo somewhere in the new Sonic game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think that plumber can run that fast?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we will see what happens with this partnership.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other stuff coming out of the Nintendo Direct, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they finally announced a date for Wonderful 101, which is on September 15th in North America and August 23rd in Europe.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's all they said about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Super Luigi U, the DLC is arriving on the 20th of June.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then if you don't want to get it as DLC, you can pay an extra $10 and get a standalone disc, which is coming out August 25th.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the reason they're doing that is just to say, hey, look, we have games coming out for the Wii U. Because...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why else they would do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of figured they would do that later on when they do a Game of the Year edition of New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: with New Luigi U. Because again, not every household in America is online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Granted, if you're not online, but you have a Wii U, I'm not sure how that works.
[SPEAKER_04]: You must live in a real remote part of the US or something, but I think there's enough people without online that justify it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, the Wii U could be in a kid's bedroom, which maybe doesn't have online or something, you know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're putting it out, so I guess that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then last but not least, this is kind of neat because I'm not going to E3, so you get to play unreleased Wii U games at Best Buy during E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to have demo kiosks at over 100 locations.
[SPEAKER_05]: E3
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting how Nintendo is really changing up the E3 strategy this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, granted, we had a couple years ago, and I think this still happens to some extent, Microsoft, I remember one year, went very big on bringing E3 home where you could download all the demos and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really wish they would do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: MOTOGP
[SPEAKER_05]: and now they don't do that anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I really wish they would do that because a lot of, well, the majority of the people that are paying attention to E3 can't go to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why do you think Nintendo is making you go to Best Buy and not just letting you download them to your Wii U?
[SPEAKER_04]: Partnership.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bet it's part partnership and it's also part so you can get the sales pitch while you're there about picking up a Wii U because you know Nintendo has just like Microsoft and just like any other company has the people who go out to the stores they're trying to sell the console too because the problem isn't getting people that own the Wii U to buy more games it's getting people to buy the Wii U so why not have those people in the stores ready to try to sell the consoles I think it's a great concept
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you want to buy a console today?
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially if they end up dropping the price, which I know is a long shot, but now it's on sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's even cheaper than it was before.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you want to get one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have somebody there to put on a little bit of that pressure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you think we'll see a Wii U Animal Crossing this year?
[SPEAKER_04]: A Wii U Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would cannibalize the 3DS one too much because that one is going to be coming out within weeks of E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, probably next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like it's really going to be anything innovative.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you can sit down now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I could sit down before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I could go get a latte and sit down.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now you can... What were the other big things?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's benches.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're the mayor.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can swim.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, they... Okay, so to be fair, they did kind of change the main plot of sorts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm sorry, but... Did it have virtual console games like it did in the GameCube version?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually liked my indentured servitude to Tom Nook and considering that we're selling virtual console games for 30 cents why can't you put some NES games in there?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like you're losing money on that
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who needs PR when you've got people to do it for free?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm curious to see how this works out for them because it could be a game changer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not going to sit here, though, and say E3 is dead or dying because there was a time when E3 didn't have anything to do with the media and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before the internet, there was still E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And granted, you would see screenshots and things in Nintendo Power, but it was not the blowout thing that it is today.
[SPEAKER_04]: E3 started because it's the one time during the year when everybody in the industry kind of gets together under the same roof.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a lot of wheeling and dealing that happens at E3 that the media doesn't even know about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: One year I went to E3, I think it was 2006, maybe it was, it might have been 2010, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apple had a booth at E3, or excuse me,
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a booth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apple had a conference room at E3.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a behind closed doors thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And a lot of people were thinking, ooh, is Apple doing a game console?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, ooh, you know, and that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Apple was probably showing off the iPhone or the iPad, depending on whatever year it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably what they were showing in that little room to developers who were there at the same roof.
[SPEAKER_04]: That had nothing to do with the media.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apple was not rolling that out to the media yet, but Apple was probably trying, again, this is a huge theory here because I don't know anything, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming that that's part of the wheeling and dealing that happens at E3 that has nothing to do with the media interaction.
[SPEAKER_04]: The media could not come to E3 and E3 I think would still happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might not be as big of a deal, but I think there would still be the necessity for the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyhow, tangent.
[SPEAKER_04]: But let's move on with something that doesn't have to do with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has to do with Steam, which we brought up earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Steam Trading Cards Steam Trading Cards Steam Trading Cards Steam Trading Cards Steam Trading Cards Steam Trading Cards
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Dota and Half-Life which you would expect of course the Valve games are going to be involved but they do have Don't Starve and Counter-Strike Global Offensive so at least there's some other games participating but I would like to see more third parties kind of get in on this to really give value added to this and I didn't really understand how it works either as far as like see here's the thing I went back to play Portal 2 I was actually just going to play Portal 2 and I noticed I don't have any of my achievements on Portal 2 like they all disappeared somehow what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I started playing it again, but I haven't gotten any cards or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then today I got a notification saying that I got some new items in my inventory.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so now I have three items marked as Steam Trading Card Beta Access.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it says, Steam Trading Card Beta Access Extra Copy Grants Early Access to Steam Trading Card Beta Game Badges and New Profile Cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Join Steam Trade Carding Group and post your feedback in the discussions area.
[SPEAKER_05]: Select add to my game library to activate, which I tried to do because I didn't see it on my library and it won't let me do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to send one of those to the username I just private messaged you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think of the whole thing as a concept, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's just assume it works as we read it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's more interesting than trophies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, because a lot of times it's like an achievement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just bring value to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed Actdeft in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com saying, you can buy the trading cards through the Steam Community Market.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he says, I sold two extra passes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got $1.50 for each.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like selling stuff in the Diablo real money auction house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except Valve didn't probably take a dollar out of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess any excuse to go back and play Portal and Half-Life and all that, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is something that has my hubby super, super excited.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, he was practically bouncing in his seat over this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gran Turismo 6 has been announced, and there's a demo going to be out in July.
[SPEAKER_07]: The information actually hit, I think, the European Sony news networks not too long ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that it's going to be on the PS3 and that they're basically going to keep it on that system.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't say anything about it being out for the next-gen system.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to have GT Academy in 2013 as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that this new version is going to have 1,200 cars, 33 locations, and 71 layouts.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's seven more locations than Gran Turismo 5 had.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it will have the UK Silverstone Circuit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says new physics engine, new modeling, all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan goes, and I will buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: He came in, raised his hands in the air and goes, and I will buy it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, interesting though that it's not PlayStation 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's the thing that really shocked people is that, well...
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 4 has this whole racing club or what do they call that game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Drive club.
[SPEAKER_04]: Drive club or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yet there's no Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is going to be on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Without the PlayStation 4 being backwards compatible, Gran Turismo 6 is a great reason not to upgrade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but also put it out this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to guarantee sales, why not put it out for the system that everyone already has?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, but that's going to be a problem when the new systems start coming to get people to buy them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that they're going to have maybe some special edition come out later that everyone's going to go, ooh, we need this instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gran Turismo 6 HD or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: WhatUpG in our chat says, each of the PlayStation systems have had two main Gran Turismo games, so I expect PlayStation 4 to have Gran Turismo 7 and 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe there's just a pattern that's trying to not be broken here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, they were saying that for Gran Turismo 5, 10 million copies were sold.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that it is the Gran Turismo franchise itself is their most successful franchise ever, especially in Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: 70 million copies over the span of the series.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a wise move to put it on PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, but it's very strange.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems a little bit like cannibalizing PlayStation 4, but I guess they feel there'll still be plenty of people wanting to pick up a PlayStation 4 for Drive Club, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, I have a feeling that they're going to really push Gran Turismo 7 for PS4 and make that a big selling point like around, say, some sort of major holiday or big sales period.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but it's just weird to me that Gran Turismo 6 and Drive Club for PlayStation 4 and the PlayStation 4 are all around the same time, essentially.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're saying that they may release another version of PlayStation 4 later on after launch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, that's pretty much what I was anticipating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's travel around the world and check out some games that will be coming out a little bit sooner than Gran Turismo 6, as in games that are out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll start with Loki in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: This week, there's actually quite a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting off, Resident Evil Revelations HD is coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and Wii U.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then I know the game that everybody is super excited for Fast and the Furious Showdown which is being developed by the guys that did the NASCAR games that's coming out on Playstation 3, Xbox 360 the Wii U and the 3DS and then there's the Worms Collection which is kind of a re-release of some of the Xbox Live Arcade and Playstation Network games that's coming out on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 this week
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, LEGO Batman 2 DC Super Heroes on the Wii U. And on the 3DS, on Friday actually, we'll be getting Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's going to be coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: And last game this week, Sniper Elite V2 on the Wii U. So hey, there's Wii U games coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, they are games that have come out a long time ago, like a year ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's travel over to Japan and check out some of the releases that are going to happen over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting off with the PlayStation 3 this week on May 23rd.
[SPEAKER_04]: Biohazard Revelations Unveiled Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: BlazBlue Continuum Shift Extend, which is getting a price cut.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going into the Best Hits Collection.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kamen Rider Batride War in regular and premium editions is out this week from Namco Bandai.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: As they call it over there, Bandai Namco.
[SPEAKER_04]: Terraria is getting a Japanese release, believe it or not, and that will be out this week as well as The Sims 3 Pets getting a price reduction on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also on PS3 this week, Z slash X, Zillions of Enemy X, Zetsukai no Crusade.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that is Zillions of Enemy X. How many?
[SPEAKER_04]: Zillions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Robby just made me sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that just makes me actually want a zillion game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like on Master System, only all updated and new.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the Xbox 360 this week, Biohazard Revelations Unveiled Edition is there as well in a regular and a limited set.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much all you get on the 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to the Vita, BlazBlue Continuum Shift Extend also gets a price cut there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Valhalla Knights 3 comes out this week from Marvelous Entertainment over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check out the Wii U. Yes, there is a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Biohazard Revelations Unveiled Edition is out there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So all the consoles in Japan getting that.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the 3DS this week, there is a new 3DS XL model, or as they call it, the LL.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Shimogami Tensei IV Limited model because Shimogami Tensei IV is out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be a pretty big release.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure there's some people going to be importing that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can actually get that retail or download.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a whole accessory set.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can get a skin for your... If you're a Shin Megami Tensei fan, you're probably importing tons of shit this week from Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck to your wallet.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you are not a Shin Megami Tensei fan, perhaps Tamagotchi no Doki Doki Dream Omesechi would be of interest to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it's another Tamagotchi game on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you should just get Shin Megami Tensei IV if you're going to import one or the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lastly, on the PSP, yes, they are still making games for the PSP in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zeroji no Kane to Cinderella Halloween Wedding in regular and deluxe editions and Rakuun Danshi coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is Cinderella Wedding?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is not, I don't think the Disney Cinderella.
[SPEAKER_04]: This looks like one of those games based off an anime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh God, it looks like one of those romance games because I see girl and guy in the bar, girl hanging off guy, guy kissing girl and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it must be one of those series.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, that's it for Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's travel over to the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 22nd, we have the Incredible Adventures of Van Helsing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Midna, stop eating that!
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Midna was eating my headphone cable.
[SPEAKER_07]: On the 24th, we have Donkey Kong Country Returns 3D, Dust and the Lesion Tale, Fast and Furious Showdown, Big Whoop, Resident Evil Revelations, and Sniper Elite V2.
[SPEAKER_04]: to register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Use the passphrase, test.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There it is, UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a couple more stories for you guys, and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so Nintendo has kind of taken an action against these Let's Play videos on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's going to happen is partnering, I guess, with YouTube, they're going to be using their content ID match system to basically take the ad revenue that these Let's Play videos are getting
[SPEAKER_05]: if they're monetized and that's all going to be going to Nintendo and then also they're going to be having ads I guess before and after the videos as well I guess it's going to somehow automatically get added in for Nintendo stuff
[SPEAKER_05]: um so that kind of sucks I guess um although I mean I know YouTube has policies against the let's play stuff you know although there's still a ton of it on there and it's kind of you know confusing because some companies will let you do let's plays on their stuff like Minecraft for example there's a big thing in saying hey do film whatever you want do whatever you want you know we're not gonna it's it's cool you know so um
[SPEAKER_05]: and I know other they're not taking the videos down but I mean the fact that they're kind of like hey we're taking all the profits from it that's kind of like I almost wish they would just take them down instead you know what I mean it's kind of a little weird mm-hmm
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the thing I was most surprised to learn from this whole story is that there's people that make livings off of doing Let's Play videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had no idea you could make that kind of money on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm like, wow, I'm in the wrong business.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, I need to do some sassy Let's Play videos or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was joking with Rob saying that, hey, because I do monetize some of the videos I make for YouTube just...
[SPEAKER_05]: First hits and giggles because I know I'm not going to get millions of hits on it, but hey, let's just see what kind of money we'll rake in from this.
[SPEAKER_05]: With the few videos that I have, and a few of them have like a thousand views or something, a whopping 26 cents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm retiring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think Nintendo is evil for what they did?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I understand that they're saying, oh, you guys shouldn't be making money off of our content, but it's less about making money off their content and more of just like it's commentary and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't really do a Let's Play video or a commentary on gameplay without showing the gameplay, unless you have some sort of weird riff tracks thing that you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've seen a lot of anger directed at Nintendo on the internet this week over this whole thing and it's like okay to some extent I do get it and I feel I can understand where the YouTube community feels a little bit slighted on this and I can certainly understand hey this is the internet and we can just pick up and move it to somewhere else you know I'm sure there's a lot of that talk going on right now but you guys Microsoft did this in October of last year and
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I believe it was October 9th was the date the news went out is that Microsoft now they did something a little different, but they actually put it in their whole little terms of service that you cannot earn money from these games like Halo 4 and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that if you cannot enroll in a YouTube partner program, if you are playing one of these Microsoft games.
[SPEAKER_04]: but here's how that's I just think a lot of gamers forgot about that in their anger because everybody's like oh Nintendo's just doing this because the Wii U sucks and all this stuff and I'm like well Microsoft did the same fucking thing seven months ago does that mean the 360 sucks?
[SPEAKER_05]: but they do this they're doing this now and then and of course we don't know it's confirmed yet but the rumor is they're going to be kind of rolling out the same features that the PlayStation 4 has where you can share videos and gameplay and stuff
[SPEAKER_05]: If they have it where you can live stream and do commentary over that stuff, you're not going to be able to monetize those videos that you put out there even though they're making it super easy for you to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They just want you to freely advertise their game without any sort of... That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're kind of advertising their game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like you...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: But those interactions were designed by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the place I fault that argument.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want the word to get out of every game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want your game to look fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want it to get out to the people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whether they're seeing it like if I come over and watch someone playing a game, how's that any different than watching it over the internet?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not saying I necessarily disagree completely that Nintendo made a bad decision with this but I also think there's a lot of gamer entitlement going on here that you guys if it was a movie do you think I could put up a copy of Star Trek Into Darkness with my commentary on YouTube and not have that get struck down with probably something a lot worse than the monetary it would be a copyright strike
[SPEAKER_04]: If I were to put something up, you know who's really fucking crazy about their intellectual property is sports.
[SPEAKER_04]: The NBA and the NFL, especially the NFL.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I were to put up classic football clips and be talking over them and stuff, they would come after me, legally.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be a lot worse than what Nintendo's doing here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think there's gamer entitlement going on here, and this is just a rude awakening, and I'm sorry, but I think gamers are getting it a lot better
[SPEAKER_05]: some of these other well Rob also keep in mind like for another example this is the Rift Tracks guys have to get licensing which and they don't even don't they just do their sales that they don't attach well they don't have to get licensing they only have to get licensing for when they're actually doing like a show like an actual movie in a theater with you know the Rift Tracks the most of the stuff they do is in the public domain now
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: People, the whole reason that you're having this share thing on the PlayStation 4 and stuff is to kind of, you want to share those moments with your friends and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you're going to start saying, okay, we want you to get that footage out there, get that footage out there, and then start hammering them down.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, well, I'm sorry, but that footage was too long.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, but you're trying to make some money off of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not going to be motivated to continue doing those Let's Play videos if they're going to make no money off of it because they're trying to put out content and if you're saying, well, you can't make any money off this, that's basically...
[SPEAKER_05]: I know it's a little stretch, but it's almost like saying, we're telling you what you can and can't do with this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh, sorry, you can't sell it used.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're telling you what you can and can't do.
[SPEAKER_04]: In part, that's where I do agree with you, is that this wasn't a smart PR move on Nintendo's part on a time where they need a lot of good news.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think what should happen here, and this is probably a limitation of YouTube, quite honestly, is that maybe there needs to be something where it's a split revenue stream or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, Loki, if people are making money, they're making a living off of Let's Play videos, that tells me, what, $40,000 a year minimum, right, to live off of.
[SPEAKER_04]: You got maybe, in some parts of the country, $30,000 or less.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're talking, multiply that by how many people on YouTube are doing it for a living.
50?
[SPEAKER_04]: 100?
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a lot of views.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of views required.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like thousands of views to get a penny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, I'm going to look it up right now because I can look at my monetization and see what exactly I'm...
[SPEAKER_04]: bringing in I guess yeah but again you know I and I'm not dissing the talent of these individuals and they're funny witty stuff and so forth because that would be kind of biting the hand that you know makes up this show here but uh then again we're not displaying images of the game in motion the whole time during the during the show or whatever I don't know I don't know
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's stupid though that they... We're also not trying to make a living off of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, here's the problem too is they basically say, okay, yeah, we're going to have this partnership program that we're going to partner with IGN or something like that or Machinima or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then you have to become an affiliate with them but they may not let you become an affiliate with them so once again you're given these big guys how's an indie supposed to shine if you're just saying sorry you can't show any of our gameplay we only want IGN to show our gameplay find another way to monetize it
[SPEAKER_05]: But how do you do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: If I knew, I would have the money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm saying, though, that if there's another way to monetize it, they're going to still hit you for the same thing, that you're making money off of our videos or off our content.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if it's like PayPal donations or something like that for a Twitch stream or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure people make money off of that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think if there's going to be a standardized way that people are going to make money off of videos, whether it be monetization via ads or whatever, maybe they can cater those ads for those Nintendo videos to Nintendo products.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That seems to make more sense to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I do think, again, I think the smarter thing for Nintendo to do would have been to partner with these people to come to a solution that has both people in mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either it's split revenue or it's ads that support Nintendo or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: But by putting the hammer down, they made themselves look like dicks.
[SPEAKER_04]: But my point is they are well within their legal right to do so.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think people need to...
[SPEAKER_04]: Give Nintendo a little bit of a break here.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you hear about that people are making a living off of this, Nintendo is entitled to some of that money.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm rolling the money.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just made 7 more cents.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm at 31 cents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's a good example right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of the videos I've been uploading, like different Ouya videos and stuff like that, the one that I have the most views on so far is a how to sideload apps tutorial, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's only a few minutes long.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have 2,170 views, 6,977 minutes, 24 cents is what I've made off of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just to give you an idea of how many views you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to get millions and millions of views combined over your channel.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to take a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody putting out a Let's Play video is not going to make...
[SPEAKER_05]: A ton of money, and they really want that ad money?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_05]: You want that, like, maybe a buck that they're gonna make if they get thousands of views?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously?
[SPEAKER_05]: That seems a little greedy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, going to a couple more chat comments here, and then we gotta move on with the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But SSJ100Matt says...
[SPEAKER_04]: ShadowNextGen says, The people who make these videos might take a few hours to make them.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't have the right to make money off of the new Zelda title that Nintendo took years and millions of dollars to make.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but look at what kind of money is Nintendo making off their title versus the amount of effort Nintendo's putting into their title versus the return versus the person that spent like an hour to make a video and his return.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's fair because you look at the amount of money that they're making.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like the guy that's making the Let's Play video is making more money than Nintendo on these titles.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I just don't see where Nintendo is necessarily losing money on this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they suggesting that people are watching these Let's Plays and going...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's enough of that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't need to buy it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just like saying, oh, hey, someone pirated our game.
[SPEAKER_05]: We lost the sale.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can't attribute that.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no data to correlate lost sales.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make all the excuses you want, but the fact of the matter is your system's not selling well because you don't have any games on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: MM2K says, YouTube just needs to establish a standard fee against revenue of anyone using copyrighted material, maybe 5-10%.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again though, I mean, I'm with you on that for like games, but like movies, I can't post a copy of Star Trek Into Darkness on YouTube and expect that, you know, oh Paramount gets 5-10% because I'm giving my sassy commentary over this movie that just came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's...
[SPEAKER_04]: There's got to be something there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what needs to happen, and this is, I think, would be, this would be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nintendo needs to be one of those companies, like Mojang, with Minecraft, saying, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're cool with you putting the videos out there and, you know, do with whatever, but if you monetize our videos, then maybe that they...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that would be fair enough because they're getting their products out there and they're advertised.
[SPEAKER_05]: The people are more inclined to put out these videos to spread the word about these Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, if I haven't played New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: U and I watch some Let's Play videos, I'm like, hey, that looks like a pretty fun game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe I should go buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you're going to try to get these people not to put these videos out there, I'm never going to hear about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought on this whole thing is that, again, although Nintendo maybe didn't have the best timing with this sort of move, this is not something that's going to be limited to Nintendo, and it is not limited to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, Microsoft did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega did it with the whole Shining Force or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one random game, they were taking down all these videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is still a new media that a lot of companies are exploring, and I'm sorry, but if you are just using this to further your Nintendo hate boner, you need to spread the hate around equally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your position needs to be the same for all these companies that are doing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's kind of one of my big things with this, is that at least if you're going to be mad, be mad at everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's move on and do one more story here before the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hooray, it's a porn story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kids like porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hardcore pornography apparently coming to the next Xbox.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's what the headlines all say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's what it's really about.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sugar DVD.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, they do films like Hairy Asian Schoolgirls Masturbate.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that's just a made up title.
[SPEAKER_04]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there really a porn called Don't Tell My Wife I Ass Fucked the Babysitter?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a pretty great parody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's Don't Tell Mom the Babysitter's Dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like a little parody on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's actually a real porn.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you'll find out on the new Xbox very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the quote from SugarDVD's Rebecca Bolin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any console would benefit from having unlimited HD adult content at the click of a button.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, did you hear that?
[SPEAKER_04]: All you gotta do is click your mouse.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Rob, that does exist.
[SPEAKER_07]: I looked it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is an actual, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was gonna say, they have a lot of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: My search history is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that one New Year's Eve?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was got to be 2006 or 2007 where we were looking up the pornography on the Nintendo Wii web browser and looking at what like Xtube and we found the pterodactyl porn which was a guy in a pterodactyl suit having sex with some girl and it was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just the little motions the guy would make.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we were trying to look up for some reason we were looking up donkey punch and there was a guy dressed up like a donkey.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would actually punch, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: hilarious when in doubt more porn stories all right let's uh let's travel to a time when you know you know a porn game porn on the console was Custer's Revenge and Bubble Bath Babes and Miss Nude World 96 that was that was porn in gaming it's the classic game of the week where DarkSakura is going to walk into her classic gaming vault and she can do that tonight she's literally right there
[SPEAKER_04]: and find a game that she says, hey, you kids should be playing this game, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't think she picked a porno game, so don't get too excited, but DarkSakura picked something just as good as a porno.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Today's classic game is Hagane, The Final Conflict, which is not a game that came out widespread in America.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was one of those blockbuster-only games like Final Fight Guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so this is a game I do not own.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would love to own it, however, it is $700 on eBay right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy moly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm not even joking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me get some of the audio from the game here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It came out in 1994, and it's a side-scrolling action game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was developed by Keita Amemiya and Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost said Redertainment, you know, one of our listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was Red Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was published by Hudson Soft for the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: And like I said, in the US, it was only one of those blockbuster video games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, I do have the other blockbuster game, Final Fight Guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That one goes for 300.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, the story behind this is that the Huma and Koma ninja clans are basically in a big rivalry against each other for the Holy Grail.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the Huma clan is based off of the Chinese Zodiac.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you play this one guy who is in full armor and Dan and I, when Dan was playing because we have a version of it quote version
[SPEAKER_04]: Amulator.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan was talking about some of the resemblance to Strider.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to say, you love this game because it's freaking Strider.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Strider ripoff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if Dan likes anything Strider or Strider related.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Strider meets Shinobi is what I'm looking at here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is actually a game I would... I don't even care if it's just the Super Famicom version, which is still like 50 bucks on eBay here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would love to have this game, but the big problem about it is that it's freaking hard!
[SPEAKER_07]: Super hard, and no save.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why emulators are awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Save states.
[SPEAKER_07]: But basically, you're playing as a ninja cyborg.
[SPEAKER_07]: who is going to kill all of the Koma clan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um, basically it's just a really, really cool side-scrolling game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very difficult.
[SPEAKER_07]: But one thing that it did get some less-than-stellar reviews on was actually its graphics.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was said not to show off the best of Super Nintendo at the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't think Hagane is on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was sort of... It wasn't really, I mean, considering it was only released to video stores or whatever, it wasn't really... I mean, we haven't seen Final Fight Guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, this was a very limited release.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could only rent this game at Blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: and then, like I said... Hold on, EricRPG in our chatroom says that they had it at his video store, so it may not have just been Blockbuster, but maybe, like, video stores in general.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, no, these were actually released only for Blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they showed up at other video stores, then they were purchased from Blockbuster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, because Blockbuster had, like, a limited release deal just on certain Japanese-only games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this was one of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And honestly, I would love to have this game in my collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really, really difficult.
[SPEAKER_07]: But a very rich, good side-scrolling game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And don't say fucking Blockbuster because Blockbuster is dead, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one around the corner from my house is gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are vanishing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw one in a strip mall the other day and I was like, oh my god, it's a museum.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's where I picked up a copy of Parappa 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so I'm checking on eBay right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's one for $295.
[SPEAKER_07]: One for a buy it now of $700.
[SPEAKER_07]: And another one without the box for $400.
[SPEAKER_07]: A Japanese copy is $45.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't even care.
[SPEAKER_07]: I...
[SPEAKER_07]: Haganay
[SPEAKER_04]: for the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck finding it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and if you find it, give it to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a tip.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because you love me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's going to do it for Part A of Orange Lawn Tradio, but don't go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have plenty more to come, including the Fugle Question of the Week, all about this controversial Nintendo Let's Play topic.
[SPEAKER_04]: More stories about EA and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to talk a little bit about the stuff from the Google press thing this week that has to do with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple E3 stories for you guys and plenty more including your phone calls and emails when we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi there!
[SPEAKER_00]: This is Redertainment, and you're participating with Orange Lounge Radio, the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I want to use my voice to tell you that Garrus ain't got nothing on Samantha Trainor.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shots fired.
[SPEAKER_00]: Watch out, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shots fired.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 505 in progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks to Red Entertainment for starting shit here on the second half of our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to leave a bumper for our show, more information available in our forum at the VOG Network forums, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're finally getting a few of them in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have another new one to play next week, so thanks to you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Dance 4
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: But I gotta say, I really like, especially in Just Dance 4, well, A, the song list is very, like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, there's some really, like, you know, they have the stuff you'd expect to hear, like some top 40 hits, like J-Lo on the floor, and Pink, So What, but then, like, there's these picks, they have a cover of the Time Warp
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, which is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have Army of Lovers with Crucified.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you guys remember that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: You love that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember that song?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, Google that music video.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song is in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it have a video?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: But I really like that they have these full workout modes where it'll actually do like a kind of like a warm up little like, you know, generic electro beat or whatever you pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you'll do a bunch of songs and you do like a cool down.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it actually the way it think it's not just a bunch of songs on shuffle counting the calories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that I really liked.
[SPEAKER_04]: So for 20 bucks, I was very happy with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, that was a game I forgot to mention earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we can get into some rapid-fire news now, if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the folks behind The Incredible Machine, which I sunk a lot of hours into back for one of my first computer games, they are making... I love that game, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it's fantastic.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, what do they call those, the Rube Goldberg machines or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: Which reminds me, or as everybody knows it, the opening sequence to Pee-Wee's Big Adventure with the Mr. T cereal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm pitiful, they don't eat my cereal
[SPEAKER_05]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: So yeah, they'll be coming out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably have to pick that up because I love the Incredible Machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is also cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another Kickstarter game called Auto Duel.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a multiplayer car combat game.
[SPEAKER_05]: So probably it's a good thing that David Jeff has signed on to help...
[SPEAKER_05]: Make This Game, and on top of that, Zach Norman, the creator of Interstate 76 and Vigilante 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least I think he created Vigilante 8, but Vigilante 8, one of my most favorite car combat games.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a pretty good pedigree right there, so looking forward to that, maybe back that when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I don't know if they've actually released or have this out yet as a Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably soon, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And last but not least, the Assassin's Creed movie has a date, or at least a time frame.
[SPEAKER_05]: May 2015.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also saw it was July 2016, beginning of the Angry Birds movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: By then, I don't think Angry Birds will be a thing anymore, or at least anyone will care.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, it's... We can all hope.
[SPEAKER_04]: A long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, before I get to my rapid-fire stories here, DarkSakura, I see you chatting like crazy in our chatroom tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did I read that right?
[SPEAKER_04]: You said, had I not romanced Garrus in all 17 times, you've beaten Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's more than 17.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just made up a number.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might have a problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I've...
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Justify, Justify
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna go play some Japanese Sonic Adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just to spite Bobby.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll livestream that shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have fun with that while I read the news about yet another Kickstarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the world we live in, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is a really cool band.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a lot of you like these guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anna Managucci, the chiptune artist.
[SPEAKER_04]: They have a Kickstarter of their own up for Endless Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're very proud of the fact that they've completed this 22-track album over three years without any help from a label, to which I say, you guys go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the goal for this, getting the CD out there, $50,000.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're sitting just under 200k right now, so safe to say they've met it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now with 13 days still to go, so if you pay, I believe, 15 or more, you get the CD pre-order of Endless Fantasy and you get the digital download with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know we have some of their tracks in rotation on VOG and great chiptune artists, so congrats guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if this game would make $200,000, but it's sure worth a shot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shaq Fighter is apparently a name that has been trademarked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, I'm sure you all remember Shaq Fu, which is what, on Super Nintendo and Genesis, I think as well?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it was the fighting game that starred Shaq, and it's kind of a cult game, but it's one of those games that everybody's like, oh yeah, I remember Shaq Fu, and then you actually play it, and you're like, oh yeah, I remember Shaq Fu.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there was also Shackdown, which was a mobile game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They came out with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now apparently the folks that run the Shack.com website, which I didn't even know existed until now, they registered to trademark for Shack Fighter on May 8th.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know if this is yet another mobile game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this is the Wii U's killer app that's going to get everybody to buy the console.
[SPEAKER_04]: or maybe it's another mobile game or maybe it's another like attempt at a 50 cent blood in the sand Shaq goes after terrorists perhaps perhaps I don't know but hey Shaq's pretty pretty awesome so this is gonna be it's gonna be worth checking out if nothing else before the lulls
[SPEAKER_04]: Wave Forward, who did the game's Adventure Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Ice King, why'd you steal our garbage?
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, DuckTailed Remastered, which had everybody screaming like a little girl at PAX East, is going to be doing another Adventure Time game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Adventure Time Explore the Dungeon Because I Don't Know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love Adventure Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is pretty much, you know, any video game ever, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Explore the dungeon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You will be exploring the secret royal dungeon underneath the Candy Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, you can play as Finn, Jake, Marceline, and more.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be co-op as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be out Wii U, 360, PlayStation 3, PC, and 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually kind of excited about it because the last game was only 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, 3DS and DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: also happening regular show uh Mordecai and Rigby in 8-bit land on the 3ds uh they are Mordecai Mordecai excuse me I don't I don't know this show should I is it really funny it's supposed to be very funny I know Adventure Time I know that one if you like Adventure Time you'd like this show okay is it one of those things that's like funnier if you've you know smoked a certain substance beforehand uh I think it's just the same type of humor okay then yes uh okay so um don't do drugs kids
[SPEAKER_04]: So anyway, of course I meant smoking a hookah, which is perfectly legal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smoking meat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or a water.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smoking water.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a water bong.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, so as that name would talk about, the heroes will be transported inside your favorite games.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty much what you'd expect in an episode of a regular show anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's 8-bit land for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess they already have a game on iOS, which most...
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of assume that everything has a game on IS.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft says, I like the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots and lots of 80s references.
[SPEAKER_04]: QueenSimi on our chatroom says, regular show is more of a stoner hipster show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like I thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to guess what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Disney has registered some domains that means that they might be doing some type of racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's Disney Speedster, Disney Speedsters, Disney Racers, Disney Racing, Disney Kart, Disney Kart Racing, and Disney Karting.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually have a Disney Speedsters Twitter with no tweets on it yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, not surprising, Disney has their fingers in most things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, there is Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is basically, it makes me think a lot of Pac-Land.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you remember?
[SPEAKER_07]: But like on a 3D scale and it's basically Pac-Man wandering around in a 3D world It looks neat It's also based off a new TV show What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I need to go back and watch 80s Pac-Man cartoons
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, last but not least, Google did a tribute to Atari's Breakout by having, if you type in Atari Breakout into the Google Images search, you will find your screen turned into a Breakout clone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Another little Google Easter egg.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually, I super, super loved what Google did for Saw Bass's birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saw that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, I just kept watching it over and over again and then I had to watch It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World because that man is like my hero.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sad he's dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you still play the Pac-Man?
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember the Pac-Man thing they did was legendary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you still play that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I can find out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't they leave that up on the internet somewhere where you can still play that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I will put the link into the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to the Foogle question of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take Facebook and Google and slam them together, you get Foogle.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every week we ask a question in our Facebook and Google Plus fan communities and read some of our favorite answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I am going to have to limit how much I read tonight, guys, because there's just so many long answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so I do want the show to be over in a reasonable amount of time tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I apologize in advance if I don't read yours.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will start on Google Plus tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm going to read this from Travis H.,
[SPEAKER_04]: with the majority of the gaming world hating on their new console and a lead developer from EA coming out last week calling the system crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't even read the damn question, did I?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I said it was going to be about the Nintendo Let's Play thing, but let me read to you what I said for the communities.
[SPEAKER_04]: What are your thoughts on Let's Play videos?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you like to watch them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you someone that creates them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Lastly, how do you feel about the news story itself?
[SPEAKER_04]: Has it soured your opinion on Nintendo or do you think they were well within their rights to make money off their game images?
[SPEAKER_04]: And I link to the story that Loki talked about earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so now going back to Travis H's answer over on Google+.
[SPEAKER_04]: With the majority of the gaming world hating on their new console and a lead developer from EA coming out last week calling the system crap, I feel like the big N needs all the help and gamer love they can get.
[SPEAKER_04]: I own a Wii U and a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: In my opinion, Nintendo is failing miserably.
[SPEAKER_04]: They need to focus more on making some damn games for the Wii U and stop bitching about free advertisement and promotion of their games.
[SPEAKER_04]: As for the content and spoiler aspect of the videos, if you don't want the game content spoiled for yourself, here is a novel idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't watch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hashtag wake up Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that is a very similar thing that I've read on many places on the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you feel the same way about Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just making sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm assuming you do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Reading some of the other answers here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go to Facebook and I'm purposely being a little picky choosy from names I don't see all like in chat and in mailbag and other places.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I do encourage everybody to go read all of the answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll read this one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vince from AKVG Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a person that loves making and watching Let's Plays.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody that actually does Let's Play videos.
[SPEAKER_04]: I neither disagree or agree with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, LPs can be a gain or take on sales depending on how a certain game of theirs is handled.
[SPEAKER_04]: B. So does reviews and articles.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was typed via mobile so I'm thinking autocorrect really fucked with that sentence there but I think it's depending on how a certain game of theirs is handled but so do reviews and articles.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a tough topic really because we don't really know if Nintendo is right or wrong with making this decision.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess for now if you want to make a living off Nintendo long plays you'll have to contact Nintendo and work something out with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least you're still able to do them and not disappear from the internet like other companies do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chiggers asks, what's a Let's Play video?
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that tongue-in-cheek?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going to Zether.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zether says,
[SPEAKER_04]: and they were fun to watch as opposed to most of the YouTube partners who do game long plays for the cash like PewDiePie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even people like Chugga Conroy who play Nintendo games are not in it for the money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo is doing the right thing and frankly these people deserve what's coming to them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a pretty pointed answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: um let's see um Andy R says I don't watch let's plays myself but the news did solely my opinion of Nintendo a bit at least among the couple of people I know who do their own let's plays they're not trying to profit off the content they just want to provide entertainment and to share something they love with others
[SPEAKER_04]: Benjamin H actually replied to that and said, Andy, those LPs can still provide entertainment and share something they love.
[SPEAKER_04]: If they're not trying to profit from the Nintendo-based content, are they really going to be majorly affected by Nintendo trying to profit from it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Under Leveled Video replies and says, I do Let's Plays.
[SPEAKER_04]: I only monetize the videos that the publisher of the game has said it's okay to monetize.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blizzard, Minecraft, etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't care because they see it as free advertising for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Several indie game developers have gone on record to say if it hadn't been for people playing their game on YouTube, they never would have sold as many copies as they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: In an ideal world, I think the ad revenue generated should be split between the game developer and the YouTuber, but
[SPEAKER_04]: But perfect worlds are impossible in this money-grubbing existence.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting, because I suggested the same thing earlier.
[SPEAKER_05]: Once again, I'm just confused that the amount of money that they're generating per each video is so... It's so small that you really think that...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, it just seems kind of odd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand it's your property or whatever, and you're mad at people making money off of it because they like your property and they want to show people stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's not like they're putting out a DVD or something with your game on it and saying, oh, this is my game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let me finish the comment here from Underleveled Video because I think the end of it is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is a gray area, though, in copyright and fair use.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo owns the game, but the YouTuber owns their actions in said game as well as their commentary on top of the video.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a court case needs to happen to make legal precedent.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a scary thought, but... Is it really going to come to that?
[SPEAKER_04]: It might.
[SPEAKER_05]: uh not in Nintendo's case but maybe another company it could be something like you know where they use that fair was the content ID system and they overreach their bounds and like ban an account that's made a lot of money on something they've done that was Angry Game Nerd or whatever got his channel taken down one time and
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, to be fair, again, I just want to be clear, Nintendo is not doing the strike thing against the people.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were very clear, and they tried to make themselves look like the good guys in the comments saying, hey, we didn't do what certain other entertainment companies are doing, and we're just switching the monetization thing, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not actually doing copyright strikes that will get your channel taken down.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in the eyes of people who are thinking they're being the big asshole, being less of an asshole doesn't make you not an asshole.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I understand that they're doing the thing or whatever, that they're not taking down videos, but at the same time, they could also be like Minecraft and Blizzard and say, hey, it's cool that you guys show videos of our games.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yes, I understand that they can take down games, but the fact that they're taking all the ad revenue from it is still kind of a dick move.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, I want to read one more here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is a very interesting response.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of, you know, we've heard a lot of people that are very supportive of what Nintendo's doing and this one is kind of going the other direction that supports the Let's Players a little more.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let me read this.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's from Jeff B. A Let's Play video is one's own content.
[SPEAKER_04]: That person's style of play and their commentary make it their own.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is not the same as just posting a trailer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo makes the sandbox, we play in it, or choose not to as we're seeing now.
[SPEAKER_04]: relatively few YouTube creators make a sole living just off that content most of the time the best they get for doing that work and make no mistake a quality LP is work is a part-time jobs pay or enough for one nice dinner out a month honestly it doesn't even really matter whether Nintendo was legally or morally justified because it was bad business no matter how you slice it and I imagine this problem for Nintendo will diminish quickly as they continue to copyright claim people's LP videos
[SPEAKER_04]: When Nintendo started this, they had to have known it'd stop Let's Play videos of their own games getting made by a good chunk of the people putting out quality game content on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's free advertising that Nintendo's own, most loyal community does that gets more of their games sold.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Nintendo wants to nickel and dime, literally nickel and dime in some cases, some of their best community ambassadors, they can go right ahead.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure they're legally clear to do that, but maybe they should think twice about turning on their own fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: I welcome them to come over to Twitch and try the same advertising revenue claim and honestly I'm starting to hope Twitch caves it means no partners will be streaming newer Nintendo games more room for League of Legends streams just kidding I hate League of Legends someday Nintendo will realize that giving people access to your game in nearly any way you can not taking it away brings in sales and by doing this on YouTube they are indirectly taking access away because the community will stop showcasing their games
[SPEAKER_04]: So, very much saying that these guys are doing you a favor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo, you are... I'm kind of summarizing in my own words.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo, you are going to lose a lot of support on this.
[SPEAKER_04]: I found the tangent on Twitch interesting though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure what the point... I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure what the point was you were trying to make with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because does that mean you want Nintendo to go over to Twitch and you want Twitch to cave on that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because then no more newer Nintendo games on Twitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: But...
[SPEAKER_04]: Why would you want that to happen if you hate League of Legends?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's just saying, you know, it'd show them, like, you know, even if they get rid of, you know, YouTube videos of Nintendo games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And how old are we going here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are we talking about, like, if I have a NES Super Mario Let's Play or something like that, they're going to monetize that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because that right there, they're trying to sell virtual console games, and people don't know what the hell this game is, and they look up a Let's Play video for it, and they're like, hey, that looks kind of cool, I'm going to buy that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't have demos for those games, even though they really should find a way to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello, we're 2013 and you can't fucking figure out how to make a demo for a game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why aren't you getting people to your website where the YouTube is posted to make money off your website?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not... There's something I'm not... Because it's automatic.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's automatic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because ad revenue is automatic.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's just like, you know, why put ads on your website?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if I have Nintendo content on my website and I'm making ad revenue through those same... Literally, it's the same ads that you're getting through... It's all the Google Analytics stuff, so... It's kind of a workaround, I guess, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know I honestly think that the money part of it is a smaller factor than them trying to control content because I mean think about it you've got basically unsolicited advertising coming up yeah but it may not be exactly what Nintendo wants to see out there
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe that is a workaround.
[SPEAKER_05]: You make a private video.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, hey, someone could even get on this bandwagon.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have some sort of service where it creates a webpage for you that you go to to watch this video, almost like a URL redirector or shortener or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And look, there's ad content on there through Google Analytics, but you're still making money, but you just don't have an advertisement on the video.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: People love loopholes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Companies don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: there's some of the answers again because a lot of these were lengthy and I only have a little bit of time I did not want to read all of them but I encourage you guys to go read them for yourselves facebook.com slash orange lounge radio also google plus there was another answer over there at search for orange launch radio on google plus I would give you all the numbers but you'd forget
[SPEAKER_04]: E.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: has no games for the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I think a lot of that has to do with that they're pushing to do the Frostbite 3 engine for a lot of their games including I think sports games and Frostbite 3 does not work on the Wii U or basically they just don't want to make it work on the Wii U because they are developing a new Frostbite engine for mobile so
[SPEAKER_05]: In theory, they could create a Frostbite 2.5 or something like that that runs on Wii U and just have to port it over.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's just not worth it to them to do that because they're not making any money off of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, FIFA 14 is not coming to the Wii U because FIFA 13 sales were not very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although that's not a really good comparison because FIFA 13 was just FIFA 12 but re-skinned with a roster update.
[SPEAKER_05]: Literally, that's what it was on the Wii U. So...
[SPEAKER_05]: whatever but that's the case I think with a lot of these companies they're not porting their games to the Wii U because it's just not making any sense and one of these games that was a big part of E3 their presentation was Ghost Recon Online still on hold even though it was supposed to be coming out when is it coming out we haven't heard anything since like a year ago I don't know let me ask a question here is EA still making games for the Playstation Vita
[SPEAKER_05]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's necessarily like EA has it out for Nintendo or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've also heard the theory about maybe a botched relationship with Origin on Nintendo or whatever, which actually might be part of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think it's more in general an inability on Nintendo's part to grasp online.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think, for one, the online pass system couldn't be implemented on the Nintendo, which was a problem, I think, for EA in some regards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you don't see it in Mass Effect, do you?
[SPEAKER_04]: In the Mass Effect game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you don't see it in Mass Effect, but is it on Assassin's Creed 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because wouldn't that have Uplay on it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uplay is on Wii U because it's in Zombie U. Well, that's similar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, but there's a whole little separate Uplay channel that you can download and all this stuff on the Wii U as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't there be an Origin channel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: But what I think is, I think there's something about the online store and its inability to do what EA wants when it comes to a lot of the DLC, when it comes to the online passes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of the Mass Effect 3 DLC ever came to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: None of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not the free stuff or the pay stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Only the stuff that they were able to put on the disc, like the extended cut.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now that I think of it too, did any of the DLC come out for Black Ops 2 on the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure it did.
[SPEAKER_04]: so there's something weird there and to me that's the problem and I don't think it's I don't really buy the whole they can't do it I think there's not as much money to be made not because there's a lower adoption of Wii U's or whatever because if they're still making games for the Vita then that's not the only problem but the Vita, it's very easy to incorporate it works just like the Playstation 3 with all the DLC
[SPEAKER_04]: so I think there's something I think there's something with that is the real reason why EA is not continuing to put games out there because it doesn't match their vision of of being able to nickel and dime you online and possibly whatever is coming after this online pass maybe Wii U can't do hmm think I might be onto something maybe yeah yeah maybe um
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know what the sales numbers are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it is something that's worldwide.
[SPEAKER_05]: FIFA is a really big game worldwide, so maybe that happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or maybe they're just going to take the easy way out and just take the game from last year and once again just update the roster and just release a really half-assed game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: They might.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they could have done that with the Wii U, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just release the Wii version?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, no, the Wii U version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just release it again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just get it and update the rosters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was that in your little blog?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's move on to some news out of Google this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Google had their whole little... What was it called?
[SPEAKER_04]: The IO conference or something like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: and they announced some changes coming to Google Maps.
[SPEAKER_04]: They talked about some of the Hangouts and Google+.
[SPEAKER_04]: They talked a lot about one of the things they talked about on Google+, is that there will no longer be Google Plus games after June 30th.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, if you actually go to Google Plus games right now, they say they are no longer going to be available after June 30th.
[SPEAKER_04]: GameServices.com
[SPEAKER_04]: It's part of Google Play, a game service that's going to launch out of the Play Store that will link together mobile, social, and cloud gaming.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I seem to remember they were showing a demo that showed one guy playing on the web, one playing on a phone, and one on a tablet or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're all linked together.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm assuming Google Plus games, I mean, let's be real, they probably were not that popular in the first place because Google Plus did not catch on the way Facebook did.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's popular.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cultish, but it's not mainstream, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the games aren't catching on, so now you've got this instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're saying it's going to be different from Apple and what they do with Game Center because there will be back-end support, and this is not going to be just a standalone application.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyone making a game with Google Play has access to the developer services.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some games will have this incorporated already, like World of Goo, Kingdom Rush, Beach Buggy, Blitz...
[SPEAKER_05]: Osmos and so forth it's not mandatory there's no certification process interesting and it's cross platform which is wonderful they showed on one of the demos it was like a tech demo this racing game where they had all these different tablets and phones and stuff next to each other and it created a racetrack like a slot car racing thing but it was cross platform cross device and it all worked flawlessly
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so my thought is that they'll probably incorporate this at some point into Google+, where it's like play the game on the web or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of an evolution of that, which sounds a lot cooler than Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything sounds better than Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I get one more fucking invite for Candy Crush Saga, I'm going to cut somebody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Being stabbed in the eye is better than... Not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slightly better than Facebook games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I got some stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about Nintendo stuff?
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, Nintendo won an appeal to keep selling the Wii in the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, there was the whole litigation about Motiva, is that how it's pronounced?
[SPEAKER_07]: Saying that the Wii had infringed on two of its patents to track body position and body movement.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the judges agreed that their motive was just to win damages or a settlement, not for licensing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they said no, and Nintendo won.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Nintendo can keep selling the Wii, even though they should be trying to get that thing off shelves and try to make people buy Wii U instead, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they should just give up on the Wii U and actually put out a system.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's too early.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand why everybody's like, Wii U's dead and it's only been nine months.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, 3DS, same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we're sitting here after the holidays still saying the same story, then we can call the Wii U dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm not ready to say that yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'm not saying it's dead, but it really is highly underperforming for a Nintendo system.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you remember how hyper everyone was about the Wii, and then the Wii U comes out, and I'm still finding them no problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, piles of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 3DS was a Nintendo system, and it was the same story.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sold better than the Wii U. Did it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it, yeah, it's selling better than the, well, it's definitely selling better than the Wii U right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, but the price to get one was also half as much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Less than a Wii U, for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it's $250.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, and think about it this way, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, having a home console is a lot more, I think, of a commitment than having a handheld system.
[SPEAKER_07]: And with a handheld system, you have the advantage of it being just that, something you can carry around with you.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think with the 3DS, too, I mean, look at it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had a gimmick that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a 3D display without any 3D glasses.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that was like, whoa, that's a neat thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Versus the Wii U with, A, it's a tablet controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: People are used to playing with tablets, so it wasn't that big of a new thing, but 3D graphics without glasses, that was like, holy crap, even if no one uses it anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, there's phones that do the same thing now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan's old Galaxy did.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: The lenticular screen?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just not still willing to say it's dead at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I will say I think one big mistake they made is that they made that touchpad was really a step back to where touch gaming is at right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the whole having to use a stylus.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I guess you don't have to for some games, but it really should have been as good of a touch as modern tablets and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, yeah, people do know a tablet and they expect it to respond a lot better to touch than Nintendo's tablet does.
[SPEAKER_07]: For the record, Dan said that his phone that had the lenticular screen was the thrill.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it wasn't his Galaxy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was still kind of neat, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gave me the same type of headache the 3DS does.
[SPEAKER_05]: So are we going to have them release a Wii U with Tablet Plus that's going to have multi-touch on it and it's going to be an upgrade of what they do with Wii Remote Plus?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still would like to see some more games for the system I have, but I wouldn't be surprised if that's a place we end up next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: but I think this year is all about this is not a year to release any hardware maybe that whole Wii Fit thing which I'm sure is one of the games they're going to be pushing for the holidays that is a little bit different because that's an add-on with a very specific purpose but this is not the year to be pushing hardware for the Wii U or anything in the living room it will really alienate the people that have supported the system
[SPEAKER_04]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, OUYA.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was joking about this on Bobby's show.
[SPEAKER_05]: OUYA is going to be at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, at E3 in proximity to E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to be in a parking lot outside of E3 in a van.
[SPEAKER_05]: Down by the river?
[SPEAKER_05]: By the river, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, actually, they're going to be in the parking lot and they're going to be... They basically said, everything you need to put on a killer game demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: OUYA console, controllers, and TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not how you put on a killer game demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because... Granted, there are a lot of games... I mean, there's games on the Ouya, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: Not all of them were like, hey, buy me because this game is on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although they could show that parking game with no brake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Parking game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to know how they're going to fix my controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because my controller is all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_05]: And apparently the newer consoles that are shipping now have a fixed controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: So where do I RMA that bitch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: This is likely the same lot that Saints Row the Third used last year, which is across the street from Staples Center, which got even more exposure because, hey, it was right during the time when the Lakers were in the playoffs last year when E3 was going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or was it last year or two years ago?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it was last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: So even extra exposure, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, well, Konami talking E3 or at least a pre-E3 show and they've been doing this kind of, they've been doing like the Nintendo Direct thing for a little while too.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do these videos that go out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So Konami will be doing a pre-E3 show that will give the latest on some of their franchises on June 6th.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the third year that they've done it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Notice how, I think the last time they did it was when Rock Revolution came out.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: New trailers for Castlevania Lords of Shadow 2, which was also seen last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: A year before last, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: But also, Metal Gear Solid 5, which I'm sure some people are very excited about.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Phantom Pain.
[SPEAKER_07]: Snake is even older.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that will be there as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sure there will be some other unannounced goodies, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know we have some longtime Bomani fans who still listen to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would not go in anticipating anything as far as the beat games go, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: You never know if the new Xbox has this Kinect thing built in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they'll try the Rhythm Party thing again or Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think Dance Masters did very well.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Rhythm Party was just on sale over the weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might still be, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you don't have Rhythm Party and you like Bomani games and you have a Kinect, Rhythm Party's...
[SPEAKER_04]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem is there's only like five songs in the base game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all DLC.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's a pretty well put together game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They should have just made it a disc game with a well-rounded 50 songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wouldn't hold my breath as far as music games go, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you're going to see Beat Mania 2DX or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just call it a hunch.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of that stuff is long gone.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what the heck they would be putting up then because...
[SPEAKER_05]: Pro Evo
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week you guys send us emails, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and DarkSakura dives into the email bag head first and tries not to catch anything as she's pulling out your emails to read here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, why don't you read some emails for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we have three.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three whole emails.
[SPEAKER_07]: um, the first one dear OLR, a very belated congratulations on your achievement of reaching 500 plus episodes excuse me thanks for being there with me on so many long drives to work and back I wish that I could join you on live shows more often but family commitments usually conflict with that I have been listening to you since before my son was even born six years ago who is now old enough to game with me thank you for making me feel old
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: With the new Next Box being announced this week, I continue to be very excited about gaming even though I miss the days of the arcade or days gone by of trying to finish games we rented from the local video store.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes I feel that gamers today are very jaded considering there is a gamut of options out there on every imaginable platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: The constant complaints can often be disheartening.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'll go ahead and read it because it's kind of long.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's up to you if you want to read the rest of this on air or not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hoping DarkSakura, since she is unemployed or someone OLR, can use this license either for the show or even just to enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're welcome to keep it or give it away as you please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_07]: A one year subscription to Adobe Creative Cloud.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I saw that in the email bag earlier this week, and I was like, oh boy, DarkSakura's going to be pretty excited about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need new underwear, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: If she doesn't want it, then I would like to get the new audition.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be great for podcasts.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a very, very generous donation, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm always amazed by the generosity of our listeners just in being here and participating and even when there's free stuff like this to come out of it and a lot of that stuff will go right back into helping the show and VOG.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, given that I'm doing all of the graphics for the site and everything, yeah, I think I have a use for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me, I'm actually tearing up a little bit now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you cry on air?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I won't cry on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: I cried on air when we got a gift once.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why can't you cry on air?
[SPEAKER_07]: You've cried on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have cried on air, probably more than once, but anyhow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I usually just cry from wank, but this is actually like, oh my god, it's super, super awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, again, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You really didn't have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know that shit ain't cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you might have had it in or whatever, but I really hope you did not have to pay a lot of money for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't the current CS suite something like a good $700?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I know that when I tried to get the student edition for CS6, it was like $300.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm still using 5.1.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I'm feeling verklempt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk amongst yourselves, we'll give you a topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nah, I'm ready to go on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just a little floored right now, and probably sinus medicine has something to do with that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dear OLR, after a two week vacation, I came back to find my Wii U gamepad was left on in TV remote controller mode the entire time plus a day.
[SPEAKER_07]: or 360 hours straight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It responded when I turned it off and I later started the Wii U to see if I had burn-in on the pad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope!
[SPEAKER_07]: It was plugged in the whole time or it would have turned itself off.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good argument for unplugging it while playing and that's from Rababa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a long time to leave that thing on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that thing was only supposed to work for like three hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess maybe because the remote doesn't really use the transmitter functions.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: He said it was plugged in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's plugged in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But on top of that, though, it not having any burn-in is... I'm sorry, I'm still a little floored by the other thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It not having burn-in is actually pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember... Now, of course, this was 19 years ago, earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, having Samurai Shodown 3 and the big screen having burn-in after a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I mean... I remember the Apple IIe monitors were really susceptible to burn-in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had to be careful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, you had that little icon in the corner like forever that was your computer icon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it lived there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It never went away.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's actually a really good sign of a quality product.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I won't rag on the Wii U that much anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you will.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't lie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you know me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a hater.
[SPEAKER_04]: Liars don't get codes for software.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so we have one more email.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this person does not give us a name, so I'm just gonna say Kirk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good evening, my OLR peeps.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Kirk, and I wanted to email you guys and say that for about six to eight months, I was taking a break from console gaming and listening to gaming podcasts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your show was one of my gaming podcasts I would listen to on a regular basis, and even though I couldn't make it to the live streams, I've been a loyal listener for many years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw, we love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this past year, I decided to be a real adult, which leads me to buying my first home, going back to school to finish my degree, and finally working on those New Year resolutions of losing weight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Currently have lost 121 pounds.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's like losing a supermodel.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to say, though, with all due respect, I think that's great that you have those priorities, but I don't own a home, I don't have a degree from college, and I'm fat.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are not that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still feel like an adult.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just saying, you don't have to have those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I understand the point the listener was trying to make.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are not that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: with being occupied with all those things along with a full time job gaming fell by the wayside and I've given up my PS3, Xbox 360, 3DS and listening to gaming podcasts things have settled down recently this year with me adjusting to my new townhouse except for the noisy neighbors and keeping a regular routine with school and gym time I've gotten back into gaming
[SPEAKER_07]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_07]: On My Favorite Hobbies was listening to you while listening to podcasts in the background.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I wanted to say thank you for entertaining me for so many years.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm glad to be back as a loyal listener.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we are glad to have you back.
[SPEAKER_04]: This fat homeless dropout is so happy to have you here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had to, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I get the real point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes in order to make change happen in your life, you have to change some things.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I get the point.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have one thing that is becoming so distracting to the point that you can't get anything else done...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: People who drink, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: You either can cut it out a little bit and you're fine or you have to cold turkey it and not drink at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or smoking.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be able to get to your other priorities and stop something that's getting in the way of a productive life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or smoking, Jamie, because some people can do it cold turkey or some people have to do it cold turkey.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some people need the patch or a support group or, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you're my uncle and you smoke the electric cigarettes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will go ahead and say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nicotine in and of itself is as bad for you as caffeine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all the other crap in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, I personally take exception to the real adult thing, but I understand it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, same here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I'd like to have a job.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not for lack of trying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But at the same time, you know, I think that you could, and I've had to explain this to my mother, and I always give her a hard time because I was like, how much of my Nintendo did you play when I was 12?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can be into gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can be into people years older than me who are still majorly into every new anime that ever comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not as much as I used to be even though something comes out that I might like or I like watching the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone's got their thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing wrong with enjoying something and having fun as long as you don't do it to the exception of all else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think that's the real point, yes Exactly, and yeah, I'm not going to go off anymore about that But I do have to say congratulations to you, Kirk, for your fantastic achievements I mean, you lost a person That's amazing Dan lost that much Yeah, Extifer from Horde House lost a whole heck of a lot as well And I know that took a lot of work, and it's very impressive
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, thank you, Fifth Dream, for not making me feel like I'm the oldest person in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hearts.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for the emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com Before we get back into some gaming news, it's time for us to get a little ranty with a segment we call the F-Years of the Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess the only F you that I have is to this cold that I got from Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: But other than that, I'm looking at the Adobe site with tears in my eyes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm seriously like shaking with joy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like Panto knocked on my door and said we want you to design everything in the world for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that ruins the angsty segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to that emailer for the generous gift for screwing up the FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and F you to everyone putting spoilers out about Star Trek Into Darkness because I haven't seen it yet and I'm not reading any reviews because they've all been spoilery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, to UEF for their controllers being all sorts of broken.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just the analogs.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really annoying.
[SPEAKER_05]: It can be fixed with a software patch, but it's not really fixed.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just kind of a workaround, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: It still sucks, though, because I'm trying to play some of these games and it's just like, ugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My FU of the week goes to... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things are fairly well, so I don't have a lot of angst.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to traffic on the way to the Bay Area, because it took me three hours to make a drive that should take an hour and 45 minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: and FU to the Kabuki Theater in San Francisco although actually it's kind of like the good kind of FU because like I loved seeing that movie there so much because it was in a theater that served booze and they only let 21 and up people in there so no babies and the reason why I say FU is now I want to see every movie at that theater in San Francisco and that's not possible
[SPEAKER_04]: My movie-going experience bar has been forever changed because of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The bar has been raised.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a couple more news stories for you guys, and then we will get to Twitter topics and our Skype line here eventually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So let's get to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there was an announcement a few months ago about Batman Arkham Origins, and it was revealed that
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, Batman's not going to be voiced by Kevin Conroy anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be a new person.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there was much bitching.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thankfully now, the deal has been put in place where, yes, Kevin Conroy will be Batman because he is Batman.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he will be returning as the voice of Batman in the new game when it comes out in October.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also revealed, thanks to an Amazon pre-order, there apparently will be DLC where Deathstroke will be playable in some form.
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably like the Challenge missions and the other games.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, uh, neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Glad that they have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll make a lot of people happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm glad that they have the original voice coming back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, is Mark Hamill actually going to be doing the voice of the Joker again in this game, or is it going to be just like... I don't think the Joker's in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's how they got around it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but Mark Hamill has officially retired.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure he has.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, he actually really has retired.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently it was doing a number on his voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, so, yeah, Deathstroke would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know we'll see
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one more story for you guys, and I apologize.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's political, but it is making the rounds on the gaming blogs this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a comment from Vice President Joe Biden.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you might remember that when the whole horrible, horrible thing in the school in Connecticut broke out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joe Biden started a task force.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was assigned by President Obama to talk about how do you curtail gun violence and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they did this whole thing about games and all this.
[SPEAKER_04]: In May, the vice president met with 20 representatives from face-based organizations to talk about gun control and immigration.
[SPEAKER_04]: He talked about video games in this as well, according to Politico.
[SPEAKER_04]: Franklin Graham, who is the son of Billy Graham, the evangelist, I guess is what you call him,
[SPEAKER_04]: said to the vice president that, quote, media and entertainment that portray violence should be subject to a special tax with the proceeds going to help victims and their family.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is according to a rabbi, Rabbi Julie Schoenfeld, who was also in that session.
[SPEAKER_04]: Biden said, quote, there's no, quote, no restriction on the ability to do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no legal reason why they couldn't
[SPEAKER_04]: do attacks on violent media.
[SPEAKER_04]: Going on, the quote says, he said they really need a good scientific study, which they've done on things like smoking.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's interesting about this is that it's not necessarily limited to games, which I can appreciate for one, is that when they talk about attacks on violent games, then I'm like, well, what about R-rated movies and NC-17 movies?
[SPEAKER_04]: And what about things on TV and networks and
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I think that's just ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only way I could see them ever doing that is because we need the tax dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, other than that, I mean, it's just... It's kind of ridiculous, because once again, you're just taxing things that don't necessarily have a direct correlation with violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, the problem with this, it all goes back to the root problem with that California law that we spent all this money trying to defend.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Supreme Court overturned it because it was all up to somebody's interpretation.
[SPEAKER_04]: And how can you tax something that has to be interpreted?
[SPEAKER_04]: To be fair to the Vice President, even though I don't necessarily agree with what he said, he did say we would need a really good scientific study.
[SPEAKER_04]: They would have to have facts.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to need to waste more money.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just don't think it would be successful because what is violent?
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody would have to set that line and it's too what's violent to me might be not necessarily what's violent to you what's not violent to Franklin Graham or Rabbi Julie Schoenfeld
[SPEAKER_07]: And what they're ignoring is that there actually have been scientific studies that have disproven that violent video games aren't just as likely as a movie or watching the news or reading a book.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're as likely to cause violence as any other portrayal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, the whole rating system in and of itself is a really horrible joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not talking about the game ratings.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game ratings are actually better right now than the movie ratings.
[SPEAKER_04]: They really are.
[SPEAKER_04]: The movie ratings is in need of a serious, serious...
[SPEAKER_04]: Reorganization.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, everything from the fact that you have R-rated movies that are like Saw-level violent, then you have an R-rated movie like Romy and Michelle's High School Reunion is an R-rated movie because the F-word is used more than once by Janine Garofalo's character.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I put a movie like Romy and Michelle next to a movie like Saw and I'm like, you know, we got a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Janine Garofalo is just an R-rated actress, so it makes sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, didn't she also turn Scientologist?
[SPEAKER_07]: It just makes me roll my eyes and feel very sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever, you know what, that's her thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's totally not the point I'm trying to make here is about the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a joke that a movie like that, I mean, should kids see it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not necessarily, but I think a 14 or a 15 year old could see it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's no worse than there are.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a movie about high school for fuck's sake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, it's nothing different than what they're hearing at school.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Degenerate Johnny in chat at live.vognetwork.com says FCC has been quoted to state that the ESRB is the best rating system of all entertainment.
[SPEAKER_04]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says Evil Dead, the new one, was originally rated NC-17 until they cut a few scenes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have zero interest in the new Evil Dead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zero.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard things about the movie and I'm just like, no thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does not have the chin.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can get you legit caught up.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I really don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, but... I kind of want to see it, but it doesn't have Bruce, so what's the point?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's in the cameo.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a Bruce Campbell being in the movie movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of cameo does he have?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, does he open the door for somebody?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is he a manager at S-Mart?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know and I wouldn't want to spoil it.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was a producer on the movie, so that's why.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: If the proceeds from this movie go to making an Army of Darkness 2...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: It exists for a purpose.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, judge however you want to judge, but I will be there as I am every single year for the showing of Showgirls at the Castro Theater hosted by Drag Queens because I live for that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, I need to go again this year because I didn't go last year and I'm sad.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, judge me all you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won't go see Evil Dead, but I'll go see Showgirls for the 10th time in the theater.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what's Elizabeth Berkley doing right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: I seriously think that we should... They should kickstart a sequel to that movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: They, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why we're talking about this on OLR, I don't know, but we're almost at the end of the show, so we can do this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Showgirls 2, Pennies from Heaven
[SPEAKER_04]: was the sequel.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's on IMDb, and they actually were selling DVDs, and they screened the movie earlier in the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to see that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I haven't seen it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not going to bother watching it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought she was a great sport for going and participating.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, there's a Showgirls Off-Off Broadway production right now, and she actually is in it right now as the character she played in the movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just realized I won't talk about Evil Dead, but I know the In and Outs of Showgirls.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's so bad, it's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Essentially the same thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't help myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't like violence and body parts and animal violence.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love titties.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think that's such a terrible thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: To be fair, the sex scene in the pool kind of looked like she was being attacked by a shark.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, that's sort of similar to the violence you see in video games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, seriously, who does what she does?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, we get to the show where it's time for... And it was like trying to get her last year because it was like the 20th anniversary or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were trying to get her, but I think she was pregnant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even better.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't show up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Baby on the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we're about to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get to last-minute stories and Twitter topics and the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: But in order to start getting the Skype calls, I've got to free up the Skype line, which means I've got to say bye to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm lusting over the Adobe Suite right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, go install that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm already installing seven programs right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, save the audition license for me because I might want to check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not downloading it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry you had to be here remotely.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we really like to have everybody here in studio, but with no show next week, that's a lot of Jamie to be missing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm glad we were able to come up with something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Feel better.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually am starting to feel a lot better.
[SPEAKER_07]: My drugs are doing the trick.
[SPEAKER_04]: The power of OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show heals.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be healed.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to tell you that Dan warned me about him being sick in enough time and that we had shared that soda that I started taking precautions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so I'm not nearly as sick as I might have been.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually do not.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was one attached to the Sega thing, but it's a little bit outdated, so I'm not going to bother.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: I am going to Alabama, and if any of our listeners in or near the South with transportation would like to drive me around because I won't have a car, I'll pay for your gas.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're hitchhiking with OLR listeners, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that what this has come down to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you remember one of the times I went back maybe about seven years ago?
[SPEAKER_07]: I went to Biloxi to a DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where they had the fifth mix machine and they had just gotten a fifth mix and we had had it for like ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was, you know, perfect attacking stuff and, you know, they're like, oh, what do you think of this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone was so nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love meeting the arcade folks and I got to go to my old arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm going to try to make it by the cyber station at the former Bel Air Mall at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: you know I used to work there we may not be the most popular podcast on the internet but I really love it because you know what some podcasts out there they'll ask you for a hundred thousand dollars on kickstarter to meet stretch goals here at OLR we just want to bum a ride yeah I'm gonna be staying in Daphne which is an hour automobile and I kind of don't want to be in Daphne the whole time while my mom's at work oh gosh all right well good luck to you and uh Pixar didn't happen
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll probably just get pictures of oyster shells.
[SPEAKER_04]: It works for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great night, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you back in a couple weeks here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hearts, hearts, hearts.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm sure she'll be in chat to say good night to the listeners and so forth and finish out our show in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you want to stop on by, if you happen to be listening live, live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want to say hi to DarkSakura in the email bag, you can always do that as well, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to the last minute stories, and I'll start to bring up the Twitter topics, and we will open up the phones at 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're already getting calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: The words had barely escaped my mouth, and we're already getting phone calls, so let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: What up, guys?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Zeno from the OKC.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you been?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, ZenoCore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_02]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, making music here and there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know you were... Yep, yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't... Or at least I didn't remember you were a music maker.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, it's a recent thing I picked up over the past four or five months or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Got stuff up on SoundCloud.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Slice Unicorn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Check it out when you have availability.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome plug.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys are discussing the Let's Play situation.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think Nintendo is going a bit overboard, although I think it's a bit of an automatic attack just due to the way that their stuff is set up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But taking the revenue, it's really just giving the guys a noogie on top of taking away their content.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's the way I look at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, everybody has the luxury of doing it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have seen other companies do it before.
[SPEAKER_02]: But really, I mean, they'd be better off leaving it as open advertising for their games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, because on top of that, the whole sandbox situation does apply.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the fact that they gave a product out for play, the moment somebody starts playing it, it's completely different.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like you take Video Games Awesome Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their production for what they do on top of the game is tremendous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and they do it not just for games but for releases and everything else too.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they're going to cut that off, they need to cut it off for all media that they do that with.
[SPEAKER_02]: So nobody's allowed to do anything unless they pay Nintendo some money.
[SPEAKER_04]: So meaning like reviews and things or what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, if they're not going to treat it underneath fair use, then everybody who openly plays that for longer than five minutes or so needs to pay Nintendo that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't think, like, for instance, Revision 3, their reviews go on for eight or nine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, they're a big name.
[SPEAKER_02]: They'd never undercut them, but the little guys will step all over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: or that I well one thing I was kind of thinking with this is that I'm surprised a lot of people have just said all right we'll just not use YouTube because YouTube could kind of get some of the blame in this too for kind of letting Nintendo or quote-unquote letting Nintendo do it right split their videos up into what I say it's five minutes or 459 you know it's kind of a pain in the ass it's a pain in the ass but you know whatever I mean if that's what needs to be done
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's also going to cut into... The viewers aren't going to be there either.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, you have to take into account how many video game tournaments are paying rights.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because not that many as far as I saw.
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless it's sponsored by the video game company themselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: That means the streams for Team Spooky are also going to be cut out.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they can't show any of the video game tournaments as well as EVO coverage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that means going up against Justin.TV, and if they really want to undercut Justin.TV out of that much revenue, then they'd have a court case fight there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think there's an easy answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think it's going to go back to that guy on our Facebook that said it's going to take a legal precedent to really figure this out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And although, sure, it was a dick move on Nintendo's part, and I think it would have just been a better situation if they've all split the money or worked with the content people to try to figure out a solution rather than sick the lawyers on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: That probably would have been better.
[SPEAKER_04]: But again, they're not the first to do so, and they won't be the last.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, true, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other thoughts, Unicor?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that's pretty much it, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: You guys have a good show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, thanks for tuning in and lending your perspective.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more time for that SoundCloud.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's soundcloud.com slash xenocore?
[SPEAKER_02]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_02]: Give it a listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you'll like a lot of the stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of music?
[SPEAKER_04]: Chiptune?
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's sponsored by the demo scene.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I grew up with, so it tends to mirror that, but it's all over the place.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it a listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I thought you were going to say something else with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tryon Worlds announced that Rift is going free-to-play this past week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that might have been where you were going with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had layoffs, so there was a lot of rumors on.
[SPEAKER_05]: They haven't really said how many, but it was like 70%, 80% of the staff was one of the rumors, but I don't think that they said that's far exaggerated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have another call coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, it's PrinceBrightStar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, PrinceBrightStar.
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yourself?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said you were going to listen more often.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've made good on that promise, so thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've tried to make it every week since.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've also got a comment about the whole Let's Play situation as well here.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of people do.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I recently started doing Let's Play myself, particularly with Minecraft and
[SPEAKER_06]: also some of the Phantasy Star games I started this back in December but I have yet to monetize any of my stuff because I have yet to actually get into any of those networks but my understanding on the whole situation with Nintendo is they're even monetizing for themselves stuff from
[SPEAKER_06]: The IGN Network, GameStation, and such like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm wondering if they have actually broken contracts in this, and if it's time for the Let's Player community to actually get together, host some sort of charity drive, or rather a donation drive, which will cover the fees for all this, the lawyer fees, and actually take this to court.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the laws are just...
[SPEAKER_06]: Very, very out of date at this point to be able to cover something like Let's Plays.
[SPEAKER_04]: You mean fair use laws need to be reexamined?
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, I mean, Nintendo may also be cutting into reviews and such which are allowed under fair use.
[SPEAKER_04]: What about some of the things I was saying earlier?
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't put an entire movie up and do talking over the movie, but if I wanted to do a movie review, I could obviously use little bits and pieces, which I could still do with a Nintendo game, but I can't exactly upload that to YouTube where I talk over a movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why is it different with games?
[SPEAKER_06]: True, and I agree with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And in that situation, you can't do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, what most people do currently is they go and sell their tracks sort of on a site like Rift Tracks or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem with video games is they're an interactive medium.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when you're watching a movie, it's going to be the same for everybody regardless.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're playing a video game, your experience is going to be different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Granted, I respect Nintendo and any other company for doing what they want to do because it's their game, but the gameplay itself and any commentary or putting their face on the video or putting their chat on the video as well, that's their property at that point.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think, as a let's play person yourself, let's say something's got to give here and Nintendo wants a little piece of the pie and a little bit of the revenue, what do you think would be a solution that would make everybody happy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's  honestly, I think it's better that this doesn't actually go to court and each company either says you can do whatever you want or cut some sort of fee or say
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't do this and don't post any videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: Make it clear as to what you're allowed to do, what you're not allowed to.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it's also up to the community to respect that and not put out videos that the company states they don't want videos out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially maybe for newer games, you know, having Let's Play a Bioshock Infinite before the game's actually released, when a lot of people want to know, you know, what's the ending?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, that could be detrimental to the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or for, in a worst case, a game like, say, Aliens Colonial Marines, if all those reviews hadn't come out so quickly, and I realize this hurts the community even more, but with the reviews and also the embargo that was out,
[SPEAKER_06]: People weren't able to cancel their pre-orders before it was too late on that game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, PrinceBrightStar, any other thoughts for us before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll try to squeeze in one more call.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: They said there's going to be another dashboard update.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or there's a rumor that another dashboard update is going to come to the Xbox 360 before the next system comes out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Saying that it's going to update the interface again to make it look more like Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think this could be because of some of the rumors about the set-top boxes that are going to come out really cheap?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about that, but maybe they're just trying to update it so that it looks nicer or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hate when they keep changing the interface, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones and take a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lens Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, this is your opening act for, I guess, this is the last time, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I brought the shots fired.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll let it slide this one time, but you make another Chrono Triggers better than Super Metroid joke, and it's over.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all good fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_03]: So I just wanted to repeat something that I've actually been repeating, and it's one thing that a lot of people don't realize about this whole Nintendo Let's Play thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just because it's free advertising doesn't mean they have to want it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's something that a lot of people... They're like, oh, it's free advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why wouldn't they want it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe they want to control more of the advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so the argument of it's free advertising, they should be happy with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's free advertising that I've gotten over the past eight years that I haven't wanted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, that's a good analogy.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really good analogy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that sometimes, you know, like people will say something and kind of like use your site or your show or something and you're kind of like, I don't know if I would necessarily have said that myself type of thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a really good analogy.
[SPEAKER_03]: so you know just because it's free advertising doesn't mean they necessarily want it and I mean the thing like the difference between like Minecraft the reason I fully support Notch for his position is because he's not telling a story in Minecraft he gave an actual sandbox
[SPEAKER_03]: and you're telling your own stories whereas a Let's Play of Luigi's Mansion you're telling the Luigi's Mansion story granted you're going right or left whenever you want to but you're still telling Nintendo's story
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but you can say that sandbox games, you know, say if I go and just run around in Saints Row the Third and just not necessarily play in the story stuff, but just kill people or do silly stuff that that should be fair because it is telling.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I agree with you on that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's different than playing the Saints Row the Third story.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's kind of where my line is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Screw it around in Grand Theft Auto or Saints Row or Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely, that should be fair use.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Machinima is a great example.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except with Microsoft's game content rules kind of...
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to work out with them if you're going to do Machinima.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's true, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft really laid the hammer down on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't think that's all of your Let's Play people, but certainly there are some Let's Play people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell, we did Mass Effect Drunk the other night, and maybe BioWare didn't appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But once again, though, they need to get with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, sorry that, you know, Microsoft's not saying that they don't want their games associated with, you know, stoners and loudmouths and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they keep saying that they keep like going back and forth what they want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, we're going to make games that appeal to mass, you know, to, you know, core gamers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, we're gonna make family games.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think they know what their focus is almost.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to appeal to people that aren't buying their system or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But what a really interesting point is that they may not want the advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just kind of makes me think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really appreciative that there's many of you out there that put OLR in your usernames or your clan names or OLR or VOG for VOG and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: It helps spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you better not be acting like an idiot when you're doing that because then it makes people go, I don't know what this VOG thing is, but what a bunch of assholes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's not good.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not the advertising we want.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think it's necessarily that...
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe these people are fans of those games, and so they're excited about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not necessarily like advertising.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because no one needs to advertise Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everyone knows what the fuck Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: is, for the most part.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, obviously, we've seen some...
[SPEAKER_05]: Some pictures from Super Mario World and Super Metroid that people don't know how to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm just saying that, for the most part, people are aware of what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not necessarily free advertising, but it's just a unique take on it with the Let's Play stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you're just straight playing through the game without any sort of commentary on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really hard to say that you're taking anything away from them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's still, yeah, it's free advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Nintendo may not want that advertising.
[SPEAKER_03]: And maybe they're okay with the Let's Play community saying we're not going to do Nintendo videos anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe that's what they want.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so this is, you know, they're kind of doing, oh, yeah, we're the good guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, you didn't want to take our offer.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know, okay, have fun doing the Microsoft and the Sony stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, no, they won't be doing Microsoft either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but Microsoft hasn't gone through with YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't, but they did kind of make the first move in this whole thing a few months ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still, that's even weird, though, that they would, because once again, I would see that as strange if they're going to try to put out these sort of features where they're trying to get people to broadcast on Twitch and broadcast on YouTube and stuff and share all these videos and things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, but we don't want you to do that, or at least don't want you to make money doing it.
[SPEAKER_03]: well pardon me that you tell me how I should make my money Nintendo's not pulling a Sega, Microsoft's not pulling a Sega but they're just saying you can't and at least Microsoft has a licensing path so you can make money from it but you wouldn't be able to recoup the licensing costs unless you were Machinima.com or Revision3 or one of these larger sites
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what we need to do is we just need to have some sort of reform to this whole you buy the game, you get the game thing instead of it being a license because this is where all the bullshit's coming from is fucking licensing software.
[SPEAKER_05]: It needs to be you own that shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that you can turn around and say, okay, I buy Halo 4, Halo 4 is mine, and I'm going to sell copies of it and claim that it's Loki's Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but that's exactly what you're saying is that in order to own it, you have to be able to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure that we can kind of come to a sort of happy medium where lawyers won't let them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just straight up piracy that you at least own the stuff that you have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I own a car doesn't mean that I've manufactured those cars.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't go and clone my car and expect to get away with it, but that car is mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can do whatever the hell I want to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no easy answer to this, and I'm sure the conversation will be continuing through the next few weeks, especially when we see what other companies are going to follow in Nintendo's footsteps, because I bet there'll be at least one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, Bobby, before I let you go, earlier in the show we were talking about some of our predictions for Tuesday's Xbox announcements, and I was kind of curious, since you are the opening act and everything, as you say, what are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mostly agree with you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not going to... No price, no date.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: I do think Xbox Infinity is going to be the name.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that they'll give the name.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that they'll show a couple games.
[SPEAKER_03]: but I think they'll talk more about the entertainment offerings and stuff but you gotta realize this is also being broadcast live on TV so this is so they're probably gonna try to reach everything and leave a lot of the core stuff maybe to E3, I don't know I do think it's funny and I mentioned this in chat and I don't think you guys picked up on it about the Space Poncho thing they have gone full board with the Twitter handle XboxRevealTent
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and fully embracing that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's probably going to be the Space Poncho of this year or at least that's what Microsoft hopes the Space Poncho of this year is going to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have to understand you can't force Space Poncho.
[SPEAKER_05]: Space Poncho is just something that happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a natural thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can't just make a viral video.
[SPEAKER_04]: The video has to go viral.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby, looking forward to checking out Gran Turismo 6 when it comes out?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did Gran Turismo 5 ever come out?
[SPEAKER_03]: I will get to play Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you're looking forward to E3.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's only a few weeks away.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got my appointment time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Wednesday morning.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's when I'll be playing Saints Row 4.
[SPEAKER_03]: They said they're going to have a playable portion.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope I'm there with you so I can pick up the phone and actually call Loki after that and hand you the phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I got to play Saints Row 4 as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I downloaded the Trouble with Clones expansion as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're ending the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Bobby, any other quick final thoughts before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_03]: Chrono Trigger greater than Super Metroid?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a bad final thought and for that I'm hanging up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be an incorrect thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to close up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm really sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were a few of you still trying to call that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm very sorry but we are running a little over and I have to do some things after the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do remember you can always tweet us, twitter.com.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also email us, mailbag at orange.trader.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a great way to get all of your thoughts out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me, speaking of Twitter, go to the Twitter real quick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, I don't know if you had any other last-minute stories real quick here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's just a story that they're going to... I mean, they've already talked about doing this before, but they're replacing Microsoft Points with real money.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw tweeting us that BlazBlue anime is getting a fall release in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know they were making an anime about BlazBlue.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're making a game for Guilty Gear, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: A good way to kind of enhance things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Misty sending us some tweets from Asen because she was at the show and she tweeted us some pictures from Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for rubbing it in, Misty, because I wish I could be there right now because that cookies and cream flavor is so good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's that free advertising that maybe Pinkberry doesn't want the advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: We keep giving them on our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should stop that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spazinator tweeting us his Facebook fan page for his kitty, Anakin.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's a cute cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at cat pics, but I like that you set up a whole little Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Smiling Yoshi tweets us and says, Smiling Yoshi wonders if he'll someday be subject to Nintendo's defense of copyrights.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'm a Yoshi doll, and I'm so darn cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I remember this account.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a Twitter account that's this little dolly Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: that makes all these tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's really cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, there's Smiling Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a little doll.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine like a garden gnome that goes everywhere and tweets from all the stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I have that doll.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I should say Josh has that doll, but we have that doll in the house.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, so Smiling Yoshi is worried that maybe Nintendo is going to shut down this Twitter account.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you have anything to worry about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because at least, you know, I'm looking at your user icon, which is Yoshi kind of setting on your feet or a friend's feet or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm thinking, you know, that picture is like 5% Yoshi and 95%.
[SPEAKER_04]: a body in a room so I think you'd be okay I think I think that would be that would actually be okay with fair use laws just so you know
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft tweeting us, Guilty Gear XRD Sign got announced today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's the game I was talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't know there was a... Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's kind of funny, though, that name, though, you know, XRC Sign or XRD Sign, because it's like all the, you know, games have been like Guilty Gear Accent Core Plus or like, you know, they have like some sort of weird symbol after them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like XRD.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like X entry into the series and some random sign.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, a tweet from Eric RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: People often say devs are high when they make game ideas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's one put to practice, maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he tweets us a link to something over on Destructoid about the game Demon Sheik.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a novel idea!
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you listen to this show every week, Eric?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the same thing happened to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe that's why you tweeted it to us, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: If only someone would make a game like, you know, Bungie Ferret Tossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like we said, it ought to be a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: If only that was available on Xbox Live Indie Games.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, Demon Sheik is apparently a crossbreed between WarioWare, Earthbound, and The Curse of Monkey Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know how that goes together there.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I guess if you're a fan of Destructoid's podcast, then there's lots of lulzy in-jokes there for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: If Podtoid's gonna get a game, then you know what I want?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I want?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want two games!
[SPEAKER_04]: One game isn't good enough anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that was it for Last Minute Stories, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys very much for tuning into our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like our show, remember, this is an indie production.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do do everything here, you know, for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't really monetize the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we ought to, but we do pay out of pocket to do the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We just love the community.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like paying the money to spend time with our friends every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: All we ask, help us grow our community.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell a friend or two about the show and help spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It helps.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep showering DarkSakura with gifts because she really likes that too and gets her all of the glint.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was really awesome though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a great idea too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that because it's something that in turn will just help VOG in general.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, before we close up shop, we've got to go around and get final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: My final thought is that I showed quite a bit of self-restraint in this digital games mayhem sale on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I didn't buy a lot of this.
[SPEAKER_05]: I buy random weird shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I only bought two things.
[SPEAKER_05]: I bought the Sam & Max collection, which is all three seasons of Sam & Max.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's like 18 episodes of gaming to play.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Saints Row 2, because I didn't have it yet on Steam.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, that'd be pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, and, and, I need people to give me suggestions for game night.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, because otherwise I'm just gonna pick something at random.
[SPEAKER_05]: It may end up being Call of Duty or something, because I can't think of...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, it'll be like 8, 8.30ish.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, I think that way we can play a lot longer because, you know, we won't have to worry about, you know, the work day next day for most people.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yes, let me know on the forums what you want to play so we can consider that.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple final thoughts from me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will echo what Bobby Blackwolf in chat is saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some VOG announcements coming on June 2nd, so stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Horde House has a big surprise this week, so tune in on Wednesday at 7 o'clock Pacific to hear that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I guess just plugs from me.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will be back probably in two weeks, but stay tuned to our Twitter just in case we're able to pull out a show during Memorial Day weekend.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll let you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But otherwise, have a great week.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of you in the States, have a great three-day weekend on Memorial Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of you throughout the rest of the world, have a great week, whatever you're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And E3's almost here, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of gaming news coming at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brace yourselves for this Xbox thing on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a great week, everybody, and have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_01]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_01]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next week!