[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight, April 21st, 2013, Nintendo announces a sequel to one of their classics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could a cancelled TV show be brought back for the new Xbox?
[SPEAKER_07]: And an old, unreleased Sega console is unearthed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 501 for this April the 21st of 2013.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's our blue jeans episode, I guess you could say, coming off a high from last week in our 500th episode.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's so 80s.
[SPEAKER_01]: They don't really use that marketing anymore, do they?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hi there, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if they use that marketing anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that's a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember those commercials where they would sing the blues and it was the 501 blues.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just remember the Saturday Night Live commercials that were bad idea jeans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do they have those classic clips on YouTube or did NBC pull them all?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had a bunch of them on Hulu.
[SPEAKER_02]: You could watch a lot of the goth talks and fluffy talk.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was back when all the funny people were on Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: The funny people were on Saturday Night Live my senior year of high school.
[SPEAKER_08]: or I mean to be fair before somebody snaps at us if you're not talking about the originals from 75
[SPEAKER_08]: the what not ready for primetime players nodding my head at that because clearly they hello Belushi but I wasn't born yet so but I have come to appreciate after all this time Gilda Radner comic genius love that woman yeah and they were all great really but 1994 best year of SNL oh yeah without a doubt good stuff I'll say hello to Techmaster Loki hi did you ever watch Saturday Night Live back in the day uh
[SPEAKER_06]: I've watched it off and on.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a time where there was a lot of people in there that I thought were funny and then I stopped watching after a while because I'm like, eh, they're not funny anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I came back and they're like, oh, okay, you're funny again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now we're kind of at that, oh, they're not funny anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't really watch it anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: If really funny things happen, the internet blows up about it and there's clips on Hulu.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I remember back in the day when I was in junior high school, that was the thing, was staying up late on Saturday night to watch Saturday Night Live and like,
[SPEAKER_08]: Could you get all the way?
[SPEAKER_08]: Could you stay up late enough to make it to the end of the show?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or do you fall asleep after weekend update?
[SPEAKER_02]: You had that much problem?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, my Friday night going into Saturday morning was a pot of... In junior high, yes, I had that problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, this was high school, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was a pot of coffee, probably two, and it was Saturday Night Live followed by Headbangers Ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Followed by 120 Minutes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I would like listen to like Pantera and all that all night and then go into The Cure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And all of my prog rock.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, we're going to have a Kate Bush revival tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome to my senior year.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember there were some video games based off Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the Wayne's World game, which was awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the Wayne's World game was awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bringing it back to video games, which the show is about.
[SPEAKER_08]: With you guys live in our chat room, the always present fourth guest on our show, live.vognetwork.com in our chat room if you want to join us here.
[SPEAKER_08]: We do tape live every Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_08]: at the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com, 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern, right after the Bobby Blackwell show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So tying it back to games, Saturday Night Live games, there was a Blues Brothers game, I'm pretty sure, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: When they had that movie, when they had the Blues Brothers 2000 or whatever, there was that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were there other Saturday Night Live movies that might have been, or...
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I'm just imagining what if there was an It's Pat game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you ever see the movie, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched part of it, and I was like, the hell is this crap?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, the Wayne's World movies were great, but not a good game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com, fifth dream in our chat says, Kier cross Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Lord.
[SPEAKER_08]: Padov song, Why Can't I Be Mew.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Love Meowths.
[SPEAKER_02]: uh Mr. My My's where the hell did you get this from only the is that was that on tumblr or some shit you need to post that somewhere where I can find it on tumblr and repost that because that sounds like the type of thing that came off tumblr I'm sorry but fifth dream said it best though later on um I wanted John Belushi samurai game
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Samurai Taylor.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was it, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there was also the Samurai Butcher and the Deli.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's always him in different things, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but I also liked the one of Dana Carvey as... God, no, who was it he was being... Brian Adams, was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: From old school SNL people to video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Real quick before we get into our gaming week, so I'll make this quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a big show last week, so this week might be a little easier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Taking it easy.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had an Austin Powers game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's sort of... Oh, they did!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's sort of Saturday Night Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for looking that up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted to throw this out there real quick technically this was the other show that I do under the OLR Studios banner which is Horde House but I just wanted to give this a shout out because I thought this was great this morning was that multiple sclerosis walk and I've talked about it on this show a couple times that finally happened this morning and great turnout and great participation from some folks here locally and the internet and the WoW community and the gaming community in general raised over $1,600 if you can believe it for multiple sclerosis research
[SPEAKER_08]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now the goal next year is to outdo that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to push 2K next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: So watch yourselves.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll do it next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now I'm thinking, you know, I had so much fun doing that that we need to think of something OLR charity related like six months from now.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's like, you know, Horde House, OLR, Horde House.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we're going to have to think of something to get involved with.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to do one of the autism charities that is not Autism Speaks because they're assholes.
[SPEAKER_08]: controversy but whatever we'll find a charity that's near and dear to our causes we need to have a car wash
[SPEAKER_02]: The OLR Car Wash The OLR Car Wash
[SPEAKER_08]: I like meeting OLR fans, and sometimes I meet them in very random places.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that the Evan that just friended me on Facebook yesterday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did he have a Liara pic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no, he has an MS pic now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, he had a Liara pic, and now it's a... I don't know, but whoever that is, you're nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, he's nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you're very nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: I met him.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should have come out today.
[SPEAKER_08]: You could have met him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now he's going to have to come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was busy sleeping.
[SPEAKER_02]: Honestly, my goal was to get up this morning, but I think I still have, like, how much booze did I drink on my birthday?
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: All of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, thank you for the beer, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was delicious.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_08]: How was your birthday?
[SPEAKER_08]: Happy late birthday to DarkSakura, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: My birthday was gamey.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in, you did not sing any Atlantis at my party, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, we only made a cameo and I didn't get around to singing Alanis, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Becky sang Alone for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I ended up singing in the background, I think, because I was drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played keyboards for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You played keyboards.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I downloaded the song just so that Becky would sing it, our resident, very good soprano.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think I sang Band on the Run once.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, this was the funniest part.
[SPEAKER_02]: This happened after you left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Julian, Becky's son, who's going to be six in like a week or so, he wanted me to sing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that Dan's little cousin?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan's cousin's daughter.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was Hannah's daughter, Sophia.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were cute, being cute kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were adorable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Julian was like, sing the Pink Robot song!
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is Yoshimi Battles the Pink Robots.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, about a third through the song, Julian has the chorus memorized.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's singing along to the song with me, and it's like my second favorite song ever in the universe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're sitting here swaying back and forth, and I've got a good three beers and a shot of vodka in me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we won't be able to get an encore now?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: and Julian is singing along with me and it is seriously the cutest thing that has ever happened in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Midna decided to come out and be Little Miss Social, which I thought she was going to go hide in the back room, but no, she's like, oh my god, people pet me.
[SPEAKER_02]: She hates Gary.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Amanda?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, she said she couldn't do it this night.
[SPEAKER_02]: She had to do it later tonight because she has something Depeche Mode-y going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know she does a lot of blogging for Depeche Mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's going to like seven of their shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, she went to like a series of 12 shows in Germany last year.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: It's tequila that I don't hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: It still kicked my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: I almost got you Patron.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to tell you this for future reference.
[SPEAKER_02]: No tequila.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I thought you liked Patron.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like Patron OK, but do you know how long it took me to drink the last bottle you got me?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finished it for my birthday last year and you got it for me when I turned 30.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then I must have had a psychic moment because I was going to get it and then I was like, you know what, maybe I should just bring beer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob brought me Guinness and Guinness is the best gift ever and I'm going to cook steak with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, apparently the theme of my birthday was booze, which is pretty much the theme of every birthday every year, if I'm not at Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they busted out, George brought his Wii U, and that Injustice game, whatever that DC game is, you know how I feel about DC.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was actually kind of neat, except I thought that the character models were supremely bizarre.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard a lot of good things about Injustice, but not on the Wii U. It's interesting to me that that was the platform you got exposed to it on, because I've heard the Wii U one is a little weak compared to the others.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I had no basis of comparison, and I'm sitting here like... And I'm just copy-pasting internet hearsay, so... I'm catching the end of the game when, like, three of my friends are passed out from booze.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm sitting there sobering, because you know how quickly that happens for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm like...
[SPEAKER_02]: watching this game and going what the hell is up with Wonder Woman's hair that's the only thing I could focus on was Wonder Woman's hair and that there were two Batmans when I was playing Mortal Kombat vs. DC Universe I was a little fixated on how weird Wonder Woman was too and then like Joker looked bizarre but it was the right Batman it was Kevin Conroy oh nice
[SPEAKER_02]: The Cure and Depeche Mode in one podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like goth lounge radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: No way.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're progressive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to attack the darkness.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw in our chat saying Injustice is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I beat the story mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you see, Gary was playing it, but I didn't care because I was watching it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so...
[SPEAKER_02]: The big thing I remember is Amanda waking up in time to go, that's where Depeche Mode is in this game, and going back to sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now I remember that the end song was done by Depeche Mode, and it was actually a really neat song.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I mean, it was mostly a lot of us hanging out in the kitchen, in the dining room, staring at the evil bell pepper pizza that, oh my god, it was so gross.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had to pick all the bell peppers off because I'm allergic.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then just drinking and then children running all over the place.
[SPEAKER_02]: But cute children who don't piss me off, so it was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my birthday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was going to ask about your gaming week, but you did a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, then why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll just do our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Catastrophic Moggy gave me that Sam & Max game on Steam and Resonance.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one other game, I forgot what it was, but I downloaded everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I played some of the game I'm not supposed to talk about, Trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, I'm in love, I'm quitting well So, um, I, uh, what else did I play?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I live streamed Mass Effect 2 And so what I'm gonna do since we don't have anybody on Thursday We don't have any shows on Thursday Is that I'm just gonna play through Mass Effect 2 on the stream So that people can hear me talk shit about the characters Which is, basically, well Shane was there for that
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically all I do now when I play any of the Mass Effect games is that I talk back to the characters and I'm pretty rude to most of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's sort of like, what is my Shepard's Inner Monologue?
[SPEAKER_08]: So if people want to see a playthrough where they're not talking back, don't look at your channel because you're a talker.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, it's like, I'll play it mostly quiet, but sometimes somebody will say something, and it's like, because you know how I feel about a good portion of the writing, and I will just go, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or go, no one cares what you have to say, Jacob, you know, and move on, and it's that type of commentary.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sort of MST3K-ing it as I play.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the DarkSakura experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've had pink berry and coffee, and I'm very hyper, so excuse me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Couldn't tell.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Say hello as well to Loki, and how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week, I played Defiance.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played lots of Defiance, actually, and I'm up to 340 now.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, I don't really have levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like power levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should maybe get this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they don't have, like I said, levels.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like your power level, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon Ball Z-ish.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because you can do stuff... I mean, you do level up and your power goes up by so much, but you can do other things that raise your power level as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have side stuff, like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Very much like Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the whole game is very similar to Borderlands as far as, you know, the whole style of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so you can do, like, these time-challenged, you know, okay, this is a rampage and you have to kill, you know, this many people in this amount of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it's kind of its own instance thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then there's also, like, races and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which sucks because when I first attempted some of these races, I was actually doing pretty well on them, but there was some sort of lag in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd finish the race in the correct amount of time, but it would add two seconds to the clock every time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wasn't like I was missing a pylon or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would just...
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, it was weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully I did manage to hit silver on those, which is what you have to do to get your extra experience and levels and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other thing I don't really like about it, because I have some guns that I find that are really fun to use and stuff, but once you've maxed out the level on those guns, you stop gaining experience on that weapon class.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I have to switch to a different saw now to...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's, I don't know, it's alright but I wish they had a little bit more variety to it maybe that will come out later on I did notice though, one of the things that they are doing is they have, I think I mentioned it last week they have specific challenges for the entire season and then specific challenges for each episode so as the episodes play on TV you get different stuff that I guess ties in with the episodes on TV like they have certain challenges that you have to do and stuff so I thought that was kind of cool
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Diablo You're a loner
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's not that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would be fine joining clans and talking with them and stuff, but my wife reads or plays on the computer, and she hates it when I talk over the headset while I'm playing games because I have my noise-canceling headphones on, and so I tend to be loud because I think I'm talking on normal volume, but I can't hear myself because I have a headset on or headphones on.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, it's been pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've been playing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I played a little bit of more Modern Warfare 3 just because I've been having trouble finding... Well, I wanted to play Defiance during work, like on lunch, but our internet sucks where we're located right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of the wireless hubs is over there that is not working, so I can't get internet on my Xbox 360 over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: so I've been doing kind of like the survival modes in Modern Warfare 3 and that's been kind of fun and you know multiplayer deathmatch when we can get enough people over there and really I think that was it this week it's been pretty much just Defiance just playing that
[SPEAKER_08]: Those MMO type of games will, you know, take up a bit of time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm having fun, even though it is very bland looking.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, it's not a whole lot of variety to it, but it's entertaining enough to keep me interested in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, my gaming week, not a whole lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I revisited a few old things.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played World of Warcraft, of course, because I do that a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Still doing PvP and having fun with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did cancel Final Fantasy XI which I talked a little more about on Horde House but Shane was very upset but he's coping and I'm waiting for Civ V to go on sale so he can do his half of the bargain that'll be fun other old games I revisited random, super random, started playing Dota 2 because I hadn't really ever played it I've had the game viewer for a while but hadn't played it myself and the nice thing is in Dota 2 you can set up a bot game because I'm too afraid to play with real people because I have no idea what I'm doing and playing with the bots just reinforced that
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: There's one that's not very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Guardians of Middle-Earth.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not really a genre I play.
[SPEAKER_08]: Otherwise, I played some more of Harmonite this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is another new game I played this week, but you'll have to wait for my review at vognitwork.com on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look for that on the site on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's really about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since there's the Tuesday game and then WOW took up most of my time, honestly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was busy with out-of-town guests and so forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you at all interested in the Star Trek game coming out next week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I would like to actually check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Star Trek game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's based in the movie universe, it kind of bridges the first two games together Yeah, I've read some stuff about it, I'm interested in it Some of the Star Trek games for home have been pretty bad though It's supposed to have been in development for at least three years Well, it was supposed to come out with the first movie, and it didn't So they held it back to make it better or whatever, so let's hope it worked Some of the Star Trek games have been real stinkers But I remember the Next Generation game on Super Nintendo was awesome
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I actually did like Star Trek Online until they went free-to-play and ruined the skill system.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to see, you know, a game that plays like that but on a single player, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com Sile, I can never say that name.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so sorry, guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sile says, I can't MOBA to save my ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Queen Simia says, now I don't really get Dota 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: How did they work that out legally?
[SPEAKER_08]: Team Fortress Quake Mod
[SPEAKER_08]: so they hired them to make Dota 2 obviously Blizzard was not a fan of that but they worked at they settled as these legal things usually go Blizzard is going to call their game Blizzard All-Stars now is is their MOBA game and League of Legends was never called anything in the same category but I believe someone else involved with the original Dota mod is with the League of Legends team and Riot Games but I mean Riot Games is doing very well with League of Legends so you know
[SPEAKER_08]: There's plenty of room at the table for all of them, apparently PrinceBrightStar in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says If you want a free-to-play that isn't pay-to-win, PSO2 is a great game I'm dying to play PSO2, but you must be playing the Japanese version, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because it's not out here yet, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't think they're remotely doing betas yet I signed up for the beta ages ago, but I don't think that we're even close to US beta
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I am thinking that's an E3 thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm thinking Sega's sitting on it until E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's literally nothing on the table for them coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I tell you what, there's nothing on the table for them coming out right now except for a couple of PC titles in June.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have no announcements so far.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing pending.
[SPEAKER_08]: uh i speaking of sega i did overlook an ios game i played a little bit this week sonic dash it's free on ios it is temple run sonic that is all it is with if you want your temple run with sonic rings there you go i actually find it to be i mean the pros of sonic dash is that oh sonic
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty, bright, vibrant compared to Temple Run, which is a little bit drab.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I love Temple Run and Temple Run 2, but it's kind of a drab palette in those games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sonic is very bright, vibrant.
[SPEAKER_08]: Characters you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: The ring sound is always refreshing to use that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then I do find it as a game and so forth to be underpolished compared to Temple Run.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Pitfall was really well done for a Temple Run ripoff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very interesting to see all these established franchises kind of ripping on what's going on now that's popular.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really fascinating to me how that kind of comes full circle.
[SPEAKER_02]: You actually indirectly reminded me of another game that I started.
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy Dimensions for iOS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I only just started it, but it's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very old school.
[SPEAKER_08]: The control's interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: The good news about that one is that it's free.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you like that one, that's very similar to what... I'll get five.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, what five looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But five is... But I don't want to pay 17 bucks for it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't mention it in my week because I haven't gotten it yet, but my Ouya has shipped, apparently, via DHL.
[SPEAKER_06]: So... I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a chance that I may get it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should get it next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll get it eventually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe in time for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, anyhow, that's it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've said enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, just quick housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have any off shows coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe gone Memorial Day weekend, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might be out of town.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's not until the end of May, so we'll keep you posted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you go to Disneyland, take me.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not going to.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a pass anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: So?
[SPEAKER_08]: If I go to Disneyland, the next time I will probably go is in E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still have to figure all that out, which, you know, I've been a bad boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should do Discon.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's two parts to registration.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've done the first part, but not the second part, because I need to get off my ass and do it, but I keep getting distracted with all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But regardless of whether I go to E3 or not, Bobby's going to represent VOG, and...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so Facebook Facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR Please follow us in our fan communities And next week on the show If all goes according to plan Which I don't see why it won't Two long time friends of mine Who I've been trying to get on the show for years Are finally going to be here next week And I'm really excited about it And one of them hosts another podcast That you all ought to be listening to And I'll tell you more about that next week We should all do lunch
[SPEAKER_08]: We will try to work it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twerk it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let us get into the gaming news this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a lot of news out of Nintendo this week, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had their special Nintendo Direct thing that was all 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mostly 3DS, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_06]: 3DS-centric, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of the big announcements there is, hey, we're doing a new 3DS game for the Legend of Zelda series on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a sequel to Link of the Past.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, we just took the best game we made and we made a sequel.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was very, very happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm most happy it's not another freaking remake.
[SPEAKER_08]: That they're doing something different with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I really would urge you guys, if you are a 3DS owner, check out the trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because the trailer, YouTube doesn't do it justice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like seeing it on 3DS is pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even better than the trailer, they actually have some leaked gameplay of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's like, I think at least like five minutes of gameplay and it looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: but it takes place in the same world as Link to the Past in fact actually they had there's some people on NeoGAF I think that actually took some of the screenshots from the video and lined it up with like some of the stuff that's in game and yes it does there are a few minor changes but yes it's the map is pretty much the same or at least it appears that's gonna be what happened
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then a whole lot of other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So first off, you've got Pikmin 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were wondering when the hell this was supposed to come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was supposed to be a near launch window title for the...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still not sure if it's launch window because it is now August 4th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Game & Warrior now coming out June 23rd.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's going to be a brand new system update for the Wii U, I guess, pretty soon this coming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's supposed to add some stuff that they were teasing about before on some of the other Nintendo Directs.
[SPEAKER_06]: one of those being the ability to install updates while playing other games so you're going to be able to install software and updates and that kind of stuff it's also improved load times from starting new apps up to switching between stuff and returning back to the Wii U menu also if you hold the B button when you start the system up it'll go into Wii mode in case you want to play a Wii game you don't have to take all those extra steps I guess so you can play with your Wii easier
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, and you'll be able to transfer data between USB drives and some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, to kind of coincide with the whole Legend of Zelda announcement, they're going to be putting up Legend of Zelda Oracle of Ages and Oracle of Seasons on the 3DS eShop.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's May 30th.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wii U Virtual Console is coming out next week as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're going to be...
[SPEAKER_06]: Which game are they launching with here?
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't say what the brand new game is, but basically the launch lineup, Excitebike, Super Mario World, Mario Bros., Punch-Out, Super Metroid, Balloon Fight, F-Zero, and GBA games and Nintendo 64 games planned later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: New Yoshi Island game coming to the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not sure if that's going to tie in with that new Yoshi Yarn type game that they have coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they showed a little bit of footage of it and it looks just like Yoshi Island.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario and Donkey Kong Minis on the move coming to the eShop on May 9th.
[SPEAKER_06]: New Super Luigi U DLC coming to New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: U later in the summer.
[SPEAKER_06]: New Mario Party is supposed to be coming out this fall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario and Luigi Dream Team coming out in Europe July 12th and North America August 11th.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm changing between, you know, the different softwares.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because it's super slow right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's not that great right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some other little features you might not have known about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that's the one everybody's waiting for, but also you're going to be able to transfer data between the USB drives, and you can install background downloaded software while playing other games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't realize you couldn't do that now.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought you could do, like, remember, because remember the system updates, you can kind of install those while you're playing...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, regardless, that whole thing is going to get better, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Wii U will continue to download and install software while the system is powered down, which you don't have to go set yourself on that screen and wait for it to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, these are all things that seem very logical in this day and age, so thankfully they're catching up there.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can also, this is pretty cool, hold the B button at the startup to go right into the Wii mode.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you just got Pandora's Tower or something and you're playing it on your Wii U, it's a great way for you to just bypass all the crap and go right into the Wii if you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's stupid that you just put in a Wii game into your system and have it just boot up.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it has to go into the Wii shell.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's so dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I think the way the console's built is that you have a Wii in there to do all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's still really dumb.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird, but if they're using different graphics processors and all that, then I get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's weird, but it might just not be technically possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Loki touched on this a little bit, talking about some of those virtual console releases, but just to confirm...
[SPEAKER_08]: Virtual Console happens on Wii U next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Launch lineup, Excitebike, Mario World, Mario Brothers, Punch-Out, Super Metroid, Balloon Fight, and F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of those games have already come out through the 30 Cent program.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know F-Zero is one of those, Balloon Fight, Punch-Out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some of these haven't happened yet, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Super Mario World isn't one of them, and I don't think it's in the lineup.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think... Is the next game Super Metroid?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, the next game is like a Yoshi game, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say Super Mario World.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like 30 cents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But GBA games are part of this, which is cool because that wasn't on Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: You didn't have GBA games on Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had them on DS, 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But not we.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think you only got advanced games through the Ambassador Program.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have they done advanced games?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they have.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this could be interesting, what'll happen there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't know why they wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo 64 games coming out in the future as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which were on the Wii, so, you know, for most people it'll be an upgrade, I suppose And then, DarkSakura, I think you have a Whopper bin of news for us too, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I do, if Bobby will stop spoiling Seriously, stop telling about the future You know what happens, you watch Doctor Who, don't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway
[SPEAKER_02]: Earthbound is going to be coming out in North America and Europe as in Mother 2, as it was in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will be on the Wii U Virtual Console towards the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I don't see that there is an actual release date on it yet, but I'm expecting them to have a date out before E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, unless they're saving that date for E3 or whatever the hell they're doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll probably be a bullet point, E3, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that could be one of those things where it's like, oh yeah, remember how we said EarthBound was coming out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Go get it, it's up now, right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, why don't we get Mother 3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know the fan translators offered to give it to Nintendo for free, but legally I don't think that can happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why if they agree to it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see what... I think it's just weird territory because they had to do things that Nintendo doesn't endorse per the terms of license in order to mod the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like dumping a cartridge to your computer is not something you're supposed to do to begin with.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not in your user agreement that is that fine print in the manual.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I think if Nintendo were to legally acknowledge that, it puts them in a really weird place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but people do a lot of stuff they're not supposed to do all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that they would find a way around it if they wanted to find a way around it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's their property.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can give the permission.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, leaving it there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm excited even though I already have it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I'm excited about Earthbound 2 just because it's a much, you know, for those of us that don't have a cartridge lying around, which I don't anymore, now I'm kicking myself for selling this shit years ago, but it's a nice way to pick it up again.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the Wii U Virtual Console is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_08]: They pulled it off very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: The sound sounds great out of the four speakers between your TV and the gamepad.
[SPEAKER_02]: I need to come over and actually just sit and play the Wii U for a while.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we're probably holding out for the PS4 ourselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: So far, that's where we're landing at home.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, so we're curious.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a lot of Nintendo news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm curious in here in the room, what were you guys most jazzed about from the Nintendo Direct?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, first off, I should take a big step back because, Loki, you're the biggest critic of Nintendo on this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you moved at all by this Nintendo Direct?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or are you like, meh?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm the biggest critic of everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: None of the news... I mean, once again, I'm not going to go buy a system.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not going to go get a 3DS again just for Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's cool that they're doing that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the other announcements I couldn't really care about.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, like Yoshi's Island.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do a sequel, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just... I mean, at the same time, I like that they're doing sequels to their old titles, but I kind of wish there was something new.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, just something new from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because a lot of it seems to be going back to, like, rehashes of old things.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know everybody loves nostalgia, but I just want something new.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like a brand new property from Nintendo that doesn't resemble Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't resemble Nintendo Land.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not a...
[SPEAKER_06]: 2D Mario remake or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario Galaxy was a good example of something.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's sort of like Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it was so different.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Mario, but it's really not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I want something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even if they put Mario or Link's face on it, you're okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just want some new ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I just want something new.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, because a lot of...
[SPEAKER_06]: and don't don't get me wrong I think that the whole you know new Zelda game is pretty awesome but I mean I guess it is a little bit different it's a different approach to it in the same world and stuff and it's all 3D now but
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just kind of want something new from them, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something innovative.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ross Steel UT in our chatroom says, I wasn't really jazzed about anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 3DS is doing fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need Wii U news and not fucking Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think there's a reason this is happening now and not at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because a lot of people are saying, shouldn't they have announced the link to the past sequel at E3?
[SPEAKER_08]: That seems very weird that they would just on a random day of the week for no reason announce a Zelda sequel.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's a pretty big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hoping that means they are clearing space.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's what they did last time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, they had three Nintendo Directs and their stupid press conference.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, also keep in mind, Nintendo can only really speak to a lot of Nintendo stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't always get into third-party stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do, obviously.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do sometimes, but sometimes a lot more third-party information comes out at E3, which, considering the Wii U could really use a boost from third parties, that would be a great thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think maybe Bayonetta 2, this E3, do you think they've been able to push it out this fast, or maybe not?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't think so?
[SPEAKER_01]: It needs to be on stuff other than the Wii U.
[SPEAKER_06]: It won't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, but it needs to be.
[SPEAKER_06]: Never say never.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, never say never.
[SPEAKER_06]: And here's why.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's why.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because... Don't stop believing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tecmo Koei developed Ninja Gaiden 3 Razor's Edge for the Wii U. It was published by Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Came out in other systems later on, published by Tecmo Koei.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could easily, if it flops, and I'm sure...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd hope that they have something in there that says, okay, this game flops so we can put it on other systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it'll come out later.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's going to be like a time delay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like they're going to have a window or something and then it'll come out later on.
[SPEAKER_02]: All five of you who bought a Wii U, here.
[SPEAKER_02]: A month later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, everybody else.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of think they're going to price drop at E3.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's just the inevitable thing that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they might sneak out the Wii backwards compatibility if my hunch is correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think a price drop is going to help.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it'll help, but it's not going to be enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: because the excuses right now, I think there's nothing I can say on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All they have to do is exactly what they did with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they do exactly what they did with the 3DS at this E3, if Reggie comes out on stage and says, you want some fucking games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's some fucking games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then bam, bam, bam.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to fix everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's easy to sit here now and say no, but when he comes out and says... If he goes F-Zero is fucking happening on the Wii U, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo is saved.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hurrah.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they're going to have time because, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they pulled Mario Kart 7 out of thin air.
[SPEAKER_08]: They pulled the, what was the other game that came out?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's just say it was being worked on behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could still be working on stuff that we don't know about.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's such things as NDAs and people who don't break them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just think, though, that, but right now we know that there's no EA, for example, there's no EA Sports titles for the Wii U at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: No Madden, no FIFA, nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so far, no NBA 2K either.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, I understand if you're thinking about purchasing a new system.
[SPEAKER_06]: And let's say a lot of mainstream people that buy games do play Madden or do play a sports title.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, not everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a lot of people do.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's kind of disappointing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It kind of makes you think, do I really want to get a Wii U or do I want to pick up another system that's going to actually have the games I want on it?
[SPEAKER_06]: and it's also a photo of lack of confidence from these publishers and EA being a big publisher, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Activision's supporting them with garbage right now but they're supporting the Wii U. They have their Walking Dead game which is absolute shit and then followed by the...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Fast and the Furious Showdown, which I'm sure is going to be awesome and not total shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty will be coming out, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some comments in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Strudels89 says, Rob's such the optimist.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just don't think they're going to roll over and let all their critics get the best of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't do it with the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, I'm just...
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand that, but what is... Let me say this too, because this is an important follow-up comment.
[SPEAKER_08]: Flaco Jones says, another third place finish like the GameCube, but they'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I could see that happening, that maybe the Wii U is not going to shatter whatever this next Xbox, although if some of these rumors about the next Xbox come to play, I don't know if Nintendo would necessarily be third.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Sony's looking pretty good right now out of them all.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, even if they did finish third, and another comment, WhatUpG says Nintendo will be fine because their handheld is doing well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it does put Nintendo in an interesting position where if they do decide to just, you know, okay, Wii U went all Virtual Boy, we're going to write it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: They might be in an interesting position where they could do another console and
[SPEAKER_08]: After whatever Microsoft and Sony does, it's going to put them in a very interesting position if they fix their mistakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: The history has shown they are not going to fix their mistakes.
[SPEAKER_06]: How long has it taken them to understand how to do online?
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that's been around for a decade now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to disagree with you there.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they can't get online right, they're doomed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still think that no matter what, Nintendo's going to be fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're making plenty of money with their handhelds.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, basically, they could just put out a console for shits and say, hey, look, we have a console.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called the LOL U. LOL at you for buying it.
[SPEAKER_02]: LOL at you for buying it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: but either way I mean it's and I've seen people draw comparisons between them and Sega with the Dreamcast which I actually think that that's completely not even close to the same part because what Sega was dealing with they were coming off the fallout of the Saturn and the very very awful marketing in the US they also didn't have oodles of money in the bank like Nintendo does exactly
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't forget all that Wii money.
[SPEAKER_08]: They made a lot of money on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Wii turned a nice little profit because it wasn't the most powerful piece of hardware in the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: That money's in the bank.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll admit, I was standing in line for my Wii at Target, but we also bribed our way into the line with Donuts and Coffee, me and Kristen.
[SPEAKER_02]: But at the same time, it's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo is coming off a series of successes of near failures that they've turned around they don't have that problem with the marketing that Sega came out of I don't really see where the comparison really is except that okay so yeah white systems don't really do very well in the US but look at the Wii I don't know what that was because in Japan it was the Saturn was a silver box and over here it was a black box and it's just marketing is weird stuff
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, before we move on to our next story, since this Nintendo Direct was one of the biggest news stories in gaming this week, we do want to take this opportunity to use our new feature on the website and go to a live listener poll.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to the live listener poll at VOGnetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you are at live.vognetwork.com right now, you can participate in our live poll.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you most excited about from this Nintendo Direct?
[SPEAKER_08]: Here are the answers.
[SPEAKER_08]: OMG Earthbound, OMG Zelda Link to the Past sequel, OMG Yoshi's Island,
[SPEAKER_02]: OMG Super Luigi U or meh Nintendo vote now live.vognetwork.com if you want to participate in the poll live.vognetwork.com you'll see it right underneath the chat box I agree with Bob Coffee Sega, he said Sega was dealing with ship management and no Sega Tatsunoshiro we would have been okay I don't know if anyone other than like three of us knows about Sega Tatsunoshiro was the mascot of the Saturn in Japan
[SPEAKER_02]: This guy with floofy hair wearing a gi going around punching the hell out of everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they did a commercial for him for the Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was even a Segata Sanshiro game that came out on Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we had Segata Sanshiro, still, the Dreamcast would have lived.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting watching the live results of our poll coming in right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mad Nintendo is winning with half the vote right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch this as it develops.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live.vognetwork.com You do have to be registered at VOG Network in order to be able to vote in the poll because, you know, there might be some little incentives on the site tied to participating.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you should check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, why don't we move on with more news besides just what's going on with Nintendo, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, so there was a series that was on TV that I was really hopeful for and then the writer's strike happened and the writing went downhill.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was Heroes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the rumor is that Microsoft wants to bring back Heroes, reboot the whole series.
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously with new people because a lot of the cast has moved on to other things.
[SPEAKER_06]: They kind of did this with heroes on the web.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had their webisodes or something like that with some different hero characters that the fans designed, which were crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it'd be kind of cool to see a new series kick off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hopefully it just didn't fall into what I like to call the Matrix problem, where you give...
[SPEAKER_06]: A character like Neo, way too much power, too fast, and you're like, fuck, how do I deal with this the next movie or next season?
[SPEAKER_06]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just need to ramp it up slowly.
[SPEAKER_06]: But apparently they're saying that this is going to be part of the whole TV focus and might be some of their original Xbox programming.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I can see this happening, especially since you have Netflix and Amazon doing reboots and brand new exclusive series for those content streamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it makes sense that they could do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: This certainly leads to the other interesting discussion that goes with this of what other series could be revived?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm sure a lot of us go, Firefly?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we have Firefly?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we have more Firefly?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know that's not going to happen because then Joss is just going to kill everybody else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and Fox would never...
[SPEAKER_08]: So Fox will just not let it happen just to spite.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I think I saw that horse twitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to kick it in its face again.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we'll get into this a little more with our Fugo question of the week later on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's very interesting with all these content delivery services coming up with their own programming.
[SPEAKER_08]: You see Netflix doing it too with Arrested Development.
[SPEAKER_08]: They brought Back from the Dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got Whose Line coming back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but that's a CW show, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but still, I'm saying, you know, there are these series of revivals going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Technically, Whose Line is a game show, so it follows, I mean, I know it's kind of not, but I think it actually follows the rules of a game show when it comes to TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's a weird, you know, game shows come and go all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am very disappointed that they didn't try to go all meta with, you know, Whose Line and have Bob Barker host it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would have been hilarious.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, did she just have him guest host one episode?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Aisha Tyler's a great choice.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she's one of us.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's a total gamer, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: And she's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's really funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm looking forward to seeing...
[SPEAKER_02]: As long as I get my Greg Proops on there from time to time, I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Drew Carey was a great host, but he's got another gig.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which is weird, because Aisha Tyler does that talk show.
[SPEAKER_08]: They tape a whole three months worth of shows in a day.
[SPEAKER_08]: They figure it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: What else do I want to say with this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we talk about what kind of potential extra cost could be?
[SPEAKER_08]: If they're going to save a show like Heroes, that's not going to come for free, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Would that be Xbox Gold?
[SPEAKER_08]: Would maybe I get that as an Xbox Gold member?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or maybe this is part of a new Xbox Platinum or something?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or what happens?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they'll charge any...
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xbox Platinum was that crappy little card that did nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's say they ignored it like I did and did it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think that they would do that per se.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that they could do more advertising, but who's to say that they're not going to be fucking greedy and still want more money on top of it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Although, it's going to be a hard sell if, like, say, the PlayStation 4 still has the same type of scheme where it's, you know, regular PlayStation, you get online multiplayer, and plus you get, you know, extra stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, I gotta be honest, I mean, I do a lot of gaming on the 360, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: I am jealous of the deal that you get with PlayStation Plus.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's pretty nice with that instant game collection stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: But unfortunately, a lot of my friends are on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, before we get into the next story, I want to go to the results of the live poll that we took earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you most excited about from this Nintendo Direct?
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to say, I'm a little surprised with these answers, but this is why we do this, because sometimes we learn things.
[SPEAKER_08]: The winner of the poll, Meh Nintendo, 50% of the vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: 50% don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was kind of looking in the chat room, and just so you know, among the non-Meh crowd, 25% of the vote for the Zelda Link to the Past sequel, 18.75% for Earthbound, and 6.25% for Super Luigi U.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that 6% Ranma?
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could look at the results, but I'm not going to look at who voted for what.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was looking at chat to try to figure out why people are voting the way they are, and it seems like a lot of people are just like, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't been convinced that I need to pick up these Nintendo consoles, so this news doesn't really get me excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand that they have certain strategy with announcing titles because they don't know development cycles and how far... They don't want to announce a title...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, you can wait until E3 and do it and make a little bit of a splash and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I would think it would be in your best interest to help your console now instead of later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the more time you wait, the worse it's going to get for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because say you have someone that's waiting for a Wii U. I really want a good title to come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then it's just like nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't hear about anything for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just going to get an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_06]: Money's already spent.
[SPEAKER_06]: And oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: They announced a good title already.
[SPEAKER_08]: What also surprised me about some of the reaction I'm seeing in the chat room as to why people voted that way is that a big reason why they do these Nintendo Directs is to get out there on the internet why you should own a 3DS because you don't already.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a Zelda Link to the Past sequel didn't sell that for people yet?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, granted, to be fair, I totally know that people are like, I'm not going to buy a freaking system based off a two-minute trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Show me the game, and then we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can respect that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The 3DS, I don't think it has any problems whatsoever saying reasons you need to buy a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that there's plenty of games out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got a lot of really good games, and I think there's plenty of reasons to own it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm talking about the Wii U. That isn't there.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this Nintendo Direct wasn't about Wii U. I don't care if it's about the Wii U. The Wii U is hurting and they haven't had a Nintendo Direct about the Wii U. Except for the stupid what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, 30 years of Luigi.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's announce all these Luigi things.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the biggest thing they had to announce was DLC for a game that they already put out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, you need...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but I put this Super Luigi U DLC next to some of the DLC that other companies put out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's say the Saints Row DLC, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, yes, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But let's put it this way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Has it sold any systems?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did we see a big jump in numbers after they made that announcement?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, because DLC will keep it afloat and keep people having their Wii U's plugged in, but it's not going to move the system.
[SPEAKER_06]: All that's going to happen is when it gets dropped in price, they'll bundle it with New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: U Game of the Year Edition or some garbage like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll have the new Luigi U DLC bundled in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll see E3, hopefully a game changer.
[SPEAKER_08]: If not, going to be very interesting next year for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Falco just made a good point.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the best thing about your next-gen system is the release of a nearly 20-year-old game, your next-gen console sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's relying on...
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo needs to get more people excited about the Wii U, they need to pull the curtain back a little bit on what they're working on, and E3 is the deadline for that to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: But is it just me, or is there a lot of developers now just sort of banking in on that nostalgia?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: We run up to the trough and hit the feeder bar.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much did we all squee about Earthbound Link to the Past?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, apparently not the listenership.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I know I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: To be honest, I'm not super excited either.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, I mean, I really don't play... I don't have a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't get one because it gives me a headache.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really hard for me to put this into words.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want to see something new and exciting and that's why my attention has been on the indie developers because they're doing the new and exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ross Steel UT in the chat room saying why isn't the Link to the Past sequel on the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd help if they didn't ass it up with gimmicks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not this game that gets people really excited on the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_08]: My assumption is because we're going to get a Zelda trailer this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: You won't get the new Zelda this year but you're going to get that trailer that gets you just enough fan wank to get people excited.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the Wind Waker thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, the Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_08]: I meant like you know
[SPEAKER_02]: Just wake me when the wank is over.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm telling you, it makes perfect sense, and the setup is so perfect that I would be shocked if, maybe not this year, because they are a little slow to adopt, I mean, fuck, virtual consoles now just coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: How many months later?
[SPEAKER_06]: Six months later?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, so they're a little slow to adopt things, but I would be shocked that we do not see a way to play 3DS games on the Wii U. Or, let's just say that they're not going to do that, seeing some HD remakes of 3DS games coming to the Wii U. It only makes sense that they're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura brought up indie developers, and this could be a place where Nintendo could, and it seems like something could be happening there, who knows, but this would be the group you would want to get in bed with if you were a game developer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like they're in bed with Microsoft, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: So is it sexy times?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but Mojang, Marcus Pearson, of course Notch, and Jens Bergensten, they have made Time's list of the 100 most influential people in the world for 2013.
[SPEAKER_08]: For pixel blocks!
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, Time's 100 list kind of gets some, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Lady Gaga won or came in second place in an online poll of who's... So, you know, take some of this stuff with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it is nice to see gaming represented and indie gaming at that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the cool thing is is that Will Wright, you know, SimCity before it was, you know, this last one, actually wrote the introduction talking that Minecraft was, quote, a wonderful combination of accessibility and depth allowing for complex output with simple input.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, Minecraft...
[SPEAKER_08]: Minecraft was an amazing thing for gaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm glad this is getting acknowledged.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went from hater to tolerator to digging holes in the ground prairie dogger.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to make it a point this week because I've been really bad at not going to the server.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to play every single day this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I live streamed it last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to play every single day.
[SPEAKER_02]: My prairie dog house.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess apparently Time did that poll online and this is saying that Notch ranked second in the poll.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was Notch or it was Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you know, what's the difference, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lady Notch.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're essentially the same person.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so congrats to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now the question is, what's next?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know they had that, what, the Universe game was their next big project, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't remember the name of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they have Scrolls that they're doing right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, Scrolls.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got the, I don't even know what the fuck the game's called.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like 0x00.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's the one I'm thinking of, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: yeah so although that one he's claiming that he's running into kind of like a writer's block almost with it so he's working on other things right now until he figures out what to do with it gotcha all right let's move on um we're still a little ways from the classic game of the week some more news for you first
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now this is something I'm excited about, even though, yeah, it's kind of me biting myself because of the nostalgia thing, but I was super happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Castle of Illusion is getting remade for PlayStation Network, Xbox Live Arcade, and PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is being developed by Sega Studios Australia, and it will be, I guess, a 2.5D kind of game.
[SPEAKER_02]: um well it says a 2D 3D hybrid and it is basically based off of the uh Genesis slash Mega Drive game with the original director working with the developer now so um there's a trailer out for it I totally recommend everybody watch it because it looks super good but I do not see a date on it yeah I don't think they have a date for it yet yeah
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I mean, I played the shit out of this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I even, when I graduated high school, I traded my Super Nintendo for my friend's Genesis and sat playing this game for just the whole night.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I found his Master System converter and then was playing Alex Kidd and Shinobi World and that was pretty awesome too.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, Castle of Illusion is one of my top Disney games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that was a great game, so it's exciting to hear about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The pictures are absolutely gorgeous, but seriously, watch the trailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is maybe not as orgasm-inducing as DuckTales, but, you know, there's lots of wank.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll still get you going down there a little bit?
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll make one moist.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just a fun word.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moist?
[SPEAKER_08]: Moist.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to bring it up here in studio real quick just to be able to see some of this here in action.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me get to the actual gameplay part of the trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does look really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: The graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, this is more, there's not much of the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay, Maleficent!
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that Maleficent?
[SPEAKER_06]: Her face looks a little weird, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't have any gameplay in that, but they actually have some screenshots that look pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Codeman, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: This is you.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually have a friend, our friend Beanie.
[SPEAKER_02]: You say the word moist around her.
[SPEAKER_02]: She full body shudders.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't that the mom in Dead Like Me?
[SPEAKER_02]: I never watched that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dead Like Me was a great show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legocity Undercover The Chase Begins
[SPEAKER_06]: Tuesday, Dead Island Riptide coming out on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dragon's Dogma Dark Arisen, it's kind of like the game re-released with their expansion in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then Star Trek on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: And those would be your games for this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it is April and hardly anything comes out in April.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, Star Trek and Dead Island Yeah, it's a decent release It's not as dry as some of the weeks have been Next week, on the other hand Deadly Premonition And that's it Alright, let's travel over to Japan and check out what is coming out in the Japanese release dates this week We will start off with the PlayStation 3 and on the 25th of April Bioshock Infinite gets its Japanese release So now you guys over there can see what we've all been raving about for a couple weeks here
[SPEAKER_08]: Atuteki Yugi Mugen Scrolls that comes in I think there's like a limited edition a regular edition and then some like selection edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, you know what it is?
[SPEAKER_08]: The original Mugen Souls is getting a re-release price edition and there's Mugen Souls Z comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the deal there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon's Dogma from Capcom out this week on the 25th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shin Kamitachi no Yoro 11 Hitome no Suspect gets a price reduction this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also in regular and limited editions, Steins Gate, Senkei Kosuko no Phonogram comes out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tomb Raider gets its Japanese release this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We talked a little bit about the voice.
[SPEAKER_02]: With DLC Japanese voice track.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: You already get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But to give you an idea, if you want to import this baby into the US, $84 to import that guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's why it's, you know, games cost a little more in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, let's travel over.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's look at the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tomb Raider over there as well, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dragon's Dogma as well, and Bioshock Infinite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most of the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Steins Gate 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Caladrius, also in regular and limited edition this week on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Taking a look real quick at some of the handhelds.
[SPEAKER_08]: PlayStation Vita, Kajiri, Kamui, Kagura, Akebono no Hikari in regular and limited editions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Katamari Dimashino Vita gets a price reduction this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be the Katamari Dimashino game that was out of launch.
[SPEAKER_01]: The music's still stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make You Crossblood Infinity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Out on the Vita this week as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Photokano Kiss and Ragnarok Odyssey and Ridge Racer getting price reductions this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lots of price reductions on games this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shinsengoku Mosu next.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tales of Innocence R. So if you are a Japanese Vita owner, this is a great week to stock up on games you might have missed.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the Wii U this week, nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Absolutely nothing on the Wii U this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That really shouldn't be a surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: On other systems, checking out the Nintendo 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm showing that we're still sending to the feed, so I'm going to move on for the podcast.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo 3DS says Detective Conan, Marionette no Kuyo Yoko Yoko, Pocket Monster PC covers for the 3DS XL, you know, for those of you Pocket Monster fans, and Starry Sky in Spring 3D in regular and limited editions.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_02]: and Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: uh it did the feed did drop on our end just you know yeah i don't know what's going on well well we always do we always do a um you know before before well now it's showing it's connected before we ever we before we start olr every night we always reset the router reset the modems and everything in the house you know so just think if we were an always connected game console we would not be working right now keep that in mind for your future game console needs
[SPEAKER_02]: Dear Microsoft, listen to our podcast every week 6 o'clock Central Time I mean Central Pacific Time Alan, is my computer on?
[SPEAKER_08]: No?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay I just want to make sure I didn't have Dropbox running or something Yeah, Rob did mention Detective Conan I did Which is a very popular anime series from the 90s Yes, which is getting a game release in Japan that I already closed the window for
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, do we do UK release dates?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: A bunch of crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: A few more news stories for you guys and then the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so we've already talked about how the Wii U isn't selling very well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And technically we don't have the MPD numbers out for hardware because Nintendo's not going to come out bragging that, hey, we only sold like 67,000 units.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but apparently, according to a leak on NeoGAF, they have the console numbers, which is possible because I get email updates occasionally of MPD numbers.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, yes, the Wii U apparently only sold 67,000 units in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: during the five weeks from March 3rd to April 6th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then also, I guess, roughly...
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, the Vita didn't do much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_06]: They did only 33,000 units during March.
[SPEAKER_06]: Were there any Vita games during March?
[SPEAKER_08]: Quick, name me games on the Vita to get excited about right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm thinking the Persona 4 release, but that already happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm like... Tear away if you're into... Project D.Va.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tear away if you're into Media Molecule.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is Killzone, if you like Killzone.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, here's a question for you all.
[SPEAKER_08]: We sit here and we've razzed Nintendo about, you know, well, you know, they're just not getting those titles out there, but look at the frickin' Vita.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, I think, with the Vita.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, Nintendo, we recognize the potentials there that they could be doing much better.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Vita, I don't think we have much expectations for them other than, hey, it's a nice piece of hardware, but for some reason all the games that come out on it aren't very good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, dude, they had Call of Duty...
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Ops come out on the Vita that should have been System Accelerate there but no instead they just had a quick rush of a game come out by someone that did Resistance and it sucked ass it's
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully they're taking all that stuff first party now and they're going to be developing instead of having third parties develop their games for them.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Killzone hopefully will be much better but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if Tearaway is not going to save that system.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's going to save that system I think a little bit is the fact that the PlayStation Network is a really good place right now for indies.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a lot of indie games coming out in there so I think we'll see some interesting stuff from there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe what develops with the PlayStation 4 because
[SPEAKER_08]: Before I get accused of being a Nintendo fanboy and always defending them here on this show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I like to think of myself as devil's advocate against gamers hate everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think the PlayStation 4 is in a good place.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it has a lot of good buzz around it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, PlayStation 4 is going to be a real contender for the Wii U, which doesn't...
[SPEAKER_08]: you know unless they really knock our socks off at E3 you definitely are going to have PlayStation 4 on another level come out with something absolutely amazing and it could be interesting with how the Vita could tie into that I mean we've already seen a little bit of that early press conference you know so I'm I'm really curious to see how that enriches as we as time goes on here so Akuma JP mentioned a game called Obura Muramasa I guess does that have to do with the sword?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, he linked us to the game there in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's take a look.
[SPEAKER_06]: Muramasa Rebirth, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I can bring it up without destroying our feed again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Muramasa Rebirth.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the HD, well, not really HD, but like a remake of Muramasa the Demon Blade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, it's just Muramasa the Demon Blade.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that looks pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Screenshots are taking forever to load.
[SPEAKER_08]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Vita does have such a pretty screen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is a great piece of tech.
[SPEAKER_06]: They do have some good Japanese games coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got the Persona stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got Muramasa Rebirth.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's also Odin's... Well, not Odin's Sphere.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's Dragonblade.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that chick naked?
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at her.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're skinny dipping or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a perverse game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: You need to stop being so white boy about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, boobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's only here that people have a big stick up their ass, a big rough sandpapery stick up their ass about boobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe that we should have more boobs on TV.
[SPEAKER_06]: I fully support this.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, are you saying I have a stick up my ass?
[SPEAKER_02]: I like boobs too boobs are great but I mean people in general it's we're fine with violence and blood and gore and you know saw and everything I like boobs covered in blood but show a tit and everyone loses their shit hey that rhymed
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be my new motto about America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Show a tit, lose your shit.
[SPEAKER_06]: We haven't come to that part of the show yet, but we do have a story later on about the evil within, which did have a four-armed demon chick with boobs and blood on her boobs.
[SPEAKER_06]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: The violence boob quota.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blood orgy, yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Organ orgy.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like organs launched at the screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright Let's see, did you do the other sales story about Yeah, NPD I don't want to repeat what you just said again No problem The March NPD stuff, Bioshock Infinite obviously the top selling game The utter disappointment of a game, sequel Tomb Raider, only placed 2nd
[SPEAKER_06]: heads will roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, what a disappointment.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ironically, Gears of War Judgment on 360 and then God of War Ascension on PS3 were 3 and 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is going to be so wrong and I apologize in advance, but
[SPEAKER_08]: Only an Asian company like Square Enix would be like, why can you only be the second best-selling game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Am I right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Only the parent company in Asia would be like, why weren't you the number one game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why you get an A-?
[SPEAKER_06]: You came out in the beginning of the month.
[SPEAKER_06]: You should study harder.
[SPEAKER_06]: Call of Duty Black Ops 2, Luigi's Mansion, Dark Moon actually on their number 6, MLB 13 The Show on number 7, NBA 2K13 8, Walking Dead Survival Instinct just again proving that Walking Dead the franchise will actually sell anything whether it be a good game or absolute shit so that was number 9, Naruto Shippuden, Ultimate Ninja Storm 3
[SPEAKER_06]: Number 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's not on this list?
[SPEAKER_06]: The two big titles for the Wii U. Lego City Undercover and Monster Hunter 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not even the top 10.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's gotta hurt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe Laura should have been a doctor.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on to fighting game news, or maybe a little change going on or another perspective.
[SPEAKER_08]: Vice President Christian Svensson over at Capcom has made a remark about a fan-submitted question on the Ask Capcom forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: This was about stories in fighting games.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I don't know how many people really play fighting games for the story, although some of them do have good stories, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you raising your hand over there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, why, okay, if I don't play fighting games for the stories, I would have never touched any of the Tekken games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I assume the people that play the fighting games for the stories are the same people that read Playboy for their articles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anyhow, here's the interesting comment about story mode and fighting games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quote, the strategic marketing group here has for quite a while been pushing for our fighting franchises to have more and more better single player content of which full-fledged story modes are one component.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, I...
[SPEAKER_08]: but then again you know you look at a franchise like Mortal Kombat Mortal Kombat's done really well with their story modes in their recent releases especially this last one so Tiger Claw mentions that the story in Injustice is really good and is getting Capcom thinking about making better stories in their fighting games
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Injustice is just NetherRealm Studios that just did the Mortal Kombat game, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, same, same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, one other thing to mention about Capcom.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, more DLC in Capcom's future, which isn't really unexpected.
[SPEAKER_08]: But just not on disc.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is talking about Capcom's recent strategy.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a lot of very interesting revelations here in Capcom's forecast about where the company's going, saying that...
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, they don't want to outsource games to Western developers as much anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: That it has caused a drop in quality.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to promote DLC in the consumer business.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aim for growth, surpassing the market by reinforcing the online and mobile contents business.
[SPEAKER_08]: iPhone games, Android games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And strengthen earnings base by expanding the title lineup in the P&S business.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: More DLC, just hopefully not included on the disc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or just announce the Mega Man rebirth already.
[SPEAKER_08]: We all know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_08]: A Mega Man reboot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: To register participation for this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com, use the passphrase Banned.
[SPEAKER_08]: That just about brings us to the end of the first half of our show, but we have to take a trip down memory lane first off with a segment we call the Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't have reboots back in the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: You didn't reboot a gaming franchise.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, you just put out some crappy sequels and then tried to make people forgive you with the third one.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's see if that is the case with tonight's Classic Game of the Week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, DarkSakura, what is the Classic Game of the Week tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic the Hedgehog 3!
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I couldn't find anything else and I've been haunted by the Ice Cap music.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oddly enough, for some reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is what's in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, I mean, it's basically Sonic the Hedgehog.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I really liked the first one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really liked the second one.
[SPEAKER_02]: But three for me just, like, lit everything up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the last real... Actually, no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic CD was the last really good Sonic game, as far as platforming goes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually even put Sonic 3 above Sonic CD.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Bobby, the Japanese music was better.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Sonic CD, just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Sonic 3 also had some interesting things going on with it too.
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically could pick between Sonic or Tails as you could in Sonic 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it was basically the same type of gameplay you had all the same usual stuff you had your six levels with two parts you had a boss at the end of the very full thing you could keep going back to the level you have new abilities like you could hold the jump button while in mid-air and do like a quick shield for protection you tails could fly or swim underwater for a short time before getting tired and going back down and
[SPEAKER_02]: So Tails could actually go to places that Sonic could not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And his tail could actually be used to attack enemies.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you have a second player controlling Tails, then he can carry Sonic while flying.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically it opened up to all kinds of exploration.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there were the different shields in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like there was the fire shield.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my favorite was the lightning shield that attracted coins.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not coins, rings.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if you hit a checkpoint while holding 50 or more rings, you got a bonus stage, which was the bumper stage.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, I'm sorry, the bumper stage pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of any bonus stage ever in any game, for some reason it was that sort of semi-isometric point of view.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would just give me a headache and I couldn't do it at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now I make Dan do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's how you earn your Chaos Emeralds.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, like, someone even took the time to chart out how the various bonus stages were.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was also a thing you could do with Sonic & Knuckles where if you attached an older cartridge to it, like, you could play Sonic 2 with Sonic & Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if you did another one, if you hold, like, a certain button press, then you could go on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I want to talk about music for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a big thing going around with the music saying that Michael Jackson had done a lot of the music and then he removed himself from the Padres or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a series of clips on YouTube where people have compared music in Sonic 3 to Michael Jackson songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I mean, it's pretty obvious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the Ice Cap Zone sounds like Smooth Criminal.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is actually my second favorite music in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is the Lava Reef Zone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Really good music.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, so basically, you know, you can, if you got all of the Chaos Emeralds, you can turn into Supersonic and then Knuckles punches the crap out of him and takes the Chaos Emeralds and you have to go to the Death Egg.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, which I always like... Yeah, they called him Robotnik, but it really did make a lot more sense to call him Eggman because dude looked like a freaking egg.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, hey, he was in Wreck-It Ralph.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically there have been a bajillion different releases of this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had Sonic and Jam in 1997 for the Saturn, Sonic and Knuckles Collection and the Sonic and Garfield Pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic and Garfield Pack?
[SPEAKER_02]: For PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic Mega Collection for the GameCube, Sonic Mega Collection Plus for PS2, Xbox, and PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sega Genesis Collection for PS2 and PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic's Ultimate Genesis Collection for Xbox 360 and PS3 and Sonic Classic Collection for Nintendo DS plus you can get like these various packs on Steam I'll be honest the only one of those I've ever bought was Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine because hello it's P.O.P.O.
[SPEAKER_02]: there have been like I said the digital releases for Steam there's been the Wii Virtual Console one in 2007 Xbox Live Arcade in 2009 and it even has a split screen multiplayer on Xbox Live so it was given when it was released EGM gave it a 9.5 out of 10 and honestly I think it was well deserved it's one of the best games to ever come out so
[SPEAKER_08]: We will be back after a quick break with plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio Don't go anywhere guys, we'll be right back
[SPEAKER_08]: Blame me!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Get that sausage.
[SPEAKER_08]: So when they're ripping out organs of this patient, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You can even go earlier than that.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the funny Swedish guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perform a double kidney transplant.
[SPEAKER_06]: In an ambulance.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the ambulance is moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh great, the ambulance is moving.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, guts.
[SPEAKER_00]: The kidney's just floating around in the back.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh lordy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am buying this when I get home.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to wait and don't play it until you can live stream it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go, Bob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll do it tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll put that in our chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry to the podcast folks, but just look it up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's a ton of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was great about the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Surgeon Simulator 2013.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have records.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have people doing record surgery, the times, how quickly you can do surgery, and murder times.
[SPEAKER_06]: So how quickly you can kill your patient.
[SPEAKER_08]: SJ100Matt says in our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com says, Hey, I remember playing the original surgery game, Life and Death 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those games were scary shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, for me it was Trauma Center.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we got Trauma Center on Wii when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I remember...
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I was drunk on something no no no it was the Vicodin when I'm sitting here leaning back in my chair I was on Vicodin it was right after um I think I was playing it right after my surgery so I'm sitting here with my hand in a cast trying to hold the Wiimote going can't hold it and then like I ended up like using my left hand and so I was slicing people to bits it was hilarious
[SPEAKER_08]: S2100 Matt though, I was playing the original surgery game Operation by Milton Bradley.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only thing about Life and Death 1 that kind of sucked was that from what I remember at least we can only get to the first surgery which was it was removing an appendix and unfortunately they do not allow you to play tic-tac-toe using the scalpel.
[SPEAKER_06]: That will kill the patient apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quickly covering some of the other things going on in the gaming world this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we'll get to the FUGO question of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: But first, rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Supposed to be coming out June 25th.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because Deadpool's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and PC.
[SPEAKER_06]: June 25th.
[SPEAKER_06]: The OUYA has got a firmware update that's allowing people to change their credit card information.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently you can change this at any time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And also they're going to be adding some different payment options as well later on.
[SPEAKER_06]: But right now you can change your credit card information.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fantastic.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they've signed up 10,000 registered developers because technically everybody within OUYA could be a registered developer at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: and last but not least Bethesda was teasing all week long and finally released the trailer for The Evil Within which is the brand new game from Shinji Mikami known for the Resident Evil series
[SPEAKER_06]: And I gotta say, after watching the trailer, other than the fact that there is a lot of organs and stuff, it looks very Silent Hill-ish.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, good Silent Hill-ish.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was a little bit scared.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: I was a little bit scared just watching the trailer.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me bring this up here in studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like brains.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I thought there was a YouTube here.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll look it up when I get home.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like anything that's Silent Hill in a good way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I have to get Shane's review of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I trust Shane in all things remotely Silent Hill looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, don't inflate his ego like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like a two-minute trailer, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's ads on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, let's come back to this in a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we'll do.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, I will read a few stories here.
[SPEAKER_08]: The bonus games for Capcom Arcade Cabinet revealed.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you bought all the games for Capcom Arcade Cabinet, all the download stuff, you will get two free games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the bonus games were 1943 Kai.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is the laser 1943.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Volgus, which was the very first Capcom game in arcades.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, just so you know, the other pack of games came out for Capcom that rounds out this pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Sun Sun 1942 and Pirate Ship Higemaru, which I love that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Higemaru is a pretty neat game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, if you want just classic shooter, you can't get any better than 1942.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for vertical shooters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mad Dog McCree 2 The Lost Gold Move Control
[SPEAKER_08]: HD Scrubdown New Difficulty Modes and Online Leaderboards Also, a rating has shown up on a Korean rating site for Metal Gear Solid The Legacy Collection
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm gonna fast forward a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the good stuff's towards the end anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really realistic right there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go a little further.
Ooh, blood!
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I wanna play this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: I like organs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob!
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are you showing me that, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one of those games to get my mom to watch me play.
[SPEAKER_02]: We need to get your mom watching you play one of those games and we need to stream it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was thinking a great one to have my mom react to would be Bioshock Infinite, so I'll work on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should do, like, Rob's mom, the series.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Did a ROM hack that basically installs it in place of the original game chips on the motherboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there is a YouTube video going around of the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a site called This Old Game is doing the artwork for the Pauline edition.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it will be like $100 and has a marquee, monitor glass, control panel, side art, and instruction stickers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I even have Mario being held by Donkey Kong and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that's awesome, because that's like... I mean, it's even in the right style, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next up, the 3DS XL Circle Pad Pro is finally in North America.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it costs $20.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can order it on Nintendo's official online store.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is the only place that you can find it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But not too many games use it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mostly Monster Hunter 3 and Resident Evil Revelations and Metal Gear Solid 3D Snake Eater.
[SPEAKER_02]: Godmode
[SPEAKER_02]: Party Hats Party Hats Party Hats
[SPEAKER_02]: and then basically it's just lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of crazy fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it costs 10 bucks on Steam or 800 Microsoft points or 6 pounds 99 pence for our friends in the UK.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com Prince Brightstar asking a question about one of the stories you just did, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can arcades legally earn money from the Donkey Kong Pauline game?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's a good question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_08]: In all honesty, probably not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would think this is more of a novelty that shows up at trade shows and private owners, not something you put down at a miniature golf place or at a bowling alley to actually make money.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would probably get you in some hot water.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a ROM hack, so it's not necessarily that they're selling pirated stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's basically modifying your system.
[SPEAKER_08]: It also wouldn't be the first pirated game to ever show up in an arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, at Classic Gaming Expo, someone had done a Donkey Kong 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was basically just a rehack of Donkey Kong where you found unused sprites and basically redid levels.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it plays exactly Donkey Kong style, but he put up his dump and everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sounded awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: He put the ROM dump up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shut up, Rob!
[SPEAKER_02]: You're five.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just served it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Five years old, Rab.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's my dump, y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it wasn't my dump, it was his dump, and I just happened to be there for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was number two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I quit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going home.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done with y'all.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is... Three words.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for the pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I remembered that he had distributed it to some arcades.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're still red in the face.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: His little comment about what it was, number two.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't Prince Brightstar so happy that his question led to that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a serious, a really good serious question led to, yeah, poop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and we supposedly have a mature rating because we're not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get to the Fugu question of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's class it up a little bit here with some listener feedback.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good fucking luck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Facebook, and Google+.
[SPEAKER_08]: Throw them together, you get Foogle.
[SPEAKER_08]: Foogle+.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we ask a question of the week every week on Foogle.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this week has to do with the Heroes show reboot rumors.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rumor is that Heroes, a TV show that used to be on NBC, could get a second chance as a television show on the next Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you watch something like this via Xbox?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think this type of content delivery poses a threat to cable television as we know it now?
[SPEAKER_08]: What are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll start on Facebook tonight with Critical Myth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love this answer by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Setting aside the fan perception that the show quickly went downhill after the first season and thus bringing it back doesn't make a lot of sense, I don't think this alone is a threat to network or cable television.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would only be the combined success of these alternative outlets like Netflix, Hulu, DirecTV, and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: What it does say, along with some of the other outlets, is that a cancelled show may have many other options than might have been the case just a few short years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Add to that the crowdsourcing possibilities, Veronica Mars, and the initial end of a show might not be the final end after all.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, there's a show on ABC that I really like, I think it's really funny, called Happy Endings, but it's supposedly kind of done because the ratings haven't been very good, but everybody's already talking about, like, can it be on cable or something like that?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I'm going to Red the Haze.
[SPEAKER_08]: Would you support Heroes or what have you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope, I haven't paid for a live subscription in ages and I'm satisfied everywhere else with my gaming and entertainment needs.
[SPEAKER_08]: My internet connection isn't fast enough, and a large percentage of the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: has the same issue.
[SPEAKER_08]: This won't threaten cable TV, but other reliable services that are catching on, like Netflix and Hulu, are more of a threat because of the low barrier of entry with Rokus and smart TVs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rebooting a canceled TV show that nobody remembers fondly isn't a good gamble.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, somebody else jumped in there and said, hey, wait a minute, nobody remembers fondly.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, remember fondly?
[SPEAKER_02]: What was the dude's name?
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it Hiro?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I liked him and I liked his buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, he's not probably... I would say that most of the cast would not be back because you have them all doing their own things.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all in other shows now.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's on Hawaii Five-0 right now and the one chick's on Dallas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nashville.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Nashville, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, but there's always the possibility that they could do cameos or what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Heroes wasn't necessarily... The idea was the Heroes were going to get all killed off in the first season anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was supposed to always be new people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it just didn't work out that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I am with... I thought Heroes was...
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched it if there's George Takei
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because, you know, he's my gay daddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm of the mindset that then, you know, when they started introducing all these other characters in season two, it really went downhill.
[SPEAKER_08]: I stopped watching season three.
[SPEAKER_08]: I couldn't take it anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I heard the show started to get back to its roots and got a lot better season four and maybe ended a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never saw.
[SPEAKER_06]: I never.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I never gave it that second chance.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I would be down with a reboot.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you're going to ask me to pay a lot of extra money for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if it's part of a service that's something else with it, I might be open to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I tried actually watching the first season, but all I would do is just watch the Hiro and Nando scenes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I wanted to like Cheerleader Wolverine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Could not get into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But one of my friends was on that show.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is supposed to be about the listeners, so let me read the rest of the answers here.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkCharger says, if the writing and acting is good, I will watch it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I already pay for Xbox Live, as do millions of subscribers, and this just adds much needed value.
[SPEAKER_08]: There isn't a single show or channel that will usurp cable.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, I believe consumers are willing to dump on an...
[SPEAKER_08]: to stomp on an antiquated business model if an IPTV model is perceived as an equivalent or superior.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_06]: The theory was that cable providers could then offer their cable channels over the internet to other people that would be out of the area.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't have Comcast in your area, thank God, and you wanted to get Comcast channels, although...
[SPEAKER_06]: They all kind of have the same channels anyways, but that was supposed to be a way to do it, was with this box.
[SPEAKER_06]: But remember HBO's talking about doing just internet only.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that would be kind of neat, although I just don't want to pay like $8 for each channel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Burr replies and says, never cared for Heroes, but I would gladly watch a show on my Xbox if it was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if it's a threat to the whole system, but it's yet another step towards the a la carte delivery consumers have been clamoring for, much to the cable company's chagrin.
[SPEAKER_08]: Picaruno says, if it ain't one versus a hundred, dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_08]: High five, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Preach.
[SPEAKER_08]: If they say the next Xbox is bringing back 1 vs. 100, I would have to give it serious consideration on that merit alone.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they need to guarantee me it'll be up for at least a couple years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, Nikki E replied and said,
[SPEAKER_08]: I pay for Netflix to be able to watch what I want when I want if some other service has an exclusive thing I would either not care buy it on DVD later or maybe end up downloading it I think too much competition via exclusive deals and making content only for your own streaming service would just lead to more piracy just when the streaming services were beginning to compete with the convenience of the internet thanks for a great show thank you that's a good point I don't want to have to give every
[SPEAKER_08]: Content Publisher $10 a month to watch their show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that dilution is going to lead to a lose-lose situation.
[SPEAKER_08]: Piracy, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, piracy.
[SPEAKER_08]: People get what they want to see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, people do get what they want to see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Degenerate Johnny says I don't particularly think this service will pose a threat yes interactive entertainment has played a role in the steep decline of ratings within cable television through Netflix, Hulu, Amazon and other various services which is why you see cable news upholding the interest of those networks by focusing on the negative pertaining to interactive entertainment ooh interesting do you think maybe it's a whole little that's why cable news has it out for games is that it's competition that's awfully little no
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's just the same reason why certain people on cable news that have very racist comments, I just think they're very short-minded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, Andy R says, depends what kind of pricing is involved, but I would like something like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't pay for cable because I don't watch much TV, which makes it difficult on the few occasions when there is a show I want to watch, like Game of Thrones.
[SPEAKER_08]: If I can watch it in a manner where I'm not paying for a ton of services I don't want, I'm all for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mike B says cables should be trying to keep up with the times.
[SPEAKER_08]: The future is a la carte programming.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's not the first one to use that term.
[SPEAKER_08]: Commercial free shows and movies via the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I already do this now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little pricey but no commercials.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me go over to Google Plus and Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: who said,
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, that comment from Red Entertainment on Google+.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the comparison to Web TV is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: If at first you don't succeed, try again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I apologize I didn't get to all the comments, but do check out our Facebook community, facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio and Google+.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just search for Orange Lounge Radio to read all of the great comments in their entirety.
[SPEAKER_01]: In the meantime... Yeah, because there's some wink going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, the chatter's mad at you.
[SPEAKER_01]: You didn't read mine, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe because I read a lot of your other stuff, and you guys call in pretty regularly, so I wanted to read people that don't get to participate as much with the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: So just throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, but you know, I have to give... You have to fan the flames.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to fan them.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm like Karl Lagerfeld and his fan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Without being an asshole.
[SPEAKER_08]: I appreciate all of the comments and encourage everybody to go read them in their entirety on Facebook and Google+.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, more news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the second round of THQ auctions are happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently the news will be out Monday afternoon on to who has what.
[SPEAKER_06]: This included back catalog rights and also kind of different lots, including the Darksiders franchise, Red Faction and Homeworld franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course, you know, the original auctions, you know, sold off the other stuff like Saints Row and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying they're going to make six to seven million dollars from those sales.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing, though, that we do know that's going to happen, the whole crowdfunded movement to buy the rights to Homeworld failed.
[SPEAKER_06]: They didn't have enough money to win the bid there, so...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thankfully, they are refunding everyone's money.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they have that going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: That means somebody put up a lot of money for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So somebody recognized the value in it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then somebody outbid those guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they had, I guess, it looks like they had around 80 million dollars.
[SPEAKER_06]: 80 million?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, not 80 million.
80,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: 75 to $80,000.
[SPEAKER_06]: $80 million.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the most successful Kickstarter ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think Saints Row went for that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: So $80,000 is what they had between their Indiegogo and Kickstarter campaigns.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, they were not able to get it for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's sold for the price is right rules.
[SPEAKER_08]: and this belonged to Tim Langdell who is the founder of Edge Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, a court order has stripped him of that trademark.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's because of a petition by Dice and EA who made Mirrors Edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: The U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: Patent and Trademark Office issued notice of the canceled registration on April 17th.
[SPEAKER_08]: This whole thing has been going on since 2010.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moby Game made a game called Edge and they've discounted all versions of the game by 50% in celebration.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game had been taken down from the App Store previously due to issues with this trademark.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, anything that had the word Edge in it, this guy was coming for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hide your wife, hide your edge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm, that sort of sounds like Ville.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so maybe this will set a very interesting precedent and send a message.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to create a game called Ville.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just Ville.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, this guy is welcome to call his company Edge Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a problem with that, but Edge Games and Mirror's Edge?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's no similarity there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like Monster Cable.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm all for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should kill off more stupid trademarks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can think of a few we've come across in gaming that need to be cancelled as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on to some more news.
[SPEAKER_02]: In other news, now the original link, by the way, didn't work, so I had to hunt it down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh well, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: So there is a prototype of a Sega machine that was called the Pluto, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a guy's posting on Assembler Games forums with pictures of one of the second prototypes.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were only two of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically says it's super heavy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had two controller ports, a flip-top drive bay, a cart slot, a power button and the reset button.
[SPEAKER_02]: It still says Saturn on it, but this was apparently they were going to brand whatever this Pluto system was with the Saturn name.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you plug it in, it actually has the Saturn logo
[SPEAKER_02]: Loading screen, the drive empty screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, just looking this over, it apparently works.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was, I'm sorry if I'm having to go through this because unfortunately the original thing didn't work for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is region locked, but it is a USA NTSC Saturn.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it had the networking capability.
[SPEAKER_06]: They bought this for a dollar at a Stockton flea market.
[SPEAKER_06]: $1.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, turning around and selling it on eBay right now, already up to like $6,700.
[SPEAKER_08]: For real?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was at a flea market?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other one was at a garage sale.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think the Stockton area as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, okay, it's a Saturn with a netlink built in.
[SPEAKER_02]: This needs to be in my collection, damn it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have a few thousand dollars to pony up?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I have a desire to buy a house.
[SPEAKER_08]: If only you'd been at that flea market.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't live in a Sega Pluto.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can try.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is pretty big.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say, looking at it, it is pretty burly, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a Saturn and I'm happy with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn, that is a monster, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want to read a quick comment on the Edge thing, because people in chat are still talking about the Edge story, and I think this insight from Dungeon Buster is pretty good in chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Langdell picked a fight with EA, and EA decided to litigate his trademark into oblivion and won.
[SPEAKER_08]: The guy was nuts.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'd sue over anything that he thought infringed on his trademark.
[SPEAKER_08]: He made up proof that others were using it, which the courts didn't appreciate.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was hilarious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, that's from Dungeon Buster in our chat room at live.vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also do want to repost the forum link just because people need to see photos of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, of the Pluto?
[SPEAKER_02]: Of the Pluto.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I mean, I've seen the Neptune one because they have it at Classic Gaming Expo every year.
[SPEAKER_02]: This thing is huge and it looks like a Saturn and a Sega CD had an ugly baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Poor Pluto keeps getting shit on.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a real planet.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a real system.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good thing we didn't name this show Pluto Lounge Radio or we might have been in trouble Good thing we weren't Pluto Edge Radio You see what I did there Loki, were you going to get into something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I think I cut you off
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I was going to talk about how successful Microsoft is.
[SPEAKER_06]: They turned a profit in their third quarter, which just ended March 31st.
[SPEAKER_06]: And apparently, I guess, $2.53 billion, a 56% increase over last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, citing that, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: Obviously, Halo 4 is a big part of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were saying that, I guess, overall, though, they said the operating income of $342 million was up from a $242 million loss last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Overall, they're up, but some of their costs went up as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're saying right now,
[SPEAKER_06]: specifically Xbox Live memberships grew 18% now 46 million members and they're saying that the console I guess it shipped 8.9 million units in the first 9 months of fiscal 2013 down 3 million units from the same time last year but it's to be expected it's been out for 8 years now you expect there's going to be a little decline no price drop or anything recently to motivate it yeah
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: the games that supports right now Animal Crossing New Leaf and Tomodachi Collection New Life which isn't something we have here but those are the games that are going to work with the service and you can even see in a little screenshot here you see the games and I guess you take the screenshot and you just put them right up on Twitter and Tumblr which I find interesting that those are the two that are picked not like Facebook or something but again it's Japan Facebook might not be in Japan what it is here and honestly do you want more of that shit on your Facebook?
[SPEAKER_08]: click block
[SPEAKER_08]: You're right, I don't want more of that shit on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Facebook is actually on my shit list for a big reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I've been talking bad about it for a long time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome to the party.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, no word, however, if this is something that's coming to our side of the pond, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I imagine it's one of those things that might surprise us in a future Nintendo Direct.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would imagine maybe they are trying to incorporate some other services that are big here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't imagine they wouldn't try to do Facebook.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to think what other...
[SPEAKER_02]: Look, I just hit Tom Nook with a bug catching net.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just made somebody fall into a hole.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope they incorporate more of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: They should do this type of instant screenshotting for virtual console games.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I would have loved something like this when I was playing the first, well, technically the second Animal Crossing on GameCube and had my town lesbian.
[SPEAKER_02]: or like look what crazy shit I got this guy to say I know like well we had what one character because I think we brought over your card to have our our town people meet and now like half of my town members started saying pussy and then we brought it over to Adam's house and with his and on his wife's game and then half of her town started saying it too
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I caused an outbreak.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a virus.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob caused an outbreak.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got one that said a really, really nasty word, and there was a certain friend at the time that really did not like that word, and it ended up moving to her village.
[SPEAKER_08]: She worked for months, from what I hear, to get rid of it, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_08]: In retrospect, I feel bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Memories.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Memory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Animal Crossing ruining lives left and right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is the part of the show where we would do the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lol, nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no emails tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Freeze Pop emailed us.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're selling merchandise to benefit the folks in Boston.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: They are from VOD.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so go check out Freeze Pop's merchandise.
[SPEAKER_02]: We love Freeze Pop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I almost sang Sprode last night, and then I was too drunk.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the reason why I kind of snickered in the beginning is because we get a lot of stuff from them all the time about what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that is definitely a cause worth plugging.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm going to give it one more refresh just to see.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just in case?
[SPEAKER_02]: And if anybody sent me an asshole email in the interim, then you're banned.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope!
[SPEAKER_08]: Send us one for next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com Send me something funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's okay because if I'd played it tonight, I wouldn't have had anything for next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So don't forget to send in bumpers and more details are available at thevognetwork.com forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: Use your gaming voices to tell people stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, what are you... Something coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mewing out over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Something looks hideous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well let's do the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of hideous and wrong... And horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: to the girl who is at Panda Express.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not one working there.
[SPEAKER_02]: She walks up, this girl walks up to my car and says, Hi, can you please buy us dinner?
[SPEAKER_02]: My mom just lost her job.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, she was totally lying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was, she was there with her friends hanging out and drinking cups of water from inside the... Not an Oscar winner.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, and so I just looked at her and said, No.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she's like, but we need food.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was like, there's assistance programs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not even going in Panda Express.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I went into the Rite Aid because it's like right next door because I wanted to buy cheap crappy sunglasses to wear over my regular glasses.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then, um, so I walked back, um, in, um, to go find my food and I'm sorry I didn't get you any hot and sour.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually ended up having Panda earlier today by coincidence.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it works out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, so anyway, um, by the way, the guy who talked about my hair a couple of weeks ago was there and he said, you did your hair that way again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but, um, the girls were sitting out there just being completely stupid and harassing customers, but they didn't have, like, any kind of security going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: They had no way to ask them to leave.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I was like, oh, I am so sorry, your customers are being harassed right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, um, to the Audi, the person driving the Audi who kept trying to pass me, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't want to go all Seinfeld, but seriously, what's up with bicycles built for two?
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, I saw on the way here, there's a lot of bikers out right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like a tandem?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like, it's a bike with two seats and people both pedal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you meant like the one in back, like the classic tandem bicycle or if it had a buggy or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no, the classic, like you see it in cartoons where it's a bicycle built for two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Riding through the park together.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like the Muppet movie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like, I understand, you know, if you're on vacation or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's get a bicycle built for two.
[SPEAKER_06]: But these were people that were, you know, the bikers that you see out on the road that dress up.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ones that, like, have their team sponsored.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're not sponsored by any fucking person, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: You just have this stupid biker thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: You look ridiculous in a bicycle built for two.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I'm supposed to be, you know, convinced that you're training for your bicycle built for two marathon race that you're gonna be in?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, come on, it's just... Now that song is stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just annoys me extra.
[SPEAKER_08]: My FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll keep it short and sweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you to those bastards that set the bombs off in Boston.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was some straight up fucked up crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or the MIT shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was all the same guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the same people?
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you not see the fuckery that blew up everywhere?
[SPEAKER_02]: I just saw that it was somebody.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't see that it was the same people.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was fucked up, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Props to the city for banding together to stay safe and find the guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they killed one and arrested the other guy who's like half alive right now, so maybe they'll be able to get some answers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't be the hardy boys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby had an interview with a very nice developer who's making crime games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you want to go solve crimes, go play her games.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I do have to agree, though, that major kudos to the Boston Police.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also F you to CNN.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, they fucked up this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: CNN earns fuck up of the year already for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because of how shitty their coverage is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I go to BBC for my news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just wait for the official press conferences.
[SPEAKER_08]: The thing I cannot stand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I cannot stand about situations like this is when there's a lull in actual news it's let's talk about the why let's theorize on all this crap we don't know about why did they do it or make up these theories that's the stuff that drives me bonkers when it comes to news I think you played video games
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really, oh god, I got into it with my mother today too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was super disgusted over that sort of closed-minded mentality that, oh, they ain't white, they must be in trouble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you literally cannot get, literally cannot get more Caucasian than these guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were from the Caucasus Mountains.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_08]: That is, like,
[SPEAKER_02]: Uber Caucasian.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is literal Caucasian.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am with Misty.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, shit like this is why I stick to the Bloody Weather channel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's gonna rain.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm about ready to sign up for that group going to Mars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck this planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will find a way to Skype from Mars.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can we move on to more gaming news?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk about green people instead of white people, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they have a mod for Skyrim that turns the Argonians into ninja turtles.
[SPEAKER_02]: That looked frightening.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then if you don't want to be Argonian, you can put the shell on yourself and you can be like some strange cat turtle or some chick turtle.
[SPEAKER_06]: The dude that they have in the picture here looks kind of like The Rock wearing Turtle Shell.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's like, what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm totally serious about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know if it's on ModDB or if it's actually one of the... It's probably on ModDB or Skyrim Nexus.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Skyrim Nexus is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_06]: and yeah, check it out if that's your thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And maybe this gives you an idea what the new Michael Bay movie is going to look like because it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, one more story for you guys before we get to the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or use your name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: A new album being produced for record label Game Chops.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called World 1-2.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not just about Mario.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's about kind of like what's new and what's going on in bit rock and all that stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: including people like super hexagon composer Chip Zell, Manami Matsume who did Mega Man and we talked about also doing some tracks for Shovel Knight, Austin Wintory contributing to this, Akira Yamaoka apparently going to be on this too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would marry that man.
[SPEAKER_08]: The album comes out May 2nd for $10.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can check out some of the tracks on
[SPEAKER_08]: on the website music.gamechops.com the full URL is slash album slash world dash one dash two but I'm sure if you get yourself to music.gamechops.com you'll get to see some of this now sadly we can't preview the Akira Yamaoka track for you because it's not there but I could try to play a little bit of this this is the Manami Matsume song one shot one kill Matsumae excuse me can I play this
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to play a little bit of it, but it's not working.
[SPEAKER_01]: LOL Live Radio.
[SPEAKER_01]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: LOL Live Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me see if one of these others will work here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's try this Chip Zell track real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it won't work for some reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: You gave them the website.
[SPEAKER_02]: They can listen to it if they want to.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can check it out for yourself.
[SPEAKER_02]: After they've listened to us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or you can try to run both at the same time, but it might give you a headache.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to give us a call, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll talk.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can talk about whatever tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we're getting to the last part of the show a little sooner than usual, but let's be real.
[SPEAKER_08]: The last few shows have all been like three and a half hours, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, now I can go get my grocery shopping time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: We still might have some calls coming in that could be a good time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So again, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last minute stories, Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you have anything tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just am shopping on Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: I picked up Surgeon Simulator 2013.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course you did.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they also have a double pack of Breath of Death 7 and Cthulhu Saves the World for 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not bad at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the Portal games were on super sale this weekend, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but I already have Portal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who doesn't have Portal?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would think most of our listeners picked that up by now, but if you didn't, for whatever reason... I mean, I'm surprised it's not $0.99 yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll probably give it away.
[SPEAKER_02]: They gave Portal away, literally, at one point, and I'm sure Portal 2... Portal 2, right, I think was at a 50% off sale just a few days ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I think that's the whole one this weekend anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we do have a call coming in, so let's get to the phones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hola, bienvenidos a... Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, X-Link, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, doing good.
[SPEAKER_00]: Long time no talk.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been a long time since I've called in here.
[SPEAKER_00]: Happy... Last week, happy 500 episodes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's been awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: 500, that's very... A lot of episodes, so... We're so old.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was calling in because I was excited by Earthbound but I was a little disappointed because during the announcements for it they were saying that it was coming for the Wii U and I was hoping that it was also going to come for the 3DS because I do own a 3DS for that and that is one of my favorite games playing while growing up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't count out the 3DS, but I have a feeling they know a lot of people want Earthbound, and so they'll probably keep it exclusive to Wii U, because if you can even sell a handful of consoles to people that really want to play it again, they'll do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, I don't know why you just wouldn't get a Super Nintendo and get the cart, but the cart...
[SPEAKER_08]: is not exactly... I mean, it still goes on eBay for like $150, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: I just like the portability of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like the fact that usually when I go to work, sometimes I take the bus and stuff, so it's kind of nice to have it so when I do the bus trips, it usually takes about 30-40 minutes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can just sit there and just, you know, level up my character or do whatever it takes.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just play and have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why won't Nintendo just open it up so you buy one, get them on all consoles?
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be the... You know, they're still making money not doing it that way, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: You know, they should take that, but then again, that's a playbook out of Sony too.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sony kind of does that with some of their games with the PSP to the PS3 or, you know, vice versa kind of deal to that.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I mean, I don't know about the Vita, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: I was referring more to the fact that you buy some of their quote-unquote arcade games, their lower-end games, like the pinball and stuff, that you can actually play on both systems without worrying about rebuying it like six times.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not like that's
[SPEAKER_00]: nothing against it because believe it or not here in the household here between me and my girlfriend we had bought Planes vs. Zombies like six different times for six different, almost six different forms of platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think a lot of people did.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, you know, I do look forward to that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, really quickly, Rob, you really love League of Legends.
[SPEAKER_00]: I would love to sit there and play with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think you would have a lot of fun with that over Doa.
[SPEAKER_00]: Doa is just, the game is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a lot of
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear I'm gonna give League of Legends the good old once over, but I gotta finish up a game, I gotta write a review for it first, and then I can get into League of Legends over the next week, while there's still not a lot going on for me in WoW right now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, it's one of those games...
[SPEAKER_00]: where it's nice enough where I can go in there and play a game for an hour or two and not worry about anything like right now I'm level 19 out of 30 so I'm working my way up to 30 right now but it's nice enough where I can sit there and play a game or two and not worrying about that you know I have to worry about subscription fee or anything like that unlike some other games like WoW or something what worries me most about League of Legends though is the other people I hear the community is really awful in League of Legends like no offense to the fans out there but I have heard your community is really awful
[SPEAKER_00]: There is a lot of people that are really awful in the game, but there's also a lot of good people in the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's good and bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: But WoW is not that much worse.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, look at the people on there from Kel and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's just the horror stories.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can tell you just sitting here just, you know...
[SPEAKER_00]: Talk about that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, that's with any game in general.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're going to have the good along with the bad.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, you know, that's the fun of it, like playing with friends and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: That way you don't have to worry about that so much, you know.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's like one of those things where if you do something wrong or something, people will point it out saying, hey, by the way, you're not doing this right.
[SPEAKER_00]: You should do this instead or just follow this or go here and look at this.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of like they do in WoW.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's kind of nice to know that there is a lot of people that's willing to work and, you know, as long as they're a lot good as there is bad with a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, I will give League of Legends a serious try.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've fired it up a couple times, but I haven't done anything serious with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will take my friend's offer to help school me a little bit on it, and I'll let you guys all know how it turns out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But give me a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give me a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like I said before, if you need any pointers or anything, I'll be more than happy to... How about I kick your ass at it?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, okay, you want to do that, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd be more than happy to do that, play a one-on-one game with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can stream it on Twitch like everybody else.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_00]: That's pretty much about it for right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just wanted to get my input out of Earthbound and stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm also kind of worried, too, wondering what they're going to do because now they're announcing this after so many years.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm kind of wondering if they're going to sugarcoat it or take stuff out or what they're going to do to replace it because I know a lot of the issues they were having with that was with the music.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I'm kind of curious to know...
[SPEAKER_08]: I am very curious as well to see if it comes out unedited or if they make any changes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It will be very interesting because they're not going to announce it until it's already out.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's probably an E3 thing too.
[SPEAKER_08]: As long as the happy, happy cultists are still there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're my favorite.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm sure it will be.
[SPEAKER_08]: They remind me of Shane because everything has to be blue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blue, blue, blue, blue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have a good night, man.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_08]: You too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: All one word.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am still, by the way, singing the praises of Drunken Robot Pornography.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, you've been raving about that game on Steam and all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone needs to play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's hard as hell, but fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has a catchy theme song.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you played it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need it.
[SPEAKER_08]: How much is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Five bucks?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ten bucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to the next call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the one and only Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey buddy, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I saw that DarkSakura made some new album art for Anime Jam Session.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looks good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I mean...
[SPEAKER_05]: she took my idea and just took it to the next level because that was not what I was expecting I'm just like the entire staff pretty much loves the new logo great
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I'm glad that you like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now tell people to hire me.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you go to the official Facebook page, there is a link to your fan page where people can contact you for commissions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I would appreciate that, trust me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did not mean to derail your call with singing the praises of DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: I did, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a couple of things.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little bit different from what you were talking about.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's something I've been meaning to bring up in conversation prior.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember Loki bitching about Smartglass.
[SPEAKER_05]: And truth be told, I understand where he's coming from.
[SPEAKER_05]: But my thing is, with Smartglass and the new upcoming PS... Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Upcoming Xbox...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd like to see Microsoft use more smart glass integration when playing games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'd also like to see Sony get on the bandwagon with the PS4 because truth be told, not everybody's going to have a Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you know, if you're going to be beaming stuff to the Vita, which its operating system is slightly similar to Android, maybe we can get a little app on our tablet so we can kind of have a little fun with that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure it can work as fast as, say, a Wii U because a Wii U, you know, uses that whole dedicated broadcasting channel to transmit to the pad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a lot different than the technology in something like smart glass where your little iDevice beams to your wireless and the Xbox or whatever is on that same device.
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything's kind of running through your router.
[SPEAKER_08]: It actually slows things down a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's not like your device can be a controller suddenly or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's not going to work like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I wouldn't want it as a controller, but like a secondary screen or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The weird thing about it is that that's what I always thought smart glass was supposed to be, and smart glass was really implemented poorly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's another example of something that Microsoft really half-assed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, they put on a great show at E3, and then they half-assed their way through it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Connect Labs is another great example, Game Room.
[SPEAKER_08]: They half-assed a lot of this shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: They didn't see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: XNA, sorry about it, but they didn't really give it the due that it deserved.
[SPEAKER_08]: The vision camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the vision camera.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, the list goes on and on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just add smart glass to the list.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really unfortunate because you kind of see the potential there, especially with it being such a media device.
[SPEAKER_08]: And watch, at E3 this year, when they're selling their little dedicated channel, they're going to push the second screen technology again.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to push smart glass again.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I really hope to hell someone calls them out on it like...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, wasn't this supposed to be there already?
[SPEAKER_08]: And like what?
[SPEAKER_08]: A handful of movies have it?
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Dance Central and Halo.
[SPEAKER_08]: And all Halo does is launch what is a separate app anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can download it as a separate app.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I still can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, Forza or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Forza Horizon uses it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I still can't, on my Android device, actually pull up the map.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't have any of that actual smart glass function.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, hey, look, Xbox app.
[SPEAKER_06]: We renamed it smart glass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Smart glass ought to be a hell of a lot better than it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's really disappointing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, they could be doing these...
[SPEAKER_08]: It might not be fast enough to be a controller, so you can't even do little sub-menus and things like that, but why not maps of levels that you're playing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like static images that change.
[SPEAKER_08]: It blows my mind how ridiculous it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't mean to cut you off, but you're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But because, I mean, the Wi-Fi frequency, I mean, it is not as fast, but it gets up there because smart glass is pretty much like an over-glorified controller that...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty much what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell, I use my tablet to tell it to play videos on YouTube on my TV through the 360 or the PS3.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's pretty fast.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: The new system is supposed to be running on Bluetooth versus this Wi-Fi thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now they can have an app that directly communicates with it via Bluetooth instead of over Wi-Fi, so you're going to have less latency and you can do more amazing things with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, E3 is going to be Microsoft touting all these features again, but we'll see how many of them actually excuse me, actually get implemented to its fullest.
Yep.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, anything else you want to share with our listeners today?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have a funny Paxi story.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, go for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we're all in one of the rooms, we're all sitting there, you know, we have our 3DSs out, we're, you know, we're swap noting and cross-friending and all that cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby happens to, you know, walk out of the room because he had to go take care of something.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of my friends in the room, he's going through his friends list and he's like, oh, Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I'm friended with him now.
[SPEAKER_05]: He just said it very nonchalantly.
[SPEAKER_05]: The entire room just gets quiet and looks at him.
[SPEAKER_05]: And he's like, what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I say, um, that was Bobby Blackwell.
[SPEAKER_05]: He just walked out the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: So is this somebody that was like a fan of the show that had no idea that Bobby was right in front of them?
[SPEAKER_05]: My friend Paul, who goes by the name of Oshie, he used to be, I think he used to be like a mod on the G4 forums and the chat room and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they go way back.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's like he didn't realize that was Bobby in the room.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: and we kind of gave them hell for that the whole weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, especially through this radio thing, I've met some people and they're like, you know, you don't look anything like you sound.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm just like, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: How do you respond to that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think Bobby looks like a Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know how to respond to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that an insult or a compliment?
[SPEAKER_08]: It could go either way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still remember that cat to come.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're walking around in the dealer's room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not even five minutes and the guy goes, You're Rob Roberts from Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blush.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it happened.
[SPEAKER_01]: You remember when we were at John's Incredibly Shitty Pizza?
[SPEAKER_08]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: And one of our listeners was there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, listener.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a very nice, like, it's an uber compliment, but one thing to remember, guys, like, I'm not Tom Cruise, okay?
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank God I'm not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like more Tom Cruise.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a fan of video games just like the rest of you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: So when people are like, oh my god, you're Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just like, yeah, I'm Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me about yourself.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been listening to me for all this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell me about you.
[SPEAKER_08]: So yeah, it's very humbling, but very flattering.
[SPEAKER_05]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm gonna let you go, Ranma, to see if anybody else comes through, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: You got it, bro.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: You too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange... Y'all right over there in the kitchen?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan's making a mess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's go to some tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw sending us a tweet.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys might have read about this in the news.
[SPEAKER_08]: LulzSec member sentenced for Sony Pictures website hacking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they went after some of those guys that were involved in that and it looks like they've sentenced a few of them and one of them for the hacking of Sony Pictures website.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not related to the Sony PlayStation Network hack though, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Different, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'll never forgive Comcast for what they did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't it weird now that that's all really, really over, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Props to Attack of the Show for the ending.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a very nice way to end the show with a nod to Leo Laport and Alex and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and I know Leo Laporte is still doing his podcast and such.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think Chris Perillo is doing live streaming.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they have a studio in the North Bay out in Petaluma, I think it's located.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody I know went over there for something.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's cool that they still kind of have all that in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might not be in the city, but they're producing great content outside the city.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, I didn't mean to derail you, but what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, once again, I did want to wish you congrats on the 500th episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you believe we're still here?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I feel old and I need to see if I can find the old episode where I was there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you remember what episode number it was?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know it was summer of 2003, but that's all I remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Two tips for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is the Orange Lounge Radio wiki, which is orangeloungeradio.wikia.com and Dark Tetsuya has put together an awesome little summary of every single episode.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you look at the summer of 2003, you might find the topics and you might go like, oh, I was there when that happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there's another website, and Dark Tetsuya will correct me if I'm wrong on this, but I think it's olarchive.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's O-L-R-C-H-I-V-E dot T-K I think he had to change the forwarder so he'll give me the new address here in chat in a minute but there is look for it on the VOG Network forums look for Dark Tetsuya he has the OL Archive and there's a lot of old episodes they have up on like a SkyDrive somewhere so there's a lot a lot of old shit
[SPEAKER_08]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, I'll have to check them out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for the hookup, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: There it is from Dark to Sea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bit.ly, so Bit.ly slash O-L-R-C-H-I-V-E.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you want to, and this goes out to the general listenership as well, if you want to hear what Orange Lounge Radio sounded like back in 2003, you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I do want to, I always kind of put this out there, it was a very different show back then.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was busy reading Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So part of the reason why I'm calling here tonight as well, DarkSakura, I just sent over the details for Phantasy Star Online 2 for you, but there's something on my mind aside from that that I kind of want to get out there, and it's got me a little bit worried here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Regarding that game, it was announced that it was supposed to come out here in the West, and then we rolled past the release date, and all Sega had to say was it's delayed and nothing else.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's not the first time that this has happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: Colonial Marines, that just happened as well for the Wii U. Obviously that's under a different company but it's got me wondering what's up with the management because there have been other incidences with Sega recently such as the recent Shining Force debacle back in November.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of got me wondering what's going on there and
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we potentially seeing Sega of America closing soon?
[SPEAKER_01]: When has Sega had good management in the US?
[SPEAKER_08]: I am hoping you are just out here yelling the sky is falling, which is perfectly valid.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have good reason for thinking that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I would say E3 is kind of Sega's chance to be like, all right, put it out on the table.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's coming?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is Phantasy Star 2 on that list or not?
[SPEAKER_08]: and if it's not, then I would start to get worried.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I kind of think that's the type of thing they keep in their pants until E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I seriously think that Sega is still going to have a U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: presence regardless, even if they have to cut back operations here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of Japanese companies still have an American presence in the games industry.
[SPEAKER_04]: They may have the translations done in-house at Sega of Japan, but I was just at PAX East recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did not have a booth there, so that's part of what's got me thinking this.
[SPEAKER_08]: PAX is kind of hit and miss.
[SPEAKER_08]: It depends if they have something to show or not.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some companies that don't really do PAX.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take Blizzard, for example.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were there at PAX East because they had something to show with this whole new Hearthstone game, but they don't usually do these cons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Blizzard's like, LOL, we'll do our own con.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's actually just it.
[SPEAKER_08]: They don't usually do these things, so they kind of do it when it's convenient for them, which I don't blame them for.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the record, I would go to SegaCon Just saying Agreed Well, what are we missing?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're playing Phantasy Star Online 2, obviously What are the rest of us missing?
[SPEAKER_08]: I really want to check it out at some point You mean in the game or other games?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, in the game In Phantasy Star Online 2, how is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: The level design is superb in that even though it's randomized, it's still got a lot of familiar elements and you can just randomly encounter a boss outside of the boss nets.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does this mean that you can make the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles in Phantasy Star Online 2?
[SPEAKER_08]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But can I still headshot a Wrappy?
[SPEAKER_04]: You can definitely spend at least an hour per character just building it.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many Rappies can I expect to kill?
[SPEAKER_04]: Tons.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they still play dead and then get back up and you can shoot them again or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: My friend actually spent $100 to buy a Rappie plushie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was Julie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there a big English-speaking presence on the game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are there a lot of people like you who are playing it even though it's not out in this country?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, people got fed up with how long it was taken, and so they just ran with it, basically.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fan communities do amazing things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly don't see Sega really having too big of a problem with it, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, I mean, remember the support that they gave when they closed down the original Phantasy Star Online servers?
[SPEAKER_04]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: They did open up the Japanese form.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly, but they also provided U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: players with the data for their character to transfer to private servers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think that happened.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought that was something that fans were hoping for.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, because I was going to do it, but I ended up just sort of not caring because I hadn't been playing Phantasy Star Online for a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they were allowing full character transfers into private servers.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a limited window that they did it, but they had it available.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to look that up again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, Prince Brightstar, thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's good to hear from you for so long.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, welcome back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yep, I'm probably going to be here every week for a good bit here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Appreciate the support.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you have a good one, okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: You too.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice to hear from an old friend.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's really awesome for somebody that's like, you know, I fell out of the habit or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Real life gets in the way and you don't end up listening to the show anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then it's like after all this time, it's like, wow, I came back and y'all are still here and it hasn't really changed that much.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it's a really awesome thing to hear.
[SPEAKER_08]: So thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_08]: We outlived Tech TV G4 Womp womp Alright, let's see if we get a few more tweets out here I don't know if there's any other last minute stories But quickly, some more tweets from Tigerclaw Centipede creator sees lack of diversity in the game industry Hmm, is that just because it's sequel, sequel, sequel, sequel Milking out the IPs?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my assumption here Hold on, I'm bringing up the article here Why would anyone be surprised by that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't seen these because they're tweeted to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's also depending on where you're looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, if you're looking at mainstream gaming, then yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, here's the headline they're pulling that quote from.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, here's the quote they're pulling that headline from.
[SPEAKER_08]: So much progress has been made in the development cycle and the way games are developed.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is according to industry betting Dona Bailey.
[SPEAKER_08]: It seems there hasn't been enough progress in the diversity of game designers and gender equality for game designers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that does make sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I probably totally butchered the name.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably Donna Bailey, but I said it wrong because it's spelled a little differently than what I'm used to.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, sadly it's something, you know, it's not like we haven't heard it before, but I think the best way to help combat that a little bit is prove some of these analysts wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: The people that say that, you know, the masses won't support a game with a strong female lead and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's important that, and I'm not saying you have to support a game just because it has a female lead, but find the one that you like and really rally behind it and, you know, gather support for it and so forth and show these guys they're wrong.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly think that we need to see more games that give you a choice
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I made this comment during Bobby's show, and I think it's worth exploring a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll bring this up with you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's obviously part of a larger problem with society, and my whole thing is that let's take the dude bros who buy Xbox, and I'm totally stereotyping here, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bear with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's take the dude bros that buy their Xboxes because they're only interested in Madden games and the basketball games and all the sports games that come out every year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you can't play as a woman in Madden, but that's not video games' fault.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's football.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would, but I don't see it happening just because of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, we're in a total patriarchal society right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not just right now, we've always been.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's completely disgusting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm going to say one thing, that there are...
[SPEAKER_02]: There are degrees of this physical expectation that's put out for sports.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I've seen some women's NBA players who could totally school guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't see why we don't have an integrated team.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate to refer to the movie, but you remember A League of Their Own?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: That shit happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where all the men were in war, they had female baseball teams fully on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the WNBA is a thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I mean, I'm saying that it's not like we haven't had a precedent for having women in sports or even having integrated sports teams like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just that people have this notion that it shouldn't be done, that it can't be done, that there's a big physical difference.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that if a person is physically capable of being a part of whatever that sport is, whatever that event is, they should be allowed to be in it without having to deal with judgment because of their gender or because of any other factor.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, I did close the Skype line for now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't mean to get on this discussion, but it's a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: So sorry to those that didn't get through on Skype, but feel free to email us, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comment from ShadowNextGen, has DarkSakura seen how the UFC has started highlighting women's MMA?
[SPEAKER_08]: The next season of The Ultimate Fighter has two female coaches that will coach both men and women.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just curious about your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually don't watch much UFC I tried watching when oh god what was his name that was in WWF he god I can't because he was just like the most boring dude ever but he was amazing to watch but he came from UFC and then I think went back to UFC and I also watched when Brock Lesnar went to UFC for a little while dude he was vicious but I didn't really I haven't kept up with it
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does this do the image of the woman in sports favors?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or does it hurt because, well, Danica Patrick's in a game, but it's cutesy la-la land.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's definitely not hurting her wallet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, props for that, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't look at it so much as a hindrance, although it is, I think, going back to a little bit more on the stereotype.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's definitely getting her some getting her exposure apart from just being pretty awesome on her own.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, aren't we now seeing like more women in NASCAR to like more female drivers?
[SPEAKER_08]: She's certainly not the last.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and Bobby points out too, Danica wasn't the first female driver either.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, she wasn't the first.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just said she wasn't the last.
[SPEAKER_08]: She wouldn't be last.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my problem with Danica Patrick is that she is having to rely on stereotypes to keep her popularity up.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, that whole, well, you gotta show a little boob or you gotta, you know, be this...
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't be just a talented driver.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to be a sex symbol too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That I hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate, I hate, I hate.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some people really, like you've got Ross DLUT in chat who says Danica Patrick didn't break through because of her racing.
[SPEAKER_08]: She broke through because she sexualizes herself in GoDaddy commercials.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you've got people that kind of resent the whole TNA, if you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm even going to go into another, because one of my heroes, because I've been trying to work out a lot more, is a weightlifter named Samantha Wright.
[SPEAKER_02]: And she is adorable.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's probably my height, and I think that if I kept working out like she clearly does, I would probably be about the same build.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've looked at her because we do have a lot of physical traits in common.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that her body type would be a good ideal for me as far as working out and health.
[SPEAKER_02]: But she's getting all this extra attention because she is so absolutely adorable.
[SPEAKER_02]: She is pretty.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I will say that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there have been other female weightlifters who have been just as, if not more talented, if not stronger than her.
[SPEAKER_02]: and if you look at people who are actually physically strong and I'm not talking about the people who you know are those muscle competitions because they starve themselves to nothing they are at their least healthy when they're at a show you look at the actual strong people the people who do the strongman contest who are pulling semis with their body weight they're built like trunks and the women who participate in these they're built like you know complete
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny you bring up the bodybuilding because it brings to mind one of, I think, a great example of where there were very memorable men and women in this, and I'm using this term very loosely with my quotey fingers, sport, American gladiators.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because there were memorable men and women on that show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it was really like an equal...
[SPEAKER_02]: I can tell you one thing about that, and just because I learned how to recognize it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oddly enough, when I worked at GNC, because we would have so many roided guys come in.
[SPEAKER_02]: Teenagers take in that andro because of, what was that stupid baseball player?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck whatever his name was.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, there's a way to tell when a woman is roided.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were some women on that show who were very naturally strong.
[SPEAKER_02]: They looked like a strong woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to see what a woman looks like without steroids, who has worked out, who has a small frame?
[SPEAKER_02]: Linda Hamilton in Terminator 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I'm serious.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that, honestly, to me, people are like, oh, she looks so bulky.
[SPEAKER_02]: Man, I thought that was really attractive.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought that looking strong was a very good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Mark McGuire, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not Barry Bonds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, but then you had the other ones like, and I'm going to go back to using China.
[SPEAKER_02]: A woman cannot carry that type of muscle structure naturally without having a genetic predisposition towards it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can tell how many people are augmented who have, uh, uh, breast enhancement surgery on top of having taken steroids because it will very much give more masculine traits to a woman because your beard basically taking steroids.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just giggling because some of our chatters are like, you know, Actdeft's all sports lounge radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't mean to get this on this big tangent.
[SPEAKER_08]: My whole point with this before we just kind of went on and on and on with it, my whole point was the whole female leads in video games and we don't have enough of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not right that that's happening, but my point I'm making with it is that I think it's a reflection of a much larger problem with society.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not specific to video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't mean to go off on the other, but I think we agree.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the whole point is that, and this I think is going really towards anything, is that
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you have... Even the really brilliant women out there, like just even in academia, are not drawing the biggest attention, are not being taken seriously if they don't also have a certain type of aesthetic, you know, appearance to them.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's really a very sad thing because you can have... Pardon me for saying this, the dumpiest looking guy ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can have neck bearded, you know...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: even if she had three times the degree this guy did and had done all this fantastic biomedical research on appearances alone she wouldn't be taken seriously by the majority of people and that's where I think that we're getting into the really sad part and it doesn't and like I said it's not just affecting our gaming world it's affecting culture across the board and I get absolutely so sick of living in this society sometimes just because of it
[SPEAKER_08]: I did think of another positive, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did think of another place where I think it's done well, where we get male and female sports heroes that we failed to mention, because this is one of the few sporting events I really, truly enjoy watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Olympics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think the Olympics are great, because you get a lot of strong athletes, no matter what, from all these different types of sports, and great stories and things.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great thing, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, even then, I hear, what was it on NBC?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, the coverage of the Olympics this past one was dreadful, to say the least.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but that's another issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: But what I'm saying is that you get side commentary from people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like I would go and look at YouTube videos of some of the events because I wasn't keeping up with it all the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I would see comments, oh, well, she looks like a dude or she looks this or she looks that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why I go into a southern accent when I imitate a stupid person.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you still get that trying to ascribe aesthetics to what should have nothing to do with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, Tangent Train, Tangent Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a good discussion, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and some chatters talking about tennis.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is a really good example, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tennis has a lot of good people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mixed doubles is pretty fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, good job, chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob turned on my ranty switch Maybe some emails next week Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com But for now, we have got to wrap up the show And say goodnight Oh, I may not have got all the Twitter topics I'm sorry, let me quickly try to grab some of these SJ100Matt tweeting One of the most popular card games Is being made into a game for 360 Steve Jackson's Munchkin
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: No way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_08]: A link on Ain't It Cool News of all places.
[SPEAKER_08]: That site's been going on forever too.
[SPEAKER_08]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Munchkin, the video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is... I'm going to put the phone down and no more Twitter topics for tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR, though, if you want to send us stuff for the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get off my feminist pedestal for right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a discussion that needed to be had.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's wrap up, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're about done.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're closing up shop for the night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, you've been quiet over there while DarkSakura and I have been yapping.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: We should set up some time to livestream Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where everything's going.
[SPEAKER_08]: All of a sudden, all the VOG people have just gotten really into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby's doing it, Jamie's doing it, I'm doing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, see, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't really know when to be on when no one else is on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I think it's inevitable that some of us are... I think I was trying to broadcast when Jamie was on.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just I didn't know she was...
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it's inevitable some of us are going to step on toes, but I think as a general rule of thumb, we just try not to be live when a live, when, excuse me, a premiere VOG show is on.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, like, Monday nights are usually really bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, as long as we're not stepping on the toes of... Do you do commentary?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you do not?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you not do commentary?
[SPEAKER_08]: What are you guys doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, like...
[SPEAKER_08]: I do commentary.
[SPEAKER_08]: She does commentary.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I was watching Bobby, he had very little commentary, but they have had some.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do commentary, but the problem is, though, is once again, it's the whole talking in the same room with my wife.
[SPEAKER_06]: She gets annoyed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even if I'm in the back bedroom or something like that, I could try it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure it'd be fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So yeah, I'll hopefully start doing some of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm going to be selling more games this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of those being Injustice on 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh wait, all my friends have it on PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Son of a bitch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because I got a copy for free and I don't want it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because I'm not in the fighting game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll start at one penny tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft says, we were doing commentary yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I missed your stream yesterday because I was out drinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Grandpa was in town from San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_08]: Buy me doubles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a little more drunk last night than I did on the 500th episode.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry it wasn't broadcast, but it's for the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought tonight is thank you all for continuing to listen to Orange Lounge Radio and showing up for an episode like 501 right after 500.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whether it be live, whether it be podcast, I appreciate your support.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think I forgot to say this last week, which was really stupid.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I want to say, as always, thank you for checking out the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you like what you hear, remember, we don't ask for a lot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Help spread the word about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell a person who stopped listening five years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, did you know those schmoes are still on broadcasting?
[SPEAKER_08]: Help bring people back into the fold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Help grow our family a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good lord.
[SPEAKER_08]: And last but not least, DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Down with the patriarchy.
[SPEAKER_02]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, that does it for this week here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week on the show, I'm hoping we'll have some special guests here in studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds like that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Could be a long show next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And pretty cool interview with two people I really enjoy next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: So come here live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Be here live to ask questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Next week, 6 Pacific, 9 Eastern.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next time here at Orange Lounge Radio for episode 502.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_07]: To join us for a live show, tune in to VOGnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_07]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week!