Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Tonight April 14th, 2013
Could Capcom be ending HD fighting game remakes?
Level 5 is set to work on a Playstation 4 game
And could one government be investigating in-app sales?
Orange Lounge Radio
We are live!
And welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio for tonight episode number 500
For this April the 14th of 2013
My name is Rob Roberts
And I'm here with you every week for this very long, long, long time with my co-host
Say hello first off to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you Jamie?
I'm caffeinated now, now I can start drinking
You've had coffee
Now bring on the booze
Bring on the booze
Bring it on
I brought a bottle of pre-made mimosa
Nice
What is pre-made mimosa?
It means that you don't have to buy orange juice and champagne separately
How lazy are you?
They did that shit for you
I did something called saving time, space, and money
By just bringing it already done
Because, fuck it
It's booze, it drinks the same way
Speaking of fuck it, I decided to mark the occasion tonight
I'm gonna wear my pajama pants
I'm gonna take a picture of Rob
With all these little lips all over them that say kiss me
Because I'm wearing my pajamas to OLR tonight
Rob wants his pants kissed
I give no fucks
Happy 500th episode
I think you gave the last fuck last episode
So we're fresh out of fucks, sorry
Alright, say hello
Say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hello
How are you Loki?
I wish these fries were better
I'd throw them all away because they're crap
You went to McDonald's, duh
It's a crap shoot, I know
I wasn't that hungry so I expected them to suck
I just wanted to be pleasantly surprised that they were good
But they were not
Is that the tragedy that has followed you for 11 years here on this program?
Yeah, it's just, it's a
The problem is that I was very indecisive on what I wanted to eat
So, it was kind of like, you know
First I started driving towards Jack in the Box
And I'm like, eh, I'm not that hungry
Don't judge me
I'm not hungry enough for Jack in the Box
So then I went to McDonald's
I'm like, oh but I really want Subway
But it's across the street
So I'm like, eh, I'll just eat McDonald's
Because I need to get gas
Okay, so thanks to Alan for distracting things
Sorry, Loki
But while Loki was talking
Alan came over here and dropped on the table
I got this bag of the chicken and waffles Lay's
Because I knew Jamie has it
Actually, Alan got it
I have had them
Oh, you have had them?
They're pretty good
They're fairly amazing until you get halfway down through the bag
And then I was like, what the fuck am I eating?
Brad from Pod Culture said they were the worst absolute things in the world
They're amazing, I love them
I don't think they're the best potato chips I've ever had
But they're not bad
The cheesy garlic bread ones though are pretty epic
Are they?
They are quite epic
Whoever came up with that little contest at Lay's, genius
Here we are talking about food yet again
Why break tradition, folks?
Duh
I'd rather just have a waffle
Alright
Dude, waffles would be awesome right now
We do have a special guest here joining us tonight
Say hello to Becky
Greetings
How are you, Becky?
I'm doing pretty well, thanks
Welcome back
Now Becky, for those that don't know, is Jamie's BFF
And so Jamie sometimes talks about her on the show
And she's also quite the chef
And so Becky was kind enough to actually cook
Here we go with food again on a video game show
Was kind enough to cook for us tonight
What did you make for us tonight, Becky?
I made red velvet brownies
And they look like murder
They are beautiful, glorious, dripping red
Hope y'all don't see the food boner in my jammies right now
Cause
I'm gonna go take pictures
That sounds pretty epic
Of the food boner?
No comment
Alright
Going to our chat room at live.vognetwork.com
The always present fourth guest on our show
I know we have a fourth guest in the studio
But also always with us as you guys have been
And we would not have made it to 500 episodes without you guys
Let's be real
Hello everybody in our chat room
What the hell comment do I start with tonight?
How about Mako Chan?
Starts us off tonight saying
Murder is pretty fucking tasty
It would be awesome if you drew like super meat boy on those
Because that would be
That's perfect
That's it, Becky, we have to do this again next weekend
So what's going on, live listeners?
Is the stream not work-
I guess a lot of people are bitching that the stream is like
Stopping going tonight or something
So I don't know what's up with that
We're not doing anything different
I can do it
There's too many of you listening
That's what's happening
Bite your tongue
Alright, we do tape live every Wednesday
Every Wednesday when I'm not here
What fucking show is having a birthday today, Rob?
We do tape live every Sunday at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
At the Voice of Geeks Network, vognetwork.com
And thanks to all you guys who do turn out live
Or who do listen to us in the podcast
Speaking of Vognetwork
Are the brownies like really, really good?
Alright, I'm about to eat one
Okay, I want to try one in a minute
But I have to talk about Vognetwork things
Because this is really exciting
Fine, you can talk and we'll eat
Fine, sounds good, alright
So
I think I need new pants
Last week on the show
I complained that I wanted the Vognetwork website to have something
And that was the ability to have instant polls
So we could go and actually ask the listeners questions
And actually poll them instantly
Well, Bobby Black Wolf, in celebration of our 500th episode
Has made that a reality
So for all you guys that are right there on live.vognetwork.com
Because it's the only place you're going to see it
So if you're tuned into IRC via MIRC or something
Make sure you bring up live.vognetwork.com
You don't need to refresh the page or anything like that
This is going to happen automatically
But it is time
For the very first time
We are going to go to our live audience poll
Dork
Alright, tonight in the very first Vognetwork live poll
We are going to settle the great debate once and for all
Because we have to start with an epic question
So here it is
Tonight's question
Let us settle the great debate once and for all
Cake or pie?
There it is up there at live.vognetwork.com
You can participate right now and vote in the poll
And look at this
How cool is this
We see the results live as they come in
It's all tied up right now
Oh, cake just pulled ahead a little bit
This is the most amazing thing ever
Bobby is a genius
He's great
Alright, so there it is
Let us settle the great debate once and for all
Cake or pie?
We will read the results here momentarily
But it does look like cake is quite a bit ahead here in the live poll
Alright
Moving on
What else do I want to talk about tonight?
We have the new feature that I want to talk about
Anything you guys want to say in acknowledgement of our 500th episode?
What the fuck are we doing?
Look at your life
Look at your choices
Well said
I'm going to go drink now
I want to drink too
That poll is going to be too distracting
Because it's just
I have to keep watching it change
I know right
It's, it's, it's
Hypnotic
It's hypnotic to watch
Alright
That's awesome
Yeah, I love how it lives up
We are going to be required now
They'll use that sound clip though
Every time we do an instant poll
That was the plan
Oh sweet
So
Do brownies count as cake?
That's a good question
Maybe I should have added brownies to the list
Oh well
But what does ice cream cake count as?
I guess cake
It's not real cake
But what about pudding filled cake?
Like Boston cream pie
It's called a pie but it really has cake bits
Okay, you're making it too fucking complicated lady
So
I didn't see Boston cream pie as one of the options of cake versus pie so
Uh oh, here go hell come
So
And of course how thoughtful
Oh hi Alan
Hi
What did you just set down in front of me here in studio?
Take a whiff of it, smell it
Oh god
Oh my god it's that stuff I can't have
I'm getting drunk just smelling it
It has to smell how awful it is
You want to smell it?
This is a present from Brad from Pod Culture
Our pals
Thank god it smells more like whiskey than it does like cinnamon
Um
Do you want to smell it at all?
Alright
Uh, Alan do you want to introduce the drink?
Yes it's fireball whiskey
The bottle art is amazing
And we don't have anything for a chaser really
So I got you a glass of water
Apple juice I think would have been really good
But we don't have any so
I forgot to make apple pie
We poll
Um
Chase it with a brownie
Alright so uh
You have to chase it with a brownie
I'll chase it with a brownie but here's the thing
When was the last time we did drinking on OLR?
It was a very long time ago
I don't know but I remember one time I ate half a box of waffles
If I didn't have to take my son to uh
You know to school every morning
I would have totally you know
I know
Crashed but um
I forgot to take tomorrow off work
I remember when uh you had the uh tequila binge
That was kind of hilarious
I don't drink tequila
You did once
No I didn't
Or was it vodka?
It's always vodka
I could swear it was tequila but okay
Remember he married a Russian chick
It's always vodka right?
And
She doesn't drink anything
She likes rum
Are you ready to launch into your gaming week if Rob ends up in a coughing fit after he does the shot?
Get the first news story ready
I'm ready
Um
Don't we have a disclaimer we usually give during drinking shows?
Don't drink and drive
I live here so I can drink
Um
Don't be irresponsible
Uh
And keep it in your pants
Yeah
Drink moderately
Don't come up with you know next gen game console ideas after you know consuming vast quantities of alcohol
Okay so here's my cheers to all you non drinkers
Can you toast me with something?
I'm gonna go make me a coffee
Alright yay cheers 500 yay
One
Two
Three
Hi Rob
I wish you guys could see the look on his face he's like gone immediately for the water
Wow
This is fantastic radio
Poor Rob your face is red
500 episodes I do what I want
I'm gonna go make my mimosa after I do my week
Oh my god
Brad thank you for the bottle of Fireball because this is so worth it right now
The webcam's at my house I've been using it to stream drawing
Loki is there anything you wanted to say in memory of our in celebration of our 500th episode?
No not really I don't have anything I want to say
Technically Rob just had a double
Just that I wish that the wife was capable of taking the son to school so then I could partake but yeah
I said I cannot
Alright I just really want to thank everybody for you know supporting our show and being here
And you know it would have been great to do like a giant convention for our 500th episode and just have you all in one room
But you know money
My apartment ain't that big
Exactly exactly
We're happy to just have you all here and chat with us
I do want to acknowledge this as well because this is like the most awesome thing that ever awesomed
This is something that one of our listeners Code Man
I need to take a picture of that too
Who would you who has a who has a YouTube channel and I'm a horrible person because I can't remember the name of it right now
But hopefully somebody will dig it up and post it in chat
But Code Man is a graphic artist like Dark Sakura
But he designed this really amazing poster to commemorate our 500th episode
And Jamie's going to put a picture of it right now at orange-radio.com
Yeah I might start reposting stuff just to tell him because it will take less time
I believe his channel is Ratchet 1785
Thank you you're very Tiger Claw tonight I love it
Alright so it's a poster to commemorate our 500th episode
What's awesome about this is that he's drawn us as these little chibi characters
And Dark Sakura is like an N7 trooper, she's basically femshep
Loki is Grand Theft Auto and he's got a bloody baseball bat
And I'm World of Warcraft and look guys look
I'm flaming there with my hand
And we have a ferret with dynamite strapped to him
But you know what I really love about this is that if you look at the background
He layered a bunch of listener names in the background
I don't know where he got this list of names because I recognize old and new names in there
Like I look at this list and I go okay Jim Sally of course I know who he is
But then I'm like Roboboy430 I haven't seen that name in years
So I think he did like a combination of people from like
The wiki as well as people he's seen in our chatroom and so forth
So you guys are all a part of this poster as well which I think is just amazing
He should sell prints of it I really wouldn't care and I think he'd make some good money
So I bet a lot of you guys would like that
Alright so oh Tigerclaw found it it's C Taylor 1785
Thank you Codeman he also does
Oh you know what he co-hosts a show called Down for Maintenance I should plug that
And it has very good artwork go figure
So thank you Codeman for that
Should we go to the results of our poll?
Sure by the way some of the photos are already up they're just being slow
Okay
At the very top of OrangeDawnsRadio.com
Alright here it is the results of our poll we're gonna go ahead and end it now
So if you didn't get in too bad
The results of the poll was
Cake 1
And cake was 62.86% to pie 37.14%
You all pissed me off
Alright
Just kidding
Alright I'm finally gonna eat one of these brownies I think it's about
I think it's about time to get into our gaming week
So DarkSakura how was your gaming week?
My gaming week was semi-productive
I really didn't play like a whole lot of stuff
But I did play some more drunken robot pornography
That game is so fun I swear
Okay everybody in the world by now should know how much I love Jumping Flash
It's Jumping Flash with guns and giant robots
And really really good music the game is crack I cannot wait for more of it to come out
I also played something that I'm not allowed to talk about
So I'm not gonna except I will totally leave one game for this one
That's all I can say
Oh yeah I played Minecraft I actually streamed me playing Minecraft so I could show off my house
Or I should say my underground bunker
So that I can hide from everybody else no one can find my house
You've been getting really into this streaming thing lately
I've more or less just wanted to get it to work
Because Dan and I have a plan
I'll go ahead and do like a semi-announcement
Dan and I have a plan to start doing classic gaming stuff on Twitch TV
And I'm trying to decide if Twitch or livestream works better
But we want to eventually get it to where we can run our capture card into
Well we get a capture card to run the video game systems through the PC
And then have everything run off of the main monitor while we
Sorry the liquor is starting to hit me so if I start smiling for no reason just ignore it
I was like Rob I'm feeling good
By the way I like never drink anymore so the fact that I had that is
I have no tolerance I have the alcohol tolerance of a
Oh Jaylinx you are hilarious
Of a child
But yeah so I've just been practicing like with different things
Like lately I've just been streaming playing Mass Effect 2
Because there's a couple people who watched it who just completely skipped it and are playing 3
So like no no no fixing this
And then I was playing Drunken Robot Pornography and I've been doing some drawing you know
I tested out the webcam with it but I don't know if I'm going to keep doing webcam stuff
Now I don't know if you heard Cyl on Horde House this week which we all love Cyl
I love Cyl
She's the best but she was talking about some of her experiences in livestreaming
And how you know because she has the webcam on her and she's very resilient
And able to do that because she gets all these trolls coming in there going you know take your top off
Will you do you know will you make out with a German chick will you do mouth to ass
Will you do so yeah have you put your mug out there
No
Okay you probably don't want to
I had it pointing at a piece of paper
Don't take that the wrong way you're a very pretty lady and I don't think you give yourself enough credit
But there's just too many people on the internet that are crazy horny
Yeah they're crazy horny
Well fortunately none of them are my problem
But thank you Jason I will look into the black magic capture card
But no I was just practicing you know doing stuff and trying out different things
Because I think that what we're going to do is we're also going to maybe try to start bringing up you know
Stuff that's actually in our collection like lovely pajamas Rob
Like we have a whole lot of deluxe editions of games like for example the cyber bots limited edition
And that stupid card capture soccer game that I had to have and played once it came with a damn pillowcase
But we're just really wanting to and part of it is to we might actually be selling off part of the collection
Legasp
Legasp I'm talking about like the stuff that we actually don't play which you know would probably be the Neo Geo CD and the Intellivision
That's probably about it but yeah I still haven't decided what I'm going to use the rest of it for right now until we get this officially started
But Dan and I have been in the works talking about doing something like that for Twitch just because you know we're inspired by like classic game room
And the angry video game nerd which I just think that guy is absolutely hilarious
It didn't make our show roll tonight but I heard something about he's getting his own game or something or was it a movie or a game or what?
He did a movie already
He did a movie already because they had a kickstarter for the movie and it was so dumb but it was great
Yeah the movie looked ridiculous
The movie was absolutely ridiculous but it was hilarious too
Okay I just want to point out when Becky just took that brownie she left these in the shape of a dick
Did you notice that?
You were so perverted because I was thinking they were in the shape of a T
No those are balls and that's the shaft
I have never seen a dick that read before
That is a letter T
You would have to do this to make it a cup
Now it's balls
That is a cross because this show needs Jesus right now
You know what? You know who needs Jesus Rob?
Sorry did I offend the Jew? My bad
You didn't offend the Jew
Now try harder
The atheist is here
Well then let me just call Justin Bieber because then maybe Justin Bieber can really offend you
You know Rob I'm so disappointed
You're such a heathen
No I don't know I don't care
I'll eat a ball
Best nuts ever
You don't even want to see the disgusting thing I saw today by the way
Anything else you want to say about your gaming week?
While you chow down on those balls?
Tasty balls
Alright I'm done
Alright Becky
Oh yeah I played well
Okay now I'm done
Okay Becky I know you don't play a whole lot of games but I think Dark Sakura got you into a game recently right?
God she got me into Mass Effect and it has sucked away my whole damn life
True
One of us one of us
You're welcome
Alright femshep or mailshep?
Femshep I have done a broshep I call it broshep because mailshep sounds weird
But I did a playthrough just because it was the only way I could romance Jack
Fair enough fair enough
I don't get why Jack wasn't a crazy lesbian hookup
I don't get it either
Doesn't make any sense
I would have gone for it
Who is your romance of choice? Because I know and I think it's a good one
Who is your romance of choice?
Thane
Now Thane kind of they really screwed with him in Mass Effect 3 by you know spoilers killing him off
The game is a year old now right?
But they tried to make things right with the Citadel DLC were you happy with what they did?
I was very happy with it because it never actually bothered me that he died
I mean he had a terminal illness if he hadn't died I would have found it stupid
I like that they let him die
It was realistic
In a heroic kind of way
What pissed me off was that nobody said they were sorry for your loss if you romanced him
I mean Garris is there at the memorial wall standing right in front of his name and doesn't say a word about it
And that was the part that pissed me off
So actually getting to have a memorial service made me very happy
Yeah and I have to admit I did watch the whole thing on YouTube and watching the videos
Because there's an extra video
Because you find out that Thane
This really isn't that bad of a spoiler you guys
You find out that Thane made all these videos
Well he said he did
Yeah and no matter if you romance him or not you get to see most of the videos
But if you romance him there's an extra video you get to see it
I have to admit I got a little choked up
And what especially got me was the goodbye scene at the very end when they're all getting back on the ship
I was like
The feels, the feels
I cried like a little girl
I copied off Becky's save files from her Xbox so that I could mod her Shepard
And so I played through all of the memorial and everything with her Shepard
Which it's always very weird playing somebody else's Shepard
But yeah I actually had to go get tissues and cuddle the cat for a little while
Because like ehhh
Technus in our chat room says
I think Jack being either bi or a lesbian would have been kind of cliche IMO
But Breakman corrects and says
It is part of Jack's backstory
She was in a relationship with a man and a woman
And that's again live.vognetwork.com
And Extover says
There goes any interest I had in playing the game too
Oh shush
Shush ya haters
Alright
Any other games that you've been into besides space operas
I've been adventure time
They do have adventure time DS games
Watching my son play a lot of adventure time and screaming at the computer
Is kind of adorable to watch an almost six year old going
Stupid computer stop that
You're not supposed to do that
It's so cute
It's so interesting watching kids now
When like you know back in my day
When I was six we had Commodore 64
And that was cutting edge
But now you know
Wow you had Commodore 64 when you were six
You're such a baby
Becky had to play with sticks
Alright
Assuming there's nothing else for Becky's gaming week
Let me go over to Loki
Loki how was your gaming week?
I played
Let's see
Lots of Saints Row of the Third actually
We've been trying to go through and 100%
100% almost everything
I guess it would be 98%
Because I don't want to play all the co-op stuff
I don't really want to play through the game for like a fourth time
It would just be so annoying
So I finished up the DLC stuff
I'm actually finishing up right now
The Gangstas in Space DLC
Which is alright
It's like the first DLC really sucked
And the other two were okay
They weren't necessarily like
I mean they were still kind of side missions
But they at least dressed them up a little bit more
And they're just so short
They're like three missions long
And that's it
It's like ten minute missions
And thirty minutes for like seven bucks initially
Kind of a rip off
So whatever
So I'm playing The Room
And hopefully I'll be done with it pretty soon
I'll finish the game and get all my achievements on Steam
And move on to something else
They have been playing Defiance
More of that
And actually still don't really know too much about
What's going on in the world
It's hard for me to follow
But the game is very similar to Borderlands
For example if you take a franchise you love
And then you think
Oh hey look there's a sci-fi rip off of that franchise
That's what Defiance is for Borderlands
It's basically a sci-fi rip off of Borderlands
And they've got all these different weapons
That you can use and stuff
And it's not necessarily that you specialize in anything
But the more you use a weapon
The better
Well eventually it gets better
And the more you use a weapon
The better
Well eventually it gets better
And then
They have the different elemental stuff
And it's kind of hard to get good weapons in the game
I've found so far
Unless I'm not doing something right
But they have these lock boxes
That you basically scavenge parts
From killing people
Or taking weapons that you find
In loot and breaking them down into parts
And then you use those parts to buy keys
And then using those keys
You buy these random loot chests I guess
That have two random weapons
Which for my so far
Doing tier two and tier three chests
They've all sucked
So
That's kind of lame
You were telling me about the TV show beforehand
And Tigerclaw is saying some stuff in our chatroom about that
Did you watch the TV show?
I haven't watched the TV show
I don't even know if it's on yet
But one thing I did know
Strudels89 in our chatroom says I think it airs in a week or so
I think it's coming soon
Monday
I think it's this week
Either Monday or Tuesday
I think it's airing
But here's the thing
They are trying so hard to almost be like a Battlestar Galactica
Or something like that
Like I was mentioning they have their own lingo
Or their own slang I guess
To be fair it's by the creators of Battlestar Galactica
Okay so
That is quite fair
So at least they're ripping themselves off
Yes they're ripping themselves off
But they're kind of forcing it a little bit
Because you know in Battlestar Galactica one of the most recognizable things
Is the use of the word frack instead of fuck
Well now they're trying to do the same type of thing for Defiance
Except they're kind of taking it even further
They have two words
Shtaco is one of them
Which is I guess equatable to shit
And so they say that a lot in the show
They're just like
What you're trying to be a fucking Battlestar Galactica
I mean seriously what's going on here
But anyways the game itself
It's kind of fun
I like the fact that you can kind of just run around and do whatever
I've been playing solo through the whole thing
But there's
The way it kind of works is if you happen to go into an area
Say you're doing a mission or something like that
And you're going into an area and someone else is also there doing a mission as well
You kind of get credit for it if you go and help them and stuff
So you can almost like
It's almost like partying but not
But you can actually party in the game I just don't
And then these arc fall things that happen
Which are a little repetitive but
They're pretty hard
And you have like you know
30 or 40 people just
Trying to take down like a massive alien or something
And that's kind of fun you get a lot of experience doing that
But basically I mean the whole like
Look of the game is very bland
I guess like I don't recognize
It's not like this is supposed to be San Francisco
And driving around I couldn't tell you
Like
I don't see any landmarks that I recognize
Well it's the future
Nuclear war and all that you know it changes things
It's just it's kind of bland
But here's the thing who cares if it looks bland
It's fun I'm having fun with it so
Yeah
And I have not paid any money for
Because you can pay money to get a lot of things in the game
Not necessarily anything that's going to help
I mean you can buy I guess you know
Tokens that give you more experience
Like go up your experience by 10% or something like that
Or money drops or weapon drops
And that kind of thing
Or they will have like you know customizable things
To make your character look
Because right now my character looks like a 50 year old
Trying to look like a teenager
And it looks stupid
But I don't care because I don't really look at my avatar that much
He's facing the other way
But I swear to god there's like no customization
As far as how they look
They all look like some weird fucked up person
But that's fine
Because you can get a suit that covers their face up
And you'll ever see them again
I'm kind of surprised at all the hate for
Battlestar Galactica in our chat room
5th Dream in our chat says
70's Battlestar Galactica is only Battlestar Galactica
Brad from Pod Cultures asked
Good Battlestar Galactica
Remake Battlestar Galactica
I like the new Battlestar Galactica an awful lot
I guess I'm just crazy
But yeah it's fun
I just wish more people play
The only person I know that plays the game
Other than me on 360
I have a friend I met a long time ago
Matt who works at
Zappos actually
Oh rad the shoe plays
He was one of the line directors
There so
He plays
I friended him on Xbox a while ago
That's the only guy I know that plays that game
I think it's fun
Buy to play
There's no monthly fees
If you're running into Xbox
Outages like we had this week
You know it's not a big deal
Because hey I can just play later on
And that's kind of the thing I like about it
And the other thing I saw that was kind of cool
They have a lot of these
Different things just like in Borderlands
How you do different things like kill
Kill people in an assault rifle
Go to these places
Do this type of mission or something like that
And once you complete
All these challenges or whatever you experience
Well they have it broken up
Season 1 is all these
Different challenges so they're going to have different challenges
For the next season and I think actually
The whole game is going to change for season 2
So whatever happens on the show
Is going to reflect in the game and vice versa
Like if
I don't really know if there's any competing factions
Or anything right now but if they have something like that
It may reflect on the show
So it's interesting so far
I think
So I'm going to play a little more of that
And then the other thing I played that I really probably shouldn't be playing
Because it's
I think piracy
I mean we shouldn't really talk about it
Shame on you
Whatever I'm buying the game when it comes out anyways
But I wanted to play it early so that's
As long as you're going to buy it
I'm going to buy it so
The gameplay was Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon
It's fucking awesome
Is that the Xbox Live one?
It's Xbox Live
PlayStation Network and Steam
It's going to be amazing
It's 15 bucks when it comes out on the first
It's going to be fantastic
It got leaked out earlier this week
Because of some hack on Uplay and stuff
So I had to try because I watch all the trailers
I watch gameplay footage and I'm like I gotta play this game
And it's just
It's so awesome
This is basically a developer making a game
They're like okay you guys make a game that's fun
That you guys want to play
It's just so fucking
Why aren't all video games?
It's just so cheesy though
Shouldn't that be the mindset that goes into any game?
But it's just so cheesy
It's basically this cliche
B science fiction type plot
That takes place in the year 2007
And it's
A lot of the details they have
First off they kind of poke fun at themselves
With the whole tutorial thing
Basically you drop down
To invade this base
And your partner
He kind of trolls you
By enabling this tutorial mode
In your suit
And so through the entire tutorial
Which is giving you stupid commands
And just breaking it down
Jumping allows you to
Change your orientation
Along the Z axis
Weird stuff like that
So he's just like I hate these tutorials
This is stupid I just want to kill somebody
It's kind of funny
And then there was also
Like a part where that guy is
Hacking this missile guidance system
Thing and all the jargon
He's throwing out
I'm hacking the motherboard
I'm doing this to this
It's just all completely
Obviously made up jargon
It's just hilarious though
And then they reference stuff that no one has any idea
What they're talking about
It's just like that time in South America
Yeah and then they go in there
And then also
I like how his partner
Uses the phrase
Motherfucker a lot
Because he's the cliche
Black action hero guy
Like we're gonna get those motherfuckers
You know
It's just awesome
Is Samuel L. Jackson voicing him?
I'm imagining those words coming out
Like if it was a comic panel in the same font
As I'm gonna get you sucka
Pretty much like that
And here's the best part about it
All just like old PC
Animated cutscenes like they're all static
Images that they're moving around and stuff like that
It looks just like an old NES game or something
Seriously it is an awesome
If you like Far Cry
Pick it up it's like 15 bucks it's great
The island's still pretty big
They have blood dragons
Which are cybernetic like
Dinosaur things that shoot lasers out of their eyes
And they're cyber panthers
Cyber panthers
I want a cyber panther
Yes I don't
I don't normally condone piracy but
This is a game that I was gonna pick up anyway
You just couldn't wait
I couldn't wait
I was already planning on
Picking it up on Xbox Live or Steam
Because I'm multi platform for some reason
You just gotta have achievements
I do
Anything else for your gaming week?
That's it
My gaming week pretty quick
Not a whole lot of new stuff
That freaking addicting
Jetpack joyride
If you're still listening you suck for getting me addicted to that
Also World of Warcraft
Been working on PVP
My character's level 65 now
I did try some new IOS
Games this week I wanted to plug real quick
Talk about a couple of them
I know some people don't really consider the iPhone
Games actual games
But whatever deal
I'd like to see them play through
Escabagaluda
These games are not quite as tricky as Escabagaluda
But I want to talk about them anyway
To be fair I've been playing them on my iPad 3
Which is the new iPad
But not the newest iPad
The first one is called
Puzzle and Dragons
Which apparently is a big hit over in Japan
Yeah I was about to say
Isn't that like a rehash of the old
Yeah it's partially a puzzle game
Mixed with Pokemon
It's an interesting little puzzler
And it has Pokemon elements in it
Where you can kind of combine
Which is funny because the combining elements
Was very similar to what I saw in that card game
Guardian Cross
From Square Enix that I got into
A couple of weeks ago
Overall Puzzle and Dragons
I didn't really care for it
The puzzle mechanic part of it
I didn't think was very good
Because you touch to move things
And line them up in 3's
And that doesn't attack
But you can literally move them anywhere
And you end up building up combos
And things like that to ultimately be able to take out enemies
But the challenge really wasn't there
And it felt like a bit of a grind
Fest and I just wasn't a fan
I would have to see it because I remember something about it being
Related to the
What was that game?
I actually did it as a classic game ages ago
The Puzzle and Desu
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Because that's where I heard about it
Because somebody was comparing the two
It could be but I didn't play the other one
So I couldn't tell you
Overall Puzzle and Dragons
It entertained me for a couple of evenings
But I'm kind of already over it
The puzzle mechanic isn't enough
To keep me interested in it
I'm sorry to say
I also checked out Nimble Quest
Which if you guys know Nimble Bit
They made Tiny Tower and Pocket Planes
Which you know hello crack
But this new game is actually nothing like those games
It still has the whole 8 bit feel
But they basically created a new version
Of Snake and they are not
They even say in the tutorial
Remember this game and they show the little cell phone
Picture of Snake and
That's basically what they've created but what you do
Is that instead of picking up
Squares that make your Snake longer
You pick up more heroes
And some will throw fireballs, some use swords
Some have bombs
You know and that's kind of the gist to it
And the other guys
Running around might try to attack you
So it's all about maneuvering
Not running into yourself
And kind of being in the right place
To use different attacks
It's very addicting
How long will it take Zinga to steal it?
I'm sure they've already worked on it
They're already working on it right now
So you know it's also free to play
So you can download it for free
You level up your characters
And they can get stronger but of course
If you spend real money you can level them up real fast
That's kind of the catch
But overall I liked Nimble Quest quite a bit
The only thing I didn't like about it
Is that you go through the same
Levels over and over again
You start at level one
It's like you're going through the same levels over and over again
Which you know is fine that's how a video game works
But in a game like this you would
Sort of think at some point
I can either branch and go to different
Stages or I can resume
Where I died or something a little
Different I was a little disappointed
That that basic mechanic wasn't somehow
Improved on
The last game that I checked out this week
Which actually is probably my favorite of the three
Is not free to play it's a 99 cent game
It's called Slayin
And this game is really cute it's very 8-bit
Style and it's retro-tasticness
But um
Basically it's just got left arrow right arrow
And button and you move left move right
And jump and your character is a little
8-bit knight that constantly has a sword
Out in front of it and you can either move left
Or right and you're killing little
Slimes or you can jump in the air
And hit little flying skulls
And as I talk about it
It sounds like super basic but it's really
Addicting and the graphics are
Part of the charm the music
Is part of the charm I like how at the
End of the level you can upgrade weapons
And it even integrates
Game center where you can kind of see the tombstones
Of your friends where they died and so
Forth so I thought that was kind of
Cool so I
Yeah I like that one that was my favorite of the three
Is Slayin so out of
Those three that's the one I recommend but go figure
That's the only one that's not free but it's only 99 cents
So
Rastielutianchat asks
Why the hell does no one ever do 16-bit
Retro?
You see it once in a while
To the moon? Yeah
I would say maybe even Slayer
Looks a little more 16-bit
Than 8-bit it's somewhere in between
It's like a 12-bit
Like a turbo graphics game
Or something it's kind of a little bit in between
It's two 8-bit processors together
So there you go
That was really my gaming week just a bunch of iOS games
But you know that's one of the places people
Play games on now
To be honest that's where I'm doing a lot of
My handheld gaming I haven't touched
My DS and
Except when I cleaned it
Actually the last handheld system I played was a Winter Swan
Well I still have been playing Harmonite
But I talked about that last week already and of course
Swap Note but I'll talk about that later in the show
And you know there's still other three
I even booted up Kid Icarus 3D classics
The other day just because I love
Kid Icarus and the 3D remakes
Surprisingly good because they
Didn't change much besides
The backgrounds and
Giving it some 3D effects so it's really
Good so
Anyhow let's get into
Tonight's news
Yes we're going to do news tonight just like we always do
So let's have Loki start us off
Alright so
EA has
Let some people go and of course
They're not going to say who or
Why or where but they
Basically
Had layoffs and they're
Not seeing which teams they're coming from and that kind of sucks
But isn't some of that leaking out to the internet anyway?
Who it is?
Yeah I believe it was EA Montreal if I remember correctly
It was supposed to be
I think some of the people
That are affected by it
Yeah EA Mobile Montreal
So
I don't know
And they're saying that I guess
60 to 70 permanent employees
Were let go and I guess another
100 people working under contract
Were let go as well
Mostly QA testers
So
I don't know
It's just kind of a normal cycle because after all
EA did have a bunch of games
Just come out recently and like you know
Three
I want to say like three or four games
Yeah four games
I want to say that they just had Tiger Woods
Army had two
Dead Space 3 and
Crysis 3 so
It might just be that they're
You know
They're just slowing down right now
And so they don't need people because the only other game they have coming out right now
Is Fuse and then NCAA
Yeah but we're on the cusp of the new E3
And who knows what's being developed
For next gen systems
Battlefield
My guess is a lot of Bioware people
They've already ruined the IPs now it's time for the
Layoff phase
Another game coming out?
It's Mobile
Montreal
I don't know what exactly EA Mobile Montreal
Was doing
Facebook games
Bioware is working on at least
The Don't Call It Mass Effect 4 game
The Dragon
E3 and the Unknown
Game that the old Mass Effect
Team is doing because they are not doing Mass Effect 4
The multiplayer team is doing it
So we'll see
Probably at E3 get some more information about that
Yeah because EA
Montreal
Well Montreal is
Army at two
But that would be just EA Montreal
Not necessarily Mobile Montreal
What else have they worked on?
As long as our friends
Here locally at Bioware Sacramento
Are okay but I think they're doing a lot of
What were they before?
ClickNation
They do a lot of Facebook
They had a really popular Facebook game
That's why they got grabbed up
So I'm sure any Dragon Age
Mass Effect kind of like Facebook tie-ins
Or something they were probably working on
I don't know I've applied for them three times and they haven't hired me
Aw poor thing
Sorry Loki anything else?
Yes and unsurprisingly
In a row they have been voted the worst company
In America by Consumerist
Which is you know a poll
That they have on a website that people vote
That are consumers that visit the website
It is completely
Well all the nominations
Are done by people that review the website
And then they take the top 16
Or so nominations I think it's more than 16
32 and then they
Narrow it down from there
And this really seems to carry a lot more weight
Than it ought to like a lot of people
I see a lot of people that are pissed
Like why did EA
Win this when Bank of America
Is a far more evil company
When Comcast is more evil
It's an anti-popularity contest
It's not even that it's just like
Bank of America was one of the I think even they went up against Bank of America
And it's just people voted
Maybe Bank of America is just not
That much in the forefront for some of these people
It's a fucking internet poll
Like do we give this much
Weight to something that's on Yahoo.com
I sure hope not
Like I don't
That's my thing like the results
It's like who's line is it anyway
The score doesn't matter
My vote for internet's
Worst poll goes to consumerist
Worst company in America
Oh you should be
We're analysts we can say this
I could run a poll right now
On the site who runs the worst poll
About the worst poll in America
Consumerist or somebody else
I won't right now
I have to save that for special
SSJ 100 Matt calls it an ass hattery contest
Whatever it's just a contest
It's just haha lols
That you know they won again
Because haha you screwed up all this SimCity stuff
And we hate you because of your DRM
And your policies regarding
Cashing in
Microtransactions and all that stuff
Haha see we showed it
We showed you
That's kind of what it is
I didn't log on to Mass Effect for a month
So I voted them the worst
Shadow Next Gen
Shadow Next Gen says in our chat room
Anyone who voted EA as the worst company
Should have their gaming rights rescinded
And be banned from the industry
Look people are welcome to their opinion as far as I'm concerned
But I'm just kind of like
You know
I tend to think
There are far bigger problems
Than you know EA
As a gamer do I like a lot of the things
That NCA has brought to the table? Hell no
And do I think they've deflected an awful lot
Of the blame? Hell yes
And have they made a lot of bad decisions
And possibly deserve to be having the lower financial
Quarter because of it? Yes
Do I think people should be losing their jobs?
No
But it's not those people's fault
It's the fault of? Who is it?
Management
So what management got laid off
As a part of this?
That's what we really should be
You got me
They did lose the CEO and that sadly
Or fortunately depending on which side you're on
Is the person that needed to take the fall
So we'll see if things get better
But if you know
If last year was any sort of
You know
Barometer of whether things are getting better
Nope
Besides how many years is it going to take
Before SimCity stops working
When they shut up those servers
DarkTetsuya in our chat room says
I do give EA credit for their pro
LGBT stance
And I do love Need for Speed
They blame that as one of the reasons they got voted
You know
It's a tricky
I appreciate the fact that
Peter Moore did come out and say
If that's the reason you're going to name us the worst
Company in America then by golly
We're the worst company in America
I appreciate that he said that but at the same time
I'm kind of like
But like
How do you focus on the real reasons you're getting
Voted for this
Like a lot of that is feeling like smoke
And mirrors and whether you deserve it or not
It's falling on deaf ears
It seems to me and that doesn't
Make it very promising
That you're going to change anything
I honestly would have put more of the crappy
If I was going just on video game companies
I would have put more crap on Activision
I think
Or maybe Capcom
I don't know
EA is the company that designed the whole
Online pass phenomenon
That we see nowadays
EA was also one of the first companies to
Hey you know those games that you had cheats in before
In Playstation 2 where you just enter
A little button press and you get those cheats
Yeah you can buy those now
And even in fact I remember
Is the first Godfather game they had
On Playstation 2 and Xbox
Where they didn't have such a way to purchase those
Bits of DLC
They actually had button presses to do those cheats
On the 360
That's going to cost some money
So yeah so they can go fuck themselves
Origin is just the thing that pisses me on
Origin is the worst part of it
Hey but Rob
There's 45 million people on Origin
How many satisfied customers
How many people on Origin
Because the game they wanted to play
Was only through Origin
If I could disable that shit I would
To be fair
And I have to say this I have to acknowledge it
Nobody liked Steam when it first came out
And it's great now but I just
To me there's a difference
I'm kind of like Valve fixing it
Yeah I kind of see that out of them
But EA fixing it I'm like I don't know if they're ever
Going to
I think that Steam though had it right from the get go
That you know let's put out games and put them out
At affordable prices
Get people interested in franchises do big sales
And EA's like oh that's not any way to make money
And look where they are
Hi
Alright well let's move on to one of those companies
That Dark Soccer has said you know they're not doing
Much better and that's Capcom
And Capcom had something interesting to say
This week where
Capcom Senior Vice President
Christian Svensson said on the
Ask Capcom forums
Quote, sadly I think we've probably
Run the course of feasible titles here
Given the drop off we've seen in sales
With each new introduction
That's in regards to HD ports and
Remakes of fighting games
That's a lot of games to be honest
Well
No they could really dig back
In the archive do like the Mega Man fighting
Games and
Capcom vs SNK
Although I guess that's coming out on the
Playstation 2 or whatever
It's going to be an old hit or whatever
Just how bad is it?
They've come out and said
That the Dark Stalkers resurrection
Sales are not good
Dark Stalkers
The Dark Stalkers resurrection didn't even place
On the list of best selling Playstation Network
Games
In further comments Christian Svensson saying
It's partially due to lack of a
Promotion
Quote, we've not given up but I'm disappointed in the opening
Sales response relative to any other fighting
Title we've put out on the same platforms
Given the frequency and urgency of
Requests we've had here over the last several years
And the quality of the execution
It's the most fully featured
And probably best project of this type
That we've done
Here's a question that comes to my mind when I'm
Reading about these stories and that is
Is possibly Xbox Live Arcade
And Playstation Network just too
Oversaturated and that's what's
Causing the drop off is that there's just
Too much stuff on there now and it's hard to stand
Out because I'll tell you what
When Xbox Live Arcade first came out
Shit I was buying everything
I bought almost like every other week there was a new
Release I would buy it like just because like hey
New game for five bucks right
I bought like everything
Now I honestly couldn't
Tell you the last game I bought on Xbox Live Arcade
I don't remember it was a while ago
Or even Playstation Network
I don't remember the last game
I got
Last game I got was Retro City
Rampage
So is it possible that maybe
Part of the sales drop off is it's hard
For this game to stick out because maybe
You know it's not
There's too much to pick
From now
Maybe just Darkstalkers
Is just not as popular as Street Fighter
But isn't that the game that everybody was asking for?
They wanted Darkstalkers 3
They wanted Darkstalkers
You mean Darkstalkers 4 but could that
Could this
Could this endanger a Darkstalkers
4 because this hasn't been selling well
He admitted themselves it was under promoted
So I mean a good portion
Of the failure to perform has to
Do with their failure to promote
ActDeft in chat says
The last Xbox Live Arcade game I bought was
Darkstalkers Resurrection
Yyr in chat says
I'll say this much
The moment Sony announced that Playstation 4
Would not be backwards compatible
I lost almost all desire to buy
Anything for Playstation 3
On the Playstation Store
That's a really good point
That's a very good point
I have to admit that crosses my mind too
And part of the
I mean and this is
I know where some people
Keep in mind a lot of people I hang out with are classic gamers
Why buy something in HD
That I have on how many
Other dozen systems
In the past that I have paid good money for
Yeah it's like I got a maim cabinet
If I want to play Darkstalkers I'll go play
Darkstalkers
I've got the Vampire Savior collection for Saturn
If I wanted to play that that's the best version
Out for a home console right now
I mean
Darkstalkers they do an anthology on Playstation 2 as well
I think so
Yeah so it's not like it's that hard to go out to your used game store
And buy a $5 Darkstalkers
It's not that hard
I do want a new Darkstalkers
That being said because it's probably one of my favorite fighting game
Franchises
But still
I mean doing these HD versions
Especially in a still depressed market
Not very
Not a very good idea you have to bring something innovative out
And just cleaning up the graphics isn't going to be enough
Interesting
But there's other HD remakes on the horizon
They might not be fighting games
But we do have the Dungeons and Dragons arcade game
And DuckTales Remastered coming out
Judging on the reaction
That everybody gave at least the DuckTales game
At Penny Arcade Expo
I'm thinking they don't have anything to worry about there
That's an HD reboot that's not in trouble
But the Dungeons and Dragons games
Now look I'm a fan
Hell yeah
But I worry they're a little niche
I don't know I'm hoping I'm wrong
I hope I am wrong
I will be more than happy to say
I was so wrong on that
And that game sold shit tons
But I have a feeling it's very niche
And it might not sell well
I keep my fingers crossed on it
But I mean they're not really giving it the best promotion either
Are they?
Well they unveiled it at the same expo
Well yeah DuckTales
But I mean since then
I think they'd have to promote the hell out of it
And to really get the type of sales they're looking for out of it
And again
I probably won't buy it because
I've already got it
Lots of people in our chat room saying some positive things about it
DungeonBuster says yay the D&D beat em ups
Marinko
I hope I said that right
Said I would love to see more Dungeons and Dragons
Well y'all better go buy it
Chiggers wants Mr. Do
They never did I thought they did a new Mr. Do
Not that long ago
I thought they did I could be wrong
I think it was out on a compilation
Or some type of like new Mr. Do
But it was really nothing like the old ones
The sequel Mr. Pooh
Mr. Does
Mr. Did
They had a Mr. Do game I don't remember what it was called
But yeah they actually had an arcade game
Where it was really weird
I don't remember
Like a platformer or something
And honestly though
Back to comparing the D&D to DuckTales
People underestimate
The love for the old DuckTales game
The DuckTales game was freaking sweet
I mean
That was one of the first things that Dan
And I ever talked about when we first met
Online ages and ages and ages ago
He's like we were talking about
Video game music and he says oh yeah my favorite
Is that DuckTales moon level
And I'm like oh yeah me too and you know
And then we started reading you know sharing
Bad fanfictions and it was love
Aww
Actually
You know what we met over right?
Um
Ranma one half
Oh I thought it was your sound rips you did
No I did those after
Actually I just started doing the sound rips after I moved out here
Ah
Alright well let's move on DarkSakura
If you have some news for us
Hey Codeman's in chat hi thank you for our poster it's awesome
And I need to talk to you later
Has to do with album art
Secret messages to listeners
Secret secret meh
Secret message how's that? Well there was
A survey that went out
That showed the
Income disparity between
Game developers based on gender
And it was
Actually a 2012 salary survey
That was put out in the March issue of Game
Developer magazine where
They were saying that even though the number of women
In the industry is growing
There is still a huge salary
Gap is something like
The average female game
Producer makes about
Maybe 79,000
And the average male makes
About 86,000
So we're talking about a huge
Disparity for the same work
For people who are just as capable
If not you know
Overlooking people who are more capable simply because
Gender
Well does the story get into why?
There's a big
Is that just you know because unfortunately
I can't get into the area that has the
Cool thing on it because I don't want to pay for a subscription
For it. I was going to say
Is that just an unfortunate echo
Of what can happen
In the greater world unfortunately
Well they're also
Talking a little bit more about
Where the bulk
Of women are working within the industry
And it says that
That's in art and animation at about 16%
And game designers around 11%
So
I wish I had more information
I tried to get into the thing but
I don't have a subscription so sorry
Um
Marinko in our chat room says
You would think we would be past
All this gender inequality at this point in human
Society. You would wouldn't you?
And it's unfortunately
That this industry has to
Really exacerbate that issue
It sounds like from these statistics
So
But it's just a really
It's just
Pretty sad I think
Sort of sad commentary that
I mean I am glad to see more women
Getting into the industry because I mean we definitely
Need it especially after what we talked last week
About the
Preference
Towards male leads in video games
Versus female leads when we've had
Awesome games with female leads like what mirrors
Edge and the new Tomb Raider
The new Tomb Raider
I really think that it's just
Something in the public perception that's gonna
Have to change so
Well we have the power
To change it so
If people would listen to us
I don't mean we I mean we as a generation
I know I know I know
How about this way if people would be
A little bit less distracted by
Things and actually get off their ass and do something
Just saying
Alright Loki speaking about the we changing
Uh
Yeah the uh
A lot of the features that are on the we
Online features maybe
Stuff that you don't use I'm sure it's a lot of stuff
You don't use are being
Deactivated starting June
28th this includes the
Nintendo channel the news channel
The forecast channel everybody votes channel
The me contest channel and
Some of the data exchange
With friends in other words
Data exchange includes the ability
To send messages to friends
And also all of the
Me data exchange
In some games
Will end as well
I'm wondering if that also means like the
Me plaza swapping of
Characters and stuff like that I wonder if that's gonna go away
But shit at this point I mean
That's almost like
Almost all the online functionality
Of the we I mean
Well like Nintendo's ever had
Any real concept of embracing
Online technology it's kinda
Dumb that they
Had all these curated channels and they couldn't have
Like just pulled you know
Weather information from
Yahoo or you know news
From like anything
I don't know RSS
Feeds I mean that's all they really are why couldn't they
Have just updated hey we're not gonna do these on
Our server anymore let's just update this
To like RSS feeds for different things
Uh Rasteel UT in chat
Asks does anyone use those stupid channels
I figured it'd be faster to just go with the browser
Well I haven't touched my we
It was fun to spin the globe
In the news channel and in the
The weather channel
The weather channel but yeah I mean that kinda
Loses it's luster after some time
But you know they're still actively
Selling the we
Granted the most recent model they came out with
In Canada had the internet parts just
Stripped out of it maybe that should've
Told us something but
You know it's not like they aren't
Still I mean there's a we game is
Coming out this week or just came out
The whole pandora's tower
Yeah this week so it's not like
The week itself is dead
It's dead but there's
But they're sure pulling the plug on
Basically we connect 24 is
Getting it's plug pulled anything that runs off the
Internet on the we is done yeah cause after pandora's tower
The next game you have coming out is
Smurfs 2
And then after that
Planes
Disney planes
And
Disney infinity
So it's all kids stuff but
You're not gonna get Madden
You're not gonna get in 6AA
You're not gonna get anything else
I think after this year and maybe
Maybe if you know
There's some indie developers out there
Or smaller developers that really
Want to just still focus on the we
I think you're gonna be out of titles
Probably by
Second quarter next year
Yyr in chat says
Darn I can't check the weather at the north pole anymore
Everyone you know you've done this
Guilty as charged
I have to say not guilty
Totally fun though I've actually never played with the weather channel
You wanna know where my we is?
In a dumpster?
No it's in a box at Dan's mom's house
Haven't touched that thing in months
I can't believe I waited in line for that thing
Although that was pretty fun giving donuts
And bribing for our spot online
Ravens dolphin in chat says
I don't think people were using that stuff on we
How many people sent messages on their we
And watch it glow blue
Not in years mine is on the floor
And yeah you know what let's be real
I haven't used that stuff in a long time either
So I can't sit here and go
Oh how dare they take away the stuff I used to love
It's over
I think what the thing that's
Annoying people the most is it's basically
Just saying that Nintendo's just giving up
Support on this console
They're just like eh we're done we have the Wii U now
Which they kinda need to do to help
You know motivate people to get the Wii U
Yeah but I mean what's gonna happen
When the new Wii U U comes out
The Wii U U?
Is it the Wii W?
That's funny
Her her I'm clever her
Alright
Hopefully also funny and light hearted
Like some of their previous games
And fun will be the next
Game from level 5
Level 5
Is probably most well known for
Ni No Kuni as of late
But they also did Dragon Quest 8
Which was so good and White Knight
Chronicles 1 and 2 which you know
Were kind of a little more controversial
In fact I heard the servers for those games are getting shut down
Which is kind of unfortunate but whatever
Games end
I guess in this day and age
But apparently a new PlayStation 4
Project is in the works
This is according to level 5 boss
Akihiro Hino talking
In an interview with Nikkei Trendy
It's in the planning stages
Hoping that they can announce something
More specific about it soon
Could that be
Ni No Kuni 2
Dragon Quest 8 2
Or okay to be fair
Maybe we don't necessarily need a sequel
They can do something new
That would be nice right
So
We will see what is next from
Level 5
Okay Ravenstaufen was hilarious
There's been a bunch of jokes going on in chat about Wii U 2
Featuring Bono and I said featuring
The Edge and Ravenstaufen
Says is the Wii U 2 slogan with or without you
I like it
It's funny
Yeah that is pretty clever
With or without you
Alright one more story for you guys
Then release dates, Dark Saga
I got a story for you
Well hackers gonna hack right
They cracked
Ubisoft's Uplay security
So they can download games for free
And Ubisoft actually sent out
A statement that they said that they are aware
Of the issue and are trying to resolve it
The rest of the quote goes no personal information
Was compromised
Uplay's PC download service will be unavailable
Until the problem is fixed however all other Uplay services
Remain available
So basically it was actually a group of Russian
Hackers that broke into it and downloaded
Games for free
Wow
Hackers gonna hack
Yeah but that's quite something to get in there and
Download games for free
Loki
Including that's how Far Cry
Give us some more details
How did this exactly happen
It's basically a trick with the client
I think they said it's easy
Even maybe like a console command
Or something like that
But basically
Tricked Uplay into thinking
That you own the game and allowed you
To re-download it
So they did that with
Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon
And some other stuff
To prove that it worked
And so now they're gonna try to patch that out
But
If you mean that sucks that your DRM
Is able to be defeated that quickly
Especially to have a game like that
Leak out early
But it is awesome so I do recommend
Everyone go buy it
Well they've
Taken down
Well it's not gonna stop people from the re-up
Probably how you got yours but
Once it's on the internet it's
On the internet for a second on there for an eternity
But yeah
They
Did their best to get that shut down as soon as possible
But still
It was Gameranx
G-A-M-E-R-A-N-X
Put an image of the game being
Downloaded
That was for Far Cry 3
Blood Dragon
And basically said here is us
Sending it to the torrent sites
You know
Bite our ass
So
Hackers gonna hack
Alright so don't put your full games
Online
Or like a month before they're supposed to come out
Unless I mean
I'm gonna do a brag about being unhackable
Cause usually that follows immediately being hacked
No but Ubisoft had that whole
DRM thing which nobody liked
Not that that makes it okay
I'm just saying that's you know
Probably the justification
I got the Ubisoft little service myself and I said
You know what I don't really need to play Assassin's Creed
That much
I registered some of my games with it
It's you know whatever
So
Alright let us travel around the world
Check out some release dates
And uh
Loki we'll start with you in the US
Pandora's Tower this week on the Wii
On Playstation 3, Xbox 360
And the Wii U and Justice Gods Among Us
Shimagami Tensei Devil Summoner
Soul Hackers on the 3DS
And last but not least
One week from today
LEGO City Undercover the chase begins
On the 3DS
Oh that didn't come out in tandem with the DS?
Nope
The Wii U version? No it did not
Weird. Was it delayed?
I don't know
I don't think it was ever supposed to come out at the same time
Okay
Let us go on to Japanese
Release dates
And we will start with the
Playstation 3
On April the 18th Assassin's Creed
Revelations gets a special edition
I think that's just a price reduction
Naruto Ultimate Ninja Storm 3
Comes out though from Namco Bandai
Big release on the Playstation 3 this week
Going to the Xbox 360
Yes they do release Xbox 360 games in Japan
Naruto Ultimate Ninja Storm 3
Is also out this week
I should mention that Monster Hunter Frontier
G1 Premium Package
I think that's just kinda like again a best
hits repackaging type of thing
Next week in Japan though on the 360
Bioshock Infinite
How about on the Playstation Vita
This week on the Playstation Vita in Japan
Slaughter Mania 5
That's the best name ever
Zatai Shokugeki 2
Comes out this week
That's like Becky's brownies
Alrighty
On the Wii U this week in Japan
On the 3DS this week in Japan
A new mint cross
white color of 3DS
comes out this week. That's in the extra large
variety
Also a pack to celebrate the release of
Tomodachi Collection
Shin Sekkatsu comes out this week
As well as Osahara de Koei
Konuto Asobo
Machi Hen comes out this week
Is Tomodachi still a thing?
Yeah Tomodachi I was trying to see what this is
Tomodachi means friend
Tamagotchi are the little
egg babies
Little people
It's hanging out with friends the game
Pretty much
Hang out with friends with PictoChat
Wait a second
For people who don't want to go outside
Because it's a scary place
You know what I can get behind that
Lastly on the PSP
More releases on the PSP than anything else
Amnesia Crowd in regular
and limited edition
Getsui no Kusari, Sakura in Paranoia
Amnesia Crowd?
Is that like where they're like you know
Doing one of those
What do they call that?
I forgot
That's it
That is exactly what it is
That game where they do stuff
Also on the PSP this week
7th Dragon 2020-2
It's a little late but I remember now
It's like a flash mob but you don't know why you're there
Sorry I had to look behind me to see if I could find the joke
Jonsai Gakuen
Hold your hand up over your head
You might catch it when it sails past
Alright, you know what
You guys don't deserve any more Japanese
Japanese release dates
That's it
There's some stuff coming out in Europe
On the 18th of April
We have Pappo and Yo on PC
Which looks kind of interesting
And then stuff on April 19th
Fire Emblem Awakening and Injustice
Gods Among Us
And that's it
No more
You guys don't get any more games
It's kind of a slow time of year
Yeah
Alright, let's go for a few more stories
And then the classic game of the week
I bet y'all can't wait to see what she picked for this episode
You guys are going to be so surprised
Actually, I legitimately was
Loki, what did you pick tonight for news?
For news? Let's see
I picked
The UK government investigating
In-app purchases
Because they believe it's putting too much
Pressure on children to accidentally
Or maybe
Mislead them into
Purchasing smurf objects
Or stuff that they don't need
Basically saying
We're concerned that children and their parents
Could be subject to unfair pressure to purchase
When they're playing games they
Thought were free, but which actually
Run up a substantial cost
The OFT
Is not seeking to ban in-game purchases
But the games industry must ensure
That it's complying with
Relevant regulations so that children
Are protected. Think of the children
They're coming for you smurf village
La la la la la la spend my mom's credit card
Are we going to get smurf village 2 with the
Smurfs 2 movie coming out?
Smurfs village 2 electric boogaloo?
I hope not
If it was really combining those two movies
I might have to watch it
The Smurfs movie is
It's so bad
Katy Perry is one of the
I kind of wanted to watch it just because
Neil Patrick Harris is in it
Unfortunately did not
Want to see that movie
He can't see that movie
Now if Neil Patrick Harris
The character
From all of the wonderful
Harold and Kumar movies
Was in that movie
That might be something
Okay
I have to go on a little tangent here
Dan and I had a very interesting discussion
About the Smurfs
Yes my husband and I discussed the Smurfs
Through Fry's Electronics
He picked up a plushy smurf and said
That's a big smurf. He said actually this would be about how big a smurf really is
And then he started stacking
Like what the size of apples
Would have been because they're three apples high
And he was like how did nobody ever
Find the damn smurf village
If they came up to your shins?
So
End of story
Alrighty
That means there would be no plot ever
Because everyone would be
Well maybe they just
Lived in like remote Canada
Where nobody thought to look
People live in Canada
Not that far north
Yes they do
They lived in Nunavut
Alright
Nobody lives there
Breakman voted for Gargamel
I voted for Asriel because Gargamel was pretty stupid
To register participation
For this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio
At vognetwork.com
Use the passphrase
Pancake
Well would you vote for this?
I know a lot of people are very
They're purist when it comes to their Japanese voiceovers
But here's an interesting one
How much would you pay for Japanese voiceovers?
Square Enix
Is going to be selling a Japanese voiceover pack
For the Steam version of Tomb Raider
It's already available in Japan
Through the Western store
Here's the thing though
If you want to get the Japanese localization pack
It will cost $30
That's $30 DLC
That's on top of
What the game costs already
Now it should be noted
Japanese games do tend to be
A little bit higher in price
Anyway
The Japanese version of the game
Actually comes out on April 25th
That is the same day
As the voiceover pack
And it will retail for $80
This is typical for Japan
So in a way it's kind of like
Well the $50 you paid for it on Steam
Plus the $30 for the voiceover pack
Equals the $80 it would have cost you anyway
But there went your deal
The only reason I could remotely
Think of it being that high would be
Simply the cost of paying voice actors
Especially with
I mean
It ain't cheap
They'd have to
Basically decide what they've had to pay
The voice actors for
And then see what their overhead is for the recording
And then adjust the price
There's still I think pulling a big profit off of it
And I know people will buy it
Yeah there's a lot of people in chat going
What? What? Why? But then you have Zombie Princess
That gives us a little perspective here
At live.vaughnightware.com
Says I would pay that much for Japanese voices in Mass Effect
I would not
Because it was not ever dubbed in Japanese
But neither was Tomb Raider
No
However
Actually I do have to say that Mass Effect
In French sounds pretty fucking cool
I want to know
What her voice sounds like
Did they go the route where she's super chibi
Or did they pick like a deep male
Japanese voice for her
It's Japanese voice acting she probably sounds
Super kawaii
YYR in chat says
When was the last time a Japanese game was released here with subtitles
And the English dub cost an extra
$20
You know to import a game from Japan
Remember when we used to import
DDR and BeatMania and all that stuff
Well um
Shoot what was it
There was another game
Oh yeah Sonic Adventure
Remember when it came out on Dreamcast
It had the Japanese
You could choose the Japanese voice track with the English subtitles
Which because
I played through it the first time in Japanese
On my import
So I played through it again in Japanese
Because I was used to the voices
I think of a lot of fighting games nowadays
I want to say like Soul Calibur
The Street Fighter series you can choose language
You can choose between the two
But the amount of dialogue in Street Fighter versus
Tomb Raider
But it also changed the in game voice acting
To the Japanese voice actors
Which honestly
If I'm going to listen to Ryu I don't want him to sound like
He's a white boy
Break Man
Going back in time a little bit
Excuse me
Not going back in time
But Break Man going back to an earlier comment saying
I would pay that much for a Mass Effect nude code
But I'm a perv
You know what you can do that for free it's called text mod
Let me introduce you to the internet
It is your friend and there's lots of nudity on it
Actually I have
When I was putting in all those outfits
From my Shepard and everything
One of them is completely naked except there is absolutely no features on it
I'm sure that there's already a mod out there
For Tomb Raider
Again it's the internet
It's been done
Actdeft in our chat room says
Just a friendly reminder guys
It's optional
Reminding us that if you don't want to buy the $30 pack
You don't have to
But Black Wolf goes it's required
It exists therefore I must have it
There are consumer whores out there
And honestly
It's the same reason why people buy Dubbed Anime here
Even though I paid a little bit extra
For the subtitled versions
When they were on VHS
It's people
The average person would like
To watch something in their native language
It's more comfortable
For the average person to do
People don't want to read
At least that's America anyway
Well let's move on
To a simpler time
Let's travel back in time
They didn't have to worry about
Dubbing over
On different voice overs
Couldn't talk
I'm a little bit older than that
I see what you did there
Yeah I picked a video game
That was made in the 1940's
This is the legit
First video game that existed
I am going so classic
Like some of your parents weren't alive
So chew on that
And actually
If anyone ever remembers
When I used to write for a geek life
I wrote for my
Geeks in History
David Smith Jr.
Who basically is the guy that invented this
He was from Greenville, South Carolina
Born in 1910
And he actually
Filed a patent
For a game with
Estelle Ray Mann in 1948
That is a cathode ray tube
Game that uses radar displays
Used from World War II
And basically it's table tennis
You had adjusting difficulties
You would basically
Have paddles on either side
Very pong like
If you want to have something that is a frame of reference
But it would knock the ball
From one side to the other
Using the same type of light moves
On a radar screen
It had adjustable difficulties
He also had
A missile game
Using screen overlays
You could shoot at targets
It was sort of like
The Vectrex
But it used
Basically the CRT's electron gun
Kind of like an edge sketch
The same type of
Theory behind it
Now how long before somebody
Drew a penis?
Using the technology
45 seconds?
Rob, this was in the 40s
People were so repressed
Like I said
They made a cock overlay for it
And had
Becky said they didn't
Talk about it in public back then
They were polite company Rob
Rob, you're so dirty Rob
Sorry I'm trying to
I will call her later if you push me
I love your mom, your mom's awesome
Okay but no
I'm imagining they put a little
Penis shaped overlay on it
And had the little white ball shoot out of the top
Anyway
Basically it detected
The targets mechanically
And then
I'm just going to read this here
By connecting a cathode retube to an oscilloscope
And devising knobs that controlled
The angle and trajectory of the light
Traces displayed on the oscilloscope
They were able to invent a missile game that when
Using the overlays created the effect of firing
Missiles at various targets
So we're looking at the history
Of video gaming starting right there
I mean unless you want to talk about
Why can I never remember
Her name too
Lady that created the first programming language
Lord Byron's daughter
Why can't I remember her name?
Do you remember?
I don't remember her name
Lady Byron?
No
But I mean
She invented the first programming language
So we could just go back to her but
Still
Are you looking at
I'm trying to look it up
Ada Lovelace, thank you
Ada Lovelace
So yeah
This guy here pretty much
Without him screwing around
With radar screens
Would we have
Earth Defense Force
Just ask him
Alright
Thank you World War 2
For making video games
There it is your classic game of the week
Radar games
Radar Love
Is that what you're going to name it?
We should have played the song in the background
That's great
Let's see
Akuma JP linked this to me
And this was definitely worth playing
With the prior story
This is Tomb Raider Japanese voice acting
But I want to point out
This is the older Tomb Raider
This is not from the new game
It's a Sega Saturn Sony Playstation game
She's watching a computer there
Let me fast forward
To a loading screen
Good lord
That's the tutorial telling her how to play the damn game
This is not a great video
This represented the voice acting here
Let me go back
You know what forget it
It's lost its
I wanted the British accent
Thank you Royal Steel U.T.
It's a cathode ray tube amusement device
I'm still calling it Radar Love
I like Radar Love it's easier to remember
Alright
Let's take a break guys
We're going to take a break but when we come back
There is plenty more to come
We have some rapid fire news for you guys
And why not
We're going to play match game tonight
So stay tuned guys
Match game and more when we come back
With more of Orange Lounge Radio
Episode number 500
Hi there this is Blocko Jones
And you're participating with Orange Lounge Radio
The show where every gamer has a voice
And I want to use my voice to tell you
You should all play Ni No Kuni
Rob you should beat Ni No Kuni
Now that I said in the bumper you have to beat Ni No Kuni
Or you have to play this bumper forever
Never
Never I'll never beat it you know why
Because I have gamer ADD I never beat games
Welcome back everybody you're participating with Orange Lounge Radio
Episode number 500
In progress here
And if you want to send in a bumper
Like Blocko Jones did
And we have one other bumper that was
Sent in and I'll let you know who that
Was next week when we play it
That's quite an empty space there
We're looking for more bumpers
More information at the VoG network forums
VoGnetwork.com
If you want to send in a bumper for future use on the show
Because you know we do say it is the show where every
Gamer has a voice and we mean it
We want to hear from more of you guys and what you want to use your voice
To tell people here on the show
Alright
Moving on
You doing okay
I think it might be time for me to have one more shot
Should I do one more shot
Alright I'm going to go get one more shot
What would you use
Like I'm never going to discourage you from getting shit faced
What would you use your voice to tell people
What would I use my voice to tell people
I would use my voice to tell people to give me money
Because I'm broke and hire me
That's what
That's what I'm going to use my voice for
Jamie that hasn't worked for 500 episodes
And it's not going to work now
And I think you forgot the whole thing where
We're not trying to profit off the show
I just want a job
Listen to my voice
You want me to market your stuff
I can sell you anything
Rob would you sell anything
That I offered you to buy
I mean
Rob says yes
He's off the mic
Yes I would go directly to eBay and sell all that crap
Hey
Alright
Okay shot time
What's this cheers to
The
By the way these are double shots
To the air we breathe
The air from my lungs
Rob just shivered and made stink face
Awesome
It's fiery
It's flaming
Alright I got your email
And I am so sorry I didn't get a chance to reply
To a zombie princess
Is this personal chat time here on ORR
Hey it's money shut up
Alright
Moving on let's get to
Rapid fire news
And talk about what else is going on in the video game industry
Coming up the FUGL question of the week
Match game in this segment as well
We're going to get players for that soon
But first Loki
Alright so let's talk a little bit about
Ridge Racer
That's right Ridge Racer
Driftopia
Is a new game that they announced that they're going to be putting out
No it's not like your classic Ridge Racer
It's actually kind of an extension
Of Ridge Racer Unbounded
Which is done by Bugbear
And they're doing a new one
It's going to be a free to play game
So you're going to have
I guess the ability to buy cars, repair kits, and XP packs
Hopefully it's just not going to be crippled
By the free to play stuff
It's coming to PS3 and PC
Hurry
This is something I actually backed on
On Kickstarter, Road Redemption
It is a spiritual successor to
Road Rash, it's in 3D
And they're looking for $160,000
Over the next 30 days
And
As of right now I believe
They're not quite there
They are
Let's see
$34,000
Not bad, so I think they'll make it
And it looks kind of neat
It is not though done by anybody
And last but not least
Far Cry 3 Blood Dragon
It's fantastic
If you haven't watched the trailer yet
For the game
You should definitely check it out
They even have a fake 80's cartoon
That they made for the advertisement
For this game
Seriously, buy this game when it comes out in the first
It's out on Steam
And PS3 and
Xbox 360
Hopefully all around at the same time
They have, instead of loading screens
They have tracking screens
Like VHS tracking
It's awesome
So what does that mean?
It does the little fuzzy wuzzies
Like a tape that's been de-magnetized
It's all fuzzy and then there's the tracking
Thing going back and forth on the bottom
Can you adjust it?
No
And it's great that they have tool tips on there
For example, fast travel
Is like traveling
Fast
Or
Guns, or was it
Shooting enemies within range
Will cause them damage
I need this in my life
Alright
Let's get to
Some other stories here
This is interesting
Armature Studio was working on an unreleased
Mega Man first person shooter
Called Maverick Hunter
This is in a report from Polygon
Armature Studio is the Austin based developer
That was formed from Retro Studios originally
Yeah, it was a Mega Man X first person shooter
I don't know if that necessarily means
You know, like Mega Man Legends or all that
But I think this was supposed to be a little more
Like, you know, hardcore
Or something like that
Capcom did cancel the project
You know, cause Mega Man Universe and Mega Man Legends 3
All those went to hell, so why not this one as well
Armature did have a prototype in 2010
And it looks like there was a little screenshot
That leaked to the web as well
I watched it already
How'd it look? I didn't see the video
It gave me a lot of vibe
I don't know if it would have been this bad
But it gave me a lot of the
Bomberman
Act Zero vibe
Cause it didn't really look like Mega Man
He was firing, you know, like machine guns
And stuff like that
And, you know, just kind of fighting some generic
Looking robots and doing all sorts of weird
Take downs and stuff
It just didn't seem very much like Mega Man
It looked neat, but I don't know if it was necessarily
Mega Man
I don't know
I would have probably played it, but
He sort of resembled Mega Man
I mean, I can kind of see the look
But it was very Bomberman Act Zero-ish
Ubisoft
Has picked up German developer related
Designs
They made the Anno strategy series
Including Anno 1404
Which is Dawn's Discovery over here
Ubisoft previously held a 30% share
In the company, but they have purchased the other 70%
It is undisclosed for how much
That went for, but you can expect more
Strategy style games for Ubisoft in the near future
Unfortunately, Atari
Closed a studio this week
They closed Eden Games
Which was the mind behind Test Drive Unlimited
And Alone in the Dark
A long time ago
This is according to a report from Eurogamer
I can't believe they closed that
Studio after such a wonderful game
Like Alone in the Dark
I like the Test Drive games
The problem was
It wasn't Forza
It just wasn't
That same level
They had a charm of their own
To get away from the police, you drove in the grass
I can't get you, you've left a road
How am I going to get you now?
Damn you grass
And also, Lamborghinis make really awesome
Off-road vehicles
Twitch Game Guru in our chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com says
Atari still exists?
What have they put out lately?
Actually, they were supposed to be liquidating soon
Weren't they? Because all their properties
Are supposed to be up for sale
I don't know what happened to that
It's supposed to happen
Marble Madness up for sale
Somebody needs to pick up Marble Madness
That's an Xbox Live Arcade
PlayStation Network thing worth
Picking up for sure
They would have to do a lot to Marble Madness though
More stages than 6
And longer levels
And more challenges
Dark Soccer, what do you have for us?
I have some stuff and things
It would help if I was actually on the right window
On my stupid iPad
We have a new mobile game coming out soon
The Prince of Persia
The Shadow and the Flame
Is going to mobile on that
Fun date
That we like to refer to as
Soon
But soon
And it's
Being developed by
Ubisoft Pune
Ubisoft Pune?
What?
P-U-N-E
You say it
Who likes the Pune?
Come over to Ubisoft
You gave me this story
So you can give me shit
Get yourself the Pune
You gave me this story
Ubisoft and saved yourself from trying to
It's Rob's fault
Do not get in the way of me blaming Rob for shit
I will judge you
Ok
Dark Souls
Cause I know that there are a lot of people out there who like this game
It sold 2.3 million copies worldwide
And that was
From Software
That put this out
They actually had an event to announce this out
For the Japanese press
It sold 375,000 copies for PS3 in Japan
And 1.3 million internationally for PS3 and Xbox 360
So yay for Dark Souls fans
You know what I think they should do with that series?
They should get the guy that made
I want to be the guy
And have him help with level design
For that game cause that would be awesome
Just to fuck with the fans
And make it so hard
That would make people jump off buildings
Or into bullet trains
And that type of thing
It'd be like a rehash of the beginning of Suicide Club
And then last but not least
Oh ha ha
Remember that guy Adam Orth?
We were kind of giving him shit last week
Kinda
Well guess what? He quit
Either he quit or was fired
He's the one that said
Sorry I don't get the drama about having an always on console
Every device is always on
That's the world we live in
Hashtag deal with it
He decided to retire so he could get all the Pune
Well
Rob
I've been drinking leave me alone
Well someone actually went back and asked him
Did you learn nothing from Diablo 3 or SimCity
You know some people's internet goes out right
Deal with it is a shitty reason
And he replied electricity goes out too
That somebody worked for BioWare if I remember right
Manveer
Could that have just been friends
Giving each other shit cause I'm way
Way meaner to people on Twitter than that guy was
Well
I mean the person made another good point
You lived in Seattle, San Francisco, LA
Very connected places try living in
Jamesville, Wisconsin or Blacksburg, Virginia
And then he said why on earth
Would I live there
It's a fair question
I mean I'm sorry
But
Come on like you haven't said way worse shit
On the internet like you haven't said way worse shit
I'm completely innocent
Yeah but I've said shit about places I've actually lived
Look
I get it though this is just the day and age
That we live in is that you know
Whether or not you want to represent your company
When you are the creative director for Microsoft
There are people that are going to read way
Too much into your stuff
Like you know create a second account
That's anonymous or something like that
But like cause I mean if you're like
Working at Microsoft you don't go
I don't understand what the big deal is
You're the creative director for Microsoft
You don't go posting shit on the internet
Unless you hate your job
Do you think that he ever imagined
That the entirety of gaming
Online would read so
Much into his tweets
People on the internet don't think about consequence
Usually
I know right
No one put a gun to his head to tell him to be stupid
Yeah but some people are just stupid
Okay but by your guys definition
Is stupid I act stupid all the time
Yes you do Rob
I don't but I
Rather I like my job
And I wouldn't want to lose it due to my opinion
But I'm also smart enough to not talk about my industry
Well exactly and no matter how drunk
You might be right now Rob I've seen you far drunker
And even in
You've seen me at my most drunkest
And even in the depths of inebriation
I have never seen you said I'm gonna go post
About my work on Tumblr or Twitter
Me
Rob's never done that I have seen you kiss a girl
Which was very weird
Why are we bringing this up?
Because you were drunk
What does me kissing a girl
Have to do with an always online Xbox
It's less offensive than this guy
I love watching Rob turn red it's hilarious
He is literally like blowing
I almost want to put that into a poll question
What's more offensive Rob kissing a girl
Or that guy
So anyway
The guy actually
Apart from
Somehow or another losing
His means of employment
Which by the way I'm open for employment
Microsoft you can hire me
I don't go saying stupid shit on the internet just saying
Are you sure? Rob
500 episodes dark soccer
I don't say stupid shit about my job
Honey you've said a lot of stupid shit on this show
I have said a lot of stupid shit on this show
A real friend will tell you that
I love this show
I admit it
Anyway the dude actually locked
His Twitter and deleted
His linked in account
So yeah he's like
I'm going to hide now
Can you blame him?
I don't blame him he's kind of stupid
If freaking loltaku is going to be posting everything
That you tweet about then yeah
It's suddenly going to become a new headline
Then yeah I'd go into hiding too
And you all want to know why I don't use my real name
On this show because you know
I like my job
I just don't care
What about all this mess or what?
Everything
You don't care about everything
I just don't care I still didn't get
Other than the fact that his comments
Are a little insensitive to the fact that
Hey there are a lot of people
That are trying to figure out what this new
Xbox is going to be like and
The rumors that it's going to be online only
And then you come out and say well I don't see
The problem with that is I mean after all it sounds
Like a fucking wonderful thing
And then you start being insensitive to everybody
That people might be a little bit
Pissed off about that and you just don't
Understand why well
Come on can't you put yourself
In other people's shoes obviously not
Why would I want to live there?
Obviously they're not asking you to move to this
Fucking city they're talking about hey be
Empathetic
And by the way Rob just for the record I'm not offended
I was just like that's bizarre
Well it's Queen Simeon
Chat says well hey if some people become
Bicurious when inebriated
Look I just like to make out okay
I cook
What's wrong with that?
It's actually a true story I cook when I'm drunk
Who doesn't like enjoy a little kissy kissy
Every now and then come on
You guys were playing spin the bottle
And I was the only one sober because I had to drive
Which was boring
This was like ten years ago too
This was at the U.N. Loki apartment
That was a long time ago
I remember that
I think you were there
I remember you
Some of the things that happened when you weren't there Loki
I remember you like
Matrix walking up the
Or trying to matrix walk up the wall
That was fun
Remember the
DDR parties
People would
Inevitably end up like retardedly drunk
And then try to play DDR
And hit their head on the washing machine
That was behind the monitor
I don't know anything about that
La la la la
Let's see going to
The chat SSJ100 Matt talking about this guy
Says he got death threats the gaming community
Is sad that is stupid
That is stupid
The action
Needs to be taken against the people who are making
Death threats over a video
Game console
Priorities people
This is a problem though with the internet in general
Is that it has added this
Air of anonymity where people can just let the worst
Parts of their personality out
Without any sort of real consequence
Except unless you know how to track
IPs
And then you can message them back and tell them where they live
Alright is there anything else
You want to share with us for rapid fire
News that has gone on for 20 minutes?
I'm done
Let's get to the FUGL question of the week
And let's see how many of them I can make it through tonight
FUGL question of the week
Where's my FUGL song
I can sing
Becky can sing
She's a good singer
Facebook, Google
Put them together you get FUGL
And every week we ask a question
And we read some of the answers here on the show
There's a lot of answers tonight you guys
Who is your favorite character in a video game ever and why?
Easy right?
I thought you know it's a special episode
Let's keep it simple let's keep it positive
Do it
Alright so who's your favorite character in a video game and why?
Redertainment on Google Plus says
I like it whenever I'm able to play with myself
And we're done thank you everybody
It's been a great show I'll see you later
See you next week
Episode 501
Thanks for joining us tonight
That was clue worthy Rob
I like whenever I'm able to play with myself
I like playing with characters
That I can style to be like myself
Or an idealized version of myself
That's the unique thing about video games
Rare is the media platform
That allows yourself to project yourself
Into the media experience
Rare is the media platform
That not only allows you to
Right encourages you to play with yourself
I think I see what you're doing there Redertainment
And didn't he marry our own little angel?
Huh? Redertainment?
No it was not Redertainment
You're thinking of big red pimp
Different red
Sorry
Shane just messaged me other memories
Of things that happen in that apartment that are not
Appropriate for error
Send me a message
No I'm telling him to
Flaco Jones says I have to go with
GLaDOS
I've been drinking you guys
As if she wasn't already worthy of the title
After the first game
Portal 2 manages to give her even more depth
And a backstory as well
She also may be the most quotable character
In a video game history
More quotable than the old guy in Legend of Zelda?
It's dangerous to go alone
Kirby of course
Despite popular belief he doesn't suck
Evil says
Missing no
By a simple random encounter you get
Infinite rare candies and master
Balls for the cost of being disgraced
In the hall of fame
And Dasnichi replies
Solid snake
But are you still gonna feel that way
If it's not David Hayter?
That's my question
I need to not listen to
Any more of this while I'm having drinks
What, these lulls?
Ok so on Facebook we have
30 responses, should I read them all?
30 responses on Facebook
Grandpa says Mega Man
After he acquires the boss's skill powers
He's very versatile, I like my men
My men versatile
DarkSakura
replied but nobody cares
Tim P.
replied and said Commander Shepherd
He's the sexy space marine
I always wished I could be
He said he, a brochep fan
A brochep fan
There are no room for dude chefs in my head
Burr replied and said
Sonic the hedgehog
Too fast for the naked eye
Sonic the hedgehog, Sonic
He can really move, Sonic he's got an attitude
Sonic he's the fastest thing alive
Anyway to me as a kid that was the moment
When video games started to be cool
And not just goofy fun with ridiculous looking characters
I'll always have a soft spot for Sonic
as a series
Sil replied Garrus
First time I thought an alien was damn hot
I love you Sil
Dark Tetsuya said pantsless rage
Just kidding, in all seriousness I'd have to go
with Solid Snake
That was an old ass
That was an old joke
Gamergirl says
Sophie, later known as Protos Hyas
Ok this music
is starting to not do it for me
From Tails of Graces F
because she's odd
Red the Haze says
Renegade femshep
I've never had a favorite game character but
Renegade femshep comes to mind
You know what, I actually have to
kind of agree with that playing Renegade femshep
is pretty fun, except in some
situations then it's just bitchy
But I'm playing one right now with Ashley's face
It's really funny
James S. replied and said
There's a sorely underrated mid-90s
NX game called The Illusion
of Gaia, that game rules
I have this game
Good choice
The journey that young Will endures in hopes to find out
what became of his father who ventured off
before him ultimately changes the course of the
entire world
This game came out during a time when games of this art style
weren't just for children
The themes were adult and the story utterly breathtaking
The music alone gives me chills
It was part of a three part series
Soul Blazer was one of them
Oh god, I can't remember the first
other game in the series
There's one other game in the series
It's Soul Blazer Illusion of Gaia and there was another one
Dammit, well somebody in chat will remember
Yeah, somebody in chat do our
work for us
Andrew S. said
The Chesire Cat from American McGee
He's creepy and psychologically
sane and insane at the same time and always
cool and collected
Bobby Blackwolf says
Dot in Adventure, he was so brave
He was
He had to figure out how to get through that maze
Thank you
Rasteel UT, Terranigma, that was it
Oh, Prince Brightstar actually brought it up
first too, yes it was Terranigma was the other game
Shane replied and said
Another vote for Commander Shepard
but only if he's full on paragon
He sets the bar for what qualities
I'm looking for in a man, video game character
I mean
Gio Videa says
The Eye Tetromino
Everyone always wants the eye
Alright, I have to go with Dante from the Devil May Cry
series, a complete badass
also a bit of an asshole, you really get to see
Dante go from reckless teen
to equally reckless adult
Ronnie B says
Ico, he took me through a great journey
He went through a lot in the story and overall the game was really
original
Extover says Samus Aran and I don't need
to explain why
Well yes you do
The alternate universe extover thinks Nathan Drake
is his favorite based on ass physics
Also Matt, my boyfriend's
favorite is Yoshi
Wonder Dog Harold says
Leon S. Kennedy, he's so dreamy
Degenerate Johnny says
Kreia from Knights of the Old Republic 2
From being one your companions
at the beginning to becoming the ultimate
villain at the end, you'll find that she's one of the
most unique and best written characters you'll ever
meet in a video game
Emily C. replied and said
I love all cosmos in Katamari Dimash
He is so fun, flamboyant and makes me
laugh every time, that's a really good choice
Barbara O. says
Toss up between Cloud from Final Fantasy 7
and Balthier from Final Fantasy 12
We get to watch Cloud make a terrifying
discovery about himself and then fight his way
back from it. Balthier seems to be
only a dashing pirate, but he
slowly reveals both his trustworthiness
and his strong moral convictions
At least he's not talking about being a hero all the damn time
These are all really good answers
Wolf O'Donnell from Star Fox
because he can't let you do that
Wicked says
My favorite has to be Kratos, not because
of anything relatable, but due to his
utter ferocity and severe brutality
I had not seen in a video game character beforehand
It was almost like playing a villain, as cold-hearted
and brutal as he was
Kyrian G. says
Myak the Liar because his
dialogue is extremely entertaining
That or Luther, son of Scotia from
Lands of Lore 2, Guardians of Destiny
who provided many sound bites to my family
throughout the years
Edgar R. replies
There's nothing like roaming the post-apocalyptic world
beating up mini Power Rangers
and racing poison chihuahuas
Rob H. says
Guybrush Threepwood
He's a mighty pirate who can hold his breath for 10 minutes
and he also has a rubber chicken with a pulley
in the middle. How can you not like that?
There's a lot of unique answers
tonight. I like this. That's why I'm reading them all
because there's so many different ones
I feel equally about two characters
Samus Aran, she's awesome and badass
I fell in love with her in Super Metroid
My other all-time
fave is the adorable and amazing
Garrus. I wasn't too sure of him in Mass Effect
1, but by 2 they made his character so much
better. He's sweet, a bit of a dork,
but kind. J. Link
says Will from Illusion of Gaia
There's two people that said that
Go figure
People have good taste. I could relate at that age
when I played the game about being the outcast
change kid in class and having a clique
of dorky friends. It also didn't hurt
that the game story was amazing and I really
fell in love with it as my first real RPG
Dave Falcon says
Duke Nukem. Why? Hail to the
king, baby. Tiger Claw
says I'm gonna have to say Mario. Why?
Because he always gets the girl in the end
Marinko says
Knuckles the Echidna
I can never say that. No one
has better background music than that Red Demon
Pumpkin Hill, anyone?
Haseo Sumeruwagara says
To be honest, I'd have to say Oran from Final Fantasy
X, Travis Touchdown from No More
Heroes, and Big Boss from the Metal Gear
series. I loved
Big Boss in the very first game.
That was amazing. Lastly,
Slagkick says
Bayonetta. She's a fierce
witch who kicks major ass and has great
hair. Great hair. Fabulous.
You know what? I'm actually starting
that game next week. Good answers.
Bayonetta is freaking amazing.
Alright.
So, let's go around the table.
I'm curious what you guys all think. Dark
Sakura, I'll start with you as if this is gonna be a
shock. Favorite game character of all time?
The Guardian from
Guardian Legend.
Good pick. Why The Guardian?
Because Guardian Legend, first of all, is my favorite game.
And it was just
it was really neat when playing through the game
and then
having to pause the game and going, is that
a girl? That's a girl.
Yeah. And it was, you know,
an early NES game that had
a female protagonist. And yeah, we had Metroid
but you didn't find out that Samus
was female until you beat the
game or put in Justin Bailey.
You know, it was
a character that was
going around and kicking a lot of ass
in one of the most difficult
games I have ever played in my life.
And we all know how freaking hard that game
is. I don't have nearly half the skill I used to
have at that game. It's so amazing though.
I've beaten it. God, I wish that game
would come back somehow. I don't really want
like a remake necessarily, but just a spiritual
successor of sorts. Well, I'm still trying to
I'm debating putting an MSX emulator on
so I can play Gardic, the first one.
Yeah. Oh,
sorry, anything else? Well,
The Guardian Effect, yeah.
But
I also would have to, I mean,
as far as classic gaming, that
would be probably my favorite character.
Anything more modern,
I'm actually going to go with Bayonetta.
Yeah. Because, well,
I mean, I really would like to go with
my own Shepard, but I have my own
weird head canon. Then you're playing with yourself
like ready to chamber. Then I'm playing with myself.
And I can get dirty, especially the places my brain goes.
So, Hey all!
So, um,
I'm actually going to go with Bayonetta just because
it's totally fabulous. And I love
her character concept. I love the game.
It was completely over the top.
And I watched Dan play through it for a little while
because I didn't, you know, really do a lot
of console gaming after my surgery.
Except for playing Blue Dragon.
So, um, but I've got a lot more
endurance in my hand now thanks to practicing a lot.
So I'm going to sit down and try to play through
Bayonetta. So playing with yourself has gotten
your hand a lot of practice. No, I've been drawing!
Shut up! Alright.
Becky, do you have a favorite
that you'd want to mention?
Well, since the last time I
played video games before Jamie got
me hooked on Mass Effect was
on my parents, Commodore 64.
Good choice.
I think I would probably have to say
FemShep.
I like, I really like her
mostly paragon with just a little bit of bitchiness
here and there because it makes her feel human.
Very good. Very good answer.
You're in good company with some of our listeners tonight.
Loki?
One of my favorite characters
and unfortunately they better bring him
back for the goddamn fourth game because that was
a fucking mistake to kill him off.
Johnny Gap from the Saints
Row series. Fucking awesome
awesome character.
Of course, voiced by
Daniel Dae Kim.
From Lost and stuff.
Just awesome.
Really cool character.
That's probably it.
My favorite video game character
ever would probably be
Rydia from Final Fantasy IV.
That's a good choice. Because
just literally
watching her grow up through the game
and I have such an attachment to that story too
because that game was so epic and
that was really the first time most
people in America saw the summoner
and that was such a badass thing when she would come back
to your party and she had all those
summons and you'd go to her homeland and everything
and she used the whip which was cool and
had the black magic and
she was great.
Obviously she had to grow
up a lot faster in that story and
went through tragedy and overcame it.
But I have such an attachment
to Final Fantasy IV but Rydia was an
amazing character.
Where Dan in this room, he would
probably list Cain as one of his favorite characters
from the same.
Or Zero.
I want to know what Allen
would pick. Allen,
sorry to put you on the spot. I know you came in here
to get a snack but what's your favorite
video game character ever?
Robo and Luca together.
Twins. OTP.
Good choice.
Good choice. Alright, thank you guys for
participating with the Fugu Question of the Week. I know
that was a lot this week. I read every
single answer because you know what? It's a show where
every gamer has a voice. Why not? Let's get back
into some news. Loki.
Alright, so let's
talk about some more Xbox rumors
and hopefully, I don't
know, I hope that these are all rumors
so I don't know. This is kind of almost
like the whole online thing.
But once again, I
still am under the assumption
at least I guess hopeful assumption
that Microsoft isn't dumb enough
to have a console that's
online only. That would
be a major gaming console that's online only
and maybe some of this kind of ties into it
and it's this leaked
roadmap that's been
a new roadmap that they had.
Now, this is coming
from VG Leaks so
who knows? But basically saying that
there's going to be two
Xboxes the next time around.
There's going to be a mini Xbox that's going to
operate kind of like an
Apple TV. Basically, all the
video streaming stuff
maybe even like Xbox Live Arcade
that kind of thing. That
will be online only because it will not have
a disk drive. However,
the regular console will
not be online only.
That makes a little more sense
because an Apple TV
kind of operates the same way. It's not
necessarily online only but to get
all the functionality of it, you have to be connected.
You mean to use Netflix? I have to be online?
Shut the front door.
And they're saying
that basically the
whole
tying in with the TV is going to be
a big thing. Basically, they're saying the smaller
Xbox is to compete with the Apple TV
but also provides XBLA and
360 game support
which will give it an edge over the Apple
TV. Basically,
saying that the rumors of the online
only requirement
come from the smaller Xbox unit which may
not have a disk drive like Apple TV.
It would require
a network connection and internet
to provide any real functionality.
It may be possible they will design
both consoles to be stackable.
And
of course, the original
rumor was that Durango is not
going to be backwards compatible
which makes sense. It's a
different processor altogether.
The PS4 is not going to be
backwards compatible either.
Also, the Kinect, they're saying that
a different department within
Xbox handles the Kinect hardware and
software. The focus was more on developing
and networking both consoles
with Kinect more of an
afterthought at that point. It says concerning
dealing with it, it's less an issue than hardware changes.
The main console, Kinect, isn't the
primary focus. However,
development kits require several pieces
of hardware combined. All the potential
hardware which may or may not be
required to work with each other.
Which also includes the potential for any
devices to require a network
connection which is where that required
rumor comes from.
I'm thinking
I'm just hoping that it's not all
online only. This sounds a little bit more
Microsoft. Microsoft's
always been about streaming crap to your TV.
They have the whole Windows
XP Media Center edition and that kind of
shit.
I could see them wanting to be in
your living room and have this focus and
stuff.
I'm just hoping that they don't make the mistake of
having a console that's going to be a next gen
console that's only online.
After all, Microsoft's
live service hasn't been working very
well the last few days.
It's not a good idea to say
hey, we're going to be online only.
Ignore the fact that you couldn't connect
to live the last few days.
Let me ask this though,
because here we go again reporting
on rumors.
I'm not saying us specifically,
but I'm just talking the internet and the whole
hype machine. Why do we keep
reporting on rumors?
Because we don't have anything to go off of from
them. All we know is that they're going to
have
some sort of, the rumor is that
they're going to have some sort of
reveal at the end of May, but right now
we have no information about it other than what's
supposedly leaking out.
I think mainly discussing this, I'm not saying
this is all fact. I'm just saying here's the rumor
and I hope
it's a little bit more on this side
than it's always
online. There is no other
way about it.
I want to know how important talking
about Xbox rumors are. You know what it's
time for? I think it's time for us
to poll the listeners.
We're going to put up a live poll right
now at live.vognetwork.com
If you want to vote in the poll, make sure
you're logged in. live.vognetwork.com
How much weight
do you give to Xbox
rumors? It's Microsoft, it's
all true. I think a lot of it is
true, but I'm still quite skeptical.
I think it's mostly made up stuff for hits,
but once in a while the truth leaks.
Or the internet is full of lies
and slander, and I don't
believe any of it. Vote now
live.vognetwork.com
Our Instant Poll
We'll read the results
here in a moment, and try to
get some of the answers as they come in.
Alright.
And then one other thing also,
another rumor coming along with
some of the launch titles. Next-Gen
Forza game, Rise,
a couple weeks ago I've been talking about
Rise saying, where the fuck was that
gladiator game that showed that it was supposed to be a
Kinect title? So that
may be something that's going to be there. And then
some sort of, you know, kind of
Nintendo Land-esque Kinect
game. Although I
am seeing a lot of Kinect titles, two of those
being Kinect-required titles, so
ehhhhh
Not interested, but
Forza sounds cool. Forza Horizon.
Next-Gen Forza Horizon, I could be down with that.
Alright, right now in our Instant
Poll, very much, it's very tilted
towards the bullshit side of things.
67% of the vote for
I think it's mostly made up stuff for hits,
but once in a while the truth leaks.
21% saying the internet is full of
lies and slanders, I don't believe any of it.
So only 13%
of the vote at this point, I think the math doesn't add up because
it just updated, 13% of the vote
right now only slightly leans true.
Zero people saying
it's all true. Zero.
Rob, it's on the
internet, of course it's true. Well, some
people would think that. You know what,
honestly, I almost lean towards that top
option. With Microsoft, there's
very little that's fake anymore
it seems. But we'll see.
We'll leave that poll up for about another minute.
Again, live.vognetwork.com, live on this
Sunday evening if you want to vote in that poll.
I think we're all still UT has it wrong, instead of the internet
being 10% lies and 90% porn.
I think it's 10% lies,
10% hate,
and 80% porn.
YYR in our chatroom asking
where is the poll? It will show
up automatically at live.vognetwork.com
if you are logged
into the site. If you're not
logged into the site, it may not
show up for you.
This is a feature that's in beta
right now. Trademark.
So you can't talk about it to anybody.
Literally, this
was not tested.
We are testing it as the show goes on.
So, there you go.
Alright. You're all under NDA
you can't talk about it.
Alright, we'll do one more story and then I'll go to the results of that poll.
I'll shut it off and do that.
This is a story about Animal Crossing and I
can't flippin' believe this.
I know, right? That's the same sound I make.
Mr. Resetti
from Animal Crossing, optional
in New Leaf. What?
He is not there by
default and this is because of
QQ online.
Now, tell people
about Mr. Resetti for those that don't know Dark Star.
If you didn't save your game
and just turned off your
Animal Crossing, you turned off the system
where you had Animal Crossing loading.
When you started your game back up
this mole comes out of the ground
and yells at you
for ten minutes
in all capital huge letters
and from what
I understand, because I tried doing it on my Japanese
version, he's really freakin' rude.
And it was just absolutely
hilarious. He's like, what did you do in resetting
this form? Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And he freakin' chews you out.
This mole, bitter
crass,
grumpy old mole
digs his self out of the hole just to give
you shit for not saving your game.
This is not popular in our chat.
Gamegirl says, what? He's the best part
of the game. YYR says, it's blasphemy.
Gameguru says, Mr. Resetti
has been fired. No, he's not
fired. Let me clarify here.
In a column called Iwata
Asks, Resetti's
status was updated.
Apparently out of guilt
the developers made him optional
in Animal Crossing New Leaf because
apparently he brought some players to
tears. Good!
Save your game!
They also changed the goal of the
game from paying off Tom Nook
to improving the town as the mayor.
So Tom Nook is no longer your
pimp. YYR says, Mr.
Resetti is a critical feature of Animal Crossing.
It is required for the game to
work properly. He handles many of the game's calculations
so it's technically impossible to run Animal
Crossing without it. Strudels89
says, he was a dick, lol.
Loki's a dick, but we all
love him. We keep him around.
He's a vital part
of the show. We couldn't do calculations
without him. In fact, you know what?
You know what we used to do all the time?
Fucking time travel. Fuck that
Resetti. Hell yeah. I'm time traveling like
fucking Marty McFly.
I would travel to my birthday every
year just to get more shit.
Now in an article on Destructoid, I
really like this point about it, but in an article
published on Destructoid, they talked about how it was
one of the more creative fourth-wall
breaking moments in gaming history
along with Psycho Mantis reading
your save files on the Playstation card.
I see you like Final Fantasy.
Did he actually? He only called
that other Konami games, didn't he? No, I'm sorry.
He said Xenogears
and it was on there before
Xenogears. What am I saying? Are you thinking Castlevania?
No. Yeah, he said Symphony of the Night
because Dan and I had... Sweet Coden?
It was Sweet Coden. That was it because Sweet Coden
hadn't come out yet.
By the way, we tried that
with our Japanese save file for Castlevania
and it did not work.
But what do you guys think?
Is it a great fourth-wall breaking
moment? I think more games should break the fourth-wall
to be honest. I think so too, but it was pretty cool
watching the controller move on the floor
with Psycho Mantis.
Alright, that's going to bring our poll
to an end at live.vognetwork.com
So from the last story, here it is.
How much weight do you give to Xbox Rumors?
62% of the vote saying
I think it's mostly made up stuff for hits
but once in a while the truth leaks.
Hey, finally a vote.
3% of the vote for it's Microsoft.
It's all true.
Oh, poor naive child.
12% I think a lot of it is true
but I'm still quite skeptical.
22% the internet is full of lies
and slanders. I don't believe any of it.
Hasea Sumiragawa says a good point.
Deadpool will. I'm excited.
But Deadpool you expected of Deadpool.
You didn't quite expect that in Animal Crossing.
To have a character come out of the ground
and yell at you for 10 minutes.
Whereas, I mean didn't you
ever read Deadpool
in comics? It's supposed to happen.
Hi. You know what else people
weren't expecting?
Video game match game
coming back to OLR tonight. When was the last
time we did this? It was a long time ago wasn't it?
A while. It was a while.
But we are going to do video game match game tonight
but we need some contestants for video game
match game. So let's get
a listener in the chat room. Here's
how we're going to pick a listener from the chat room.
The first person to name
that wants to play match game. First person
to shout out in chat. What
were the potato chips
that Jamie got excited about when they
were set on the table earlier in the evening?
This is test your memory earlier in the show.
First person to remember and shout it out in chat
will get to play. And
we'll take the first caller right now
on the skype line 1877 game
OLR or a user name on skype
orange lounge radio. The first person
to get through will get to play
video game match game against
our chat room
listener who answers first which is
Mako Chan or Jovidea got the
right answer. There it is. Mako Chan.
Alright so let me open
up a chat window with Mako Chan.
Mako Chan from Makoto.
Oh my bad.
Well I keep thinking of the Mako from
Mass Effect.
You know what? I kept calling it Mako
because
I took too much Japanese.
And the answer was
Chicken and Waffles and JasonXV
after that. CodeMan
TimTRP
got it. It wasn't the cheese bread. I just said the cheese
bread was delicious. Alright let's see
who Mako Chan is going to be competing against
tonight. Let's go to the skype line right now. Hi you're on
Orange Lounge Radio. Who's this? Oh my god
I got in. You got in? Hi.
OMG! Who is this?
It's Raven's Dolphin. Raven's
Dolphin! You always come out
for the big landmark episodes. I always
love hearing from you. Oh my god I
have to. You guys. I know you
have to get to match game but I have to say
you guys are an inspiration to me and my
show. What I do. I look
at you guys. I'm like wow they keep going.
I keep going. But
it is absolutely a pleasure to be
with you tonight. I totally love
your icon by the way. It's gorgeous. Thank you
so much and you know flattery will get you
everywhere but it won't win you the match game.
You can come over and have murder brownies.
Would you like a murder brownie?
Yes just send it over the internet
please. I know you have to get to match game but I
have to know one question. Alright
fair enough. Alright
so you've been doing this show for 11 years
and was there
a time that you said
I don't know if I can go on?
Yes.
Alright.
That was episode 2.
Yes.
If I
followed through every time I
threatened to quit the show there would have been about
20 Orange Lounge radios by now but
you know you find your motivation
and you keep going and you know
a lot of the drama tends to work itself
out and you know drama is drama
and drama
was something I thrived a lot more on when I was
in my 20s and now that I'm in my 30s
it's like I don't know what else
I'd have if I didn't have O.L.R.
The sad reality is
the sad reality is
this show will end someday.
I mean it has to. Everything comes to an end.
But I like to think it's going to end because
you know. Murder.
It's not going to end in murder. It's going to end
because Dark Sakura
has to move for a great
dream job of hers or something or
you know low key. It had to be a hell of a dream job.
You know I'm just saying like it's going to
be something along those lines
or you know the honest.
It would have to be something that would dramatically change our
dynamic. Or that
you know we all sit down and we agree
you know what we don't have the passion
for this we once did. And I mentioned on a
previous episode I sometimes worry about
where the gaming industry is going when we talk about all this
always online and
the management thinking they know what's best
for gamers. I sometimes sit here and wonder
am I going to be a video game fan
in a few years.
But I like to think I would
and even if I fell out of
love with new consoles the
dynamic of the show would just shift again.
We didn't start as a video
game show.
Super Orange on Radio 2X.
I was there when you
were at 2Go and I found you on a
PSP website. Which
Loki still needs to update the freaking thing.
No it was on a different PSP website.
Oh really?
Yeah it was on like this called
PSP Drive and it was formatted for
PSP and you were on there
and I remember downloading it
before the other sites and all that stuff.
This was before Black Wolf and A1 and I went like
oh Orange on Radio I'll download this.
Oh VGN I'll download this.
Yeah I have to admit Loki got
on that PSP bandwagon really early
and a lot of the PSP community really
supported that older website. We were
on whatever the AOL blog was for
PSP before they all merged into Joystiq.
We were featured on there once and
that was really cool.
As much as we joke about the PSP and that
website and how out of date it is, that
community really embraced Loki's
little project so we really appreciate that.
Now it's
Stitcher and iTunes.
Yeah it's all about Stitcher and iTunes. Especially Stitcher
I think is really the wave of the future especially as
iTunes continues to
shove
podcasting under the table.
That's for another episode.
I do have to share this. Frisbee says when that happens convert
OLR to food and Disneyland talk.
So Jon's like episode 501
dull whips.
Ragenator in chat says I've been
a fan of gaming for 32 years. I don't see
myself losing my gaming passion.
You know and I think ultimately I tend to
agree. I may get really pissed off at some
of the decisions that happen in the gaming industry
but at the end of the day I could always come on
here and talk about Commodore 64.
Right.
I keep going. You keep going.
It's an inspiration. Of course.
Let's get to the match game.
All right.
Do you know how the match game works Ravenstaufen?
Oh my god do I know.
I mean too bad we don't even have Charles Nelson
Wiley or that guy from
from Family Feud.
Well you've got me. Awesome.
Richard Dawson. You've got me and
you've got on the panel tonight you've got
Techmaster Loki is here joining us on the
panel tonight. Hello. And Dark Soccer
is here. Hi. And I'm here
and Chef Becky is here.
Iron Chef Becky is here
with her murder brownies to play
with us. Hello. And Becky you're going to play with
us too right? Sure. Sure why not.
And then also joining us in studio
tonight say hello to
Hello Mother Dolly.
Wow.
Oh Alan you're the best.
Or excuse me is it is it little
Alan tonight? It's not little Edie
it's just Alan. Hello.
All right Alan is going to be joining us tonight. So here's how
it works for the listeners who may not know.
We're going to read some statements
and these statements will have a blank
at the end of them or near
the end of them. It's up to Ravens Dolphin
and Mako Chan playing along
in our chat room to guess what will
be said in that blank by
the hosts on the panel.
For every answer they get right
they will get a point.
But like whose line is it anyway the
points really don't matter. But we'll give our
winner a little something. Listen to a no prize.
All right. So here we go
and Mako Chan if you're sitting there
in our chat room be sure to
send your answers over
private message to me as I give
them to you. All right
so here we go. Here is question
number one tonight.
Bobby Blackwolf.
It's the first question
it's got to be about Bobby.
Bobby Blackwolf brought
on the ire of 4chan
this week by voicing his opinion
on Twitter.
He didn't really seem to care at
first but he really lost
it when they came for
his blank.
Ding.
Bobby Blackwolf
brought on the ire of 4chan
this week by voicing his opinion on Twitter.
He didn't really seem to care about
it at first but he really
lost it when they came for his blank.
Chatters you can help out
by voicing your answer in our chat room
live.vognetwork.com
You know I actually did
miss the whole 4chan
thing I don't even know
It wasn't really that serious
Bobby had an opinion
and some folks disagreed with it.
You know what 4chan is for? Rolling my eyes.
And porn.
Ding for me.
Becky you good? You got an answer?
She's thinking.
Peek over
Jamie show the iPad and get some help
from the chatters. You have an answer
Alan?
He really lost it when they came
for his blank.
Am I supposed to say something now?
No no not yet because we need Becky
to ding first.
She's
Oh Becky will do
great. Help her out Jamie. Feed her one of the
answers it'll be funny.
Does Becky not want to play?
Alright Becky doesn't want to play. Alright fine.
It'll be four of us.
It's because Becky hasn't met Bobby.
She can't say it the same way.
Well here we go anyway.
So Raven's
Wait let me make sure Mako got an answer in because I didn't even check.
I usually check for that first.
Here we go.
Raven's Dolphin
The question is Bobby Blackwolf
brought on the Ira 4chan this week by
voicing his opinion on Twitter. He didn't really seem
to care at first but he really lost it when they
came for his
Ban hammer. His ban hammer.
Good answer good
answer. It's the only thing I could
come up with. Makochan in chat says
when they came for his
Anon membership card
I did not know Bobby was in
Anon but apparently he was. Alright
let's go around and see if we've got any match.
Ban hammer or Anon membership card.
Loki what did you get when they came for his
Fence. When they came for his
Fence. Not a match
if you've been following the recent drama online.
No when they came for his Fence.
Dark Sakura
when they came for his Fence.
When they came for his Fence.
That's two for Fence. He really lost it
when they came for his. Those damn kids
and his Fence. Allen what did you say
when they came for his.
Anti-brony propaganda.
Oh damn it. Not a match.
Not a match alright. And I said they
that he really lost it when they came for
his Clicky pen.
Clicky.
Clicky pen. I thought it was Clicky the pen.
Also not a match.
But it's a Clicky pen.
Alright. The score
let's look at the leaderboard right now.
Zero to zero.
Alrighty. Zero to zero.
Alright that's alright Ravensdorf and you
can make it all up on question number two out of four
tonight. Alright here we go.
Question number two.
Question number two
is the cast
of Orange Lounge Radio
was really appreciative
that Becky baked brownies for their
500th episode.
You know what would top this for our
666th show though
said Rob. Loki
piped up and said yeah
you should cook the blank.
Ding.
Becky baked brownies
you know what would top
this for our 666th show
though said Rob.
Loki piped up and said yeah
you should cook the blank.
Alright.
Ding.
Loki said ding. Dark soccer ding.
Alan ding. Alright ding.
Alright and
Mako's in as well. Raven you got an
answer? I do. Alright
here we go. Loki piped up and said yeah
you should cook the
ferret. Cook the ferret.
And Mako
Chan in chat said you
should cook the ferret.
Oh
boy alright well
let's see what happens. It's
going to be a tie either way but let's see how many
points this may or may not earn them.
Loki yeah what did you say
yeah she should cook the
bacon el diablo. Bacon
el diablo.
Great answer
but not a match.
Alright. Dark
soccer. I did go for obvious
and say the ferret. The ferret did. Oh my
god. It's a
score on the match game leaderboard.
One to one.
Ding ding ding ding.
More points than people usually get during this.
Alright excellent. Uh
Alan
she should cook the
I think this still counts but my answer
was the bungee ferret. The
bungee ferret. Let's go to the judges.
Alright the judges will allow it.
Two to two for the ferret.
Alright and lastly my answer
she should cook the
Cylon occupied
caprica cake.
The Cylon
occupied caprica cake. Old
old joke. Alright there
it is. Two
two though. That
could be the highest score ever in the history of
video game matches. I think our highest score was three
to be honest. Was it? I think it was
three. There is still two questions
to go. Here we go. There are two
questions. There are two questions. Watch your
grammar drunkie.
Shut up. Alright
here we go. Oh it's a question about
Jamie. Here we go. Question. You ready
Ravenstaufen? You ready for it? I'm ready.
I'm ready. Jamie decided
to mark the occasion
of the 500th episode
to give up coffee forever.
Lies. This is
make believe. I know. Jamie decided
to mark the occasion of the 500th episode to give
up coffee forever. She came
to episode 501
and in a coffee deprived rage
instantly screamed into
the mic. First one
to mention blank dies.
She came to episode
501 and in a
coffee deprived rage
instantly screamed into the mic.
First one to mention
blank dies.
I didn't think
of an answer for this one.
You wrote it. I know right.
First
one to mention
um
ding.
Ding.
Alan?
Ding. Alright here we go.
Raven you got an answer? I do.
Alright here we go. She gave up
coffee on episode 500. She came to
episode 501 and in a coffee
depraved rage instantly screamed
into the mic. First one to mention
double shot mochaccino.
Double shot mochaccino
dies. That sounds amazing.
I want one. Mako
Chan in our chat room says first one
to mention male chef
dies. I was thinking about
Alright here we go. Let's go around the room
and see what
we got. If we got any matches.
First one to mention Loki?
I almost said male chef
but I said Propel instead. Propel
first one to mention Propel
dies.
Do they even make Propel anymore?
Yes they do. Wow alright awesome.
It's called like Propel Zero now or some shit.
Alright Dark Sakura first one to
mention. Bro chef.
Bro chef? Really?
Oh my god.
Alright I think we're gonna count it. I honestly couldn't think
of anything else. Mako Chan pulls
ahead three to two.
Alright Alan
first one to mention
Mocha Pinkberry.
Oh my god. Why does this not
exist? That was really close
to what Raven said but
I don't think it's close enough unfortunately. Why does this not
exist? I don't know. You should
write Pinkberry.
Alright and my answer was
first one to mention. Why not?
First
one to mention
Final Fantasy 11 dies.
Alright
not a match but one more
question. One more question. So close.
So close. Ravenstaufen you can do it.
I know. I have faith in you.
I have faith in you. I know. Alright.
But what about the chatter?
Alright here we go.
Question number four
the last one Ravenstaufen your only
hope. Alright.
Loki was very happy with the
poster that Codeman drew
to celebrate episode 500 of the show.
Upon careful
examination of the poster though
he exclaimed Rob I'm
surprised he drew you as a World
of Warcraft fan and not
as a fan of blank.
Rob I'm surprised he
drew you as a World of Warcraft fan
and not as a fan of blank.
Oh that was
really quick on all the hosts.
I'm still waiting on MakoChan to
ping in there in our chat
room at live.vognetware.com where some
people are going to feed the answers right now.
Loki very happy with the poster that
Codeman drew but
on careful examination of the poster
exclaimed Rob I'm surprised he didn't just draw you
as a fan of blank. Alright
MakoChan's got an answer. Ravenstaufen
you about good to go? Yeah
I got one. Alright then here we go.
Rob I'm surprised he drew
you as a World of Warcraft fan
and not as a fan of
DDR 4th mix.
Good answer. I was a fan of
DDR 4. 4th plus to be
specific but we'd let that slide.
MakoChan in our chat room says
I'm surprised he drew you as a World of Warcraft
fan and not as a fan of
Rocky Horror.
Okay good good
answer. Alright let's go around and see if
there's a match. Loki
surprised he drew you as a World of Warcraft
fan and not as a fan of
Ni No Kuni's ending. Ni No Kuni's ending.
Wait a minute.
Alright.
Not a match I'm sorry
to say. DarkSakura
I'm surprised he drew you as a World of
Warcraft fan and not as a fan of
Para Para Paradise complete and kogal outfit.
What?
You'd be such a cute
get it. You almost named the right
Bamani game to match with
Raven's Dolphin but unfortunately
nope not gonna do it.
And I'll tell you what came with this is watching you play the damn
Abba game.
Alright.
I'm surprised he drew you as a World
of Warcraft fan and not as a fan
of Miss Nude World 96.
Miss Nude World
96.
Oh classic
classic answer.
Rob I'm surprised he
drew you as a World of Warcraft fan and not as a fan of
Hey I can be self
deprecating here. My answer was
not as a fan of
surprise butt sex.
Goodnight ladies and gentlemen.
Oh shoot I apparently
gave Codeman an idea. Uh oh.
What did you do? I have no
idea but I'm looking forward to it.
Alright.
Apparently Alan wins.
Alright apparently Alan won. Alright
looking at the scoreboard it is
3 to 2 Raven's
Dolphin I'm sorry but you're a big fat
loser tonight. I know.
But thank you for playing. You lose
good day sir.
Goodnight. We still love you. Alright
thank you for playing Raven's Dolphin enjoy
your nothing.
Laughter.
Rob you need to drink more often.
That's it you have
a requisite two
double shots. I'm actually
under straight orders from my doctor not
to drink and I'm being a
very naughty boy tonight but
what can you do? Should we get out the paddle?
No I did a second shot.
Laughter.
Alright and they're double shots but
hey who cares.
They only live once right Rob?
Alright thank you for playing along with match
game tonight everybody we hope you had fun.
Alright
Megachan what do we give
Megachan for winning tonight? My love.
Megachan if you have
something you want to plug I have a feeling I know
what it might be but send me a private message
and you can get a free plug for your Twitter
for your podcast whatever you want.
But not a butt plug. No definitely
not that. Alright
let's see moving on it's
time for the mailbag. Ah crap.
Dark soccer is always
excited to get into the mailbag and read some emails
that you guys send to mailbag
at orange lounge radio
dot com. So dark
soccer if you wouldn't mind jumping
to the emailbag there. We did get a lot
of spam like that arrived after
the real email. Oh hooray. I deleted
well I didn't delete it but we need to delete
a lot of old email.
Are we ready? Shall I do this?
Yep yep. Hey O-L-R
just thought I'd write in and respond
to that email about the graphic violence
of Bioshock Infinite. Ooh.
Not spoiling any major
plot points here but Booker's history
is full of violence. It's actually a
major part of his character that he has done many
terrible things in the past and has
a very violent history.
Whenever you perform one of those brutal finishing
moves with your sky hook Elizabeth will always
audibly shudder at the act.
As you get deeper in the game Elizabeth
questions the need for so much violence from both
sides of the conflict and wonders if it's really
helping anybody. And that way
I think it's the approach to graphic violence is
done in a way that serves the story and the
characters. Now there is
some gratuitous stuff in there but I'm a little tired
of the comparisons to Call of Duty or
that these were changes that made to
these were changes
these changes were made to appeal to that
audience. I played a couple of
Call of Duty games and the violence
though not the plot always seemed to ride
closer to the side of realistic and not hyper
real as it is in the Bioshock games
including Infinite where you can electrocute someone
to stun them then blast their entire head off.
Dude I need to play that.
You can do that in Bioshock Infinite
As we saw in Bioshock Infinite
Yes, it's awesome.
In the Call of Duty games
we rest our case
In the Call of Duty games I played I don't remember
any heads popping off like quarks
but I did only play single player mode so
who knows. My point is Bioshock
games have always been violent
and they've always been first person shooters
so I don't think the game had to compromise
anything for sales or to appeal to a certain crowd
and in fact would only have been
compromising if it toned itself down.
That was all that was on my mind
congrats on an amazing 500
episodes even if you
guys don't think it's such a big deal anymore
it actually really
is. I'm just glad I've
been listening for the last 200 or so
that's from Flaco Jones.
We don't care if you've been listening since episode 1
or if this is your very first episode
we say welcome aboard and thanks for being a part of the
family. Yeah, you're totally awesome.
So
moving on
Hi guys!
First and foremost congratulations on your
500th episode. I think it's
amazing that you've been going for over
10 years. You have an unshakable love
of video games and a cast iron army
of dedicated fans
to...dude you guys made a cast iron? I didn't know that.
Okay.
So here's something.
I think he's frying you.
Will you fry us an egg?
I bet you get really hot on
warm days. So here's something
that may interest you. Do you remember me talking
about Project Possum a while
ago? When the Inside
Xbox UK team were given the
sack, they went off on Kickstarter
to start their own show about video games.
Well, they finished the pilot and that's not what you
call your average video game show.
It's called Thank You For Playing
and you can find it at ThankYouForPlaying.com
there are dashes in between each word.
It's structured much like a game
letting you view the features in order
that you want and has unlockables in the form of extra
goodies and editorials, expanding
on the themes touched in the videos.
The plot's all about multiplayer
and I really recommend you take a look.
I thought it was really interesting and
hope to see a lot more from them soon.
Just like I hope to keep hearing from you guys
for many years to come, take care and once again
congratulations, Picaruno.
Thank you
for your support.
And remember, if you can't be an athlete, be an
athletic supporter.
I'm sorry, this is my favorite line from Greece.
Okay, this is an OLR PSA
from CatastrophicMoggie.
Oh, it's my friend Moggie who I chat with
every day on Steam. Come on guys,
I think after 500 episodes we can give the whole
Loki in a tingle costume thing a rest.
He might like that.
Instead for the next
500 we need to get Loki
in a kitty costume.
A kitty costume?
And you have to say
meow, that's right.
It has to be a kitty in costume.
I don't think he'd do that.
That's worse than tingle.
He sent an image to you but it didn't embed.
P.S. I would have
left an audio message but Rob is a meanie.
Even if I stayed up late enough
I wouldn't be able to Skype after the disaster
that was last time. So I guess you don't
get any congratulations from Moggie.
Send an MP3.
Dude, you talked to me on Steam.
Just attach me a file or something.
Excuse me.
Is that it or is there more?
No, there's one more.
I had an oddly mimosa red velvet brownie flavored burp.
Imagine that.
Alright, here's the last one.
Hello is the one and only
often imitated, never duplicated DDR dollar bill.
I just wanted to write and congratulate you guys
on your 500th episode.
To the last 500 episodes is something truly
of an accomplishment. Not just for the fact
that most podcasts end in a few years
but that the show keeps the same
basic formula without getting stale.
That you also survived in a market where some
have turned to sponsors and subscription fees
to even make a presence
is even more of a reason to celebrate.
Well, thank you.
I'm all broke.
Not everyone can podcast.
True, we all wish to be heard but it takes something
special to keep going for a long time
and not just make it into a small hobby that you grow
out of. It's a labor of love, one that
the O.L. Army slash family
have grown to be a part of, whether they
hang around, come back once in a while
when they can, or just move on.
If I could, I'd just like to take a moment
to say why I do recommend your show to other listeners.
One, the host.
Why, thank you. Every show you have
three amazing, entertaining, intelligent, yet human
hosts who talk about gaming
that can appeal to the hardcore fans as well as
the casuals. Just to let you know I'm really from another planet
once a month.
They are
people who actually do game as part of
their lives, not game because it's their
job to. We talk about gaming like
fans who talk about sports or comics or
sci-fi with that casual yet knowledgeable
flair. And when they speak about
gaming news, they do it on a dual level of
professionalism that gives a great analysis
and yet keeps it simple and fun.
Can I say something really
quick about the sponsor thing? Because we have
a lot of friend podcasters that do
the sponsor thing and we've even, you know,
we have had donations before in the past
and so forth and I just want to say, like, there's
nothing wrong with podcasters who want to get
sponsors because, contrary to popular belief,
this shit ain't free for us to do.
True. It is costing us money
to do, but that's, you know, it's okay.
We pay the money because
it's our hobby. It's like, you know,
it's like the tax you pay to
your club, you know,
your dues or whatever.
For us, that's fine.
And, you know, I have no problem with people that
want to get sponsors to offset the cost of
hosting, offset the cost of, you know,
producing the show
and so forth. But I do start to
get into a problem when, you know,
and I can think of particular
individual podcast things that have
gone up saying, we need
$30,000 to do this
podcast, this one
podcast because we're going to rent a studio
and we have to travel to conventions
and this and this and this. And
I'm sorry, but like,
you know, if they can get it and the listeners
support them enough, that's
great, I guess. But I'm
just kind of like, you ain't fooling
anybody. I could tell you how much it costs to
do a podcast and it's not as much as
you're telling people it is.
I mean, we've had
generous donations in the past. I mean,
like what Kristen did.
I mean, we would not have
new equipment if not for her.
But I just want to be clear because I have very
several peer podcasters that do
raise money through sponsors
and so forth.
We've got the ads on the site. We have been super
effing lucky that our website
has been donated very generously
for many years or
else we would probably have to turn to that
too because that could get very expensive.
So, I just, you know,
I just want to clear the air and make
sure that's understood.
So, and I've
sat up for, I mean,
just on my own hours working on
graphics and stuff
for, not just for Orange Nails, but
for VOG in general, you know.
We've all put a lot of time and effort into this.
Uh, DDR dollar bill in chat says
I think the best way to put it is
people don't like to be shilled.
And I agree with that. And I would not do that to
the audience. You guys are far too intelligent for me
to sit here and say, please send me to all these
exotic places so I can
talk about them with you. You know,
like, I'm not, I'm not
going to do that. You guys are... And we're not doing ads for the
man-grate. Yeah.
I'm sorry, I have, you know,
my overwhelming love
for, uh, Greg Proops.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. But I do laugh every time he does
the ad for the man-grate. Anyhow, I apologize to interrupt
the email. Okay. To the show.
This show, while keeping the basic format,
always finds a way to grow and yet
never loses its focus. Yes, they go off on
tangents and just Pinkberry trips to Disneyland.
Let's go get Pinkberry. Okay. Trips to Disneyland
and other aspects of their
daily lives. But I find that to be the greatest
asset because you, the listener, participate in
the show in any fashion. It's so laid back
and friendly that you do not feel they are
corporate shills. If you are right
or wrong, you can discuss this openly.
And even when it gets heated, it's still
more personal than some shows where the sense
of keeping it professional loses that intimacy
that's required for some difficult and passionate
topics. Also,
each segment does include something for the listener,
whether it's mailbag to submit your letters,
and I actually do enjoy reading the email.
I'll just throw on a hissy fit
just for fun. Um, Skyplines
to call in even when
even if just wish
to get on and say, what's up?
The classic game of the week, my favorite part,
why, thank you. We used to do the
website of the week.
There was website of the week and the advice,
Star Soccer's advice column.
I could still give advice.
Um, uh,
like, uh,
I don't know.
Pay your hoes or you might get cut.
There's
Star Soccer's advice.
Was it never bet with a Sicilian when death is
on the line?
Finish the email. Okay.
Fugal question of the week.
It's always welcoming listener input, which
leads into
dot, dot, dot, dot, the audience.
That was number three. The chatroom is
full of people who often come up with amazing
nuggets of joy. It's rarely
censored, meaning you'd really have to be
a dick to have the mighty ban hammer cast upon
yourself. But like, um,
but like a good wrestling federation,
the show wouldn't be much without the loyal fans
who have helped keep the
energy going. Friendly and
often hilarious, they are never ignored
by the host. I'm sorry if this
went on a bit more, but it was just something to
note. Here's to another 500 episodes.
I wonder how the future of gaming would look in another
11 years. Tune in and find out. Wink.
Oh, that was
sweet. That was a very nice email. I'm gonna do
a quick sweep. That
was it. I agree. The audience is
the best part.
We love you guys. For dinner.
Speaking of which.
No, seriously. And Black Wolf and chat
actually follows up with
that. I don't think we have anybody banned.
I don't think we've
had to ban anybody yet.
That's not a request or
a contest. No, no. Don't challenge
this. Bammers.
I've kicked people out of chat
for being dicks. Well, but we haven't
banned anybody. Most people
learn their lesson. Yeah.
I've smacked a few people around with a giant trout.
Anyhow. Speaking
of audience. Mako Chan has
her plug ready to go that
she won for Match Game. Do I even
have to mention this? I somehow knew it would
be this. Anime Jam session
on Tuesdays here at the Voice of Geeks Network.
9.30 PM Eastern is when the pre-show
starts at 9.15.
Excuse me, it's the pre-show at 9.15. 9.30 is the
show. Mako Chan gets to
choose the pre-show music this week. Oh
shit. And happy 500th.
Yes, listen to Anime Jam session. It's a good time.
Totally a good time.
So, alrighty.
Let's see.
Is that it for emails?
We're done, huh? You want to know something? I've actually
started getting back into
watching some old school series now. Oh yeah?
Because Dan's little brother
Mason, who is a teenager.
He was posting on Facebook
Oh, teenagers.
I'm bored and I don't know any
I was like, go back and watch some classic anime, dude.
Get to the roots of it.
You know, go watch some Yamato
or some Gachamon.
Alright. Go 80s style and watch
Bubblegum Crisis.
Let's do the FUs of the Week.
And Minecraft Server.
FUs of the Week time.
Here is punishment.
Here.
This is fucked up.
Yeah, we did
ban the song on the show.
And we banned a website. We banned
Politary. DarkSakura, your FU, please.
My FU goes to
the hoe bag who was driving behind me
in the Mercedes, trying to do her
makeup while tailgating me.
It would have been incredibly
hilarious if I had brake checked you
and you completely ruined the back end of my car
so that I get a new car and
you have to pay for it. Just saying.
Don't do your makeup while you drive
and get off your damn phone and pull up your pants.
Loki, any FUs? Get off my lawn.
I guess an FU to the driver that I encountered
last week when I was leaving the show
about to enter onto the freeway
when I had a guy pass
me on the right in the
in the meat, like actually off the
road, pass me on the right and then
cut across into the next lane
to not go on the
freeway. I don't even know why he was doing that.
It's just stupid. He could have just gone to the
left and changed lanes.
But no, he had to pass me at the same time too.
For no reason.
And then, what else? Oh.
And to my co-workers for not wanting to play
games during lunch because they're, you know,
they will flake on me unless
we get all four people to play, including
myself. And a lot of times we can't do
that because, you know, my boss will be
gone or something and they don't
want to play games with just me because I kick their ass.
So they need to...
But you're so humble about it. So FU'd at being good?
Yeah, I'm just too good
for them, unfortunately.
Um, my FU of the week
goes to car repairs
and the bills that go with them.
Oh my god, robbery!
So much money!
And everything breaks at once!
Not okay.
We all gave FU to traffic-related things.
How appropriate for our 500th episode.
We always freaking complain about
drivers. The hell.
You want to throw out a nephew to cars, too,
while you're at it?
You can throw out a nephew to Power Rangers.
Oh god, yes.
Shane might take issue to this.
FU to Power Rangers
Megaforce, which my son wants to
watch constantly and my brains
are dribbling at my ears.
It is horrifying. The acting
makes me want to strangle my own brain.
By the way, Megaforce is
playing a brand new 3DS game
coming this year.
Aw, Shane will be offended by that
and that makes me happy.
I do still want to watch the
Japanese version because I do like the Sentai series.
Shane and Chad's like,
why FU to Power Rangers?
Because she's a mom
and little boys watch
Power Rangers, Shane, not 30-year-olds.
But Shane said that Megaforce is pretty bad.
Oh god,
I wish I was still a 30-year-old.
So if
the Power Rangers fan of Chad
is saying it's bad,
then you are fully justified.
All kidding aside,
we've got a couple more stories for you guys quickly
and then we're going to go to the Skype line
at 1-877-GAME-OLR
There might be a few of you that want to call in tonight
so we'll get to that shortly,
but first a couple quick stories.
Alright, so Nintendo
totally figuring out ways to revitalize the Wii U.
Not sure if this is going to be one of those ways,
but they have a new patent.
A patent that allows them
to use the Wii remote
to remotely control mobile devices
like a robot.
That's what they have in the picture.
They have a robot with a Wii
remote in it.
Rob 2.0?
Or as the joke I made on Facebook,
Rob U?
And it will.
What the hell would a Rob 2.0 do?
The first Rob was a really
niche, stupid thing.
It just played Gyromite, right?
There was one other. Stack'em?
It would run up to people
that are playing the Wii games
not standing up,
because you're supposed to be active,
and punch you in the balls.
Get off your couch. Boom!
I need one of those
to motivate me to exercise more.
Can I get a Rob U to punch me in the balls
when I'm not, you know, exercising?
Perhaps.
Wouldn't that be awesome?
Well, speaking of Nintendo devices,
the must-have, most important
application on the 3DS has
been updated. That's right.
SwapNote has a new version
that's available now. You can go get that
right there in the little eShop.
Get the free update, and there's a note
that you should have got reminding you of that.
I've added some new OLR listeners recently,
and I gotta say, it's like a SwapNote resurgence.
My little blue light is on almost every day.
It's great. Some of the new features.
You can now use a
different color on each page of a message,
so you don't just have to use black anymore.
You can do photos
and audio while you write.
You don't have to import them from the SD card.
You can filter notes by who
sent them if you want to find a note from somebody.
You can delete multiple notes at once.
You can
see how many replies
a note has received, and you can
slide the CirclePad left to
slow down writing and drawing animations
from notes, or use
CirclePad right to speed it up.
It's like a speed up, slow down.
Very cool.
Basically trying to modernize SwapNote
a little bit with some functionality
that you kind of go, wow, that wasn't there before.
Nope.
But it's there now.
All right. That brings us to the Skype line.
1877 Game OLR.
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
If you want to give us a call on this,
our 500th episode to talk about whatever,
we will take a few calls until
we decide it's time to end the show or the calls stop
coming in.
Well, there's a whole
other plate, huh?
Oh, boy. All right. So,
we are going to take the calls right now.
I'm also going to bring up Twitter topics.
I don't know, Loki, if you have any last minute stories over there.
Not yet.
Power Rangers Megaforce game,
that's all I had.
Oh, you were trying to incorporate things.
All right. Well, lucky for us, we're getting saved
with a phone call. So, let's get to it.
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
This is CodeMan.
CodeMan, what is up?
What's up, man?
We are loving these posters you made, just so you know.
Well, no problem, man.
I hope I captured
OrangeLoungeRadio as much as I could.
Uh, yeah.
I have to ask, is the little kitten on the bottom,
is that Midna?
It could be Midna, or it could be Shirmi.
I wanted to kind of
go both ways
because, you know, Shirmi was a big
part of OrangeLoungeRadio, and
we all, as all listeners,
miss
her as much as
we can, you know.
She was a huge part of
OrangeLoungeRadio. And she was huge.
It's an every cat.
Yeah, it's an every cat.
I was going to say, because it looks kind of like Midna.
Do you have a JPEG that you can forward me
of this? Well, I think Dark Sakura,
do we talk about the album art thing?
Yeah. Is that going to happen?
Awesome!
Good, the listeners can know what we're talking about because
it's going to be the new album art to the show, and it's fantastic!
And I thank you
for, I got your message from Dropbox.
Thank you, I will be printing out a copy for my wall.
Yes, and you can, um,
you can actually, if, if, uh,
Loki wants a JPEG,
you can probably just, uh, you know, switch
that over to a JPEG and then just send it to him.
Or whatever, it doesn't matter. Is it, like, just the full 300
DPI PSD?
Yeah, it's, well, no, it's a PDF.
It's 18 by 24.
You can open it up in Illustrator,
because I did it all in Illustrator.
Um, and you should be able to just
export it as a JPEG.
Alright, you nerds,
I want to talk about video games.
I'm actually going to resize it for the frame I have.
Alright. Well, Codeman,
uh, what did you, what did you actually call in to talk about tonight?
I wanted to just call in and
congratulate you guys on 500 shows,
basically. I, I, I
started listening, um, kind of
at the end of my high school,
uh, my senior year of high school,
all the way through college, up
until now. And so that, that
Christ, how old are you now?
I am 27. I'll be 28 in,
uh, September, so. Oh my god!
You know, you
realize I'm going to be 37 on
next Friday, right?
I'm just, I'm just, I,
you know, and, and like I said in the chat room
earlier, um, I said if this show ever dies,
a piece of my heart will die.
Because this show has
been like, I think a lot of the listeners has
gotten me through a lot of hard times,
um, you know, in past,
past issues in my life and stuff like that.
And just sitting down and like,
when I'm at work, and
I'm listening to you guys, it just, it brings a
positivity to, to my day
that I didn't have before. So
that, that's one of the reasons why I called it.
I just wanted to tell you guys that you have
done so many good things
to a lot of people that are, that
are out there listening to you every,
every Sunday or on the podcast
feed throughout the week. And,
and I know that every time somebody listens
to you guys, there is a positive
jokingly feeling
of like, they're in the same room as you
guys and we're just all friends. And that's,
and that's amazing. Don't make me cry,
Code Man. Don't do it. Don't do it.
Well,
I have to tell you too
that just in the fact that we've been talking
over the last month worth of shows,
it's really nice to have a colleague
who listens to, you know,
it's, it's been kind of, it's just been
really cool chatting with you and, you know,
sort of exchanging, you know, not just
the video game stuff, but having
the design thing in common too.
Well, and, and Code Man, let me say this,
and I'm sure it goes for
Dark Sakura and Loki as well, because I know
we've had, we've all had these very difficult
shows. This show has helped
us get through a lot of hard times
as well. Like, you know, I'll
talk about myself since I have the mic right now,
but, you know, a few years ago, I had a near
death experience and that was very,
you know,
very humbling in a way. And,
and there's a lot of jokes
about, I don't want to turn 30. I don't want to turn
30, 30. I might as well be dead if I'm gonna be
30. Well, I, I almost did die at
29. So, to make it to
30, now I'm like, being
30 is fucking rad.
And it really is, like, it's, it's awesome.
I was just saying, earlier, when I turned 30, I stopped
giving a crap. Exactly. You just kind of
learned all that. So, you know, this show
helped me through a lot of that
as well. You gave me tequila
and told me not to think about it.
So. Yes, but, no,
that's, that's basically what I called in. I mean,
as far as video games go, I mean,
I've ever, I've been, I'm still
struggling through Tomb Raider. I,
I don't know, Rob, you've been playing it too,
I think, and I, I don't know, I just,
I haven't gotten to pick it up again.
When are we playing the very average
multiplayer that I, I, I, I shouldn't
razz it because I haven't tried it yet, but when are we gonna
give it a try? Uh, I don't know.
Alright. You know, anyway, yeah, I, I,
I, you know, and then, and then all, I mean,
all kinds of video games out
right now that are just, I don't know, just
eating me up. And, like I, like I mentioned before,
I have a daughter, so I, most of the time, I don't even
get to play video games, but, you know, it,
it, when I do, I, I try to sit down for,
like, just long periods of time
and play video games, but, uh,
but yes, I'll let you guys go and get another
caller in here, but, um, because it is your 500th
show, and I'm sure a bunch of people want to call in,
but, um, I just want to say
congratulations, guys, and I hope you enjoy the,
the poster. I, I put so much
heart and, and just
stuff into it that, because I want you guys
to understand how much
you guys mean to me, and how
much you mean to all of your fans
and all of your, your, your
listeners that are out there, all around
the United States, and I just wanted to kind of
put that all in a poster, and I didn't even
capture all of it, um, and-
Code Man, we talked about the crying thing, don't do it.
Hey, you better cry, it's a 500th show, come on, Bob.
Maybe
when Rob drinks more, he'll cry. I'm gonna make you
cry. Oh, Rob, is he,
is he an emotional drunk? Because I,
because I am. No, I'm just loud. But,
um, I, and horny
apparently, if these other stories are to be believed.
Oh, you can't spin the bottle. Oh, Jesus Christ.
It was hilarious. That was, that was
by the way, um, Shane reminded me, that's where
Dunk came from. Oh, no.
Alright, look, uh, Code Man,
thank you so much, and I'm, I'm so glad
everybody gets to see your talent now in
our album art, and the fact that that is
listener created, I mean, Jamie
did, did great work beforehand for, for
a previous era of the show, but, you know,
this show really is about the listeners, and,
and so that the listeners could contribute to that,
and the way you capture that by having
everybody's name in there,
or, I should say, not everybody, but a good chunk of the people.
That was a great touch. That was a great
touch. I loved it. So, that was
my favorite part. Well, it's, it's, it's, wherever
every gamer has a voice. Absolutely.
It's not, yeah, it's, it's not only,
you know, about the hosts
that are on the show, but it's about the people that could
participate in the chat room, and, you
know, give a voice to the actual
podcast itself. So,
I want, I want to thank you guys for, for
doing so much for everybody, and
just thank you. That's all I can say.
Thank you. Are you guys still doing the
down for maintenance show?
We are!
Yeah, we, we have taken
a couple of weekends off due to
just, just really busy,
busy lives. I've been doing a lot of graphics
for people on YouTube, and I've just been really,
really, really busy, so,
but other than that, yeah, we're still on,
we're on Stitcher now, which is
awesome. Nice.
And iTunes is kind of
fuzzy, because we, we're not
running the kind of server that
iTunes accepts, so,
God, I hate, this is why iTunes is
gonna, anyway, rabble, rabble.
But, look, look them
up at least on Stitcher, right? Down for maintenance.
We do have a, we do have a website, though, now.
Please. www.thedfmpodcast.com
Alright, check it out. It's a great show.
You know, probably the most ultimate compliment
we get on this show, and I'm not saying this
is necessarily true of your show, but
I, I get this so much, is that, you know,
you guys helped inspire me,
you guys showed me that anybody can really do
this, and that I can, I can do this, too,
and that, that is like the greatest compliment
when we see these other shows
arise of our listenerships. It's awesome.
So. It's one of the reasons why we did it.
Thank you so much. Alright, buddy, I'm gonna let you go
so we can get more calls. Alright, man, well,
you guys enjoy five rounds of the show, and I'm
gonna go to bed, cause I'm sleepy.
Good night. Good night. Bye-bye.
Alright, I'll talk to you guys later. Bye.
Code man. Great call. Thank you.
Even if you're gonna make me cry. Alright, listen.
I was feeling a little sniffly. The phone is
ringing off the hook, so let's get to another call.
Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio. Who's this?
Hola. Bienvenidos a Orange Lounge Radio.
Are you muted?
I see you.
Hello. One more time.
Come in, Tokyo. We don't hear you.
Alright.
Echo 123 to test your
connection, folks. I think he's off
at the esthetician.
Well, I'll bring up that joke.
Well, let's try another call. Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
Who's this? Hey, this is Brad from
Pod Culture. Oh, and we see him.
We see him. It's Brad from Pod Culture. What's on
your mind, buddy? Oh, just calling
to say congratulations on 500,
guys. Thank you so much.
You're not that far behind.
Pod Culture's been going quite a while
itself, hasn't it?
In our
eighth year, I guess. Yeah, that's something.
That's something. That's amazing.
You and I have the same color microphone I just
realized with the little...
Gee, I wonder why. I know.
You've done a lot to help this show out over the years,
Pod Culture, from getting us drunk to
getting us heard. And thank you for
all of the discs full of Doctor Who
you've sent me in the past.
Oh, no problem. No problem. I'm glad
to do it. But hey,
without you guys, you know,
I don't think we would have lasted as long as we
have, and thanks for the
inviting us into the
Vogue community. Oh,
duh. Happy to have you.
We knew when we were starting...
We knew we wanted to do something that was not
just games, but a celebration of everything
geek, and some of our
favorite shows came to mind, and absolutely,
you were near the top
of that list. You were seriously up there.
Well, thank you. But
congratulations, and I'm gonna let you
guys go and get
some more calls in, and this one's for you guys.
Oh, look at that. Oh, oh, oh! Shot
on air! Yeah!
That's one of the best video
calls we've ever got. See, you took it far better than Rob
did, because Rob turned red in the face, and it was
awesome. Well, I've had more practice.
It's become a regular thing on the show.
All right. Pod Cultures, Monday nights
here at the Voice Geeks Network, continuing
a celebration of the various
Doctors on Tardis Interruptus tomorrow.
Fourth Doctor, right? Yes, sir.
All right. Fourth Doctor was my Doctor.
There you go. He was
pretty well known.
Good night, guys. All right, take care, buddy.
All right, always a pleasure to
hear from Brad, from another great
podcast. Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio. Who's
this? It's
me, Mario.
Hi, Mario.
Hey. What's on your mind? Is this really
Extrofer? What?
Yeah, it's me.
What's
on your mind, Extrofer?
What is on my mind? I don't
know. I was just calling. Hair.
You just wanted to see what's up?
Yeah, I wanted to see
what's up in his house.
Well, we're doing this
aussism
multiple sclerosis walk
one week from today, and everybody should
donate at Hoardhouse.com through the
link, right? Yeah, totally.
There you go. Thumbs up for
multiple sclerosis
box. We broke a thousand
dollars today. That's awesome. We did break
it. We broke it.
We took it out.
We did take it out.
And I'm very happy about that.
What video games have you been playing
lately, Extrofer?
You know, Jetpack Joyride
and
I don't know, nothing else.
I'm boring.
You should know this already.
Well, what did you call to say
tonight? Did you want to wish us well on our
500th episode?
Um, no. I just thought I'd call
and say hi.
Oh, well, okay. Hey.
Hey.
Hey. Got any plans tomorrow?
Want to hang? You know what?
You still need to come over and finish watching Firefly with
me after five years of us not
watching Firefly. Who's getting called out?
Yeah, you know, I'll check my calendar
and stuff
for that and get back
to you. Well, let's see. My
week is not working, not working, not working,
not working, not working birthday. You can come.
Oh, let me check my calendar.
I'm not working, not working,
not working, not working.
And then birthday.
I guess we have the same calendar.
Awesome. Amazing.
Uh,
Extrofer, do you want to plug Horde House?
I will
plug Horde House up the asshole
for you.
Is it bleached?
Yes, it's a bleached, nicely bleached,
freshly bleached asshole
that Horde House has. Let me, let me
ask you this, Extrofer, since, uh,
you know, we have a lot of old school listeners that are
revisiting us tonight and so forth.
You know, for a while, you and I were roommates
and OLR Studios was at
your house. So what would
the listeners be most surprised
to know about Orange Lounge Radio behind
the scenes? What do you think? What do you think
the OLR listeners
would be most surprised to know behind the scenes?
Well, our studio
in our apartment was freaking
filthy.
And, um,
and, uh,
Rob falls asleep in random
places. It's totally
true. It's not just when he's drunk.
That is totally hilarious, too.
What's the most- Like, I would come
home and he'd be like asleep on the floor
and be like, oh, I'm glad I didn't trip
over you. I didn't see you down there.
I
remember coming over to that apartment
and being absolutely thrilled that you were
totally into Devil's Crush.
Oh, yeah. I love
Devil's Crush. Although, the,
um,
actually, it was- Alien Crush.
Yeah, Alien's Crush, or
whatever. My favorite Extrofer
memory was when you stood out on the line to get
me the Wii.
I know, right? And
how many times did you play that
thing?
Every day is what I want to say.
Every day. I was a huge Wii fan.
Yeah, you were a total Wii
fan. You were like- It was like
five years after it launched and you were like
Wii!
Like, every single chance you would
get, you would say that. It was kind of weird and
depressing. It was a little awkward.
Alright, well, Extrofer, before we let you go, is there
any other final thoughts for listeners tonight?
Um,
well, I gotta go wash my hands
because I did some dirty work before
you guys
gave me a call. In fact,
when you called me earlier, I didn't
say anything because
I had just came and
you didn't want to hear what
my voice sounds like right after that.
Were you- I think you just better
go wash your hands. Were you touching yourself to the
show? That's a little awkward. If you're, like, jerking
it to my voice- No! I took a shit on my
chair and I was cleaning- What did you think
I was doing? Never
change, please. Dirty work, okay? Never change.
Extrofer, I'm letting you go now.
Aww, thank you.
Alright, bye!
Are we holding him for any reason?
What the
fuck?
Like, seriously!
I totally miss Extrofer
and the utter randomness.
Ah, lordy. Hi, you're-
Yes! Oh my god, we-
School bus reference in the chatroom.
Hi, here on Orange Nails Radio,
who's this?
Oh my god, it's Slidekick. Hey,
girl. Hey, I'm the guy.
Hey, girl, what's up? Sorry, Rob.
Sorry, Rob, you're not one of- you're not the guy.
You're one of the girls. Whatever.
What's up, Slidekick?
Hey, I just wanted to congratulate
you, like, everyone else. Like, I know
it's totally not original. And, like,
how do I follow up?
You know, that call that Extrofer just made,
you know, I can't really-
I am not touching myself, but
I just wanted to congratulate all
of you on your great achievement.
And, yeah, that's amazing.
500, like, I
can't believe that. Well, thank you, baby. I appreciate it.
I feel so nervous. Like, I'm on the radio.
Like, I'm kind of famous now.
It's just me. You know me.
You've met me. I'm not that scary.
We're not that scary, right?
You're a little
scary.
Well,
shoot, Slidekick, do you want to talk any games
with us? What games have you been playing lately?
I'm actually
playing Fire Emblem Awakening.
Yeah? How's that?
And I kind of suck at it, but
it's cool. I like it a lot.
I've never really played a lot of
tactical strategy
RPGs, so it's cool.
I like it. There's a lot
of people that are really into Fire Emblem
on the 3DS, so I can't really
blame you for being a fan of that.
For sure.
So, Slidekick,
you've done a couple of podcasts of your own, too.
I know you used to do a podcast with Alan.
Not everybody knows about this, but you used to do the
Amazing Warcraft podcast,
Fabulous Flames, right, Alan?
Yes, we did.
And I have to say, Alan
has been amazing tonight.
Yes, he has. I was a big
fan of the Miss Nude World 96.
I'm always
a fan of the Miss
Nude World 96.
What are you doing these days in podcasting?
Do you have anything you want to plug?
Yes, and since
Exifer took the butt plug joke,
I'll just
go ahead and shout out to
my podcast, which is
Game Buoy. We're over at Gamebuoy.org,
and we bring you gaming news
and views that may be on your radar, but
most definitely should be.
And we are definitely inspired and
pretty much owe everything about
who we are, so thank you
for being an inspiration
and making
a community out there
for people to have a voice in gaming
because it's super important
for not just
all the blogs and
journalists
to be the only ones talking about games.
Well, thank you. It means a lot,
and your show is
very good. I've heard it. And even though in those
first few episodes I wanted to kill you over your
sound quality, you guys have improved so
much. You sound great now.
It was actually better than it was on the previous
one.
I do miss Fabulous Flames, just saying.
You sound great now, and
your content is very good and
well-researched, and you and Spike
are great. And what I love most about your
show is that you always pay it forward at the end,
and you do give shout-outs and keep it
indie, and I think that's great.
And, you know, if we helped
inspire that attitude, then that's
a huge compliment.
We're your biggest fans. We love
you so much.
I have been begging to come on your show for, like,
six months, and look at this.
I totally miss planning webcomics
with you.
I still have
the WoW viewer. We can still do it.
Yay!
Alright, well,
Slidekick, I'm gonna let you go so I can get more calls,
but anything else real quick before I let you go?
Um, no.
Except I need to get
up there and have an OLR party
sometime. You're welcome any time.
Get up here on Sunday. You have to come up on Friday.
Bring Captain Spike.
I will try. I will try.
Alright, take care, buddy. Have a good one.
Alright, you too.
Have a happy 500. Thank you.
Alright, 1877
game OLR, username on Skype
is OrangeLoungeRadio. Let's go to another call.
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
It's the undertaker of the internet,
Ravenstaufen. Wait a minute, weren't you just here?
I was, but give me
two minutes, Rob. Alright. I hope your
Paul Bearer didn't die. Alright, time
starts now.
Alright, so I want to
congratulate OrangeLoungeRadio
for 500 shows and inspiring me
to do my show. I'm not gonna
plug it, but I'm just gonna say,
Rob, your cast
and your people are very
diverse, and you kept me entertained
for years. I am now 26,
and I've been listening since
I was in high school as well.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, we're so old.
I can feel myself
aging. I've got cancer now.
No, it's, it's, it's
amazing. It's, that's amazing.
It really is amazing. I also really
like your voice.
Thanks. It's so funny. Your voice
is very much mature. I remember when you used to
call this show all the time when you were in high school,
and the years right after that
and so forth, your voice really has matured.
Like, I can hear it through
undoubtedly your own podcast and
so forth. It's, it's, it's
pleasant. It came a long way.
Everything came a long way, and I have to
say, if OrangeLoungeRadio
was a lighthouse in the beacon of the dark,
you are
awesome. Well, I appreciate
it so much, Ravenstaufen, and thank you so
much for sticking with us for all the years. It's a pleasure, as
always, to hear from you. I've, I've, I
listen to every archive. I've never
leave. It's just sometimes I do my things
on Sunday and it makes it hard. I had to cancel
my own show for you guys because I had
to be here for your special day.
Wow, that's, oh my gosh.
Wow. What would you have talked
about on your show tonight? Maybe we can
work a little bit of it into here, a little
crossover episode.
Well, I was gonna talk about, and you guys
didn't do, it was the whole thing about
Twitch TV, about that handicapped guy that
wasn't handicapped. Yeah, I heard
about this. So what, let me see if I can
summarize. Let's see. So he was getting donations
because he was sick
and I guess it was donations for a surgery,
right? And, uh, well
the cameras weren't stopping on Twitch
TV. He didn't turn them off and they caught
him getting up out of his wheelchair.
Like, just getting up and walking
away. So the, the cake was
a lie, ladies and gentlemen, but that
just goes to show, you gotta be, it's,
it's sad that we can't just
trust people and we can't, but like
you, you do have to be skeptical.
Like, that's why with the MS Walk stuff, and
you know, we've been plugging that a lot. Like, I was very
much like, we're gonna take it
directly to the MS Walk
society, the MS society and you donate
right there, directly. We're not, you know,
I don't, no funny business people.
Yeah, so we were
gonna talk about that. I mean, I had problems
in the past. I mean, I'm on Social Security
right now. I, you know, I
had major problems, went to special
schools. So for me, for someone that
fakes an illness like that, like, you
just slapped me in the face. And I'm not trying
to get donations for what I'm doing,
but it came a long
way. It's, it's, you
know what, though? That's, Karma
will bite you when you do stuff like that. Karma
will bite you. And Karma bit that guy
big time. Big time. Yeah. So
DJ Darknight
in chat at live.voguenetwork.com says
that's just as bad as the guy that was caught spanking
himself on Twitch. That's funny.
That's funny.
The wheelchair thing is, is bad.
That's evil. That's awful. But the
But that's the internet, though. Jerking it on Twitch, that's funny.
Any live streaming site, you're going
to see dick or boobs anyway. Yeah, I was
gonna say, or the one dude that had sex with his girlfriend
or something like that in the background, or like, he
just forgot it was on.
Yeah, he forgot it was on. That's why I'm very
careful about when I have the, I would not
live stream 24-7 just because
Extra for, for shame. I know
something bad would happen. Alright,
Ravenstaufen, I'm gonna let you go to get more calls, but thank you so
much for the kind words. I understand. Thank you for taking my call.
Bye. No problem. Bye.
1-877-GAME-OLR, our username on Skype.
OrangeLoungeRadio. Why not? We can do a couple
more calls, right? We're only at 9-30.
We are being
horribly rude to our East Coast people.
We are. How about one more call?
One more call. One more call. Let's see who gets in.
1-877-GAME-OLR. I'm
totally, wait a minute, I'm totally jealous of all of them
who have jobs.
No. Keep them up all night.
All night. You alright?
I was doing my Rhonda Shear
impersonation. Hello? I see, I see.
Except I'm not wearing, you know, extra padding in the boob region.
Alright, let me go to one more call. Hi, you're on
OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
Hey, what's up? It's TigerClaw. Hey, TigerClaw.
What's on your mind, buddy? Oh,
I just want to congratulate you guys
on your 500th episode.
I guess you guys can go
on record, maybe,
as being the longest running podcast
in history or something like that.
We're not the longest running podcast. We are the longest
running video game podcast. I don't
even know. Well, you guys
been around way before
podcasting was a thing, so.
I'd say live show. That's what gives
us a jump on the other people is that we had
the live 365 years and so
we kind of slid right into the podcasting
thing. But I would say
I usually say we are the longest
running internet show about
video games. Weekly internet show about video games.
Uh, yeah.
But you know what? The internet, the internet
TigerClaw, the internet is a big place.
Like, uh, I've been putting
together this special interest group on Facebook
recently, uh, with some friends and I
found that there's all these, like, other podcasters
I didn't even know were out there. Like, I didn't even know
these shows existed and, like, they're celebrating
episode 100 and, and, and, like
60 and I'm like, what?
So, you never know what's out there, which is
why I'm very cautious to stake a claim, like,
we're the longest running show, bitches.
You know, so I, I just,
I want to be careful.
Yep, and just keep on doing
what you're doing and
and hopefully people will listen
and, um,
I don't know what else to say, uh,
no matter how old you get
just keep on gaming because
you'll still feel the same way.
Alright, well, TigerClaw,
I appreciate your support over
the years. It means an awful lot.
Uh, no problem.
You're welcome. So, better let some other
people call in. Alright, we'll see if
maybe we'll let one more sneak in since you were short.
But have a good one, TigerClaw. Alright, thanks.
Alright. Take care. Mm-hmm, you too. Bye-bye.
Bye. Well, we can do
one more. Let's do one more.
One more, come on. Show up. Alright,
one more, one more. Especially this one.
Alright, hi, oh.
Oh my gosh, it's a scary
black man on the cam, oh my gosh.
No, I'm kidding, you
guys, it's DJ Rama S. You are looking
sharp in your vlog shirt. You are looking very sharp
today, young man. How are you?
I'm doing fine. How is everybody in the
Sacramento studios? We're,
I'm sobering up, sadly.
Oh, you should not be sobering up, because
I have a problem with that good sir. Uh-oh,
what's that? Well,
ah. What are you drinking?
If you can
see what I got here. I
love you, and I need to be at your house
right now.
He's got a bottle of
Glenfiddich. This is one of
two bottles of Glenfiddich I have.
Okay, I'm a BRB going on a plane.
Of course, I could just go to Becky's house.
Do you see this glass right here? Yes, I do.
Oh, wait, hold it, except for once
it says something about a Luigi hat. Give me
one quick second. Oh, lord.
Wait, they can't, they can't, they can't, we're the
only ones that can see you.
Okay, he's wearing that, well you can, Rob,
do you know what print screen is?
Oh, uh, yes, I do
print screen.
You've got Photoshop, right?
I'll print screen, we'll just get that window.
There we go. Alright, I think I got him, we'll see.
Nice.
Do I even have PaintShop Pro on this
computer or whatever? God, PaintShop Pro.
Shut up.
PaintShop Pro. I might have
MS Paint. You know what, you
can paste it in Paint.
There you go, you got it. Yes, I got it.
Woohoo. Alright, I'll save it as a paint thing
and fix that up later. Alright, so anyhow.
Bitmap.
Where was I? I'm gonna save it
with the very clever untitled
.bmp. Alright,
um, you're looking,
Rob, I already took the damn picture.
Rob is sadly not on a Mac.
I'll continue to wear it to the end of the
video broadcast, but as you can see,
I am popping this bad boy open
that has been in my freezer for the past
two weeks. Oh, nice.
And, as I
pour this, I want to thank each and every
single one of you. As everyone
said before, if it wasn't for OLR,
there wouldn't be no anime jam session.
And also,
I will not be one of those
podcasters that will beg for
money to do my show. What me,
Marco, and Ari, what we all do,
we do it for love, and we pick up
all our money and we do it together.
I'll do it for dollar
bills to show my tatas,
but that's it.
Someone
did send me money one time. For showing
your tatas? No. I do
that for free.
To Dan.
She does that for drinks.
But no, remember when I had Pump Up the Volume?
And Loki put it in my intro
to tune in and give me a dollar? Oh yeah,
someone actually sent me a dollar. I remember that.
It was good times.
Rama, thank you so much for the toast,
and as I was saying before to some of the other
callers, that is really the ultimate
compliment to hear that we might
have inspired even a portion of somebody
else's show. It's outstanding.
You need to come back for fun of me.
We're just here having a good time.
Go on.
You cut out. Go ahead, Rama.
Well, I was going to say, OLR
is not just a podcast. We're like a
frickin' family. A giant
dysfunctional family.
We put the fun
in dysfunction. That's right.
I will go on record right now.
You guys
really got me through
the passing of my mother when I called that
one night and asked for you guys to play
Let's Screw.
That was one of my favorite songs.
You guys played it, and I could not
thank y'all enough for doing that.
I'm more than happy
to do so, especially if it'll help
even just the slightest bit
in somebody's really shitty day,
to put it lightly. I'm
happy to.
Hearts.
Of course. Now to
Sky.
Loki. Dark
Sakura. Here's to you.
Here's to me. The best of friends
will ever be. If you should ever
happen to disagree, well, fuck you
and here's to me. Fuck you too,
buddy. I hope
that puts you on the floor. That is seriously
my second favorite toast ever.
That's great.
And before I go, I did say I have a
little treat for you. Okay. I love
your hand flailing. That's cute.
I thought that was the treat.
I just came back from a J-pop concert and I got
in for free, okay?
Amazing.
But I'll have PAX East.
I happen to run into a famous
Nerdcore rapper, and I asked him to do
a favor, and hopefully
this will play through.
And here we go.
This is MC Frontalot, and you are
participating with the Voice of Geeks
Network.
Shut the front
door. Oh my god.
Oh
my god. That's amazing.
Wow.
Work it.
I love you forever.
I'm buying you drinks.
Alright, that's it. New York. When we going?
Right now. Bye, BRB.
Head to New York. BRB, New York.
Alright, no. You have to pick up
Marco as you go, because if you go, take
me without her. She's going to kick everybody's
ass. BRB is stopping in New Jersey.
Alright,
Rama, that was
amazing. That was awesome.
You've been an amazing support over the
years, and thank you so much,
buddy. You don't even know.
No, thank you, because
you guys gave me this opportunity to do
this, so me running around, finding
these opportunities to give you guys
bumpers, interviews, this and that.
This is more than my way of saying
thank you, you know? This is,
you know, all I ever wanted
was to get my show on, and Rob, you gave
me that opportunity, so
believe it or not, I'm in your eternal thanks for all
of this. Well, it's the
least I could do.
Alright, take care of my friend. We have
to go wrap up. It's not a marathon
show. Yes? Stay black, my
brother. I will, absolutely.
Good night. Hey,
run, run, Sean. Yeah, that's okay, Sean.
Stay drunk.
Bye, my friend.
I don't have to have sinned.
Alright, I'm hitting hang up now,
because I've said bye like five times. Alright.
That was
amazing. It'll always be my run, Sean.
What a great show.
I'm getting a little of a clempt.
Do we have any last minute stories? Oh, I need to read
Twitter topics. Where's my iPad?
Do we have any last minute stories, Loki?
No. No, he's ready to go.
I have a last
minute story. Okay.
I like these brownies. They're awesome.
I just want to say, just kind of like a
blanket thank you to
the kind words on
Twitter. There's been a lot of tweet
activity tonight, and I just want to say a
big thank you for all of that.
I don't have the time yet, because we're
running way over to read each and every single
one of them, but I just want to say thank you.
Quickly, some of these tweets, real
quick. Act F
tweeting us about Shadowrun Returns
backers for the DRM-free copy of the game
may have gotten screwed by Microsoft,
and in a nutshell, the game will be
free, but the
original game
will be DRM-free, but the DLC
will not. So they're holding
up their end of the bargain. Basically what it is, is you get
two versions of the game. You get a DRM-free
version of the game. You get a Steam version of the game.
Steam version will support the DLC
beyond the Kickstarter
exclusive DLC, and then
the free-to-play
DRM-free game will only
support the Kickstarter
DLC, but no
additional DLC.
Tigerclaw tweeting us that
Ska Studios challenges the view that
Microsoft is bad for indies, so not
everybody is saying that Microsoft is this
evil indie thing. Bobby Blackwolf
tweeting us about this is a travesty
in a story about Disneyland. Apparently
Space Mountain was
closed while Disneyland reviewed safety.
Space Mountain, the Matterhorn Bobsleds,
and Soarin' Over California were
out of service today.
What a shitty day to be at Disneyland.
Hey, we weren't there.
You poor guys that went to Disneyland today.
But they did reopen Matterhorn Bobsleds already,
which, you know, is kind of... I'm just still
irritated they took out the basketball court.
They did? Yeah, they took out the basketball
court when they redid the tracks.
For those who don't know their
Disney trivia, the Matterhorn had a half
court up in the very top of the
mountain for cast members
to go during their break.
ActDeft tweeting us saying
Wars of Horizon getting a new free DLC
pack called the 1000 Club.
I like free DLC. I'm on board
with that. Also,
ActDeft tweeting us...
I think I went over his too, but that's okay.
A New Jersey assemblywoman wants to
ban violent video games in public
places. Yeah, was that the same one where they
want to ban M-rated arcade games? Yeah, they want
to ban M-rated and AO-rated arcade
games. Problem being, the ESRB does not
rate arcade games.
Yeah. So,
way to do your research.
How about if you don't like them? Don't take your
children there. And I just want to give
some quick shout outs. I know I said I wasn't going to read
each and every one of these, but we actually had some other
fellow podcasters that tweeted us
and said congratulations. And I think it's
important to give these guys a shout out because
community
makes us great. And us indie podcasters,
we really, really have to stick together.
So I do want to give a shout out to Godfrey
from Gamertag Radio who sent a tweet earlier
today. And they've been going
a very long time as well. I know they were one of the
first shows on iTunes as well, so
he's had many, many great
accomplishments. So props to you, Godfrey.
GameBui, who you
heard Slidekick earlier, also sent us a tweet.
Those guys are a lot of fun.
Even though I think they should go weekly,
but when they do
put out a show, it is fabulous and very well
researched. We always love it when they put out.
Who doesn't love it when they put out?
The Rich from the Video Game
Show tweeted us and said congrats on
500. Now Video Game Show, I
think, as far as I
know, I could be wrong, but as
far as I know, Video Game Show is
the only other podcast
in iTunes when it went
live about gaming the day it went
live that is still going. They're about to hit
episode 400. And again, if
we didn't have the live 365 years to count,
we'd probably be tied with them right now. So
big props to the Video Game
Show for keeping it going for all this time.
Our old friends at All Games Radio
also wishing us well on episode 500
tonight. I think that's very nice.
I'm glad to hear that they're doing well
as well too. They've added a lot
of cool shows to their lineup. They've really
diversified things a little bit.
Props to you guys at All Games
Radio for keeping it
going and Indie Radio.
And of course, to our pal
Bobby Blackwolf who's
always before us here. We love Bobby so
much. And Brad from
PodCultured. CriticalMyth
who's hitting 300 episodes tomorrow.
Nice.
And Anime Jam Session
and Hoard House and Girls Gone
Wow and British
Invaders. Have I named everybody now? I think I have.
Understation Live. Oh my God.
Understation Live. Well, I don't think that we would
be here without them. Isn't that
funny? Is that everybody's
calling in saying, O-L-R
you inspire me to do this. O-L-R you
did this. And I think this is a good note for us to end on
tonight. You know what? I'm going to sit on this for a minute because I want to end
on that note. So let me go around and get everybody's
final thought. Becky,
thank you so much for being here. I know you didn't get a chance to
say an awful lot, but we really
appreciate the culinary delights. And your
support still means the world to us. So thank you for
being here. You're welcome.
It's okay. I'm just, I'm a very
quiet person. That's alright. Any final thoughts for our listeners
though? While you're at it? Any
last words of wisdom?
Don't let your kids watch Sponge
Bob.
It's horrible.
Dark
Sakura, your final thought for our listeners tonight?
Oh, why the fuck not? Reject false
icons. Ooh,
taking it back a notch.
Loki, your final thought tonight? I have two things. One, I have a picture
of poop on my phone. And two,
uh, wow.
Let's do this
Mark IV style, motherfuckers.
My final thought
tonight, as promised, I want to
say a lot of you gave props
to us for helping inspire what you do.
But I really have to say, and I
got into this on Facebook a little bit before,
but I really just want to say that, you know,
I studied radio in college
and I actually originally was
going to be a weatherman. That was what I was in
college to study originally.
I interned at a broadcast station
at an actual
news broadcast in the town I went
to school in. And although
everybody was really nice and it was a really great
eye-opening experience, the way
my eyes were open was that most people
were very miserable in the jobs that they were doing and
it really didn't want to be something I wanted to continue.
So I kind of got into radio as a result
of that, but I felt a lot of that same
stuff. That in commercial radio
it's really not about who you know, but it's about who
you blow. And that wasn't really what
I wanted, you know, contrary to what Jamie might tell
you about when I drink, that wasn't really what I
wanted to pursue. So
I didn't finish school
because I became very jaded with a lot of it.
And I was kind of like, what the hell am I wasting my time for?
I just need to go out into the working world.
And while I don't hate school and I think it's
great that a lot of people do go to school and finish
college and all that, for me at that time
it was what I needed to do and it was a great
thing. And I love where I ended up in my career
so I'm happy. But I'm really thankful
to my time
I did spend at the college radio station,
my very first radio show at KCSC
Student Radio.
I just want to say props to that and for my time there.
And then I also want to say a big thank you to
Travis Donahue
from Understation Live for bringing me
on to his show back in
what, 2000, 2001
when I came on to his show for the first
time. And it was so much fun
he asked me to come back and I came back
over and over and over again. And through
him I learned how easy it was to do a show on
Live 365. And so
I, like DJ Rama
was talking about with his show and
Code Man was talking about his show and everybody else,
I said, you know, I want to do something like
this for the day. And I
you know, I want to do something like this for the
DDR community and for
the, you know, Bamani
community and all my new friends
that I've been making playing Dance Dance Revolution.
And Jamie, of course, was a big part
of that. We kind of thought of all the basic
concepts on that Bart ride.
And then Loki, well, he just tagged along for
the ride, but this show
would not be the same without him. I do need to thank Travis, too,
for having me on as a guest so much and filling in
for Jessica. Absolutely. Absolutely.
So, yeah,
I guess this is in a way
500 episodes of paying it forward.
So really appreciate
it. I don't know what else to say.
I see lots of great stuff in the
chat room right now. YYR says, thank you
guys for 500 great episodes and for devoting
so much of your time and energy to contribute towards
all of our lives, ours and yours.
Tim TRP says, Rob, you have a
voice for radio, a face for TV
news and a body for hardcore
pornography. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Oh, Tim.
Tim. All right.
I'm going to cry in a second, by the way.
Are you? What else can I say to make you cry?
Shut up.
If someone else brings up Sharmi, maybe.
The chips are gone.
I missed them already.
All right.
I think it's time we end the show. Thank you guys
so much for 500 great episodes.
Let's try to be less sappy next week, you guys.
I did pick something very, very,
very classic for Cookie.
Oh, we'll get to that in a minute.
All right, that's it. We're done. What do you say, guys?
We'll do it all again next week, all right?
Come on back next week for episode
501.
Until then,
have a great week.
Don't be a dick.
And have fun. It's only a game.
Good night.
To join us for a live show,
tune in to VoGnetwork.com,
Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific,
9 p.m. Eastern.
The views and opinions
expressed in this program
do not necessarily reflect
those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio
or VoGnetwork,
but you know they were all still true.
See you next week.
Thanks for watching.