Orange Lounge Radio
We're your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky and Loco UK
Tonight, June 28, 2009, we kick back and celebrate 7 years of Orange Lounge Radio with all of our listeners
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that video game talk show dedicated of course to video games
Video gaming, gaming culture and the gamer lifestyle
We like to say it's a place where every gamer has a voice
But it's going to be these three voices walking you through the next few hours here
When we tape live on all games radio
Myself, Rob Roberts and the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summer is here as well
Hi
How are you?
Beat
It's hot, it is hot in Sacramento today
It was 107 last time that I checked
And today was my walking evaluation, but we got to stay inside the air conditioning
Yeah, I was going to say, that's pretty cruel making me walk outside in the heat
Our teacher is like, there's no way in hell I'm making you guys go outside, we'll go break into the cardio room
Fun
And also say hello to Techmaster Loki
Hello
How are you doing Loki?
Good
Stay indoors today?
Yeah, I painted baseboards
Fun, being a homeowner rocks doesn't it?
Yeah
Awesome
And then I remember you said something about not being able to get shows
I'm sorry, stories for the show tonight
Yeah, because the internet was there, Comcast is working on improving their network in our neighborhood
I don't know what that exactly means
So your house is just broken right now?
Today at least, it's alright
Well hey guys, it is the seventh year anniversary of Orange Lounge Radio believe it or not
We've been talking about it for a couple weeks now
Kind of hyping it up a little bit
And sure enough, we started this little program
The very first episode was June 23, 2002
Which means this week we hit seven years of Orange Lounge Radio
And that's with no major breaks
I mean sure, a week here and a week there
I think maybe a two week break happened once or twice
But honestly, we've been running pretty regularly with no extended breaks
Through that whole time
So that is kind of an accomplishment
So we can admit it
We can take a minute to say
Thanks to all of you for helping make it happen
Because I'll tell you what, that very first show, the very first night, episode number one
We had twelve people listening
And now on AllGames.com, when we tape live, we get as many as thirteen
So we've really grown
No, I'm just kidding, obviously we have a little more than that
But it's just been great
You guys really have taken that to heart, what we say at the end of every show
To just tell more people about our show
And it's worked and we've grown a little bit
So thank you guys so much for helping us reach seven years of Orange Lounge Radio
Here's the funny thing about tonight's show
It's been a really crazy week for all of us
I think personally and everything else
Just like the show a couple of weeks ago
We didn't really prepare a list of topics to talk about
But here's the thing
Two weeks ago, we had E3
That made it easy
We had three hours to talk all about E3 and what happened there
Tonight, not so much
So we're going to just do it the old fashioned way
Because this is the way we did the show for many, many years
So we're going to see if we've still got it in us
And we're just going to wing it, folks
Here at Orange Lounge Radio
We're just going to wing it tonight
We've started assigning positions as if Orange Lounge was a starship
Yes, and what's your position?
Captain
What's my position?
First officer, because you have to talk to everybody and be my voice
What would be Loki's position?
Oh, Worf
We've given Loki's security officer position
Because he's the most aggressive of us all
And Jason is our ship's engineer
Deep Man kind of does that too, though
Well no, Jason would be like the engineer
Deep Man's kind of the person that would actually
Science officer?
Okay
He can be our science officer
Like data?
Data
Yeah
And then that means that
Because I was going to say that Tiara was our science officer
But I'm going to make her
Sulu
She's our Sulu
She can be our Sulu
Oh my
No, Deep Man can be our Uhura
Because he does so much communication stuff for us
He's our communications officer
So Sos could be our science officer
And then our Sulu is Misty
Okay
She can drive us
Now is there a farting officer?
Because we need Rice Princess to have a role
Chris is ship's lesbian
Official ship's lesbian
Okay
Would she be the Troy?
Rice Princess can be our check off
So she can scream at people
Okay
And
I like this
And do like our advanced calculations and stuff
But we need a ship's counselor
Now everybody in chat is screaming, you know
Who's going to be Quark?
Who's going to be Scotty?
Who's the doctor?
This isn't DS9, hello?
We don't have Quark
We have somebody called the doctor already
So I don't
The doctor would be the doctor, silly
Ship's doctor will be Sherby
Alright
Meow meow
She's ship's cat
Let's do what we used to do here on the show
And instead of talking just about games
Ooh, Patty and Sulu
Get away from the damn Star Trek for a minute
There's some folks that don't even like Trek listening to the show
Oh, Game Guru said that Loki's our red shirt
Hey, if you want to
That's not very nice
If you want to join the chat room and scream Star Trek obscenities with the rest of our chat
chat.orangelaunchradio.com is the place to be
When we tape live on Sunday nights at All Games Radio
At 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time
9 o'clock Eastern Time right after the Bobby Black Wolf show on Sunday nights
Let's go around and hear a little bit about
I've been changed up a little bit tonight
Because you know what, we've been doing this 7 years
If we want to talk about ourselves a little bit tonight
Get away from the games a bit
We can do that
We're going to do how was your day, how was your week tonight
Not just, you know, throw games into it
I'm sure you've played some stuff too, but
Dark Soccer, we'll start with you as we always do
How was your day, how was your week?
My day was hot
And kind of crappy
Um, also I left something, oh here it is
Um, yes, to, I've been in a lot of pain
From my finger, so tomorrow I'm having surgery
Done on it at 7 in the fucking morning
On my day off
Because I'm now officially on leave from work for a month
Congrats
Aww
With disability pay
Um, but no really, I've needed my finger surgery done
I was supposed to have it done at the end of July
She's going on the dole
Well, I, they, they, someone cancelled
And so I was able to get it done tomorrow
And that is such a blessing
Surgery's important though
Yeah, it's a 30 minute procedure
I'm going to be awake through the whole thing
Oh my gosh
But I won't feel, they won't let me watch, bastards
So, anyway
Um, as it's, as it's going, um
I've kind of, it sort of really hit me kind of hard this morning
So I've been kind of pissy
Try not to be pissy, I've tried to stay in a good mood
But unfortunately, when you're pissy, there's not a lot that keep you from just being pissy, you know
So I'm supposed to go to a birthday party today
Because Julie's birthday was, um, Thursday
And yours was Friday, so happy birthday
Indeed it was, thank you
I'm sorry, I couldn't make it
That's okay, I didn't have a lot of stuff
I called you
Yeah, you did
And we've got plans later this week
Yes
And you need to meet the BF and all that fun stuff
So we'll, we'll take care of that later this week
Indian food while I'm high is a kite, that should be funny
Um
I just want to read from DJ Morpheus in chat, our old buddy who hosts, uh, Under Sedation Live
Which, you know, if there's one show that's been in existence longer than Orange Lounge Radio, it's Under Sedation Live
Now granted, they had some big breaks, but we got our big break on Under Sedation Live
I do not have to learn to play with myself with my other hand
That's why God made toys
Those are the kinds of things that, uh, DJ Morpheus will throw out there on Saturday nights right here on All Games Radio
Where he tapes his show now
I do want to also point out, he did say, hope they cut open the right body part
Cause that would kind of suck to go in there and then like, you know, suddenly you come out of there and you have bigger boobs
They could cut open the wrong body part and take out part of it, that'd be happy
Alright
Um, anyway, as far as, uh, my week
Yes
Um
I was at work
It kind of sucked
And I was in a lot of pain, which sucked too
And, um, I walked and I, um, yeah
Tell us a little bit about the condition, because I think, you know, you haven't talked a lot about playing games yourself on the show in probably the past six months
And, I mean, granted you've had some on the DSSF, but I think people don't understand that you have something up with your hand
Like you can't really do the controllers for very long
So
It actually, I'll tell you what hurts most about playing a game is, um
And by the way, um, I agree with Travis, he is our cue
Um, what, it's called flexor tendonitis
Um, so to translate it means that the, you know, when you flex your muscles, when you flex your fingers you're bending them
If you straighten them out you're extending, so it's in the tendons that bend the muscles
And, um, those muscles, of course, are in your forearm
And the tendons run from your forearm to your finger
And, um, it's my middle two fingers of my right hand, my, uh, my flipping off everybody because they suck finger
And my not getting married finger, which is the other hand
So, um, it's on my right hand
So, um, anyway, those, the tendons that when they attach to the muscles in your fingers
There's a sheath around them of, uh, of tissue
You know, some of the kind of holds it in place so that they don't bow out, you know
Like when you have a bow strung too tightly and the things start popping out
Um, it keeps the tendons in place
And what happens is I have swelling on my hand
If you look at your palm, up above the center of your palm where the, the really fleshy part is right under your fingers
Um, I have a knot on each tendon
And what happens is that if you imagine like a pulley
The knot gets caught on that sheath of skin going, on that sheath of tissue going into the fingers
And so when I try to straighten out my fingers, it pops, like it's shoving past that
Like, like you're trying to fit something into a tube that's too small for it
You know what I mean?
Uh, act deaf in our chat room says flex or tendinitis, it sounds like a DJ
A little bit
Well, um, that, that's really, I think the best way I can describe it
So what they're gonna, gonna do is actually, um, cut my hand open
And it's just like they're, like they, um, open two little flaps on either side
And they're gonna snip the tendon sheath so that, that lump will have, won't have that tight of an area to go through
Um, and what happens is that the tendon sheath will heal around the larger lump now
And, you know, most, it has a pretty high success rate
It's fairly, you know, it, it's a 30 minute procedure
I'm gonna be awake for it, they're just gonna numb it up
Um, DJ Flexer
So they're circumcising your hand?
No, I'm not having skin removed from it
They're just making a little cut
Um, but the whole problem as far as how it hurts is that now it's to the point that even when my fingers are straightened out
If I try to bend them, that lump, it's just so much swelling in my fingers
Cause you can actually see it on my palm
Well, I'm showing Rob
Great radio
But, um, but it, it's visible on my palm now
And it's just not very, it hurts a lot actually
It's really sore
And the place where the lumps are on
You know what they say about folks with swelled palms?
They hurt?
Nevermind
Oh wait, that's hairy palms
You know what they say about, about, about men with big, with big feet?
Uh, big socks?
Big shoes
Um, but, um, now, holding a controller now is me telling everyone right exactly where the, where the owies are
Imagine having a piece of hard plastic shoved against swollen tendon tissue for, oh, longer than ten minutes
Imagine not being able to bend your middle two fingers
It hurts to hold a fork
I can't hold, um, and, you know, you know I do graphic art and everything
I can't hold my stylus or a pen that isn't, like, a big child-sized fat highlighter
Or, you know, smelly markers
For longer than ten minutes
And it's really getting in the way of my life
So, I'm just gonna say, cortisone, I've had two rounds of cortisone
Two shots in each finger
I'm, I'm done
I'm ready just to have the surgery done and get it over with
Well this is like real trauma in the ER type of thing
Although it's not really an emergency, it's not bad
It's not a big procedure
It sounds a lot like what my mom had a couple years ago
She had her shoulder operated on and her shoulder was preventing her from painting
And I know that was really rough on her
Because, you know, she's older, she's past 65 at this point
She's long retired from, you know, being a preschool teacher and nanny
The stuff she did
She likes to paint, that's how she passes the time
So having to have that surgery was rough for her
But now she can paint again and she's really happy
So soon you'll be able to play games again
The shitty thing that I'm having to put back on because my finger hurts
I'm glad I never have to wear it again after my stitches come out
Although it is cool that you can flip people off just 24-7 with that thing
Yeah, because it's basically a splint that straps to my wrist
And hangs on the outside of my hand over my middle finger
So I can't bend it, it forces it to stay relaxed
Well I bet you can't wait for Project Natal because you won't need a controller for that
You can just wave your hand around like a lunatic
That would be fun
Well I mean supposedly I could do that with the Wii mode if I played left-handed
Which actually Wii games are surprisingly easy for me to play
Because I haven't really had to do anything, you know
But like today when we were doing our exercises I couldn't do push-ups
So actually I had to use a ball, a weighted ball, and do reverse push-ups
I couldn't do the rowing because I couldn't grip anything
It's really, I mean people don't really realize exactly how much they use their hands
Especially their dominant hand
Until you're restricted in it
And it was just like, I would just sit and just sketch, you know, for stress relief
Couldn't do it
I can't massage people except with my left hand
Which fortunately enough my primary client, all of her problems are on her left side
So that's fine
But you know, it's just, it's gonna be an adjustment
But I'm absolutely relieved
Well now were you able to get into any gaming at all?
Oh yeah, I'll play Sims, I can still play Sims
After my surgery I can still play the hell out of Sims
And screw everything else
The mouse is a thumb trackball
So I can still, I still have the use of my first finger and I can still use my thumb
Have you beat the Sims yet?
You don't beat the Sims
You do if they're bad
However, I made a Mii Sim
And the first thing I mastered was video gaming
Is that actually a skill in the Sims?
Yes, it's one of the hidden skills
You can just start playing video games and you can get up to level 10 master video games
What happens if you max out your video gaming skill?
Do you become like Fatality and you get your own line of video cards and stuff?
No, you just are awesome
But Sim Mii is a professional writer
And a hacker
Just because
Alright, well
Oh and I played Peggle
I'm glad to see Sims is going fun
I played Peggle on iPhone
Yep, on iPhone
I'm glad they did that sale
That motivated me to buy it
And for people who are using Linux
They're actually a pretty good version of Breakout on Linux
I'm running Linux Mint on my laptop
And I like it that instead of using the arrow buttons to move your
Your little bar around
You actually use the touchpad
It recognizes the touchpad and you can slide your finger back and forth to move your
Your little
Bounce bar
So that was pretty fun
I played
I was at Boston Market
And I was playing Breakout over Chicken at Boston Market
Nice, Chicken and Breakout
Yep
Awesome
I am done
Loki, how was your day? How was your week?
I'm tired
I guess
Today I painted baseboards because
It needs to be done
Because they're just primered white
I mean they look white but when you paint them it's a different color white
If that makes sense
So that's what I did today because I have to work on the house stuff
And then this week
I was trying to perfect the perfect modifications to Grand Theft Auto 4
And we have a working set now
It's Absolute Chaos
I mean
There's explosions going off everywhere consistently
Basically we replaced a bunch of the weapons in the game
Starting with the
Desert Eagle now is a gun that shoots these little
Vortex
Blasts I guess that basically throw people into the air
Or cars or just whatever you fire it at
And um
So that was basically the first thing I created
Which was like a defensive weapon
And it works pretty good
And then we replaced the um
The Mac 11 with uh
It's a molotov launcher that fires lots of fire at people
And catches them on fire and cars on fire and you name it
Then the MP5 which is the other Uzi in the game
Now fires rapid fire grenades
And um
That just creates a ton of explosions
And then we replaced the molotov in the game
Because you get that in multiplayer still
But since there's a molotov launcher already
I just made it create this giant explosion
That doesn't do any damage but throws everything everywhere
So that's kind of fun
Real quick question from chat let me ask this
Chat.orangelandradio.com live on this Sunday evening
Loki is there any way we can download your mods
That's from SSG100 Matt
No I'd have to post a copy of the ISO on there
I guess I could post a copy of my modified files
Then you just have to do the modifications yourself
And then you'd have to build your own ISO
And then burn it off and then play it on a modded 360
But um
Yeah I could do that
But it's a lot of work
And then um let's see what else I do
Oh uh the
The M4 now fires a bunch of rockets
Which is kind of funny
But they don't exactly explode on impact
They just bounce around a lot
Which is kind of funny
And then um
Let's see what else
I think that's pretty much it as far as weapons go
It's just it's a lot of chaos
And then also the police car flies
And um like the bus
And the big vehicles basically are
Um pretty dense
And they'll crash through anything and go really fast
So it's just it's really mixing up the game
And it right now because I mean
We've been playing Grand Theft Auto IV since it's come out
And hell we've been playing Grand Theft Auto games
Since they've come out on the PSP
And they had multiplayer in them
So um
Yeah it's just it's really
Really fun
And I'm really looking forward to when they come out
With the two expansions on one disc
Like they're going to be doing sometime in I think October
And uh when that happens it's going to be awesome
Because not only will I be able to
Because right now I can only modify the um
Weapons that are part of the original game
Like everything that's part of the expansion
You can't modify because
Basically it will overwrite anything
With the stuff that's in the expansion
Um that's on the disc
And you can't modify the expansion
Because it's in a different file format
And that kind of thing
But when it's on the actual disc
Then yes then I can hack crap out of it
And I'll be able to modify absolutely everything in the game
Which will just be incredibly fun
Um so beyond all that stuff
Um I've been
You know just kind of unpacking
And
I don't know
I've really just been playing Grand Theft Auto this week
Because I haven't had time to play much of anything else
But I have Wii Sports Resort
The Japanese one for Wii Motion Pluses now
You were mentioning that the other day
When you were over at my house for the birthday party
And for some reason we never got around to playing it
I guess just we were
On other tangents or what have you
But have you had a chance to crack it open and check it out yet?
Nope
Oh sad
I don't know
It's all in Japanese so I mean
Well you should be able to crack your way through it though
I mean uh
Yeah
When does that come out over here?
In um July 26th
Damn it's a bummer we weren't still in the old studio
We could do a Justin TV thing
Yeah
We'll have to figure something out
Or we can still get it broadcast somehow
Kinda check that out before it's launched over here
Yeah it's no big deal
Yeah I mean
I think
With Wii Sports it's more a lot of people have a curiosity about Wii Sports
That are actually like looking forward to it
Have it pre-ordered
I don't know
I get the feeling our listener base
More curious about it before they're gonna plop down that kind of money
It's a good deal
I mean the game's gonna be pretty decent
And it's got 12 sports in it
Plus you get Wii Motion Plus
So I mean hey if the game sucks
At least you have Wii Motion Plus
And you know as much I had to buy my Wii Motion Pluses at GameStop
Just because that's where I ended up turning it into my game
So I had a lot of credit
And it was just games that I've had for a while
Or gotten free from work like
Really I'm not gonna play UFC or you know
I don't really give a crap about the Wheelman
So
Wait so the Wii Motion Plus is already out
Yes Wii Motion Plus is already out
Oh interesting
Because uh
There's nothing you can use it for
No there's three games
There's Tiger Woods 09
There's um EA Sports Grand Slam Tennis
And then there's also Virtua Tennis
Okay
2009 or 10 or whatever it is
That's right I remember the Tiger Woods game now
Cause that has some other feature doesn't it
It doesn't that also have
That's Frisbee Golf
Is that the person that has the Facebook
Or is that on Xbox
Um
That's on Xbox
That's
They're talking
I think that was just more of an example
That's not actually being done yet
So much news
Um
No but you can actually
Play Frisbee Golf and stuff in Tiger Woods
So that's kinda cool
And then
Um
Yeah but anyways
So I bought mine at
Um
GameStop
And if you aren't using trading credit
Or you know
Happen to getting
You know free games that
Are really old and crappy
That
You're just basically
Pay with cash or something like that
Don't go to GameStop
Cause they're charging
$5 over retail
They're charging
$25 for the Wii Motion Pluses
They retail at
$20
They know it
They just figure people are dumb
And gonna buy it
And yes I was dumb
And bought it
But the only reason I bought it there
Was because
It didn't really cost me anything
Since I traded in
Games I got for free
So
Who cares
You know
And really yeah
I could have gone to GameCrazy
Or something like that
But
I'm just not gonna drive the extra distance
And then go to someplace else
Other than GameStop
So
Who cares
But I did buy the last two that they had
So that was kinda cool
Um
And then I'm sure I'll eventually use them
But
I just haven't gotten around to it yet
But uh
Yeah
Just that's pretty much
I have a lot of games
You know
On deck I guess to play
And I just haven't really
Gotten to it yet
But hopefully now I'm done messing with
Grand Theft Auto 4 for a while
Cause I've really modified all that I can modify right now
Um
That I even wanna mess with so
That's
Where I'm probably gonna leave that
And then maybe I'll get into
Red Faction Guerrilla or Arma 2 this week or something
Alright
Well let's see
I'll start with games
And get into personal stuff
Um
Let's see games I played this week
I've still been playing Fuel
I think I've played
I think I've played Fuel more than Loki has now
I know
I'm really
I keep wanting to go back to him
I've unlocked four zones now
Which is still nothing
I mean there's like 19 zones
There's
There's a lot
Of orange to peel
In Fuel
Uh
The world is so vast
How are the third and fourth zones
Cause what's the third one they unlock
Ah
The
It's in the middle
The Dry Run I think
Is the name of the third area or something
It's kinda towards the middle
It's to the right side of the first area
Okay
Uh
And then you unlock a fourth area
Right underneath that
I actually haven't played a lot
In the third and fourth areas
Because I'm still obsessively collecting
In the first two
And I learned about this little trick
That lets you use any car
In any race
If you hit the back button
At just the right time
When the race is about to start
You can actually play
SUV races with a bike
And so on
That's awesome
So yeah
I thought it was actually kinda cool
Um
It really helps in some of the races too
I guess you could say it's cheating
But whatever
Who cares
It's a glitch in the game
It's a silly game
You know
I don't think Fuel should be taken
seriously
But it's
It's big dumb stupid fun
Um
And the world
The world really is huge
Like you just
I can see though
Some of the reviews I've read say
You know
And I've talked about this game
It's probably going to my third week
Talking about this game
I don't wanna kinda
Reinvent the wheel here
But I think one of the most common
Negative things I've read in reviews
Is that
Yeah you have this big open world
But full of what
There's really not a lot in it
And I think
I kind of am getting
Getting to understand that point of view
A little more
I do find this game fun
I think a lot of the courses are pretty cool
There isn't a lot that really is
But at least in the first few areas
Have you gotten to any of the like
Weather things like tornadoes and stuff
Not the tornadoes and stuff
So that's where I'm hoping
I've seen
I've seen some screenshots of that
And that looks crazy
I did do a heavy wind type race
But all that did was kind of decrease my visibility
And put this weird filter on that just made it look like
Stuff was blowing in front of my car
And everything the whole time
It was
I don't know
Like
I
It's hard to recommend this game for
$60
But at the same time
I can't put it down
Like I don't know why
Like I'm obsessively collecting all the vista points
And all this stuff
Maybe it's because I'm not playing MMOs right now
But there's that MMO driving me
To obsessively collect things
That I don't really need
So here I am trying to
Like I've unlocked an achievement now
For getting 10 vista points
I think I'm up to like 12 vista points
And for some reason
That's like my big goal in this game right now
Is like okay
I gotta play the arcade races
Until I can get the doppler truck
That I can run into
To get the vista points
Because I want all the vista points
Because that's supposed to be the prettiest areas in the game
I'll tell you what
There is some neat stuff
Like one of the vista points
You remember how last week you were talking about
That you drive through
Like a forest fire
To get to one of the zones
Yeah
Well one of the vista points is like
On a hill overlooking that fire
So it's kinda neat
Huh
You usually have some really interesting areas
So
Um
Yeah
You know
It's such a hit and miss game
If you like arcade racers
Like I do
Like just big dumb stupid fun
I think you will get a kick out of this game
But I think fans of more realistic racers
Are gonna get driven nuts by this game
I will tell you the one thing that does drive me nuts
I installed fuel to my hard drive
And I think it's causing more crashes
Than ought to be there
Is that um
Like sometimes after I do a challenge
If I do a challenge right out of the camp
The game locks up on me
When I try to go back to free run
Really
The loading times are just
A little silly
You know you
You have to wait
When you move to a camp
And then when you load for the race
And then when you
You know
It's just like
I'm having to do a lot of unnecessary load times
Well the load times I think
For the races and stuff
Is because it's
Like warping you to a different part of the map
I get that
But why does it have to reload
When I change from one camp to another
If it's just a new menu
If I'm not gonna
Like
If I'm not gonna exit that menu
Well it
It's loading the actual area of the arc
Cause when you exit the menu
It doesn't have any load time
I don't think
Um
It just seems weird
The loading times are weird
But honestly you know
I don't
It's not a perfect game
It's
I'm
I am having fun with it
And I think that's what's most important
At the bottom line
I can be as critical as I want
Of a video game on these
You know
I've driven right through a tree
Like
There are some very big
Glaring bugs in this game
But I don't know
Yet I still have fun
Collecting all the stuff
I wish there was like a trick system
Or something in that
It's fun to drive the motorcycles too
Like you know
And despite the fact that there's this big world
Practically full of nothing
There are like these houses
That will have ramps on them
And you can like
Drive up the ramp
And fly off the house
And you're flying over the trees
There is some silly fun
Well all those ramp houses
Have like fuel on top of them
That you have to stop and get
Yeah
I usually don't stop for fuel
Like I'll try to run into it
If I'm driving by it
But otherwise
Yeah
It's funny when I play on Xbox Live
And turn Xbox Live on
There's like nobody around
Anywhere
Just because
I'm surprised they don't have a way
To turn that on by default
I think more people would be using it
If it was like Test Drive
Where it was on by default
You know what I mean
Yeah
Um
Let's see
Other games I've been playing this week
Magic the Gathering
I actually bought
Magic the Gathering on Xbox Live
Despite our little story
About it last week
And all the fun
I know
Dark Soccer is holding up the cards
We still have to have our duel
But you see
I need to remember how to play again
So that's why I downloaded the Xbox Live version
That was the little point
That we were going to play
Unpracticed
Oh my bad
Well I couldn't resist
I had to check it out
But um
Yeah
I mean
If you like the card game
It's a fairly faithful reinterpretation
I don't know
I
I still think
Nothing beats
The actual cards
For a card game
But
I guess they did a pretty good job
With the translation
I mean
You know what
Uno
I could make the same argument there
Uno's a card game
But it's still kind of fun on Xbox Live
Because you have the camera and everything
And I was surprised
Magic the Gathering has the camera built in too
I didn't realize that
So hooray
A game I can get used to
Out of my Xbox Live camera
I'm excited
Um
But yeah
The game itself
I suck at it
But I was able to at least beat the first guy
And uh
You know
It's cool
I was having a problem figuring out how to edit my deck though
It wasn't
It's not very intuitive in that regard
And I'm not looking forward to all the microtransactions
That I'm sure are to come with this
But
You know what
For what it is
And considering it's only ten bucks
When the card game itself can start to cost you a lot more
Very quickly
Uh
It's worth checking out
You know
They did put together the game very well
And for
A very freaking complicated card game
I mean
Face it
Magic the Gathering is complicated
And I think it says it best
In the
In the rules
That come up for some of the tournaments
In the Magic the Gathering game
Magic the Gathering
One of its unique features
Is that the cards
At one time or another
Break all the rules
All the rules can be broken
With the cards
In one way or another
That's what makes the game somewhat unique
And
To take that
And have to translate it
Into a video game
Into a logical flow chart
That relies on
Set rules
That cannot be broken
That's a pretty tough thing to accomplish
And they did a pretty good job
I did notice it did seem to flow a lot better
Than the old, old PC game
Which wasn't bad
I had a lot of fun with that
But it did seem like the game mechanic itself
Flew a lot better in Xbox Live
So I didn't play it enough
I need to play it more
But um
Early for
For an early review
I will say
I had a lot more fun with it
Than I was expecting to
As far as how was my week
How was my day
Um
Today was kind of neat
I went to Pride in San Francisco
Which is you know
Of course the big gay Pride parade there
They do every year in San Francisco
I used to not be a fan of gay Pride actually
Um
Because I hate how the media will show that
And that is the impression unfortunately
That a lot of folks out there have of gay people
Is that we're all drag queens
And we all like to run around in our g-strings
Uh
And you know assless leather chaps
You know wearing nothing but handcuffs
Um
And that is so not true
And uh
Definitely not me
Okay
That's for sure
Uh
Hey I don't have the body for that
So uh
You can thank yourselves ahead of time for that
And B
It's just not really you know
Sure I've done Rocky Horror Picture Show
For a long time
But the rest of that
You know the
The big stuff they do out there
I don't know
It's just not me
And I don't like the fact that it's
The impression that some people get
Because some people are naive
So I used to kind of have a problem with it
Because it was so excessive
But let me tell you this
In straight culture there's a lot of
Excessive stuff as well
I mean think about it
Pride is no different from
A Playboy mansion party
The girls next door
MTV's Spring Break
Thank you very much
How is that any worse than what goes on at Gay Pride?
It's really not
MTV's Spring Break is just as bad
As anything you're going to see in San Francisco
It's really
I mean I haven't been to the parade there
But I've been to the Castro Street Fair
Which I've heard has almost a similar reputation
And it was really
Not that crazy
There was some crazy
It's not that shocking
No it's just
So you might see
A topless lesbian
Oh my gosh
You see those in France
Walking down the street
You know
I saw a couple of dudes
Running around in some tight shorts
But you know
Topless lesbian
Sweet
Who?
Brigitte Nielsen?
No
You know what
And then I always see that argument
What about straight pride?
Well I mean like MTV's Spring Break
Is a little bit of straight pride
I think in a way
But also I don't think pride
Necessarily has to do with
Just being gay
I think it's about just being different
At all
Just being
Out and proud
That doesn't necessarily mean
Out of the closet
And all that
It just means
You are who you are
And you're damn proud of it
And the hell with what other people think
So I've come a long way
In kind of accepting gay pride
As part of the gay culture
And I don't feel the gay shame
That I used to
I actually do still agree though
With Patton Oswalt
Is that the gay pride parade
Should actually tour from state to state
And go everywhere
Instead of just the cities
Where you're not really shocked
By it existing
Like Tuscaloosa
Nice
So yeah
I did that today
And that was cool
Except for having to stand out
In the blaring sun for like two hours
Less cool
But you're in San Francisco?
It still was hot
I mean even though it's San Francisco
Right by the ocean
You have a nice breeze
It was still hot
What was kind of cool
Speaking of hot
Gavin Newsom walked right by us
He was like right there
And Victoria
Who hasn't been on the show in a long time
Gavin Newsom
He's the mayor of San Francisco
And he's going to be running for governor
In 2010
He walked right by
And Victoria exclaimed
Oh my god he's even hotter in person
I was thinking of someone else for some reason
No he's very controversial
But anyway
I'm not going to get into politics too much in there
But it was just kind of cool to see
Someone that a lot of people know
Right there
Let's see
The rest of my week outside of today
I'm going to be honest
I've had a very
Bipolar week
I've had a weird weird week
My birthday was Friday
Which was cool
Because you know
I got to see friends
And hang out with folks
And had a party
Which oddly
It's the first party I've had in like a year
Where rock band and sing star
Did not make an appearance
And I had it in my car
Shocking
Right
But I don't know what happened
I think just everybody was just kind of into
Just talking
And you know
The TV just hardly ever got turned on
But for music
On the cable music channels
So it was just kind of like
You know
Just kind of a different type of party
Which was cool
Um
Let's see
And um
As far as the rest of my week
Okay look
Like
What a crazy week it's been
Like um
Especially if you're a Hollywood celebrity
Right now
Right
And you might be wondering like
I wonder if OLR is going to be doing a tribute tonight
To uh
The uh
Uh
Michael Jackson
Or Farrah Fawcett
Or Ed McMahon
Or that infomercial guy
What was his name
Was that the Sham Wow guy
Billy Mays
I don't
Obviously I don't follow this stuff
I don't stay up late enough
Um
But okay so he passed away
But see I've had a lot more weighing on my mind this week
Because um
Somebody I actually know
Who I don't
And one of the first questions I got asked about this was
Has she been on the show before
I don't believe she has
Um
Even in the few many years of the show
I think a lot of people
Um
That are on the show know of her
Her name was Beth
And she passed away on Tuesday
Which sadly was also the anniversary of the show
And uh
She passed away from swine flu
Or H1N1 virus
She'd been in the hospital for 11 days
And uh
Unfortunately used to come to
Um
Complications of swine flu
Basically her
I don't want to get into
Gory detail
But you know her kidneys failed
Her lungs failed
It just
She was brain dead
And that was the end of it
So they um
You know had to do what they did there
And um
It was just kind of the whole things kind of weird
I don't really know how else to explain it
Surreal
It's very surreal
I haven't really
You know I'm not going to proclaim that I was Beth's BFF in the world
But I really respected this woman
And I saw what a motherly figure she was to all her gays
And just people in general
Not just the gays
But you know people in general
And just you know what an accepting fun person she was
She was always like the type that lit up a room
One thing I will never forget about Beth
Is she was the first person to tell me
When I was dating a certain ex of mine
She was the first person to tell me
You can do better than that
Rob you can do better than that
And
She was right
That's just her motherly instinct in her
And um
You know we lost a really great person this week
To something we don't really understand
Which is so weird
Because you know
And so many people have made fun of swine flu
Myself included
And just like
Oh the media is blowing out of proportion
It's this big epidemic
And you know
It's pandemic level six
And all this stuff
And you know a lot of us are kind of like
Well more people die of the real flu
But
All it takes is one
To really affect you
And uh
You know
Whether she was
She was the first person in Sacramento County
To die
Of H1N1
And it's
We still cannot comprehend the impact
They're having a memorial for her next month
July 25th
And there's a part of me in my mind
That
I don't
I'm treating this like a four year old deals with death
I'm like literally thinking in my mind
We're gonna go have a party
We're gonna go hang with Beth
They're throwing a fat party at Beth's house
It's gonna rock
But like
There's a part of me that still doesn't get
That she's like not here
You know
Because I think it's something that nobody understands
Like H1N1
That I'm not able to wrap my head around it this week
So
I apologize if I'm not
As sympathetic to some of these celebrities
That have passed on this week
Folks that have contributed
I don't think anyone blames you
Well folks that have contributed great things to popular culture
And so forth, etc
I realize they don't blame me in the same way I don't blame them
I'm a little sick of hearing about
All these folks in the media and so forth
I feel for their families
I feel for what they're going through
But I understand
I'm coming to terms with why the media shoves this down our throat
For the same reason why Beth was splashed over every local news station
Here in Sacramento
Is that
I don't want to get too deep here on a video game talk show
I'm sorry but this has been a lot that's been on my mind this week
Seven years we do what we want right
Death is something that we don't understand
We have a lot of reasons and things that we try to come up with
To explain it
That's religion right
But at the end of the day we don't really understand death
So when it happens
We do what we can
To try and I guess understand it
I don't know is there something you want to point out
I actually wrote a blog post about it after
Because the day that you posted about Beth
One of my good friends at work
We found out he died
That's right
And I found out that he had been a little sick
But was just going to go see the doctor because he was experiencing heartburn
But of course heartburn also was one of the first signs of a heart attack
And he didn't come in on Monday
And I actually was looking for him on Monday
We had been talking about Linux
And I was going to show him my laptop
And we didn't see him we didn't hear from him
He's always super good about calling in
He's like the man there
He knows so much about everything you know
And just completely fun to be around
And then Tuesday one of the people in his department
Called his sister
And so she sent her husband to go check on
His name is Pete
And went to go check on over at Pete's apartment
And found him dead
So
And I freaked out
And then of course that same afternoon is when I went in to have my consultation
So
But it's like I came home
It was I think I actually wrote up my post on my blog
And I'll link it in the chat if anyone wants to see it
Just about getting it all out
Because it's like you were saying
And my own belief is that
And this is again this to me I'm sorry for getting philosophical
It just happens
I don't think anyone singled out
I don't think that there's any sort of cosmic vendetta
I don't really believe in karma
I want to make this very clear
Because a lot of people even locally
And reading comments on news stations and stuff misunderstand this
I want to make some things clear
Beth did not go to Mexico
Beth went to Las Vegas but Beth did not go to Mexico
Beth
None of Beth's friends have this disease
Those that live with her those that know her have been tested for it
This is an isolated incident
She was healthy
Yes she was a little overweight
But you know what so were most of Americans
Welcome to the USA
She was a healthy, fun loving, happy individual
This has not been explained
This may not be explained
That's the weird thing about it
It happened
Here's honestly this way
That's really in my belief system
Disasters
Whether they be something like this
Whether they be a hurricane
Whether they be a flood
I don't think that it's any
Like God's punishing people
I don't believe that God punishes people
I think God's got way too many other things to do
To deal with our petty little problems
Honestly
And so I don't believe
That there's a great cosmic hand
In the disasters or the good things that happen in life
I think they just happen
They're not in motion to happen
They're not predestined
This is how it happens
She may not have had
A good immune system
As far as that goes
Some people
I've known people who have been
Almost hospitalized
From just plain old illnesses
I had pneumonia for three months
And it almost went in the hospital
I just really think it just happens
And the best way to deal with it
Is just accept that it happens
And remember the good parts
I want to thank the chat room for being so supportive
On our big tangent tonight
Blue 22 in chat
Death is the one topic that brings people together
That's very true
And some other folks sharing their own very personal stories
About this whole thing
And what's funny
The way Dark Sakura explains it
I don't want to belittle what she's saying
Because I think she's right
Is very similar to the way Sesame Street explains it
Of the generation you and I come from
Do you remember when Mr. Hooper died?
I do
That was a huge
Thing in television at the time
Because that actor who had played Mr. Hooper died
And they had to explain that to the children
Because I don't know how they do Sesame Street now
But back then they kind of taped it
Not live but
It was only a couple weeks behind
A little off the cuff too
So they had to explain it
And the way they explained it
The actor was so upset about it
Go watch this on YouTube
You want to see one of the greatest television
I am not fucking with you
This is one of the greatest television moments ever
Go look up
I watch this live
Go watch Big Bird and Mr. Hooper's death
YouTube Mr. Hooper death
You'll find it somewhere
And watch how they explain it
Because the way they explain it to Big Bird
Is that he's wailing
He's bawling
And finally the only answer that he'll accept
This is just something that happens
Yeah
Anyway
I don't mean to get too off the subject
But with the whole
Tributes to Michael Jackson and all this stuff
And all this stuff in the media and so forth
I don't really want to join in
But at the same time I understand
Don't get me wrong
The man made great contributions to popular culture
Say what you will about his personal life
His personal life
Unless he broke, well whatever
He is who he is
Let's leave it at that
But I think
The reason why everybody's talking about it
And the reason why it's in the media and all this other stuff
Is that
This topic kind of brings
People closer together
It kind of helps people try and understand
What cannot be explained
I mean
Who hasn't heard a Michael Jackson song?
Everybody has heard a fucking
Michael Jackson song at some point in their life
Unless they're deaf
You know what I mean
Even then you've probably seen him dance
Okay
You have somehow been influenced
By this guy one way or the other
So when somebody like that passes away
There's definitely
Everybody's going to feel that type of connection
Like oh I remember that song
Or oh I remember watching it on TV
And like I'm not going to get to see that again
Although that's not really the case
Because the nice thing about being an artist
Is the contributions you make live on
Forever
It feels like something that
And I'm not going to say
Because honestly once I got older
I didn't really care for his stuff too much anymore
But I had a Michael Jackson doll when I was little
You know I grew up that way
I had the Billie Jean poster on my wall
You know when I was little
It's when you have
An icon like that
That is a part of
What formed who you are
Even if it's a little part something that's been an influence in your life
When it's gone it's like
Oh
Oh you know it's that sort of
Huh feeling
Okay but with the infomercial guy that died today
I'm not understanding that one
Do people really truly miss him
That aren't his friends and family
Which I'm very sorry to hear about their loss
It sounds like it was a sudden thing
But it's a trending topic on Twitter
Like really
Was he really that influential
Like maybe I'm missing something
And I'm sorry I don't mean to offend
Keep in mind he spawned
A lot of funny
He was one of those things
Just like a 4chan funeral or something
I would expect
So I think it's just more like
Oh that guy
You know because you don't have
Him to kick around anymore
You know
Especially though for all the celebrity deaths
I was the saddest about Farrah Fawcett
Not because of her fantastic hair
And I think it's horrible though
To die of anal cancer
That's just
A horrible thing
If I try to watch her NBC special
I can't watch it
I get so choked up I feel like I'm gonna barf
But you know what I think the worst thing was
Is that she was gonna marry what's-his-name
We are taking this video game talk show
And really just getting way too deep tonight
Which is supposed to be celebratory
It's our fucking show
Guess what
There's no Santa Claus either
And the Easter Bunny was made up by
Pagans
Bobby Blackwolf our old buddy here
One thing to realize is that he was also on a reality show
On Discovery about pitchmen
And a lot of people watched that
Because it showed more about the way he was outside
Of screaming here's how to order
So that's why I think more people got hit
By Billy Mays than you would expect
I watch pitchmen and all he does is scream
On the show
No really he doesn't
It's weird
No offense to Beth or anything
But out of all the celebrity deaths
Actually the Billy Mays one was the most surprising
It's like holy crap
What the hell
There's somebody that's in perfectly good health
But apparently
The circumstances were all around
Apparently he was on a plane
That landed really
I don't know
Had a bad landing I guess
And it caused part of the ceiling or whatever
To hit him in the head and maybe
Did some brain damage that way and he died in his sleep
What
It was an American Airlines flight
So that's what's
Going on there
He died a few days later I guess
That so doesn't sound
Real
We would be hearing so much more about
This impending lawsuit and all this stuff
I think there will be an impending lawsuit
It sounds like it but
The pitchmen show is kind of fun
I like watching it
I don't mean any disrespect
It's just been such a weird week
We've been celebrating death
I shouldn't say celebrating
But you know what I mean memorializing
Trying to understand
Who will be tomorrow? Which celebrity is going to die tomorrow?
Life in the same week
My birthday was this week
I have because Beth only got 24
And you know
It just kind of goes to show
And I know this sounds like such a hokey
Dumb thing to say
But it really is so true
You've got to make the most out of the borrowed time you got
You do if there's something
That you've been wanting to do for a long time
That you haven't done yet
You need to just do it
Stop making excuses and do it
Because you may not be here tomorrow to do it then
So seriously
And I'm going to have to use instances like these
To remind me to get off my butt
And motivate myself
Because I should be thankful I'm here to do them
The other thing I want to say
Is that obviously swine flu ain't a joke
And I'm not saying you should run around
Be crazy scared of it
Wearing flu masks in public and all this stuff
But what I am saying
Boys, when you use the potty
Wash your hands after you go
Because I've watched people go in the men's room
And then just go right out
Perverts, I'm being serious for a minute here
You know you've seen this too
Maybe you've been a culprit
Walk in the men's room, use the restroom
Then walk right out without washing your hands
That shit needs to stop
We need to have a little more sanitary
We might not be able to stop disease
Completely
We can sure slow it down
And if anything this just goes to further
Emphasize the point that Vegas is dirty
Very dirty
Well, I don't know
We're not gonna know
But here's the thing
Wash your hands
After the bathroom, in general
After eating and all that stuff
Keep hand sanitizer with you
You don't have to be crazy germ obsessive
I don't think we need to start a frenzy
And I think that's sometimes what the media does
But just be careful
That's it
Be careful and don't be lazy
So there you go
Anyhow
That's, I guess, that for the deep topics
Let's get back into video games for a minute, can we?
I know, Loki, you've been awfully quiet
This whole time. Surely you've got some game stories
To take us away
I just want to say, though, again, we don't have a script tonight
So we're just gonna kind of wing it tonight with the game stories
We'll talk about things
We'll open up the Skype line a little bit if you guys want to call in as well
Also, housekeeping
If you want to add us on Facebook, that would be wonderful
OrangeLawnsRadio
Also on Twitter, we are
On Twitter, and we like to read your tweets
And you have readRs
And all that fun stuff
And also available on LiveJournal at OrangeLounge as well
So check us out
Add us on the social networking sites, it's a lot of fun
And if you're not already in chat room
And you're listening to us live on this Sunday night
On All Games Radio, please join us
Chat.All... Chat.
Oops, I almost gave the wrong chat room
Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com
There you go
Actually, I was reading an article on The Consumerists
By having an issue with his bacon of the month club
I was just surprised that there was a bacon of the month club
Of course it makes sense
Because bacon is awesome
And why not celebrate it once a month for 12 months
But uh
Yeah, it's interesting
Apparently not a very good program though
Better to buy your own bacon
But anyways
So yeah, stuff that's happened this week
A whole lot of interesting things
I guess I'll start things off with talking about
Best Buy
They're getting into the kiosk business I guess
And they're actually installing
They're testing it right now
They're installing some kiosks into a few of their stores
That are gonna do
Use game trade-ins
And also use movie trade-ins
So you can actually trade in your games
At these kiosks
And then
You basically get credit for whatever's in there
And they give you the credit
On a Best Buy card
And you get to go spend that credit in the store
Which I think is kind of a neat idea
And hey, you know, I'm all about
You know, getting
Um
You know, alternatives to like GameStop
And you know the thing that's kind of pissed me off about GameStop lately
Is when you do trades
Before they used to go, okay
You know, they scan a game, okay that was $18
Okay, here's, this is $24
And stuff like that
Now it's just like, they have all your trades
They've already put them behind the counter
And they give you pretty much store credit
It's like, well, you know, what if that was not satisfactory to me?
What if, you know, they don't say
Oh yeah, by the way, that one game was only worth 50 cents
You know, that
I don't like how they do that, it's kind of shady
You know, every place else tells you what you're getting for each game
That you trade in or movie or whatever
Is that just maybe the particular GameStop you're going to?
No, it's, they've all been doing it now
So, I don't know, maybe it's just
They don't care or whatever
But they used to do that, so
Now, what's kind of cool about this is
Basically, it works like this
You go to the kiosk
You scan the barcodes of the games that you have
On the machine
And it will tell you how much
It's going to give you for those games
And you say, okay
Whether to accept or deny that offer
So if you accept it
Then what you'll do is you'll pop the disc out
You'll drop the case into almost like a drop box
That they have there, like a mailbox
And then the discs themselves
Insert it into the machine
And it will scan them to make sure
That they're readable or don't have scratches on them
Or verify
I guess
If it's an authentic game or whatever
I don't know, the whole process
To me doesn't seem like it would work
Because
You know, the read
An Xbox 360 disc versus
Reading a Wii disc is completely different
And I mean, if you ever tried reading
A Wii disc on your PC
It doesn't work, it's because they read them differently
They have a different file format
So if it's actually physically scanning
The surface of the disc, make sure there's no
Scratches, I guess
Maybe that's how it's working
There's another one I think that they scanned
Like a little barcode that's in the middle of the disc
I'm not sure if that's how it's working
But either way, to kind of get around the whole
People just burning copies
Or whatever, just faking
Out the machine
You actually do have to scan a credit card in there as well
For verification purposes
At the same time, it makes me wonder
Huh, you know, I get these
Pre-paid cards or whatever from
My work every now and then for incentives
And spiffs, and you can basically put
Whatever information you want on those
Like you literally go onto a website
Log in, and you type in whatever
Billing information, if I wanted to make myself look like
Bob Barker or something like that, I could do that
And there's really no way
For the system to know, so
Here's what I don't understand
Why this whole elaborate
Kiosk thing
If this is the business Best Buy wants to get into
I mean, it's not like the stores are always
That freaking crowded and full of people
They're trying to- Why can't the service associates
Just scan the games and check them out
The old fashioned way? I don't know
Well, maybe it's because they're trying to get into more
Of like a GameStop
Type of business model
But at the same time, they don't want to really
I don't know
Train people to do it? Yes
Train people to do it, and also they're planning on
Doing this later on for- Don't they have to train people
To fix the machines? There's gonna have to be
Somebody in the store that knows how to operate
These machines all the time Not necessarily
Just like, you know, the red box machines
And stuff like that, they're in Walmarts and stuff
They have an independent company that comes out there
And services those machines
And the same thing for these
I have a feeling these are just branded
E-Play machines
Because E-Play is also
Working with, I want to say
Walmart as well
They're gonna be doing the same type of thing
Game trading it, and I bet you anything
They can brand their machines so it'll look like
Any sort of stuff
Walmart's machines are just gonna say Walmart
It's not gonna say E-Play
But I bet you these are the same machines
Because it sounds like the exact same thing that they're doing
With Walmart
I have so many games I should be trading back
I haven't even sold back a game in like years
No, probably been about a year
Probably about a year and a half
Was the last time I sold back a game
What was the last one on the GameCube?
I went and sold that one back finally
Seven was the GameCube one, right?
It was a couple Wii games
Oh no, Full Auto on the 360
I sold that back and the tennis game Top Spin I had
You know, games I just wasn't playing at all
But you know, you don't get that much for them
I think the game I got more for than any other
Was Mario Party
But that's because they'd stopped making it
And it was still in demand
There's a few games that'll be coming in high demand
And stuff like that
But for stuff that I don't plan on playing
Or I may have already picked up
Or whatnot
I try to trade it in as soon as I get it
Because that's usually what it's worth the most
And yeah, I know I can make a lot more money
Selling it on eBay
But to be honest, I just don't want to go through the hassle
And for me, it doesn't really make a difference
Because I'm not really losing out any money
When you think about it
Because I'm paying nothing to get the game
And any money I make from it
Is more money than I would have had anyways
So, I don't know
And a lot of times, you know, store credit and stuff
Sits on my card forever
You know, for a very long time before I actually use it for stuff
Because honestly
You know, with the situation that I have
My Wii is modded, my Xbox 360 is modded
The PS3 is the only thing that's not really modded
My PSP is modded, my DS is modded
I don't really have to buy games if I don't want to
I mean, that's the thing
I don't have to buy games
Because I can get them through other means
If I really want to play them
But honestly, I have less time to play games now
And, you know, I'm really not going to have time soon enough
Yes, exactly
So, you know, there's really
I don't, you know, maybe that's not
A great way to look at it
Because I'm sure a lot of developers and stuff work hard
And, you know, I'm putting out the games
But you know what, it's one game
And I mean, really
I don't know
I just don't care
And I know that's probably a bad, you know, stance on that
But I don't care
I do find it interesting
Everybody is trying to get into this business
It's going to be interesting to see if GameStop
Has to do something to
And other game stores, you know, have to do something
To kind of reinvigorate their business
With all this competition
Well, I could see them maybe putting an actual kiosk
Out in front of their store or something like that
You know, hey, look
Now you can trade games, you know
While we're closed
Or, you know, the other thing that these machines
Can do is allow you to rent
Games as well
Which, you know, they're testing that
And I think that's a great idea
You know, because, A, renting games
You know, especially when you can stick these kiosks
You know, like say in an apartment complex
Or something like that
That's kind of cool
And you can also trade movies into this
Which is also pretty cool because, you know what
GameStop doesn't take movies back anymore
They've stopped selling movies because it didn't work for them
So that's something else
So if you want to trade in
Now you don't have to necessarily buy a game with it
You can buy, you know, blank CD artists
Or, you know, an iPod
Or, you know, TV
That's one thing I do like about it
Is that, you know what, I could see myself using this money
More effectively at Best Buy
Just because there's more to pick from
Or, and the other thing too
You need a gift card for Best Buy
And then you go up front where they have their gift card kiosks
You know, with all these different gift cards
For like, say, you know, Red Lobster
Or something like that
You trade in some DVDs or whatever
And now you have dinner
So it, I don't know
There is benefits to it
And same thing with Walmart
Walmart's going to be doing the same type of thing
Where you get in-store credit
And hey, you know, some of these Super Walmarts
There's your groceries
So I don't see it as a bad thing
And, you know, if anything I do like the fact that
You know, you do have that choice
Where you can buy stuff other than games
Anyway, I want to just throw out there a special note
For the folks that are listening live
Apparently we've had a couple stream cut-outs tonight
While we're taping, I don't know what's going on with that
I just watched one happen
We did get booted on our end and we had to reconnect to the feed
I don't know if we're having
Bandwidth problems in studio
Or if that's something on the shoutcast end
I turned off my torrents
I don't know, it could just be a fluke
But there's nothing we can do here in studio
So we'll just keep doing our thing
Do the show best we can
But as far as we know, it is not on our end
Alright, so let's
I guess move on with some more news
If we can
Darcy, I know you had some things you wanted to talk about tonight
So let's make sure we get that taken care of
Well this is just a bit of interest
I know that there's people who are fans of the
Serious Sam series
So there's actually a PC version of
Serious Sam HD
That came out for Xbox Live Arcade
It will be released digitally
And also in shops
And the console version
However is not going to be out this summer
So it's going to be there
When it's there
So that's pretty good
Serious Sam is serious
I don't know, it looks kind of cool
Kind of like an old school
Duke Nukem type of game
That they're actually doing something to it
Other than just, let's put it back out
Or, hey, well Duke Nukem
I guess, Duke Nukem 3D did
Like that rewind thing
Which was neat
And then I stopped playing the game
That's the problem
They need a new Duke Nukem game
For like, Xbox Live
That'd be cool
Rumor is there might be another one in development
That was Duke Zero or something
Did you read that this week?
Yes I did
And my first thought was
Stop ripping off subtitles for Batman
Because seriously it was
Duke Nukem Forever
And then Duke begins
I'm like stop!
And then Duke and Robin, who knew
Exactly
Speaking of Xbox Live, can I say this real quick
I'm sorry DarkSakura, but you would appreciate this
Have you ever played Garou Mark of the Wolves
The game that came out on Xbox Live this week
I know you may not have played it on Xbox Live
Have you played it in the past?
Yeah I think I have the PS2 version
No I have the Dreamcast one
But you realize that some of the characters
In this game have some really funny names
Like who?
There are some characters
Like Kim Kap Wan apparently had kids
And one of them is named Dong
And that's one of the characters you can play
But then there's another character in the game
And the name of the character is
I'm looking for it here
Kushunud Butt
So you can literally play
In this game
Butt vs. Dong
Or Dong vs. Butt if you will
And I know this is so junior high
For me to say
But what kind of surprised me about this whole thing
The Butt vs. Dong
Is that we still have
This whole controversy going on about
What can and can't be in your profiles
I almost want to put
In my profile Butt vs. Dong
Just to see if I get
You know
A temp ban or something and say what
I was just referencing an epic
Mark of the Wolves fight I had online
Lord
Just saying
If you don't believe me
Go look
I am not making this
Crap
I know
I saw it in Rob D's Live Journal
He had a screenshot of it
I'll give credit where credit is due
And I just started laughing and I didn't believe it
I thought it was a photoshop thing
Like he was trying to make a joke I didn't get
So I looked it up on Wikipedia like the characters
As much as I love Fatal Fury
I went and looked it up on Wikipedia and sure enough
There's a character named Butt and a character named Dong
You need to come over
Well you know what after your dinner
Let's look up the Dreamcast
And get our Garou on
My boyfriend will be so bored
If he's here
He's not much of a gamer we'll see
Why don't we watch a movie
Movie he can do
We'll watch movies
On your sexy blu-ray
God my TV is sexy
Sorry more gaming news
Well I actually do have one other little thing
Sure
You know how we like to make fun of video game movies
You know I just was talking about Silent Hill
I love that movie
They're doing an Uncharted movie
It's actually being scripted
By Kyle Ward who already did
Kane and Lynch
Bruce Willis is starring in that
Pretty cool
I like Bruce Willis
Because he's aged better than Harrison Ford
Except for Hudson Hawk
No
Moving forward
But
It's also
Being produced by
Some former
Marvel people
Avi and Ari Arad
Who are also producing
The Lost Planet
They were actually
Going to adapt Lost Planet
To a film
So hey
That might be neat
If they do it right
The whole thing
With this video game to movie
Adaptation
It has to be done right
You know
We can't have
We can't have another
Repeat of
Super Mario Brothers
Oh lord
That's a movie I've never watched
I've seen a few minutes
I've seen like a few minutes
Of the end
I've heard it has funny scenes
I thought that movie was alright
I've never seen it in theaters
And you know what
So what if the Super Mario Brothers movie
Was crap
What the hell are you going to do
Plot wise with Super Mario Brothers
I mean seriously
There's nothing that they could have possibly done
That would have made any sense
At all
And you know
Props for them trying to come up with an original idea
To be honest
So it was kind of a rip off
Of Judge Dredd in a little bit
If you look at futuristic
City and stuff like that
But hey there's references to everything in there
And you know
At least they tried
What is up with your icons?
You know what the default
The default icons on our site come from
That's the default? Oh that's the WordPress one
It's a user generated
Site
I'm never getting rid of my Deadpool
Anyhow was that it for your stories today?
Well not for my stories
But that's all I'm going to talk about for now
Well then we'll come back to you later on in part B
Why don't we?
Alright cause we're going to take a break soon
But I want to get a few more stories out
I know Loki's got a bunch he wants to get through
I'll let him get one more
But let me just give you a couple quick ones here
Because some celebrity deaths
Are crazy around Hollywood
You know if I were in Hollywood right now and on prescription medications
I would be so worried
For what it's worth
But hey Michael Jackson if you want to
Have something to remember Michael Jackson
By of course we were talking about how art lives on forever
His Thriller video is actually free
Right now
Or did it just end?
I didn't get on and get the video
It is an epic music video
Like I wasn't sitting in my living room
I was in second grade watching it when it aired
When did it end? Wasn't it just today?
It was today I guess
Today's not over?
Well it's 200 Microsoft points now so
Well it was free
Sorry if you didn't get your hands on it
You know I actually do remember when that aired
I do too MTV used to air the whole darn thing
Well there was a special thing they were doing
It was supposed to air at midnight
And my mom
I was in second grade
And my mom let me stay up to watch it
When it aired at midnight
I kind of agree with
Frisbee and chat, chat.artisanshredder.com
Just go to YouTube and watch it
If you need to see the Thriller video
Fire up your Playstation 3
And go to the web browser and pull up Thriller on YouTube
There you go, free
In fact lots of Michael Jackson videos
Available for free
Thanks to the wonders of YouTube
Thank you Frisbee
Appreciate it
Hey some other stories going on out there right now
Apparently there is some new developments
On games coming to Playstation Network
At least in Japan
Final Fantasy and Mega Man
And I am talking the old school Final Fantasy game
That's right Final Fantasy 1
So I know this is weird because
Final Fantasy 1 was on the NES
But here's the thing, this is apparently
The Playstation re-release
Or whatever
Which was the original but with some minor tweaks
It was the one that, it's sort of like what they put out on the PSP
But not what they put out on the PSP
I want to clarify that
Because the one they put out on the PSP was like really
It was almost high def and stuff
It was really fancy
They added some dungeons and stuff like that
In the PS1 version or whatever
But I don't know
Well now here's the thing
Mega Man 9 actually
Came out in Japan way later than we got it
I don't know how that happened but they did
They got the game a lot later than we did
They just got it and apparently
There is some type of competition going on
In Japan right now
If you enter this competition you get
Rockman because that's what they call Mega Man over there
Rockman Complete Works
It's Mega Man 1 through 6 which I think was some type of
Playstation compilation they had
Before the one they had here on
Playstation 2 and GameCube
Because that's when they added in 7 and 8
So yeah they have 1 through 6
Available on a Playstation 1 disc
But it's now on Playstation Network over in Japan
So hopefully keep your fingers and toes crossed
Maybe these games will come out over here
At least that's what people are hoping
My thought? Don't bet on it
I don't think either of these games are going to come out in the west
You want to know why? I don't think they're going to go back and bother
To re-translate them. Why would they? They didn't before
Do you think somebody is really going to go in
And translate Final Fantasy 1
Just to release on Playstation Network?
Fat chance
Didn't they have that over here?
There was something that was a Final Fantasy collection
It was a few games
On the PSP they have Final Fantasy 1 and 2
No they actually had one on the Playstation
They had the one that was 5 and 6
And then they had the 4 and Chrono Trigger
So maybe those will show up
On Playstation Network
That's certainly a possibility
I think it would be actually kind of rad to see
The 5 and 6 compilation show up
Final Fantasy 6
Not a Final Fantasy game that's been visited in a little while
And it's one of the greatest if not the greatest Final Fantasy game
Period
So 4 is getting a lot of attention again thanks to the after years
But 6
Oh my god if they didn't after years for 6
I'd be all over that
Don't even tell me
I'm still all over 5 by the way
I still think 5 is the best of them
Let's see
GameGuru says Mega Man Anniversary Edition actually used
The Rockman Complete Works versions
Of the NES games so they've been translated
Interesting
They still won't go back yet
You know what if they did
It would be a pleasant surprise
But at the same time I do own the compilation
On GameCube already
I don't really need it
Well hey you know what maybe they'll move to
Since they're going to be doing the digital download
Stuff now
Maybe they're going to try to move more towards
If they do a Playstation 2 emulation
Or something like that
The full Playstation 2 game downloads
Just like they have with the PS3
At least with Burnout
Maybe we'll see that when that happens
I know there's a lot of Mega Man and Final Fantasy
Fans that would love to see these come out
On Playstation Network
I would say maybe Final Fantasy 1
For PSP will be on the
Download because all the PSP games are shifting
To download only I think that's inevitable
At some point
I don't know about these exact games
By the way though I will say this though
Final Fantasy 1 that Playstation remake is only $6
That's not bad at all
But I'm telling you I don't know how this one was
On the Playstation but if they didn't update
The battle system to the more active
Time battle that they featured in the PSP
Remake the more Final Fantasy 4 style battle
I can't like it's so
Hard to go from what you're used
To back to old
School Final Fantasy battle which was
Like if you attack the monster and the
Monster dies mid round then
You lose your attack gets mixing a lot
Harder back there and
The whole thing and the magic not being based
Off of MP but a whole different system
So what if they
When I have to tell you what popped into my
Head though when you mentioned Final Fantasy
And Mega Man it's like
Mega Man in Final Fantasy
Hey that'd be kind of cool
So
Game grew also
As for Final Fantasy is it the Playstation 1
Version because Final Fantasy Origins came
Over here no I know that but I'm talking Final Fantasy
1 not the
It wasn't Origins the 5-6 combo
4-5
No 4 and Trigger was another
thing they called like Final Fantasy
Chronicles I want to say
Forgive me if my memory
Is fading it's been many years since that came out
But there was yeah
Well there was a time though that I would have hopped all
Over this but I had
The
I actually bought a wonder swan color
So I could play Final Fantasy
Still no word on Mystic Quest
Who cares
Loki
You got anything else for us maybe one more story
Before we go to a break tonight? Yeah sure why not
Well apparently
There's some more details coming out
About No More Heroes 2 and this is
Coming from Nintendo Power
And there's
I guess 3 different plot details
That I guess can be considered spoilers
But apparently
Shinobu the teen
Assassin from the original game will be returning
In this sequel
As a playable character her
Fighting style I guess will be different
Than Travis' and
She'll move faster it can even jump
And I guess you can play her whenever you want
They're expecting
That there's going to be 50 boss battles
And you'll also be able to play the bosses
With either character
And just to mix things up
And there'll be different cutscenes
And stuff like that for that
And then finally it says the primary reason that
Travis is taking on the United
Assassins Association again is to
Avenge the death of his best friend from the first game
Bishop
And unfortunately I didn't play through the first game enough
To probably get to any of those
Plot points but
I am kind of
I want to check out the sequel though
And probably go back to the first one at some point
Once again you know that would
Probably require me to
Somehow slow down time
Which I don't think I can
Need more hours in the day
Let's go ahead and do one more
I see you have a whole lot of stories there
We're going to have so much stuff for Part B
Let's do one more
Australia has decided to
Block online access to games
With content beyond the rating
MA-15
Apparently this will
Apply to
I guess
Console games
Also famous MMORPGs
Such as Second Life and World of Warcraft
Very well may be affected by
This new censorship policy
Wait a minute I thought I heard something about this a while ago
They were talking about that World of Warcraft would not be playable
In Australia or something
Is this like a further development or something?
Maybe I'm crazy
I thought I heard something like this before
Sorry man I don't mean to like
Move in on the story
This sounds like we've heard something like this before
I remember
They will be
Very well may be affected
By this new censorship policy
If it pushes through
That online games exemption on
Content ratings is the only reason
Why multiplayer games with
User generated environments are possibly in
This country
Without it it would take
One game user anywhere in the world to
Produce objectionable content
And the game environment to make
The Australian government ban the game for everyone
They're just saying
Someone's going to ruin it
But yeah
Apparently I guess
Second Life will probably be
Part of that since
Second Life is pretty objectionable as it is
Interesting
Why did they want to ban it? Just because they can't control it?
They can't release it?
Second Life is about to be locked
It says
It will be barred under
The mystery sinister filtering plan
This is going back to
The whole MA-15 thing
Because there is adult content
In Second Life
There's two sexy things
As Destructoid puts it
There's adult things everywhere
That looks pretty adult to me
I don't know
Well hey before we go to break tonight
We have a couple things we want to get through
We got to get to the classic game of the week
But I also want to get some voicemails out of the way
Because it's been forever since we played some voicemails
Here on the show
And I know we had a few on the line tonight
That we wanted to play
And I got to bring up the voicemails here
First off
Well just listen
Just listen to these voicemails that were left on the line
These are actual phone calls to our Skype line
When we're not here
You can call at any time 877-GAME-OLR
And leave us a message
Yes hello
Is this Mr. Roberts?
Yes hi
This is the Pure Dildo Factory
In Washington D.C.
In New York
We're calling in regards to your order
For two dozen big black floppy dildos
We're having difficulty delivering
Your personal batch of two dozen
Black floppy dildos
God dammit
What?
Happy birthday Rob!
From all of us here at USO
I do not condone Travis
And his dildo selling
That's a matter of you two
But happy birthday
No no no
Rob we know
You're missing your monthly shipment
Of big black dildos
We know you like big floppy black dildos
Because we know you like putting big floppy
Black dildos in your butt
So what?
Absolutely we know you just love having to do that
So anyways
Happy birthday and
You know you might want to
And check FedEx for your
Delivery of big black floppy dildos
Well thank you to our
Friends at Understation Live
Sunday nights here on All Games Radio for leaving us
That lovely little message
That I'm sorry but I find that highly offensive you guys
That was a really
I'm just like really offended that you would
Go and like joke about that kind of stuff
On your show because like really
Big floppy black dildos
Really? Come on how old are we
Like 12? Besides everybody should know
It's big hard
Black dildos not big floppy
Black dildos please
Don't waste my time
Hey let's go to the next voice mail
Hey it's Misty
Yeah I know I'm kind of
Late as always
Always with these damn things
But yeah
Congrats on 7 years guys
Also
Assuming I am off
Next Sunday
My damn old butterbee though
I will have
An announcement to make
So y'all better be fucking prepared
I'll go ahead and let you go
I gotta get ready for fucking work soon
Bye
Well sorry to hear about your fucking work but uh
Yeah that's a little teaser
If I've ever heard any
Alright we got one more voice mail
Just to be warned I think this is
Another one that came in on Saturday night
That's all I need to say
Hi Billy
Billy Mays here with an exciting new product
Zombie Be Gone
Are you tired of zombies harassing you and your family
At all hours of the evening
Try Zombie Be Gone with its patented
357 magnum technology
One shot to the head takes care of all your
Zombie problems
Filming $19.99
Act Now Wolfs give you a free batch of OxiClean
Get out those tough zombie blood stains
With OxiClean
Zombie Be Gone the only way to take care of zombies
Like me and keep Michael Jackson's
Skin white with OxiClean
Act Now
Goodbye
Yeah
I guess this is how
Some of us cope with bad news
Alright if you want to leave us a voice mail
1-877-GAME-OL-R
Oh
Travis still up to your old
Shenanigans after all these years
Anyway
Let's get to the classic game of the week shall we
Dark Sakura always likes to take a trip through the archives
And pick a game that you kids
Should be checking out and playing every week
Well you can
Play the game every week if you want
But she also gives you a new game each week that you can play
So here it is
Dark Sakura's classic game of the week
So Dark Sakura
What game should the kids be playing
This week?
They should be playing Dragon Force on the Sega Saturn
Wait like Dragon Force from Guitar Hero?
No
Boo
Let me pull up the audio here real quick
In the studio
Tell us a little bit about Dragon Force
What this game is all about
Dragon Force is a
Combination real time and turn based strategy
Game
It was actually released in America
As a working design
Translation
We never did get the sequel over here however
The sequel was pretty freaking good
But basically
You play as
One of this continents eight rulers
And
Each ruler of course has a different goal
One wants to rule the whole thing
Someone wants to unite everyone
People want to destroy it
And so you move along these paths
From towns to castles
And you want to capture the castles
And then you face off in battle
So you have your
Strategy tactics
Where you're moving around
From
Town to town across your map
But then when you
Get to towns and castles you have your
Battle and you play as the general
Commanding their troops
And so once you
Get to that part you're
Commanding these epic battles
And it's you know you have a
Also an
End game week where you do
Administrative stuff where you tend to your troops
You know you can increase the number of your troops
You can pay them more
You can capture
Enemy generals
Join your army, fortify castles that type of stuff
But the big thing
Is really the epic battles
And
This is probably
One of the greatest video games
Of all time in fact
It won EGM's game of the month award
In 1986
If you skip
Just a little bit
On that video you can get to the battle
There you go
You get to see
Your big armies and I've actually
There's battles of larger armies than that
This game looks different
It actually is really a lot of fun
In fact
It's like you really
To make this work for radio
That you kind of watch them like
There's these big armies
And they're kind of throwing fireballs
And things like across this field
And you watch the TV kind of scroll through this field
Until it gets to the other army
It's kind of interesting
It's like a side scrolling RTS game
The battles are
Term based like that
So you basically
As you can see in that part now they're actually doing melee
You know your goal is to
Capture or kill the other general
And so
Each general can attack each other
They've got their special abilities
But you can also send your troops to
Overrun the other too
You know so whether or not you want to leave yourself
Defended or whether or not you want to take over
The other general
It's pretty neat
It's like you're commanding your own army
Actually I think they based
Did they base Advance Wars sort of off this?
I think a little bit
But this definitely
Kind of thing
It's epic
This game is an epic game
Just like Dragon Force the band
Which who knows maybe that's where they got their name
You never know
Could be but um
Actually go ahead and link that in the chat room
Let people take a look at it
Because really it's something you have to see before you play
For those of you listening on the podcast
You can always search for this on YouTube
Dragon Force is two words
Just look for Dragon Force Sega Saturn
Version is very
Very hard to find
Very hard to get
It's a working designs title
Good luck
They did do a release for it
As part of the Sega Ages
PS2 collection
But that version isn't Japanese
I like that the
Troops rally
They yell and run into battle
That's pretty hardcore
You got your troops falling in battle
Doing their best to defend their generals
So it's pretty
Pretty cool
So a RTS RPG
Action-y kind of game
It's so hard to describe otherwise
It's very hard to find here in America
But good luck
Maybe you'll find something
Out there that's playable
Well in Japan it was published by Sega
But it's a working designs
Release over here
Dragon Force is the classic game of the week
Yes
And I believe that's all there is to say on that
So
That's going to do it for part A tonight of Orange Lounge Radio
But fear not we have plenty more to get to tonight
Including the mailbag, the FUs of the week
Your calls and more gaming news
And we're going to get to that all
After a quick break here in studio
At Orange Lounge Radio
So stay tuned guys, we'll be right back with more
Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
On this June the 28th of 2009
Where we're celebrating our 7th anniversary
Of Orange Lounge Radio
With nothing of particular or special
Notice we're just doing the same old crap we always do
Although we got really in depth tonight
In part A, kind of having a long side discussion
But you know we're just kind of
Just having a really chill night
No pre-planned list of
Topics to cover tonight
We're just doing whatever we want to talk about tonight
And the latest and greatest in gaming news
We'll get back into some more news
I'm hoping Loki has a few more stories for us
Maybe one more story then I'm sure Jamie's got a couple too
Sorry I'm reminiscing about
The steak I had at Daily Grill
Back during E3 because that was the best
Steak ever. Where's Daily Grill? I've not heard of that
Well this was in LA
But they actually have one in San Francisco and one in Brentwood
Have you ever been to Ruth Chris?
Uh
No. I'm telling you that is an incredible steak
It's expensive
If you and the wife go there you're gonna spend 80 bucks
But it is
Good steak
That's my favorite steak right there
The best steak though, seriously
Daily Grill, the New York Pepper Steak
As cracked pepper
Bacon and onions on top of it
Oh my god is it
The best steak ever, I'm serious
I'm gonna have to check that out at some point
It is awesome. Wait did you go there this year during E3?
I went this year during E3
It was right next to our hotel
Nice
Anywho
We've got some news
Let's see which we'll pick here
Um
How about
Let's talk about how crappy home is
Fewer than one in three
PS3 systems are connected to
PlayStation Home
According to Peter Edward
The director of PlayStation Home
Europe, PlayStation Home has gained
7 million users
worldwide with 3 million in Europe alone
And
But you know of course with
21 million PS3 sold worldwide
That's you know
Less than one third so
He considers it
You know
Well he considers home of course
The starting point for PlayStation 3 online
Of course I would say he's a little bit
Biased since you know he is the director of
PlayStation Home he kind of has to say that
But um
I don't know it's just
If a lot of people are like
Me they just
It's neat it's a neat idea
But
I don't know I just don't want to go
To PlayStation Home
Okay but here's my thing
Like I realize that's how the blogs are kind of skewing this
Is that oh nobody's on PlayStation Home
But since when was 7 million
A bad number of people to have using your thing
I mean isn't that actually kind of good
I mean at risk of sounding like a Sony fanboy
Is one in three in this case really
That bad because
Yes I understand Home is free
I guess but think about how many people are buying their
PlayStation 3's let's be honest and here's
Here's my little you know let's look at both sides
Of the coin is that I actually think these numbers are
Pretty good for Home but the bad side is
I think there's a lot of people that are buying their PlayStation 3's
Just for Blu-ray players I think their expectations
Were though that 100% of the people
Would be well dream the F on
There are 100 people on Xbox Live
Well okay granted you have to pay for Xbox Live
But I would bet there's
Not even 100% of people
That have an Xbox profile
I bet there's a lot of people
That buy their Xbox 360
And just put the game in and play
Because you don't always have to sign into profiles
And stuff to play games you know what I mean
Like I bet you there's a lot of folks
That don't bother with all this other stuff
That just use their console to play games
And that's it
But you know
It's not the splash they were hoping
To make
I just don't think 7 million is that bad of a number
I got to say
I'm surprised yeah sj100mat in our chat room
Chat.orangelandtrader.com says
There are 7 million PS3 owners
Actually there's 21 million PS3 owners
I'm one of them I think we all are
That's what I actually just said
All three of us own one
So it took me a little while
To get on board
My question though is this accounts
Or is this actually users
You know individual consoles because
I don't know about you but I have four accounts on my
You know
PlayStation 3
One for each region so I can download you know
Games in different regions and then one for Nelly
Yeah but you're an anomaly
You're not the normal type of player
You know even if they were counting accounts
I don't think it would make that big of a difference at the end of the day
So
Let's see
Corypheus in chat says
And you many of those owners now
PS3 Paperweight owners
Were owners of an expensive Blu-ray
I don't know
There's still games I've played on PlayStation 3
When I got mine it was a cheap Blu-ray player
Yeah I know it was a cheap Blu-ray player at the time
I didn't pay for mine so
Can't get much cheaper than that
Dark Soccer
Do you have anything you want to cover?
Actually I do
My feet with socks no I'm kidding
They want to expand
The cameras
Through a broader online service
So they want to use
TV, the cameras, your phones
And they're thinking of launching that
Around Spring 2010
Or at least that's their general idea
There was an article
In Fortune about
What they want to do
And it's basically saying
That they want it to be the ultimate multimedia
Experience
That, you know, if you have
The multiple Sony products
They're all linked together
Kaz Hirai
Was actually quoted saying
That the service will overlay the backbone of the PlayStation
Network but be broader and more open
So you'd be able to
Download movies to TV
Share photos between devices, friends
So basically they want to make
Xbox Live
But I don't understand
What's this whole camera supposed to be?
I don't get it
They're saying that it's just part of the whole thing
They want to
Incorporate all of their electronic
Products into this big network
I see, okay
It's spreading around
The company brand, why not?
Where do you think most of those movies come from?
Sony Pictures, right?
They're saying that basically they're going to start small
And work from there
To just basically
Get all the different services that function with each device
And then roll out their plan
I don't think I would ever
Buy a camera
On PlayStation Network
But, you know, if
Even only a small handful of people do
It's not that much resources to probably put this up for sale
On there, so why not?
You know what I'd actually like to see do
If they're really working on networking people
Is actually have a true
Teleconference
Video conference ability
Kind of do that with Xbox 360
But that's just one to one, right?
You can't really do more than one camera chat
Yeah, it'd be neat though if you could do like
Your multiple chat room
Interesting
Anyway, that's just my idea
Don't steal my idea, Sony, or I'll stab you in the face
Shove crayons down your throat
Well, wait a minute
Didn't they have the old
PlayStation 2, wasn't there itoy chat?
That came out?
There was
A late that everyone had moved on
I think to the next generation of gaming
And people weren't really talking about itoy chat anymore
Like I remember
This was a subject of a lot of mocking early on
Because it was just, you know, like
Just we could see
The potential for abuse in this thing
And, you know, they had talked about moderation and all that
I'm wondering, whatever happened
Did this game actually come out?
I'm wondering if it didn't just
Get pulled before it ever came out
Now I gotta check it out
I totally gotta check it out now
I'll research that, you talk about something else, Logie
Okay
Let's see
Apparently there's another rumor
From the Ars Technica mole
Saying that there's gonna be some
Console drops
Or price drops, at least
Coming, well, this fall
For both the PlayStation 3
And Xbox 360
Of course
In the past, the Ars Technica mole
Has been correct about a few other things
Including, you know, the
Capabilities of the PSP Go
Or the release of the
Resident Evil 5, Xbox 360 bundle
And
I guess the
360 price drop last fall
Apparently it says on the Sony's front
They're claiming that the 80GB
PS3 will become scarce
Over the next two months
And will be mostly replaced by the 160GB model
And the
I guess
Larger model continues to sell into the fall
And apparently they will simultaneously
Announce that the
PS3 Slim
And
The even more, I guess
Rumored price cuts
Will be announced around the same time
And
They don't know how much it's gonna be
Dropped in price, but they know
That there will be one
And also, Microsoft
Pro system apparently is gonna be
Phased out
And something else
Will come up in its place
Apparently the Pro will be replaced by
The 120GB Elite system
Now wouldn't it be awesome though if they dropped the price
Of the Elite to the price of the Pro system now
Then they may come out with something
Later on that's even more, maybe something
With Project Intel built in
I don't know
Or maybe a slimmer 360
Who knows, that might be neat
But apparently
The 120GB
Or the 120GB Elite
Will undergo a price cut
In September
And there will be some new bundles coming out in October
And that makes sense because they're releasing
New
Bundles all the time
By the way
I did the research on itoy chat
It's kinda hard to figure it out
I mean if this game did come out
It kinda landed with a thud
It only came out in the UK
That's what I'm able to kinda put together here
Is that it did come out in the UK in 2005
That must have been a long time ago
I remember selling it so I don't think it actually
Came out over here
I do remember selling some really stupid things
Although itoy chat
I don't think was ever one of them
Again I hate to bring up an old subject
But itoy is what makes me nervous
Of things like Project Natal
And these other motion controllers
Especially Project Natal
Is pretty much the Sony motion control
Because the Sony motion control feels to me
More of a souped up Wii type thing
Where there's sensors in the controller itself
And the camera
But Natal that relies apparently only on a camera
It makes me nervous because itoy
Was the camera too
It was great in theory
But look how old that camera technology is
And granted yes the Microsoft vision camera was no better
Absolutely not better in any way
In fact I might argue it was worse
At least the itoy actually
Might mock the games that came out for it
At least it had some sport
I believe that the company that they bought
I'd rather play itoy chat than totem ball
Yes totem ball really sucked
And itoy play was kind of okay
It was funny
And hell we used it for our webcam
For a while
I'm more confident that they would
Test this and test this and test this
They're not going to just
Splash the market with this
Project Natal and have it be shit
I mean why would they do that
That really opens themselves up
Whereas itoy I think was more of like
Hey this is kind of neat
We'll compete against
Somebody with this
But they didn't really do anything with it
It was just like hey now there's games that use itoy
DDR hey there's hands and feet mode
Which sucks
And yet they decide
Hey let's do
Wiimote and nunchuck mode
Which surprisingly enough also sucks
And then
Now there's the Wii balance board mode
Which also sucks
So maybe they should go and learn
Their lesson from this which is
The extra modes while an interesting idea
And maybe slightly consider
Innovative maybe
As a stretch
They will always suck
And 8 arrow mode
Any guess? It's gonna suck
Alright well I'm hearing Loki
Getting a little angry over there so I think it might be
About time to bring on the FUs of the week
But how could we do an FUs of the week segment
Without starting it off with a story about a dumb
Criminal and yes there was a criminal
In Pittsburgh where apparently
In the town of East Liberty somebody
Tried to break into a GameStop store
But they didn't do it the old fashioned way
No they climbed in through the ceiling
That's right they decided to cut open the ceiling
In another I guess nearby place in the shopping center
And climbed into the GameStop
Basically through the roof but here was the problem
Once they got into the store they couldn't
Get out because the front door and the back door
Were locked and I guess it was not the type of door
You can unlock from the inside
You need a key to open that up
So how did the burglar get out?
Well they went back through the hole that they made
They climbed back up through the hole
They do have surveillance tape but no sign of the criminal yet
But the thing that makes this most hilarious
Of all they didn't walk away with a damn thing
Damn thing
So uh
This guy just wasted everybody's time
In this case and whenever we hear
About a dumb criminal I'm sure it always
Inspires us to see a little angsty here on the show
So uh yeah
Let's do the FUs of the week
FU to pain and heat
Extreme heat
Whoops didn't mean to cut the music out there
Um it's hot
So if you do it being hot
I would also say FU to the fact that it's hot
Hotter than hell in here
Not in here but out there
And then I would say FU as well to um
Ah I had something else on my mind
FU to go to the doctor on my birthday
That's no fun who wants to go to the doctor for their birthday?
FU to getting old
I like the age I was when I started this show
I think I was then
31 now what?
Things get better in your 30s they really do
I hope you're right
We'll see
First of all you don't have the stupid angst you had in your 20s
And you give less of a fuck the older you get
I don't know I do still have a lot of that angst
Once in a while
I take that back
I have given less of a fuck the older I get
How's that?
I don't give a fuck
More gaming news
Do you have anything else tonight Dark Saga?
Just release dates right?
Oh god I have that too
Why don't we just get into release dates here
Tonight's just kind of a very whatever kind of show
Fuck it night here on Orange Lounge Radio
Why not it's our little 7th birthday here
We're just screwing around tonight
Dark Saga is going to kick off some release dates
As soon as she gets it brought up there on her monitor
Start off with the UK
And what's coming out overseas across the pond
Oh yeah it's July isn't it
Or it will be
So let's go ahead and start off with our
Our July releases
How's that sound?
Oh god did they actually give me any July releases on here?
No
They're not listening to July releases
Well what good is that?
Oh there we go
Sorry
Brain broken sorry
The heat has melted her brain
God I almost did
Punisher No Mercy on Playstation 3
We have on the 3rd
Call of Juarez
Bound in Blood
Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince
On a bunch of systems
Street Fighter IV on PC
Tiger Woods PGA Tour 10
And then
That's it
Gonna get some Monkey Island after that
Sweet
Let's get into some Japanese release dates
And see what's coming out
On the other side of the
Pond over across the Pacific
Only some price cuts on the
Xbox 360 this week for Bioshock
Infinite Undiscovery and Shin Sengoku
Musou 5 all getting price
Cuts this week which I believe that
Last one was Dynasty Warriors if not mistaken
Yeah that's Dynasty Warriors
Empires I think or Dynasty Warriors
Five Empires
Six Empires
That is also getting a price drop on the Playstation 3
For the fancy HD systems
On the Nintendo Wii this week
Grand Slam Tennis
Is really the only game you have to look forward to
On the Wii this week coming out from EA
Looks to be a pretty slow week
Over there in Japan but if you are
Still a fan of the Playstation 2
I got nothing for you this week
But there's a baseball game coming out next week
You can look for that
Coming out on the Nintendo DS
We have Mina no Oekake
Yasan
This is going to be some type of drawing game
Because I recognize the Oekake from being that whole
Drawing on the internet thing
That looks to be exactly what this is
Probably some type of like share with your friends drawing
Draw a penis on the internet
It looks like it's teaching you how to draw Oekake
Is what it's doing because I see this little like
It's walking you through how to draw
Like a happy little sheep there
So that looks like a fun little game
It's like painting training
I guess you could call that game
That's really it on the DS
Anything on the PSP
I guess this is a slow week when your biggest release
Is an Oekake game
Oh well they do have this game
Hatsune Miku Project Diva
Comes out for Sega this week
You know what Hatsune Miku is right?
The Vocaloid
You know where
You input the words
The tune and everything and then she sings it
This looks to be yeah a type of music game
Actually coming out over there
Having what's it on?
PSP
Yeah having the Vocaloid game on PSP is pretty cool
Rob really you should
I'm gonna find you something to play
Interesting yeah you actually
Kinda this is a rhythm game that you
Put in these
Kinda another type of syncing game
And it makes your dance
So check that out
That would be a big release coming out this week
Over there in Japan
That's it for Japanese release dates
In the US there's
Kata and Half-Blood Prince
Which will be on all platforms
Available for gaming
Steam Bot Chronicles Battle Tournament
On the PSP
So a free release of that
Or at least a port of the game I guess
Street Fighter IV on PC
Two Mega Man Star Force games
Mega Man Star Force 3
Red Joker
And Black Ace
Also
Ice Age Dawn of the Diasaurs
Which all platforms
And Grand Theft Auto 3
Or I should say Grand Theft Auto 3
Vice City
And San Andreas are all coming
Together in a brand new
PC trilogy that's being pre-released
Call of War is Bound in Blood
On PS3 and Xbox 360
Treasure World
Which is a DS game that uses
Your Wi-Fi signals to find treasure
That's kinda neat
So that'll be coming out in the DS
Ruger Twisted Towers
On the Wii
And I believe there's another Ruger game
Coming out in DS
Now this is a sequel to an Xbox Live Arcade game isn't it?
I think so
Blaze Blue Calamity Trigger
Sort of a launch
Limited editions coming out on
PS3 and Xbox 360 as well
Ummm
Let's see
And then a smaller
360 game that not a lot of people have heard about
Infernal Hell's Vengeance
Which was on PC a little bit earlier this year
That's making its way out to
Xbox 360 at a budget
$39.99
I guess that's not really too budget
More budget than full price
Ruger Attack which is on the DS
Also another Ruger sequel
Ummm
And then that's it for this week
I'm kind of happy to see
Arma 2 is coming out next week
And I still haven't gotten a chance to play the
Actual
Steam version but
Looks cool
Alright so backing up to the Japanese release
States a little bit, Dark Soccer you sent me this YouTube
What the hell is this I'm about to look at here?
This is what the
Vocaloid is like
You're gonna turn it up
Oh
This is just some really
Weird version of Don't Worry Be Happy
Well I picked something in English
But you input the words
And the tune and everything
And it plays it back like she's
Singing and she's your virtual idol
Oh interesting
So you're actually like pushing the buttons to sing?
No you just input everything
Ahead of time and then
Watch it play through
If there's one of her doing
Caramel dancing I'll find it
No thank you that's alright
But I think that's
The music maker
Well the PC ones are I don't know exactly
How the PSP one is going to be
But ever since the first one came out
There's been a ton of
New Vocaloids and
Everything it's pretty big
I think this is what a Dark Soccer
One is going to show
I think that's an
Animation that someone did
I'm going to park really cute
But yeah
Alright let's get back into some more
News, Loki you got anything for us?
Yeah sure why not
Apparently EEA
Is calling their Sims 3 leak
It's demo program
Saying that
You know you've identified our
Secret marketing campaign
EA CEO John
I'm not even going to try to pronounce
His last name
Ricotelio I guess
That was actually pretty accurate
It's a large scale
Form of large scale
Large scale piracy I guess
Was a pre-release version of
The Sims 3
Basically saying that
It was a way to
I guess
Figure out
Some data and stuff from this experiment
That they may
They've gotten a lot of people to buy the game
Based on trying this version of the game
That leaked out I guess
Apparently if you're a pirate consumer
They don't get the second town
They don't get all the extra content
And they don't get the community
That's bullshit
Yes that sounds like complete shit to me too
Because basically that's all download content
Funny enough
Funny enough that he would say that it's a pre-release version
Because right after the game came out
That version got leaked too
So oh shit
Guess that's not a real
I don't know
That didn't fix any problems
I think it sounds to me like they're making excuses
Because a leak like this
Had to have come from inside
Since it was leaked out like
Weeks early
He's doing a cover your ass
And it just makes him
Sound pathetic
So well
Hey whatever makes you sleep better at night
I guess
Yeah it kind of
Sounds more like uh oops
How do we explain this one or something
Ha ha ha you fell for it
Well I think what he's saying
Also too is what they're going to try to move towards
Later on
Is selling more services
So meaning like a game like this
Where you buy a lot of extra additional content
And stuff
And I think hey that's not a bad idea
If you want to say release the game for free
And then have download content
That you pay for that makes sense
But
At the end of the day what's going to end up happening
Except they'll probably not sell a lot of that
And you know what else is going to happen at the end of the day
Just like all the expansions for Sims 2
Those will get leaked out as well
So all your plans for
Download content
Will work
Just to say also everything that's available
On the Sims 3 store
Is available for download through BitTorrent
People have already done it
People are already doing
It's just
Really starting but people are already starting to do
A few custom items already
It's not going to be too
Too much longer
You can download everything
That's there in the store
But if you really like the game
You should just go buy it
I bought my game
Encourage them to make a Sims 4
Although Sims 4 is probably inevitable
Someday
Many years down the line
I just want a nice graphical upgrade to Sims 2
Sequel to successful franchise?
Nah
Well speaking of sequels to successful franchises
I want them to make pretty faces
And better hair
Well I want pretty faces and better hair
To play that game again
No not really not with Final Fantasy 14 on the horizon
But Final Fantasy 11 has been getting some crap
This week
Apparently they got sued this week for 5 million dollars
Apparently it's because they
Supposedly
Allegedly I guess is the word to use
They did to 100,000 customers
Deceived them for unfair business practices
False advertising
And unjust enrichment
This is Esther Leong
Who filed the suit in San Francisco
Claims that Square Enix
Lied about or concealed its monthly fees
Penalties for late payments
Interest restrictions and other things
That should have been fully disclosed
At points of purchase
So that's why they're saying they're deceptive
And if you go on to read the court filing
It actually goes on to detail it a little more
Saying among others
There's deceptive advertising, unfair and undisclosed
Business practices, here's a list
8 items on the list
Licensing of the online game software disguised as a sale
Monthly fees or fees to play the online games
Penalties for late payment of the fees
Interest charges for late payment of the fees
Charges while the online game account is suspended
Termination of the right to use the online games for late payment of the fees
User restrictions and conditions related to the online games
Termination of game data for payment of the fees
Granted, that's not like on the box
But yeah, it's all in their little fact
But that's after you bought the game
But at this point
at this point when did he buy this game because you know nowadays you can get
this game and all the expansions for like 20 bucks I mean and really is $20
worth you know suing over I don't know and so if you will sue about anything
and if you didn't make your payments well who's fault is that stupid I
actually whether or not you purchased the game it's sort of like when you
keep in mind I work in the mortgage industry it's like when you go buy your
house you know you can pick out your house and you can make all the
arrangements to purchase that house but you have to sign the agreement to
actually be able to live in your house you know and in your agreement it says
that you are paying for this this and this that your lender has the right to
church this isn't this if you don't do shit
guess what same way in that type of contract you have to read it
this person has no right to sue she's completely responsible for her own and
and they they even ask you when you're signing up did you know be sure to read
this contract do you accept these terms and you know whatever it's not their
fault she didn't read it well this is what I don't understand I played this
game for three years I had when I never heard of them charging interest not a
single person in my league shall ever talked about this if it is really late
payments I guess but if you pay late there's no paying late you pay a lot of
pay disable your account you want to pay right and if your credit card bounces or
whatever you can log in yeah but like I don't know do they charge you before the
new month is up say like I pay for a month or whatever like that they charge
in the beginning of the other month because if they charge me at the end of
the month then you know you've paid for that month and you have you owe the
money I guess for that I think the beginning of the month makes sense I
don't understand I think we need to hear more about what's the way it's worded it
makes it sound like a dummy and on top of all that five million dollars really
for something that sounds like that they just fucked up and didn't pay their bill
customer service could just resolved well maybe that's the problem but you
know I don't know yeah five million dollars a little extreme but I mean if
it's being split among a hundred thousand people is class action right so
technically all hundred thousand should be entitled to their chunk of it so they
all get what 50 bucks a pop 5,000 is that much I can't do math sorry yeah
but still well wait I think it's still 50 times a hundred thousand I think it's
still highly frivolous well it's still a 50 bucks that's you know and they're not
gonna get $50 either because lawyers got to get paid I've let's see going in chat
for our comments chat that orange entree calm Joshi 16 in chat says people sue
over $0 GS 68 says people make patents sit on them then sue GS 68 is saying he's
gonna patent eighth-generation game consoles then get ready to sue Sony
Microsoft and Nintendo so we'll see how that works out for you how about the
mailbag I think it's time we get to some emails you haven't even have an email
bag yet all right we do one more story then we get to the meal yeah I'm pulling
it now look you got another story for us in the meantime yes apparently there's
an off-broadway play that's been inspired by adventure games apparently
it's a how off-broadway pretty off-broadway I guess it's called
adventure quest and explores the convention set by Sierra's adventure
games back in time of well the 90s I guess how is that different from like
just a fairy tale I don't know it's sort of like I guess into the woods they say
oh yeah I know that play that's that's kind of a spoof on well I guess fairy
tales actually is what into the woods is about yeah but apparently I guess this
is currently playing at the brick theater as part of the anti-depressant
festival and it will be part of their theaters gameplay celebration in which
they have a they will have a variety of video game related performances
including let's take a look here this has got to be one of those theaters
that's like only seats 20 people in it you know like it's a real tiny tiny
community theater I can't imagine this is a big production they're gonna have
yes the gameplay celebration is apparently three performances executed
through video games in video game styles three video game or three game party
nights and three weeks of rot your brain video game madness and apparently their
video game party nights include an MMORPG night where you will play your
favorite massively multiplayer online role-playing game in theater rock band
karaoke and then another night will be a chiptunes dance party that sounds fun
but this sounds so off-broadway it's like in New Jersey what's kind of neat
though is like what they have like it's live actors on stage with like no set
work and then the sets are actually like artwork from like adventure games which
is kind of neat okay that's kind of neat I guess what a bunch of nerds but I can
applaud where I want to talk and they actually it's kind of cool they've got
like a little score tally running and nice all right we ready for some emails
yeah all right whenever you want to interact with the show mailbag at
orangeslaunasrated.com is a great place to do it we jump in there and read some
of your emails every week the lovely dark soccer is gonna dive in the mailbag
headfirst and see what males come up for her to read don't forget the hazmat suit
Rob mailbag at orangeslaunasrated.com
first email I just listened to last week's show and I would compare it more
to doom and the start of the first-person shooter genres about being
a BB&A versus DJ hero when a new when a new game genre first appears to the
general public it seems like the best way to classify is by calling it a clone
of the first most popular game in the genre for more recent example look at
how sandbox games were called GTA clones until a few years ago and that's from
Corky842 who also sends an addendum ps the last email was brought to you by
beer in the palm pre Wow I don't know if I have a lot else to add to that that's
an interesting comparison I didn't even think of the doom like the whole like
doom quake Wolfenstein type of connection last week but very interesting
point um cheeseburger says I miss MJ dude you're too young this one says hey
y'all I downloaded the new iPod touch firmware tonight first of all I paid 10
bucks for this why is this really good or am I an apple lemming or both the
second this update actually looks interesting the copy and paste is not
really what I'm used to but what was I expecting parental controls are good if
you're a parent as I am NOT it's useless to me the shake to shuffle feature is
nice though and really useful when my baby's crying album kicks in well that
that's awesome for Apple to charge for firmware updates I didn't pay for mine
you don't pay on the phones you only pay on the I touch or whatever oh well how
generous of them I know I don't care I have the phone yes third assuming you
didn't cut me off with the baby comment they've done something to improve typing
messages and I love them for it landscape typing makes the buttons
noticeably bigger and improvement that helps me a lot now I don't miss type
every other word yay well that's all for now
steak hair entertainment this message was typed an iPod touch which I have and
you don't ask yeah I have an iPhone actually I do really like the the
upgrade I like having five panels for my apps instead of the three and I'm pretty
pleased with it pretty pleased also I really like some of the changes that
they've made to the it's okay I like that I can text and landscape now that's
the biggest new improvement same with email but I'm not liking the fact that
the phone just seems to run slower like I guess with all that stuff in there
like a lot of my apps feel like they're running slower but I'm hoping that'll
get showing an improvement I'm hoping that with the 3.1 that's inevitable at
some point you know the minor tweaks that'll fix that all up that's what I
hope next email sure dear olr crew I just wanted to briefly chime in on
something you went over last week that being guitar hero Van Halen I remember
when they announced the game I was actually somewhat interested though that
interest dropped completely when it said the game was Van Halen and not Van
Hagar you know what I love Sammy Hagar most the music by them that I love is
when Sammy Hagar was the lead singer there's only a couple of songs that I
enjoyed that were when David Lee Roth was singing with the group I completely
agree with this by the way and so I suppose that in the opinion of many I'm
not a true fan of the group that is just my own musical taste perhaps now there
might be an opportunity for rock band to pick up the remaining music I'd freaking
love to play dreams thanks for reading it's always awesome for PS I just want
to know that it was very painful news on Thursday June 25th when Michael Jackson
died may he rest in peace but forever live on through his music and what a
great tribute that would be if harmonics gave us the real of the thriller album
is rock band DLC don't count on it now on a wishful thinking I realize
everybody's still wrapped up you know I don't want to get into this topic but
everybody's still wrapped up in the Michael Jackson thing don't count on it
something like that is gonna be years and years in the making because guess
what to the rights to that stuff now it's all gonna be up in the air with the
debt that man left behind if rumors are to be believed it these type of
struggles will go on for years did you see misty sent us clips no I didn't
misty sent us a bunch of clips I think that you should hop into the mailbag too
I might oh my gosh Wow I might have to play those during the afterbirth night
all right okay Thank You misty well I thought he's so rich but his company's
bankrupt kind of I to be honest I don't know nor do I feel like it's any my
business I kind of don't care but you know I sound rude but you know it's not
my finances I got I got my own finances to worry about well we've got two more
emails hi lol crew this is your friendly neighborhood Mexican act daft first of
all I want to congratulate you for your seventh anniversary I've been listening
to the show since 2005 though I became a regular since 2006 around episode 200 I
wish you the best for the years to come thank you acts daft well now to business
ooh so serious well we have all seen and heard the news on the newest DDR and the
latest Bemani news and how disappointing it has been how DDR has burned to the
ground and possibly lost its appeal to the true old fans of the series and
localization of pop music in the States which is a joke for those who know about
the game well call me crazy and stuff but now I'm glad Konami didn't bring
guitar freaks in germania stateside that way we got guitar hero and rock band
which are truly great and haven't lost their appeal to the public no matter how
much activision is milking guitar hero though they did bring guitar freaks
germania to this you know side of the pond I guess in the arcades yes in the
arcades but also as rock revolution unfortunately that doesn't count I still
look at because no one cared about that anyway I still wondered what would have
happened if konami would konami bro guitar Dora but considering how rock
revolution did see there we go I'm glad they didn't granted it wouldn't have
been the same game but still look at the way DDR and pop music are going not good
at all and a guitar freaks germania would have taken the same route and
doomed the rhythm games for years to come so thank you konami for not giving
us guitar freaks in germania rock revolution proved what it what it would
have happened to guitar over the years now don't screw up and don't release
another bad part of beat mania because of scratch and DJ hero heck forget about
the money in the States and let k set jay do their thing at least they know if
the record breaks don't try to fix it thanks thanks for reading this email
again congrats on the seven years entertaining the internet every Sunday
PS adjacent Enos were dead he'd be rolling in his grave right now well he's
not he's alive and well he's um he's at EA now I think I can say that he's moved
on to a better place yes um look I I don't know if I agree very much with the
whole rock revolution is what guitar freaks would have become like although I
can totally see the point about maybe if this game had come out first it would
have hurt the chances for things in the future I can sort of kind of go with
that I guess but I don't think that rock revolution would have happened if it
weren't for guitar freaks I think I don't think rock revolution honestly
outside of music alone I don't think it had anything to do with guitar freaks at
all rock revolution was an attempt to make a copy of guitar hero and use the
Bahmani brand to do it knowing that they wouldn't be able to say anything about
it because Konami did have guitar freaks they did have the Bahmani
thing and just that they just just piss poor execution stop being lazy and
hopefully you know they're learning their lesson when it's this is this game
is an embarrassment rock revolution was there's really no nice way for me to say
it with as much nice things as you know Konami has put out in the past and
people that I even know there and so on there is no nice way for me to say it
rock revolution was an embarrassment to that company and it should never happen
again anyhow any more emails oh yes we did
last one hey Rob Jamie and Matt this is longtime listener SSJ 100 Matt I first
wanted to congratulate and praise you on your seventh anniversary it's amazing
that it was a little less than six years ago that I first started listening to
the show I first discovered OLR through a friend who recommended the now long
defunct Wednesday show outside the box from there I discovered the Sunday show
and the rest was history I know you guys get enough praise as it is and for the
sake of this email I will keep it short no I like praise keep keep it I like
that somebody remembers outside the box I barely remember that show that's crazy
I was a sideshow I hosted years ago with some friends and you three have
sacrificed seven years of your Sunday nights for the sake of us the listener
and have never asked for anything in return we the listeners can never make
that amount of dedication up to you except to continue to listen tell to
people support and write for the website like my blades of steel article cheap
plug cheap plug which was a very lovely article actually check that out it's on
the website orange on twitter.com but seriously thank you so much for
informing and making us laugh for seven great years now that I have all that
praise out of the way I wanted to ask your guys's opinion on something over
the course of this next two weeks I will be having a few get-togethers with about
25 of my friends we of course intend on having video games be the centerpiece of
these parties I was wondering if you had any ideas or recommendations for great
party games that we may want to try playing as it stands now we have Gears
of War 2, Team Fortress 2, various Wii party games, Street Fighter 4, Left 4
Dead, and of course Rock Band 2, Guitar Hero, World Tour. Your input would be most
helpful and once again thank you thank you thank you for seven years of great
radio your super Hebrew pally, SSJ100 Matt. Well you mentioned the Wii party
games I was actually gonna say there's the Mario party games are pretty fun I
think you've named about what I would have named Oh Marvel Ultimate Alliance
get your four player on instant party just add Rock Band it's so true seen it
is actually pretty fun but you know if you kids are kind of worn out on that
stuff go back to the old school stuff seriously whip out Super Mario Brothers
3 you can you can get a party around the old school game oh no hook up a dream
cast Power Stone 2 it depends on the type of audience did he say it was other
gamers I'm sorry I was playing yeah this is the games are to be the centerpiece
that's what I other gamers or is it like just random kids our age you know what
if you this is what I like to do sometimes because we've had parties like
that you know before if you want to see certain stuff go on say hey bring the
system and bring your favorite in a group game and we'll we'll switch out
through them what's the problem with that hmm I guess that's true yeah it's
like a like a ball man a potluck on video game that's actually a really good
idea a potluck of video games bring a favorite game I like that so that's the
last one thank you as she 100 Matt for your kind kind word for the cowards hey
I opened up that file yeah that a Misty sent us oh my gosh there are so I don't
even know like where to begin with these clips there's like a million frickin
clips in this thing I'm just gonna pick like just a couple of these random files
and play them just because I'm curious and we're in kind of a fucking mood
tonight let's see this file is called into lesbians let's see what this one is
it's like if twin was a girl then his girlfriend would want to date him anyway
she's in the lesbian right I don't even know these are from let's try one of
these longer files to see this one says OMG gonna break your own band la la la
go into the mailbag open oh I need mailbag music let's open up the mailbag
right there might be more I have to play one Jenny Rom song just because it's
fit we're gonna play oh we're gonna play yeah you know me email me is not Jenny
Rom that's why don't you know on girl you want blonde girl you want email me
you really want me you're gonna break your own ban it's not on the normal
playlist all right actually it used to be but I took it out cuz you banned
Paul a Terry remember all right interesting god there's some random
stuff in here um surge and Pepsi blue that shows you how long this show's been
on the air Lord I want to see what this is God surge tastes like shit
how come weren't even that like okay important okay you don't like surge it
you can drink that Pepsi blue shit remember how god-awful surge was terrible
Pepsi blue I tried storm didn't like storm
was awesome though we had a vending machine at Q's are all that was in it
was surge and I love that stuff whenever it's very sad that it's gone now I'm
looking at these other long clips here Rob with candy full what the hell is
this speaking of dirty things though guess what happened hmm it's a guy he
got sued for sexual harassment a 31 year old employee of Tecmo shouldn't that
have been speaking of candy candy is delicious anyway wow we're gonna get
emails on this I already know no okay okay absolutely there is an in joke
about candy in one of my circles so anyway a 31 year old employee of Tecmo
said that our dear friend who was behind that are alive was basically sexually
harassing her the compensation she is looking for anyway she's seeking
compensation in 10 million what the hell it's candy get it this candy is not so
delicious huh huh wow let's see one more here offensive things you've missed I
like the word offensive Linda woman she's literally sent like a ton of clips
I I could we could just sit here and play these all night long and we'd have
like a whole show full of stuff let me do this and we'll do some more video
game stories let's see offensive things you've missed some of you guys may be
thinking well didn't you guys used to do the rewinds on your own damn station
sky yeah actually that's true but now it is the oldie and moldy Wednesday
flashback where we are 100 episodes behind right now so you can hear what
the show sounded like two years ago it's pretty nuts I kind of looked at the chat
and some of the response to last week's episode and I think I think Missy or
somebody had said it's a good thing I wasn't there because I would have ripped
them a new asshole so so here what offensive things you missed out on on
back on episodes 20 and 21 and all that stuff we're playing way back when so
check it out it was on our old old station we used to play shows that were
like three years old and I don't even know like a we lost a ton of shows when
one of our hard drives went out so it's which is a bummer they might still be
around you know who added me on Twitter the other day was DDR angel and if
anybody has older well our episodes between her and misty we could probably
find them all anyway alright so anyhow yay clip fun let's do a few more stories
than I guess we'll go to Skype at some point here we've done all the other
segments we need to do tonight right we did if used in mailbag really states
alright how about a few more stories then you're you you did all yours right
our soccer um yeah okay so look you have a few more forms yes apparently there is
a brand new game entering the wrestling game genre and this is being put out by
immersion software on the Wii PSP and DS I'm sorry that's by a different
Argentine developer as Sabasa studios but anyways immersion software they're
putting out on the 360 ps3 it is a lucha libre game yes that's right is actually
gonna be based on the triple-a wrestling circuit and yes it's basically triple-a
the video game and it's got all sorts of lucha libre stars including on the
screenshot here it looks like looks like l la Guido and psycho clown because who
doesn't like a psycho clown oh and they have a teaser trailer up which I haven't
seen yet but it looks awesome as long as they have was it as sent us he's got to
be in there I don't follow this crap so I that's why I'm I know I don't this
makes no sense to me but okay you boys have your fun it's Mexican wrestlers
will be awesome hey I'm not down you I'm just saying I'm not a fan well I'm not a
fan of it either but it's Mexican wrestlers I mean hell they have was it
the also the Santos line of videos you know it's a Mexican wrestler who's like
solving mysteries and stuff like that I mean that's just cheesy and weird you
know what you want to know a Mexican wrestler that was badass did you ever
play Saturday Night Slam Masters no there was a wrestler in that game and I
can't remember his name he was the guy they had this game at my local pizza
parlor and oh my god it was so much fun yeah we used to play that a lot what was
the name of that guy I'm trying to look it up on Wikipedia right now El sting
ray I was his name good times one of the guys from final fight was in the game
the mayor of Hagar yeah Hagar was in Saturday Night Slam Masters good times
so we got a couple more stories we ready to open up skype line what we doing
Skype it well Skype it were there any of the big stories we haven't got to yet
Loki or do you think we got it all code who's coming out next week at some point
that's at a game making software that's going to be available on Xbox community
or indie games whatever it's called at the moment really for 400 Microsoft
points five bucks hell yes I will be picking that up that's supposed to be
coming out sometime around June 30th they're actually going through the same
peer review process as every other developer has to go through so they're
targeting it for some time June 30th ish you know might not be exactly June 30th
but that's kind of cool very cool let me cover a couple quick stories here real
quick before we go to the Skype line let's see our con is coming to the
iPhone which makes me very happy because I remember this game for the Commodore
64 I think it actually did just come out because my friend was showing me that he
bought it the other day it is out for $4 for the iPhone and the iPod touch and
that is available no multiplayer sadly but you can download this and play it on
the iPhone I'm wondering how smoothly it runs but yeah oh god I'd love to our con
I know I've talked about on the show before it was like it was like chess but
the pieces would actually battle each other but not like regular chess you had
different types of pieces like basilisks and unicorns and shape shifters and all
this cool stuff well I've got a few more stories here real quick sure there's a
rumor that one versus 100 is coming out of beta next week and we'll actually be
giving prizes so that'd be cool ah I bet that's not true I think there's gonna be
more of a build-up to it than just oh hey next week prizes I think they'll be
more of a build-up I know I heard that the guy supposedly said something
whatever it doesn't mean anything bit trip core is gonna be coming out in two
weeks and they'll be the 100th we wear game on the service that's kind of neat
bit trip beat was kind of cool I'm wondering how this is gonna be different
I said are they changing anything it's a totally different type of game
interesting yeah okay and of course I'm sure you saw this already
Namco networks is giving burger time an update with burger time deluxe yes I
heard about this I've heard a lot of people call it crap but burger time was
an awesome game in the 80s but you know even I can admit it's probably one of
those things that's better left in the 80s but I will check this out but it
just looks like the old game was souped up graphics in new stages which you know
it's not like the stages are that complicated yeah it's probably and then
finally last thing oh actually got two things
Bethesda their parent company bought ID software so now that's kind of under the
whole ZeniMax I guess was the company that owns Bethesda now they own it's
software as well and apparently the next two games rage and Wolfenstein obviously
are gonna be published under their respective publishers EA and Activision
but now all the further games are being published under probably like Bethesda
or something like that I don't know ZeniMax unless ZeniMax has come out as a
new publisher I guess apparently if you were a subscriber to EGM and since EGM
is kind of gone right now your subscriptions were converted into Maxim
subscriptions which I think is a fair trade if you ask me so that's kind of
neat and then still yet another survey suggesting that Netflix streaming is
coming to the Wii the only difference we get this damn survey like every six
months the only difference now is instead of a one-time fee of $9.99 it
will be free so you will not have to purchase a streaming disc but hey if it
happens it happens cool and then finally Ubisoft that would make the Wii a little
more lucrative than 360 because you wouldn't have to have gold very true
that that's a that's a big feather in Wii's cap don't underestimate that
don't underestimate that can't do HD streaming though for most you know what
considering the type of stuff that's there and I'm just gonna say don't
underestimate that I'm very critical of the Wii on this show but that could be
big free Netflix essentially if you already have a Netflix account Rob how
long does it take for the internet browser to load up and you know the Wii
I mean what if they can if you'll whip it if they can figure out the
connectivity that makes you know games like Super Smash Brothers and stuff work
for like kids programming and non HD type stuff again don't underestimate it
Matt all right big and then finally a Ubisoft's collaboration with Q
Entertainment they are like it's likely to be a music game but me really when
you look at odds Q entertain exactly I mean unless it's 99 nights to which is
somehow doubt no all right look our skype lines already ringing off the
hook and I really want to get to that very soon but one other quick story for
you guys if I could Marvel vs. Capcom 2 big rumors out there that the game was
coming out June 29th not true per the Twitter's official Capcom Twitter is not
coming out June 29th they don't know where the rumor came from well let me
tell you it was from Marvel's financial reports you might want to look at that
but they're saying now it's closer to the end of July that the game will
actually come out so sorry if you guys were looking forward to that one but
it's not coming out that makes sense so because I think wasn't it part of the
summer of arcade or something like that and that doesn't start until like the
end of July anyways yeah I don't know all right look our phone is ringing off
the hook let's get let's get some calls done tonight hi you're on orange on
this radio who's this saying that it calls it almost every single week from
the East Coast I don't know how you get through every time but I'll tell you
what I've seen like seven different names pop up in the corners so you're
lucky tonight what's on your mind that much at first I want to say happy
anniversary to you guys happy birthday congratulations thank you we're seven so
we should be having this anniversary show at Chuck E Cheese yes but you're
still immature as a seven-year-old should be mm-hmm what's on your mind
tonight buddy I have a question about e3 um before you guys went you have made a
statement about how you felt III wasn't going to be the same yeah like different
feelings intake about about before you went did you feel the same way when you
went or what are you talking about the show itself or what I was kind of
lamenting about that nobody I knew was really going so it was going to be a
little weird this year a little bit of column a and a little bit of column B
the show itself I actually think was better it was better than most of the
prior years because I felt like I actually got time to play games the
lines were obscenely long I think whatever they did to kind of and I don't
know this might be in part because the economy but I think whatever they did to
kind of filter out some of the people that didn't really need to be there and
someone might argue maybe I don't need to be there but I would argue right back
mofo but I would say whatever they did to kind of scale back attendance by you
know whatever they did from 2006 was a good thing I think the show itself was
good I do want to see them reopen Kensha Hall at some point get some more
exhibitors out there on the main floor and again the stuff all that stuff is
behind closed doors kind of bugs me sometimes but whatever it's just
something we're gonna have to deal with I think overall the show itself was
better as far as the whole me lamenting about my friends not going and all that
stuff I think a lot of that got better I got to go to a pretty bitchin party on
Wednesday night that was hosted by games for windows for part of their windows
7 kind of preview thing which was actually pretty cool and I got to see a
lot of your faces from around the podcasting community and meet a couple
new ones that was kind of nice I enjoyed stuff like that the show itself was
really different without kind of having the friends there I kind of feel like
from a business angle I got more done I didn't collect as much stuff I felt like
I actually played more games but in again I also kind of contribute that to
the crowd I don't know I you know it's kind of cool the one day Loki was there
we got to go around at night at least I had my boyfriend there that I kind of
got to see at night so it didn't end up being so bad in that regard I think I
would have had even more fun and I would be like more excited and woo and I would
have gone all three days keep that in mind is that's a big thing too I didn't
go all three days this year oh okay I only went two days and I feel like that
was sufficient I got to see everything I wanted to see I was happy with it and I
know there's so many people out there that are probably yelling at me right
right now like you ungrateful bastard I would give my left nut to go to e3 and
you're just talking to your poo-pooing it down but trust me guys it's it is a
very exhausting experience it's it's a lot so if you want to go to e3 but you
can't just go to PAX because and Bobby's made this comparison before and I think
he's absolutely right PAX is probably what you think e3 is so go to PAX I'll
be there PAX East Coast PAX that is I want to be at East Coast PAX I'm trying
but I gotta make West Coast PAX work too and I'll skip West Coast PAX to come to
East Coast PAX come on I can show you all doing both I just heard that they
started doing Southwest flights to New York City now did they really yes which
women are here to party yeah go to Boston Oh boss well yeah yeah you gotta
go to Boston for PAX East well yeah it's close enough for us yeah well stop by
four and a half hours Loki you know what another flight connect a jerky when I
talk to people on the East Coast you know how many times I'm asked so if I
fly into LA I can drive up and visit you in Sacramento right not very easy well
I'm just saying you know you can take a cheap flight to New York and then you
know fly you connect to you know Boston I guess take a train or train there you
know it's not really all that far to Boston besides I want to fly jet blue to
New York City I'm sorry if we're given the option between Southwest or jet blue
jet blue and I've heard lots of amazing things about Virgin Air that's the
airline I want to try at some point yeah a lot of my friends fly Virginia they
just love it I've heard great things about it a huge float today too all
right hey Rama we got to wrap up and let you go but any quick final thoughts
on that that's it that's it later later s21 under Matt says flying to New York
and I'll drive you to Boston that's a very nice offer I might be a good way to
see some of the East Coast too I don't know it's so far off you guys I'll
figure it out don't worry hi you're on orange launch radio who's this
hola bienvenidos all orange moms radio kenis again I always call echo one two
three before you give us a call it's a good way to test your microphone make
sure everything is working just fine before you give us a ring we're gonna
open up the skype line take some more calls higher on orange launch radio
who's this well thank you very much we're potty trained in everything now
yeah I just I want to agree on the past thing that Rama said yeah I mean I want
you to come back these because me and uh Robocool and my friend that I joined us
for ORR tonight he's my friend and frequent broadcast listener he was
saying you know I want to meet Rob Roberts because that'd be the coolest
thing ever cuz I've been in him and actually been listening to your show for
a couple years probably know that about me and not him but I we I think that I'll
go for the cool and it's like wow wouldn't it just be cool to meet Rob
Roberts even though you're not like big but on the internet it's just stuff
that would be so cool well that is very flattering thank you very much I would
love to do it I I don't want to go out there by myself so I'm gonna have to
convince dark soccer or Loki it's a good idea except that's gonna be tough oh
yeah well here's the problem Loki's gonna have babies dark soccer has got
school and all that other stuff other commitments so it's gonna be tough but
we'll I'm hoping wish wish hope hope that maybe some of my podcast buddies
will be going out there too so we can do something maybe I might be if I can I
can get a part-time job I'm about 17 now if I can find myself part-time job get
myself a ticket I will make ever effort to get it to be there especially if you
are there but you know that's just helping so I want to I just want to go
to Boston so I'm gonna make packs but you know especially you know considering
everything we talked about in part a this week and you know you only live
once and all that stuff I want to visit Boston it's a city I wanted to go to I
know a lot of great people in there I want to go visit so I I'm there I'll
make it happen later from somebody that was 30 minutes away and it's been in the
city on occasion and stuff I really say I have to say it is an amazing city you
know it's it's no New York but it's got its own charm charms all I need well hey
did you call in about anything else tonight besides just the pack Tom to be
honest to be honest I I really I normally wouldn't call in without a
subject but it was the seventh anniversary and I'm a frequent listener
so I feel like I'm not trying to like make myself sound cool I just said I
would want to call and see how I didn't leave a voicemail I don't really have
much of a topic and I don't really want to get into that deep stuff again I know
this is more of a gaming podcast but I just want to let you know I really do
appreciate you going into the current news sometimes because really I listen
to ORR for the randomness that can pop up along with the mixture of the
gaming news and that you're not afraid to just have fun sometimes but I just
want to let you know that well thank you very much and you know certainly this is
always an evolving show and if our listeners want us to get back into doing
more of the personal stories then personal stories you shall have so all
right well we're gonna let you go then go right through okay thank you so much
for the call buddy take care have fun in your podcast later have a nice day guys
bye later dude one eight seven seven game OLR is the place to call let's try
going back to the phones hi you're on orange launch radio who's this it's GS
68 hi what's on your mind buddy I came back from the Philippines I wanted to
share my arcade side of the things you came back from where I'm sorry the
Philippines oh the Philippines that's right I think I saw something on your
Facebook about you were going out there oh yeah believe it or not I actually
read the status updates on Facebook and Twitter and all that stuff ice how was
it it was yes all right though like the our case there was good as last time
maybe that's good as I remembered well you know what it's because the arcades
over here probably aren't as good as you remember either look that he still have
some games that I haven't seen on this side of the Pacific Rim years like life
for example Mario Kart arcade GP with card slots but but really surprised me
when I was there was house it at that ex hmm how was that basically it's it's just
bit of a house of death but like they drew it in a cartoony style and you
probably won't believe I'm about to say but basically the storyline of the game
it's a zombie romance like that sounds awesome
zombie romance movie now that's a movie that we need who wouldn't go see that
about this zombie girl who falls in love with her with her prison guard or
whatever and they escape and you have to and it's basically a bunch of minigames
where you have to do things like catch fruit or shoot the bad teeth off of the
stage one fossil positive or better I thought for a minute there you were
about to get into lesbian zombie romance because that was the only way this story
was gonna get even that much better but that's okay
unfortunately no they can do that in the sequel that's all right it's going
through perfect and I well as I mentioned it's awesome games that I
haven't seen in years like f0ax and oh I love f0ax I gotta ask you real quick
though real quick since we have a lot of time tonight what about music games
because I know you're big music game fans is there a big presence of games
the Philippines hello big is there a big presence of music games over in the
Philippines oh I lost I think we are losing gs68 connection I don't know if
that's on your end or our end I'm gonna have to let you go I'm sorry I don't
know what happened with that connection but we'll hope hope maybe he'll call
back later when the connection is a little better in the meantime let me get
to another call hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hello hi who's
this this is leecham six hello leecham six I don't recognize that name are you
a first-time caller yes I am welcome well welcome what a heck of a night hello
well what's on your mind buddy yeah yeah I was wondering have you guys I know
you guys have addressed iPhone gaming and that sort of thing a little bit but
you know what the new 3.0 update they've you can add new devices to it like
controllers and stuff mm-hmm have you guys seen that yeah I've seen this one
it's like a NES controller but it's like a game bone yeah you know we were
hearing about some of this stuff last week I think there was a story that we
kind of got into a little bit about like especially about some of the things
they're gonna be developing for it but I wasn't under the impression that this
crap was already out you can already get this stuff I don't think so there's one
in the works though it looks like a SNES controller yeah it's in the works it's
called the game bone the only thing that sucks about that is it well they had one
I don't know if you can attach it to the game bone or what but they've got like
this controller where you can snap it on to the iPhone or iPod touch and then
they have another one that like you had to have it in like a sort of stand or
something you have to play it with a controller separately and that seemed
kind of stupid but the thing about it is they don't really have a standardized
controller yet so you buy this controller but you have to wait for
people actually support this controller in their games but I have a question so
it's a wireless Bluetooth controller right that looks like a NES controller
doesn't a lot of people already have one it's called a wiimote do that I guess I
just those do run off bluetooth don't they cuz yes put them up to their
computers yes so you could in theory use a wiimote or wii classic controller or
something like that with that if the you know if that's okay with Apple you know
if they can you know support that or trick right or if they don't need to get
approved with that if they just support it in yeah whatever game it's coming out
I would think anything well well here's my question this other thing you're
talking about that whole device the bone or the game game bone is that an Apple
official thing or is that now I'm third party come third party interesting so
that is interesting that that would come out but you would but see Apple so
locked down with that kind of stuff I'm now here I bet it's just a matter of
time before someone hacks the phone to read that yeah I'm actually I'm
surprised that hasn't happened yet I mean the iPhones been out for two or
three years now and we've had Bluetooth the whole time I'm surprised that hasn't
happened yet maybe no one sees the point because you know you can't really use a
Wiimote on the iPhone with such a tiny little screen but I don't see that's
that's that's the point people are missing I don't want to use motion
control I just want to use as a nest controller for my nest emulator and that
makes sense I I'm kind of surprised that hasn't happened I think it's just
because sometimes those iPhones are like Fort Knox to get into I mean not that
that's ever gonna stop the hackers right because how many times do they come out
and say this is unhackable and then today I never act it just seems kind of
pointless of me to have a nest emulator where my fingers cover the screen when I
play well now sir you know those the legality of those nest emulators are a
little questionable the first place so beggars cannot be choosers my friend
well obviously I'm using games that are ripped from my cartridges that I bought
when I was seven of course of course yeah you know I'm sure it's a matter of
time before the Wiimote thing is hacked but you know I don't know if iPhones
really that big of a gaming platform for me iPhone is where I game when I'm
sitting in the doctor's office waiting to be called in that it's you know I
think I think you addressed that last week actually yeah you're not really a
portable gamer yeah but that maybe that's just me so all right well hey
thanks so much for the call any other quick things you want to say before we
let you go not really just love you guys and congratulations on seven years well
thank you very much and you picked a hell of a call in you take care of color
sir later guys that was a very nice phone call by the way there was an
update on a GS 68 he got cut off unfortunately I wanted to ask him about
SV GL Sunnyvale Golf Land and if they actually did have DJ max there and
apparently they do have the final version of DJ max is available now at
Sunnyvale Golf Land because I'm going to be in the okay I think I would guess in
July yeah so I want to check that out and he did play some games in the
Philippines that were music oriented as well so let's go to at least one more
call here and then we'll show in a moment you think that you think the best
last call to end this in the night off with and who am I talking about you
hello legend Zaku what's on your pine nothing much just trying to like trying
to get through all the grief of what was last week and unfortunately earlier
today but I guess we got to move on to bigger better things basically I'm
doing this reason I'm calling today is just to bring up the fact that it and
Bethesda merged which kind of like you know kind of surprised me because I
never thought that you know then John Carmack would actually sell out to
something you know to any particular person aside from EA which he's actually
working with but not to a company like I don't know like Bethesda the folks from
fallout and I'm not or Elder Scrolls I'm not saying that they're all bad and all
but I don't know it's kind of like came out of nowhere um yeah I mean yeah we
didn't really get into it on the show but I guess that was a pretty big deal
about you know ID and Bethesda kind of having their marriage going on there but
um I don't know like maybe I'm just not as big of a first-person shooter fan
that I've been following ID all this time but I know Bethesda makes some very
pretty games so certainly the two of them coming together it's going to be
very interesting but you know what when push comes to shove money talks and you
may have thought that so-and-so was not going to be selling out but you know
when you got bills to pay and you got right he's buying there's always a you
know as long as it's still maintain some sort of creative control you know in
other words if as long as Bethesda's not like pulling their chain to the point of
like choking them out you know creative wise that would probably make sense as
long as they mutually respect each other in that level then they could easily be
you know and everybody wins Bethesda makes pretty decent games though I mean
like obviously you know oblivion is huge fall out to me Elder Scrolls is pretty
much with their bread and butter that's what pretty much put them on the map
right and look but let's not forget Bethesda not every game they put out has
been a huge success the Star Trek game that they did was not you know it's kind
of mixed but at least it wasn't terrible you'll mix better than terrible so their
track records pretty good overall so you know even though it might be something
you didn't imagine before it's not like it's completely unreasonable that ID
would go to a fairly respectable company like Bethesda yeah as I said it's all
about whether or not John Carmack felt like it was something that he should
have agreed with and you know something that I just hope he has confidence in
his decision or at least have you know or at least it itself is confident in
the decision to merge with with Bethesda but aside from that yeah I can't I can't
actually you know end off the call without making a notable mention of
Michael Jackson's contribution to video games I mean aside from moonwalker the
fact that he contributed to Sonic 3 Space Channel 5 I don't know I guess we
never could never really know of how much success this man has because he's
pretty much proven himself God knows how many times on all fronts not only on the
on the stage or on the recording studio but in our consoles well you know
Michael Jackson certainly was involved with Sega he had a lot of love for Sega
and I think we would all roll over if they would just put out a moonwalker too
but sadly it is just not meant to be well I just hope you know hopefully they
could at least port it to Xbox Live Arcade I know whoever owned well but
it's gonna be good it's difficult for the fact that God knows who also well
I said again I say I based on the same thing I said to the emailer who wanted
the thriller album on rock band don't hold your breath because exactly all
these rights being up in the air just just don't even the legal mess is only
is just a tip of the iceberg and I also want to clarify it's not that Michael
Jackson's moonwalker was really that great of a game well the arcade version
obviously it was just it was kind of all right it was a frickin video game made
out of smooth criminal that's what was cool about it but at least he had at
least he made everybody dance whether it be criminals robots or even like vicious
guard dogs dance when he did his magic you can't ignore that that you know even
if you hate music which I don't know anyone that says I hate all music you
can't ignore the contributions that Michael Jackson made to gaming I would
buy uh I would buy it again just on the fact that you can make the dogs dance
we're gonna let you go buddy but thanks so much for the call oh yeah one more
thing happy anniversary guys well thank you I forgot to mention that but and sit
in seven more years hopefully we'll see we'll see I don't know I'd be 38 at that
point all right take care buddy bye we'll always let a call go a little
extra longer if they're gonna do some butt kissing all right let's see Zaku
pilot 256 asked Space Channel 5 was a Sega made game on the Dreamcast right
uh yeah I think Sega published it I think it was yeah because Mizuguchi at
the time worked for Sega so it was a Sega made game yeah yeah I I say I think
there's confusion because Mizuguchi now has Q entertainment but he was the
mastermind behind Space Channel 5 when he worked for Sega but yeah and then of
course space Michael yeah huge well he had a bigger part in Space Channel 5 too
there's the whole yeah dance scene that was pretty cool yeah you know good times
good times all right well um gosh it's about time for us to wrap up and get the
hell on out of here for the night but before we do that we have to go around
and get everybody's final thought and I think do we get all last-minute stories
out of the way I think we covered everything we were gonna cover tonight
right pretty sure all right then let's go around and get everybody's final
thought dark Sagra once starts off tonight your final thought the second
density 3 is a freaking epic RPG they really need to give that an official
release already just put it on WiiWare for real really my final thought is I
really need to finish the Rydia after years because the new episodes come out
like in a week yeah just over a week and I'm not ready for him yet I need to
finish where I'm at right now so yep Loki your final thought tonight my final
thought is that I need to play more fuel yes you do I need to kick your butt at
fuel be fun all right all right actually we see we need to go exploring for Vista
points although I guess it's not really a cooperative type of game pretty pretty
tough to play that co-op all right that's it guys we're out of here we are
gonna close up and as we have said for the past seven years thank you guys for
tuning in to orange lounge radio it's your support that keeps us going and
let's see if we can make it to eight I'm pretty sure we will thank you guys so
much for tuning in to us and listening to the show tonight whether it be live
whether it be on the podcast we really appreciate your support remember if you
like what you hear all we ask tell two other people about the show your friends
your enemies your co-workers your fellow classmates in school whatever just as
long as they can handle it because it's a mature audience show tell two people
about the show and spread the word cuz word of mouth is all we got thank you
guys so much for seven years we'll try our best to do seven more we'll see if
we can make it thank you guys so much and we'll see you next time here on
orange lounge radio you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange
lounge radio is an orange lounge production to join us for a live show
visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific time the views and
opinions expressed on orange lounge radio do not necessarily reflect those
of the entire staff of orange lounge radio or all games calm but we're
probably right anyway see you next week