[SPEAKER_07]: Tonight, June 21st, 2009, will you have to pay a premium price for DJ Hero and Band Hero?
[SPEAKER_07]: Could the PSP be getting its own app store?
[SPEAKER_07]: And is Activision really going to stop supporting Sony?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are that show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's always the three of us here with you every week to lead you through the week's topics.
[SPEAKER_11]: But of course you guys play an important role in the show too.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I'm going to introduce you guys first tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Chatters, chat.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_11]: The emailers, MailbagOrangeLoungeRadio.com And the tweeters, or the twitters, or the twitheads, I don't know what you'd call them, at Twitter.com slash OLR And of course the Skype, 877-GAME-OLR, all the different ways to interact with the show And then of course the three of us guiding you along, talking about the topics for the next few hours My name is Rob Roberts, joining us as always, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers Yo How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, sort of.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, sort of.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And playing Sims 3 again.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's two in a row.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, but I'm only doing it in the background.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: How is Sims life going?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, for some reason, okay, there's a very small chance of getting knocked up with just plain old woohoo, as in fucking, and it always seems to happen to mine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoopee, like they used to say on the newlywed game show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's fucking.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't you remember the old newlywed game show?
[SPEAKER_11]: Where's the strangest place you've ever had Whoopi?
[SPEAKER_11]: In the butt, Bob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also joining us, and I don't want to know the strangest place he's ever had Whoopi because the wife's into porn.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_11]: Doing good.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what else to ask you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I played Peggle on iPhone Okay, that's different And it was pretty fun I just played it once and got to the third level, I guess So it was pretty fun I love those types of games, though And, of course, playing Sims 3 Which is pretty cool Okay, people in the modding community Hurry up and fix their damn faces And fix the damn hair I'll give you a dollar Start now
[SPEAKER_01]: and I played Black Knight 2000.
[SPEAKER_11]: The pinball game?
[SPEAKER_01]: The pinball game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can hear pinball noises, by the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: We just got a Lord of the Rings.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got rid of Creature from the Black Lagoon, finally.
[SPEAKER_11]: I liked Creature from the Black Lagoon, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Machine was a bitch.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It seems like it would be a bitch to maintain because isn't it like the thing where there's a top level and then there's like a see-through underneath that or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just like a hologram and you can just change out the hologram.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: But really, Dan really wanted Lord of the Rings so he said he'd get rid of Creature for Lord of the Rings and the opportunity came up.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he's out there playing it right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: He's been playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know practically every piece of dialogue coming out of that game now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: and I've been playing a lot of Solitaire and I downloaded a bunch of games for my new netbook.
[SPEAKER_01]: I put Linux Mint on it so I've been exploring the gaming in Linux and actually they've got a bunch of game packages just available to select.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm playing one called Capman, which is Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_01]: and Sudoku and some of the little stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have a version of Lode Runner.
[SPEAKER_01]: They have all kinds of neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: As soon as I find kicks, I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you've been enjoying your Linux Mint, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've been talking about installing it on one of your computers for months now.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was going to do the old one, but every time it happened, something would go wrong or the CD had a scratch or some crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so I finally just said, you know, fuck it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Completely got rid of...
[SPEAKER_01]: I completely got rid of XP because I hated all the crap that Dell put on it and just like you know what I'm gonna go completely Linux on it and I don't regret it at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love having multiple desktops especially on such a small screen and it's been pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, sounds like you've actually been pretty busy with games that weren't The Sims.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, duh!
[SPEAKER_11]: But then also plenty of Sims 3, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're making out right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're making out right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to ask you to update the listeners on what's going on in their Sim world right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I actually started over with the same couple because I got tired of them having nothing but girls.
[SPEAKER_01]: They seriously had nothing but girls.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I started over.
[SPEAKER_01]: I started over and I'm just hoping for a boy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, no, they've got a boy now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, they do now.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they have a girl now, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Didn't play much.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played Grand Theft Auto 4 still.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then I also played Saints Row 2 when, you know, obviously live was down on Tuesday for a brief moment.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, well, actually all day.
[SPEAKER_12]: But that meant we had to play something that would allow us to play System Link and Saints Row 2 would be that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I kicked the crap out of everybody in Saints Row 2 really bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did go back though and play some more Saints Row 2 with the actual download expansions that were available for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's only two real paid expansions, so I had already downloaded both of those.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they're okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: There is one escort mission I have to do for escorting some... I have to guard these trucks that are picking up nuclear waste.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, unfortunately, they're really retarded.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they keep, you know, the cops just spawn out of nowhere and just crash straight into the front of the truck and just kind of sit there for a while and does constant damage.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I have had to repeat the mission about eight times and I still haven't passed it yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's really annoying, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: I hate escort missions.
[SPEAKER_12]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because the AI is really annoying.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then the rest of the missions are just kind of what you normally expect in the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently these are the last two actual things that they're adding on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh well, I guess I'm done with Saints Row 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: But then Grand Theft Auto 4, I'm looking to mod it some more.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I've been just waiting to get my computer set up, which I did today.
[SPEAKER_12]: So hopefully later this week I'll be able to tweak it some more.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: How's the house going, by the way?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know we talked a little bit about your new house last week, but now you're getting settled in a little more, probably.
[SPEAKER_12]: Still unpacking, got the internet and cable hooked up and everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: So just still unpacking and trying to get things cleaned up.
[SPEAKER_12]: My mom and my grandparents came over yesterday and they were helping with just some of the stuff I need to get done around the house.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, patching holes in the wall and painting stuff and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: So yeah, it's just a constant project, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually played a game through to completion.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Shock and awe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I have this thing called Gaming ADD where I always jump from one game to another spending $60 on one game, never finishing it and going to another.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure plenty of you are like that because a lot of games take a long time to beat.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the game I beat was Final Fantasy IV The After Years.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although I didn't really beat it.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to say two things about the story.
[SPEAKER_11]: One, for a real fan of Final Fantasy IV, this story is great.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it is a great written sequel.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's just basing it off the main episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: But even just reading what I've read about the upcoming episodes and so on, I think this story is going to be great and real fan service to fans of the original.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the second thing I want to say about the story is, if you haven't played the original, don't bother with this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It will not make sense to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: There is so much that references the original Final Fantasy...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: and then in Final Fantasy 4 you go underground but the airship can't fly over lava.
[SPEAKER_11]: So then you get the Uber airship that can fly over lava.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, they have ways of restricting where you can go and they definitely do that in this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not all open from the start.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, yeah, I, you know, if you're a fan of the original game you gotta have this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know it's taking a lot of crap for the fact that it is episodic and that they are charging, you know, $3 every episode means the game's gonna cost, you know, probably like $30 for all the parts.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I try to also value my game on how much time I'm getting out of it and how much reward I'm getting from the investment.
[SPEAKER_11]: And honestly, if these three bucks a pop are going to be...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, other games I've been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of old school role-playing games, I was playing Phantasy Star 2 for a good chunk of time this week, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, I have that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, you know Trixie360 on Twitter, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Trixie, she's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: She just had her baby, too.
[SPEAKER_01]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_11]: She did.
[SPEAKER_11]: Congratulations, Trixie, who just had baby Trixie this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: She just spawned this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, she just spawned.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, uh, yeah, she, um, she was giving away codes, and, uh, you know, I just happened to be on Twitter one night when she was giving them away, and I was like, okay, my Google Foo skills are awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: These little trivia questions she's asking about the 90s, I can do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do this for the online games I play all the time that don't relate to video games with, like, some of the roleplay I do.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can Google Foo faster than anyone, and sure enough, the second time she gave away a code that I was watching, I won a code for Phantasy Star 2, which...
[SPEAKER_11]: In retrospect, seems a little useless because I do have the Sonic Genesis collection.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I, you know, I wanted to see, did this game offer anything different?
[SPEAKER_11]: And the answer is, not really.
[SPEAKER_11]: Except achievements are in it, for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't gotten any yet because you have to get to level 10 to get the first one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I only played... You want to talk about a game, an old school game, where you have to do a lot of freaking grinding?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, right from the start.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't really go anywhere until you grind your way to level 3 or 4.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to start off poor.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've actually got a figure of her.
[SPEAKER_11]: The one that turned out
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, don't spoil.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: 20 years old.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not true.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I never played it on the Genesis.
[SPEAKER_11]: But granted, I could have gotten it on PlayStation 1 or any of the millions of times they've re-released this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: But for whatever reason, I'm just now playing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: She actually doesn't turn out evil.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's something else weird that happens to her.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's not really...
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've barely been paying attention to the story.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you want my little figurine, you can have it, because she's cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's a cat girl.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've been having fun with it so far.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll have to play a little more.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are leaderboards, too, which is something a little extra you don't have in the Mega Genesis Collection.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also, the smoothing is in both, but the save system's a little different, but that's not really anything to hoop and holler about.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can save anywhere in the game, though, and I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't play it enough in the Mega Collection to know if that was the case.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think for anybody that owns a collection, there really probably isn't much point to having this game unless you really want achievements or you are just that much of a fan of the system.
[SPEAKER_12]: I kind of wonder why they decided to release that collection if they were planning to release these games.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would seem to me that it would be a good idea to...
[SPEAKER_12]: Suck in all the money that you can, then BOOM!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, Phantasy Star 2 is alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you haven't played it one of the million other ways you can get that game, then it's worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is a piece of gaming history known for its notoriety of being an incredibly difficult RPG.
[SPEAKER_01]: God, seriously though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's actually one of the best Sega RPGs out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's why they've released it so many times.
[SPEAKER_01]: Make sure that people who want it can get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: What else have I been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've actually been playing a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuel is another game I've checked out.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is something that Loki was raving about on the show a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mentioned that I touched the game last week, but I hadn't really played a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've spent a lot more time with Fuel this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, you know, I think, honestly, you're going to have to file this game and love it or hate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I've been trying to look at some of the mainstream reviews, which I don't usually do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I've been trying to figure out why the game has not been scoring kind of better as a whole.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I think there is a lot to this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's really just a love it or hate it type of game.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are some pretty in-your-face type of flaws with the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: There is some graphical clipping that is just like, oh my gosh, did I really just drive right through that tree?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did that really just happen?
[SPEAKER_11]: There are some big flaws.
[SPEAKER_11]: I feel like this game was slightly rushed.
[SPEAKER_11]: If they just spent...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, the GPS.
[SPEAKER_11]: or all these liveries on your GPS or you can actually run into cars and get the car a little later on when you unlock the second area.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: A lot for somebody who likes to collect things in games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Arcade style controls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you try driving from the first camp to the second camp?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know I have a funny story about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes I did because I wanted to get that achievement because I looked at what achievements you had got and I figured well anything Loki has I can get.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I actually tried to get that achievement, and the funny thing is I didn't finish it because I got fooled.
[SPEAKER_11]: As I was driving there, and right when I crossed into that second zone, it said, oh, achievement unlocked.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I was like, oh, well, I guess I don't really have to drive all the way into the base camp.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just have to drive from the one map line to the other.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_11]: The achievement I found out later that I really got was the one for driving 100 miles cumulatively.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just happened to get it at that moment.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so now I'm going to have to go back and do it again.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's cool though because you drive through a forest fire while you're going there.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's where I actually unlocked it.
[SPEAKER_11]: They have done some pretty imaginative things with the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just don't think it's for everyone.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think there's a lot of people that are going to pick this up and go, what the hell's the point?
[SPEAKER_11]: What am I doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: The game is not kind into kind of a ramp up learning curve.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just are kind of thrown into it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, so what do I do?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're kind of like, do I drive around aimlessly?
[SPEAKER_11]: Do I...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: But I thought maybe this was because I was adventuring out in the middle of nowhere in the second world.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or second section of the map that you unlock.
[SPEAKER_11]: So maybe everybody's in the first area.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or maybe it was because I was playing at 1 a.m.
[SPEAKER_11]: on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I didn't run into anybody.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I did try some of the Xbox Live races.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: And it was like hardly anything on the map.
[SPEAKER_12]: We got to a new area and that was it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You actually, you can get further faster if you're smart about the way you do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you drive on the freeways with a freeway vehicle, you'll go really fast.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if you try to just go from point A to B off-road, like as the crow flies, you're not going to get there as fast.
[SPEAKER_11]: You really do have to take the freeways and the bullet car and go 110 miles an hour to get places faster.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just, you know, you're so tempted.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I just want to drive off-road, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of it gets a little annoying.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, some of the challenges that are just endurance.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, it's a 15-minute race.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not even joking.
[SPEAKER_11]: From one point to another.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then to, like, come in second on that 15-minute race and get nothing for it is a little frustrating.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you don't get a silver medal or anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's like, oh, you lose.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you want to try again?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or the chasing the copter thing and you're just like...
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I took the wrong turn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are some areas like that where it's like, come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is like one big thing I would have fixed is I would have given some type of reward for second and third place or give me a reason to waste 15 minutes, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: But otherwise, there's a lot of collectible to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will play it again.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've got to play with Loki online at some point.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to have a race to drive from one point to another.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would be cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gosh, I've talked a lot about games, but I've had time to play them again thanks to not playing WoW.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all I'm going to share for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know there's been some other stuff, but that's all I want to share.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to actually get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_11]: First, some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: essentially no break and when I say no break granted of course we've had a week off here and there for holidays or trips or travel or what have you but honestly there's never been a break longer than I think our longest downtime was three weeks once and that was like a one-time thing that happened but we've been going like non-stop ever since I don't even think it was three weeks I think it was two weeks when like we were moving out of
[SPEAKER_11]: One... Like, remember when Loki and I used to live together?
[SPEAKER_03]: We did the show there?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think when we moved from that to the new setup, I think that was our longest break we had, because it was such a big move.
[SPEAKER_11]: So... But yeah, seven years of Orange Launch Radio, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: When we started doing this show, I was just about to have my 24th birthday.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was 23 years old, and now I'm gonna be... It's funny enough, OLR started three days before my birthday.
[SPEAKER_11]: So now I'm turning 31 this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a long time of doing this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they're still going.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_01]: Things get the best when you're in your 30s.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I say.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, okay, and we'll be actually having more of a celebration, quote unquote, next week, although we have nothing special planned.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you start to get a certain age, you kind of hope other people will throw you a surprise party so you don't have to do any work.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what there is to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: So certainly we'll open up the Skype line to your calls about the show, maybe share some favorite moments.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some of you guys, I would love, some of you guys that are archive experts of the show, dig up some of your favorite moments that are out there and available, and we'll try to replay some of them next week if we can find any.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seven years next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw points out, and I've been ignoring chat all night, I apologize.
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw points out, today is a holiday, well sort of, of course, Father's Day.
[SPEAKER_11]: So to all of our gaming dads out there today, happy Father's Day to you, or whatever father figure happens to be in your life.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe a grandpa or a brother, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: So happy Father's Day to all of you fatherly figures out there.
[SPEAKER_11]: And as TigerClaw says in chat, today is a holiday, well sort of, happy about to be a Father's Day for Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: since as we all know the wife is Prager's.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they celebrated it for me anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: They got a shop vac, which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Power tools.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I need the shop vac.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like any good father should have.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, let's get into the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: And for those that listened last week, which I hope you all did, it was on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our podcast feed's been on time lately.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have kind of changed the format of our show a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Less stories, more time with each story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know, you guys can go on and, you know, kind of get a rundown of the gaming news on hundreds of different websites.
[SPEAKER_11]: But this is one of the only places where you can really talk about them with other gamers who aren't jerks.
[SPEAKER_11]: And leave comments that say, first...
[SPEAKER_11]: So let's talk about this week in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's been some big stories this week, especially a huge one.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura is going to start us off tonight with some gaming news to talk about.
[SPEAKER_11]: And your call is at 877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, we have a case of it could be a business decision or it could just be a case of pissy bitchiness.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Activision's got some PMS going on.
[SPEAKER_01]: They just say they might stop supporting Sony.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, their CEO, Bobby Kotick, said that they would have to cut the price because they wouldn't be able to make the games that people would buy because the console is too expensive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, I think there's a certain amount of cost that goes into doing anything for Sony because they've got some pretty expensive rates.
[SPEAKER_01]: I said that they might just have to stop supporting Sony come 2010-2011.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're also considering not just the PS3, but the PSP as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: They pay $500 million in royalties to Sony, which is roughly about 40% of their profit.
[SPEAKER_01]: So under those circumstances...
[SPEAKER_01]: I kind of don't blame them if they're trying to really make back their money honestly Xbox and Wii is going to be where it's at for Activision I would think
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, you agree?
[SPEAKER_11]: It won't happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if I totally agree with the whole it's only there on Xbox and Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I get that sentiment.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I do think you have your hardcore Sony audience that would justify the cost of porting the game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bobby Kotick has been bitching about the Sony PS3 price for a long time now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Every time you hear about some Activision bitching about the price of the PS3, they think it's too high.
[SPEAKER_12]: They think there should be a price drop.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're hoping there's a price drop.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're always complaining about the PS3 price.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't sell as many units on the PS3 as they do on the 360, but they still sell quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm sorry, but you're going to just cost average everything across the board for most of the games you develop.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, if you don't want to develop for the PS3, then don't.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I think franchises like Modern Warfare 2 and Guitar Hero and stuff, the PS3 is still a very integral part of those franchises.
[SPEAKER_12]: And to just get rid of it because, oh, it's too expensive, well, that's not really a good reason.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, let's just say if they are crazy enough and they actually go through with it,
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to suck for Sony.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's going to be something I don't know if they can be able to make up ground on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Empty threats?
[SPEAKER_11]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or a username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm reading the chat room here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranma says, good for Activision.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, from what I heard, or remember reading, EA, I guess, I don't know if maybe EA dropped, or Sega, they weren't supporting the Genesis or something like that at one time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, EA had dropped them for similar reasons.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, it'd be interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think that's going to happen, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, I mean, all it would take is something like that to happen, you know, say...
[SPEAKER_12]: Activision has stopped publishing Guitar Hero on the PS3 and boom, Rock Band will come in and swoop up all those sales right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Modern Warfare 2, I'm sure there's going to be another military shooter out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: If not first party, then someone else putting something out.
[SPEAKER_12]: and um I don't know it's not gonna just like it's not gonna just kill them for not having Activision there's a couple listeners in chat that want to say it's the Dreamcast that EA dropped oh Dreamcast okay okay that's what it was um I just I knew it was the Sega system but I couldn't remember which one um so yeah I mean I I doubt that at this point they're gonna do that
[SPEAKER_11]: There is a response from Sony.
[SPEAKER_11]: Obviously, this thing caught so much momentum around the internet that Sony had to make a response, and they did.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the response goes something like this.
[SPEAKER_11]: PlayStation has tremendous momentum coming out of E3, and we are seeing positive growth with more than 350 titles slated to hit across all of our platforms, including many anticipated games from our publishing partners.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this, by the way, this quote is from Patrick Sebold, who is a spokesperson for PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_11]: We enjoy healthy business relationships with and greatly value our publishing partners, and we are working closely with them to deliver the best entertainment experience.
[SPEAKER_11]: So in other words, they didn't really address the issue.
[SPEAKER_11]: They just kind of said, we still are awesome, and we're just going to ignore this guy because he's a boob.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, he may be a boob.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: He's kind of...
[SPEAKER_12]: He seems to whine a lot, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it really doesn't matter if he thinks there should be a price drop.
[SPEAKER_12]: They shouldn't have to drop their price because he thinks there should be a price drop.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fuck him.
[SPEAKER_12]: He doesn't work for Sony.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: and so on and so forth.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that they're working on something similar to that with the PS3 as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe that might be something that they can look at as an option to save some money for the third-party publishers and give them a reason to develop more on the PS3, but it's not a reason to drop them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know though, because didn't a few companies leave ESA, but not everybody did?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think necessarily one, and Activision was kind of, that's one reason I almost would believe this guy if he's a boob or not, is that Activision did drop ESA for a while, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have to set up freaking queues on our website to handle the load and they're gone in 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't need it.
[SPEAKER_11]: On one hand, despite the thought that I'm kind of torn, I'm like, yeah, it sounds like an empty threat, but at the same time, track record shows Activision is willing to make good on these type of threats.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, he doesn't even have a time frame.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, 2010, 2011.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you do not drop your price by December 31st, 2009, we will be gone June 1st, 2010.
[SPEAKER_11]: That seems like a closed-door conversation, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: Part of me wonders, though, is this much ado about nothing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did this guy make an offhanded remark, a soundbite, if you will?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did this guy just make a careless remark that got picked up and ran with by the gaming press and overanalyzed by folks like ourselves?
[SPEAKER_01]: I kind of don't think so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, who?
[SPEAKER_01]: Kodak?
[SPEAKER_01]: He made it to the Times.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think he was pretty clear on it, but the fact is, I mean, how many times have we been reporting on, you know, company heads making stupid comments about something and, you know, and the fallout from it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, Sony is a perfect example of that, you know, and thank goodness they got rid of the crayon-eating...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think anything's really going to happen with this, and that's really kind of the issue.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yes, I think that they should drop the price of their system, but for entirely different reasons other than Activision says so.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, that's not the reason to drop the price of the system.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's some good debate going on in our chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe that's why everybody's afraid to call in, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also, I think we had a slight listener dip tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if everybody's aware, but we shifted a little bit on the radio stream.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is not right now on the front page of allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess they're doing some remodeling over there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: AllGamesRadio.com
[SPEAKER_11]: But Ranma retorts with this, PS3 is not a premium console, neither is Xbox 360 or Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sony won't price drop because they'll take a higher loss on each unit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't forget, Rob, Best Buy, GameStop, and other companies told Sony to drop the price of the PSP or else they'd stop selling it.
[SPEAKER_12]: that is a problem when the companies that are selling your product are saying they're going to drop you I think more so than the publisher because to be honest they could probably make it through without Activision even though Activision right now is the number one publisher out there only because EA dropped the number two but I don't know it's not going to kill them if they go away
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me read this comment as well from Bochikawa in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a total bluff, but it still puts into people's mindset to stop dealing with Sony.
[SPEAKER_11]: And even then, I doubt they will stop dealings altogether, leaving ports or minor titles to them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because think about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's another thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Think about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Would you really want to ruin your relationship with Sony?
[SPEAKER_12]: Say, okay, we're going to stop supporting the PlayStation 3 and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, the PlayStation 4 comes out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you just burned your bridges with Sony because you're being a dick, and now you have the PS4 coming out, and you could have had some really good partnerships with them to get some good launch titles and that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, but you were a dick, so now they're going to not, I don't know, maybe be so kind to you because you decided to drop them dead weight.
[SPEAKER_12]: It may be possibly hurting the launch of your next system.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know how I feel about the whole PlayStation 3 is not a premium console content.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if I necessarily call it premium, but let's face it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The PlayStation 3 does have one big component you cannot ignore that the Xbox 360 and the Wii doesn't have, and that's Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially as we're getting into more high definition and Blu-rays are starting to penetrate the market more and more.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're kind of where DVDs were.
[SPEAKER_11]: What, 12 years ago, as Blu-rays are starting to penetrate the marketplace more and more, I don't think you can ignore the fact that the PlayStation 3 is the only one out there right now that's a Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's not something that, despite all the rumors, Microsoft ain't even considering, and Nintendo sure as hell ain't considering this whole Blu-ray thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's one thing that Sony's always going to have, making it...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: And for the average consumer, the PS3 is an awesome Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_12]: It does all the updating for them.
[SPEAKER_12]: They don't need to worry about, oh, will this disc play in my system?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because a lot of people out there that don't own a PS3 and just have a normal Blu-ray player, you need to have that thing connected to the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: And to update your system to the updated firmware so that it can play whatever Blu-ray movie is out there, there's a lot of...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: But I've got to think, now that Blu-ray has been out there for at least a few years now, the price of the components have to have come down by now.
[SPEAKER_12]: They've got to find ways to cut costs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe putting out new systems with larger hard drives isn't the way to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe you should just keep the same hard drive size and start dropping the price.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or drop something else.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Make it cheaper.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, let's see, a couple more comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ranma says, Loki, that's reminiscent of the whole Nintendo Square debacle years ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and Square's back.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's true, but Nintendo did take a pretty big hit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy going over to the PlayStation was huge.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was just absolutely huge.
[SPEAKER_11]: In some ways...
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe I'm just a little biased here because I happen to be a role-playing game fan.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Nintendo 64 didn't do so hot in part because of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really, but they did get Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, it was a Nintendo franchise.
[SPEAKER_01]: But seriously, the Pokemon franchise... Oh, your sound is off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is your mic on?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, it's... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was going to say, Nintendo did have Pokemon to keep them above water pretty much.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that's what saved the Nintendo 64 as long as it did.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two Africans in our chatroom says simply PlayStation 3 is a great system.
[SPEAKER_11]: On what planet?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it is a good system.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is a good system.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a good Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah, it's a good Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's much quieter than the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: I enjoy playing games on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's got the better controller than the 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't fault the PS3 as a bad system at all.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think it is a bad system.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they just marketed it terribly.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was too expensive to begin with.
[SPEAKER_12]: If I hadn't gotten mine for free from...
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_12]: We just got a call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind about this whole PlayStation 3 debacle going on in Activision?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you think they're going to make good on the threat?
[SPEAKER_00]: No, not at all.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, there's a slight possibility, but the possibility of it's kind of, you know, there's always a possibility that, you know, it could snow in southern Mexico, but isn't very likely that it happens.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's likely, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but I don't know if that's totally the same thing going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what about, okay, like, I could ask the question, do you think Sony needs to drop the price of the console?
[SPEAKER_11]: But who's not going to say yes to that?
[SPEAKER_11]: But the question I'm going to ask is, do you think Sony has real legitimate reason to drop the price of their console right now?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, yes and no.
[SPEAKER_00]: Depends on how you want to look at it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm kind of on the fence on that subject.
[SPEAKER_00]: On one hand, I can see why they're not pricing it, because, you know, mainly because of the Blu-ray drive itself, they're still kind of expensive to manufacture, and they're already taking a hit by, you know, selling at the price they're at.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the same time, at least for most consoles, I think, except for the Wii and the PlayStation 2, generally speaking, console manufacturers always take a hit on consoles, and it's kind of like a stop-loss kind of thing, where they tend to make all their money through the licensing fees on the games, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: They just don't... They don't...
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_00]: probably not, I hope not, at least for the sake of all those that only own the PlayStation 3, although they're going to have to
[SPEAKER_00]: I can't remember if Spassinator is the one that plays Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was him or one of the other listeners that plays Final Fantasy XI a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: That made me think that Final Fantasy XIV is on its way to PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: God, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: There are some exclusives out there on the horizon, but is it going to be... Here's the thing with Sony.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's been this way ever since the launch of the PS3 and even the PSP.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: And even with like the PSP, the PSP Go price, are they fucking crazy?
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's put it out for $250.
[SPEAKER_12]: Great, that's a perfect way not to sell any more consoles.
[SPEAKER_12]: That PSP Go is going to fail like crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's just they're really, they need to get smart and they need to figure out a way to gain ground now.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yes, exclusives will help, but price drop will help even more.
[SPEAKER_01]: If the PSP Go, I think, had a $99 price point on it like Dan had mentioned a while back, then I think they'd be selling like freaking hotcakes.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_01]: And on top of that, looking at the construction of them, about what they took out, the machines themselves can't really be relatively that expensive to produce, nor can shipping and marketing costs really be that much if they've already got some momentum going with it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So really, say that...
[SPEAKER_01]: To cost ship and market each individual system, it costs them, say, 80 bucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Put it out for 125, you'll make tons of profit still.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because you'll get more units out, and the more you mass produce them, the cheaper they are to produce.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got to move on with some more stories, and we will, but I want to say... My point is, that's simple economics, simple business, and Sony should know that.
[SPEAKER_01]: If they want to get the games, if they want to keep some of their people, if they want to sell the systems, that's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think one place that Sony is losing to Microsoft, as much as I do enjoy my PlayStation 3, is that they are not staying current as fast as Microsoft does.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that is killing them this generation.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because Microsoft had a hard time doing that with the original Xbox, but right now they built that 360 to get these upgrades and all these things.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: to the PlayStation outside of home.
[SPEAKER_11]: And some would argue home was not all it was cracked up to be.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's definitely not the big hub that they thought it would be.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of a neat thing to play around with, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, I'm sure this story is to be continued.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be interesting to see how long this whole little stalemate lasts.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, speaking of PlayStation, the PSP Go has an interesting rumor kind of related to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, there's a rumor that Sony is working on an app store for the PSP Go, and that's going to be revealed at Gamescom in Cologne this August.
[SPEAKER_12]: and they're basically saying that these games will be limited to like 100 megs and basically that's only the limit for the content.
[SPEAKER_12]: But any apps that they want to create including non-game applications may also be available as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: So some of these smaller programs at cheaper prices or maybe free kind of aligning themselves with what Apple has with their app store.
[SPEAKER_12]: It'd be interesting if this is going to be the draw for the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes sense to me that they're going to do something like this, because really, this has to be the only thing that they've got in the cards for, because what would be the draw to the PSP Go if basically all the games are just digital downloads now?
[SPEAKER_12]: and the system's more expensive.
[SPEAKER_12]: You need something unique to it to draw people to pay that extra $100.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of thought this already existed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not so much a storefront on the PSP, but I thought your PS3 store was supposed to interact with the PSP as well as you could get something like this on your PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not necessarily...
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's an iPhone store.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are they going to sell music and movies on it, too?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they already do on the PlayStation Network, so... I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can get it on your PSP, but I would bet you they ain't doing half the business Apple is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: and they're like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a cell phone contract with my company right now or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of an inevitable part about doing business with a phone company in this day and age which is too bad in some ways.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm probably not going to do my upgrade though for some time.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I mean, I'm already an iPhone user.
[SPEAKER_11]: The 3GS does not seem to have enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially, I would have to pay extra money because I'm not eligible for upgrade yet, which is AT&T's problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: They took away that thing where...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you still have to be in a certain window, though, that I'm not in.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I've got an old iPhone.
[SPEAKER_01]: So for me, it makes perfect sense to upgrade it, although I'm not going to do it until about a month from now, but still.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wait for them to work all the bugs out of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, if you're still on the very, very old one, I can see why.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm on a 3G, and there's just not enough about 3GS that really... Yeah, battery life, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm down for the faster processor myself and having a better camera on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I don't know about this whole PSP store thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess it's a good idea, but I kind of think it's like kind of in a way it's too late.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I guess there's a lot of people that don't have nor want the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: And again, I have to think about that college kid audience that seems to be the PSP target audience that really has these things.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the other thing too, the college kid audience.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you really want to, you can mod your PSP and there's the homebrew community that's already done this and has been doing this for years now.
[SPEAKER_12]: So why bother paying for something that you can get for free and it'll probably end up being better anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: And seriously, if the PSP Go does take off, then those PSP 2000s and 3000s are going to be even cheaper.
[SPEAKER_12]: You might as well do the 2000 because the screen isn't...
[SPEAKER_12]: Space Invaders Extreme
[SPEAKER_11]: Honestly, at this point, probably not.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's because I'm not a fan of handheld gaming in the first place.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've gone into this rant on a previous show, and I realize this is a personal preference that makes me weird than a lot of other gamers.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do not like playing portable games.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only place I can play a portable game is at the airport, on an airplane, when I'm on a trip and don't have my consoles with me, and I have to play something.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if I'm at home...
[SPEAKER_01]: I would not be caught dead with the DS in my own home playing in my house when I have a Playstation and all this other stuff readily available to play well if I want to play a particular game if I've got the system for it I'll just play it on whatever system it's on if I want to play Cooking Mama I'll play the good version on the DS which I've been known to do
[SPEAKER_11]: for me to go that far there's so many games out there it's kind of like there's lots of games I want to play and I'll just play the ones I want to play on the console while I'm at home and again I know I'm weird but a game on the handhelds has to be really good and really anticipated for me to play them when I'm in house Scribblenuts
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll probably end up picking it up for when I do travel, but I don't see myself sitting in my bed playing it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I'm weird like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you play games on your iPhone?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: There's all the time, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I sit here when I'm chatting with people online, and I'm playing Vi right now, which was an old NES RPG that they put out on my phone.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been playing that.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so anyhow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know I'm weird about the whole handheld thing, but sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got off the original topic about the PSP App Store.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess it's an inevitable thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: How successful it'll be, I guess it all depends what apps are on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it has the must-have apps, but I don't see a lot of people just downloading it for the calculator.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's look at what other people have done, like the DSi Store.
[SPEAKER_12]: Their apps suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, what's up, everybody?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Kajudo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Kajudo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, hey, welcome to the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you think about this whole PSP store and the PSP competing with the iPhone in a way?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't own any of the PSPs just because it just never appealed to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm more of a DS fan where I like the innovation.
[SPEAKER_06]: They just seem to build games for that system.
[SPEAKER_06]: The PSP to me just seems like, okay, you want to take your PS3 or your PlayStation 2 in the car.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can have that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And really, I'm not interested in playing those types of games in my car.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd rather just a little simple point-and-click type game.
[SPEAKER_06]: But what I'm concerned about is this, uh, what is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: The PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm, PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, what happens if I install these games on the PSP Go and I get my PSP stolen or I lose it?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like all my games are just basically down the drain now, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: They're tied to your PlayStation Network accounts just like if your PS3 got stolen or exploded or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you can re-download them again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it was something where you buy it off of their online store and it's saved on there and if you lose it then that's just...
[SPEAKER_06]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that's certainly a valid concern, especially when you go to this whole digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yeah, I know on PlayStation Network, I mean, I don't buy anything for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it's the same deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Once you buy something, it's yours and you can re-download it later if you need to.
[SPEAKER_11]: But isn't there like a thing like there's got to be a way to prevent me from going to a friend's house and downloading the game and they play it?
[SPEAKER_12]: What if that service, for some reason, one day they no longer provide that download?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's always another concern with me with things like, what is it, Valve?
[SPEAKER_12]: Steam, Steam.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm a little concerned with that, like,
[SPEAKER_06]: What happens if one day Steam just goes away?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where does my games go?
[SPEAKER_12]: Then they go into oblivion, unfortunately, unless you have them downloaded to your system.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I would think, I would hope the respectable thing to do would be to release, if your company's about to go under, release something that's going to require, not require Steam anymore for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, that or the other option, too, if you know that they're going to, you know, granted, I don't think the Sony store is just going to up and die all of a sudden, but, I mean, if you...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Bobby Blackwolf in chat would like to clarify Steam has a failsafe for that reason they've already stated that if they go under they will remove the digital rights management so it's kind of like I speculated that they would do the right thing and just disable the necessity of having Steam in the first place well hey thank you so much for the call and we appreciate it I just have one game recommendation for Loki you must get Red Faction Guerrilla I have it I just haven't played it yet
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, oh yeah, I really gotta play that game.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I also have Prototype 2, so I have to go back to that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Fuel, I have to go play that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So there's a lot of stuff, and I just got my... I'm trying to unpack right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now is just not a good time to move.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have to unpack.
[SPEAKER_12]: The summer's dead for me as far as what's coming out.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's a good time to get all these games now, because then I can play them through the summer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Enjoy the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good night, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_11]: 1-877-GAME-OLR
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought that the rumor was actually that it was going to be treated like a console launch and people thought that it was going to be a new console.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I thought too.
[SPEAKER_11]: But also the fact that it was going to be not so much like a new console console, but you know how PlayStation 1 and then there's PlayStation 1 Slim a couple years later.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think the thought was there was going to be an Xbox 360 Slim.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, the CEO of Microsoft, Steve Ballmer, actually came out and said that... Well, I'm sorry, that actually, he was the guy that made that first remark about the whole Xbox 360 hardware integration that caused everybody to run with everything going on here.
[SPEAKER_11]: The director of product management for Xbox 360 and Xbox Live, Aaron Greenberg, actually straight up told Kotaku earlier this week, there will be no console.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're not going to be launching a new console anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really believe he was speaking about Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_11]: We want to make sure people know that we're excited about Project Natal, but we're barely halfway through this generation.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're happy with the Xbox 360, so there are no changes from that standpoint.
[SPEAKER_11]: For the time being, we're really just showing a whole new category of gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then they're talking about, are they thinking about doing the hands-free stuff in a new Xbox 360 configuration?
[SPEAKER_11]: They did say, yes, we have looked at that, but we haven't announced any details for something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they're just really kind of lying by omission, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's exactly what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think there is.
[SPEAKER_11]: In a way...
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's the most important quotes from this.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are saying that the Natal will run on the Xbox 360, so there's no new hardware to purchase.
[SPEAKER_11]: What we're doing that's unique is instead of asking you to invest in a new generation of hardware, a generation that's already well established, extending the experience even longer by adding this whole new category of experiences with Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're changing the rules just a little bit like we did with the new Xbox experiences.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just going to be, they're going to do a new console.
[SPEAKER_12]: It may be slimmed down, it may not be slimmed down, but it's going to be some sort of a new revision and it's going to have Natal with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's basically it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It may be integrated into it if they decide to actually slim down the form factor of it, but there will be a new console.
[SPEAKER_12]: There will not be a new console because it's not going to be the Xbox, you know, the next one, the 720 or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It won't be a new console in that sense, but just like how the PlayStation 2, spelled out T-W-O, is not a new console, it's just a slimmer console.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the same console, but just...
[SPEAKER_11]: You've noticed the way he's wording it.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's not saying no.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's reassuring people that they're not going to have to buy a new console to enjoy Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_11]: He didn't come out and say, we're not releasing a new set of hardware.
[SPEAKER_11]: He didn't really say that.
[SPEAKER_11]: He said, don't worry, Project Natal will work on your existing hardware.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I'm hearing.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's reassuring people that they don't need to do this hardware upgrade.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I still think there's going to be... There has to be some perks to doing an upgrade.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think there will be at least a bundle that comes with Natal.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think they're really going to push this thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why shouldn't they?
[SPEAKER_11]: It is their answer to the Wii after all.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's going to be kind of... They're going to treat it like a new launch, so why not relaunch the system?
[SPEAKER_12]: See, because that's what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're even going to probably phrase it like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is...
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: But in reality, they did go back and pump up the hardware a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because remember, you couldn't really have NXE on your system if you didn't have a hard drive or a memory card or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you had no memory, you can't even store NXE.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now there's hardware out there that they've doubled the memory that it's now 512 megs built in that can fit NXE and probably some of the other stuff on your actual physical drive.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: And they've gotten rid of their arcade games.
[SPEAKER_11]: This kind of confl... Well, that's true too.
[SPEAKER_11]: But this kind of conflicts with what he's saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: I knew this was coming a long time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember you saying something on the show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they were slowly transitioning.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was the console that they had the holiday bundles that they can do with the games packed in.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope that they do make a slimmer one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could be talked into upgrading my system, actually, because I still have my old-ass Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could be talked into it for HDMI, quieter system, and maybe any other perks they're going to throw at me with new hardware.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would be quieter because of the smaller chipsets, less heat, less need for a huge fan.
[SPEAKER_11]: But here's my concern.
[SPEAKER_11]: My old hard drive's not going to work with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because if they slim down the system, that massive drive's not going to fit on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they could.
[SPEAKER_12]: It'd be the same thickness, or maybe a plug-in to the top.
[SPEAKER_12]: They could do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope they do.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I wouldn't want to have to get a new drive and all that stuff again.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would turn me off.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would think that they would.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, look at the PlayStation Slim.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, all the peripherals, for the most part, work with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, there's obviously... The multi-tap doesn't, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: Other interesting things, going back to talking about Activision again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Activision, I guess the prices for their new peripheral games are actually starting to come out online.
[SPEAKER_12]: Retailers like Amazon and GameStop and stuff like that are starting to take pre-orders on them.
[SPEAKER_12]: People are kind of shocked at how expensive they are.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now,
[SPEAKER_12]: This is Activision we're talking about here.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not shocked at how expensive they are.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it is interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, for example...
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Hero I think we talked about this a little bit before it's going to retail for $120 and it's of course bundled in with the DJ controller which when you look at like previously releases like say Guitar Hero with a guitar bundled with it that's typically been $99.99 for an Xbox 360 or Playstation 3 version the Playstation 2 version though is coming out at $99.99 so there is like a $30 premium on all these different
[SPEAKER_12]: BAND HERO
[SPEAKER_12]: Guitar Hero Game
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: So maybe they think they're justified in that sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well, what's Band Hero bringing new to the table?
[SPEAKER_11]: I can tell you what Beatles rock band is bringing new to the table.
[SPEAKER_11]: But what is... Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some folks might want to argue with me on that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But at the same time, I'm telling you, put the Beatles rock band gameplay next to Guitar Hero Van Halen gameplay, and I'll tell you what justifies that premium Beatles prize.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's something funny, though, if you think about it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: Guitar Hero World Tour right now I think is like $180 if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's like $179.99.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, I'm going to look that up right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: But let's just assume with Guitar Hero 5 coming out, you've got to think that they're probably going to do a price drop on Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because they've got to clear out the extra units that they have and maybe they're not going to do it right away.
[SPEAKER_12]: But
[SPEAKER_12]: You would think that they were going to drop it because that's what they normally do.
[SPEAKER_12]: They drop the version that came out last year in preparation for the new one.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you've got the bundles that are available out there right now for World Tour.
[SPEAKER_12]: And say that you can get them for, I don't know, $150, $149.99.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure that's not too much of a stretch.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, so now you have this new game coming out for $200 worldwide.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why should I buy that bundle when I can buy a bundle with World Tour and I can buy the game only of Band Hero for the same price as buying the bundle for Band Hero?
[SPEAKER_12]: It makes no sense whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it does seem kind of a rip-off to be spending that kind of money on a bundle that is readily available right now for a cheaper price.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yeah, it looks like World Tour...
[SPEAKER_12]: The Band Kits Okay, $190 So they're still pretty expensive Um Actually $190 Right now that wouldn't be that But that's still $10 more than, you know Yeah
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, for $10, even $10 is $10 still.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially considering, you know, they're not bringing that much new to the table, it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_11]: But here's my thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going back to the DJ Hero thing for a minute because I'm excited about DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks like the game's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: The song list looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looks innovative and this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: But when I heard it was $120, it was like getting kicked in the crotch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like...
[SPEAKER_11]: $120 is a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll tell you what, if they had said $99, I would have been like, sold, gonna buy it, I'm there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep, I got it, day one.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's that third digit that makes all the difference in my mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm very disappointed.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like to travel with my game consoles and peripherals and stuff like that, so that, you know, would appeal to me, but I want to see what I'm getting for this $120, because it's kind of expensive for, you know, and I know the peripheral is kind of neat, but I'm sorry, it's a turntable, it can't be that sophisticated, it's, we've had Beatmania controllers out there, and I mean, really, we're not talking too much different than that, and hell, the guitars aren't even that sophisticated, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: Where's the money going?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I'm curious about that too.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think what also really sucks is that you can't really demo DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_12]: You're going to have to either play it in a store, play it at a friend's, or take a chance.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you want to hear something funny?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is coming from a company that's bitching about the price being too high for the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: Funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't even think about that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, the PlayStation 3 is too high.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hell, that's almost the price of our, what is it, Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_12]: If they drop the PlayStation 3 price another $100, it will be the price of their Band Hero bundle.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry, that seems kind of a rip-off to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, at the same time...
[SPEAKER_12]: Band Hero was Band Hero
[SPEAKER_11]: And I do a show about games every week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm supposed to be on top of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I literally thought Guitar Hero 5 was just called Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was the same game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was like, no, they're putting out two?
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do we need that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, okay, Van Halen's coming out at the beginning of August.
[SPEAKER_12]: Guitar Hero 5's coming out at the beginning of September.
[SPEAKER_12]: Band Hero's coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why I'm... Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not feeling it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially, you know, they're going to charge like 50 bucks for Guitar Hero Van Halen.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, I guess that's them.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see how this sells, of course, and how you guys anticipate it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not a lot of chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're talking about pay goal in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess there's not a lot of care about DJ Hero or Band Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's shift topics and talk about another game.
[SPEAKER_11]: This game definitely has its cult following, which used to be me many years ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Magic the Gathering.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_01]: That was me in college in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_11]: and it was me in high school many years ago actually I've actually got a couple magic decks over here I got them for free here's the thing about Magic the Gathering say what you will call me whatever name you want in the book I do think Magic the Gathering is actually a lot of fun it's just a good game like I think it's a good card game to play but
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: In the full version of the game, you can kind of make your own deck.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can do your own thing with it, you know, and add the cards that are there, and you gain and lose cards as you fight enemies and so forth.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, it's hard for me, and like Lazy Days in chat says, demos don't count.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I don't want to base my evaluation of the game off of it, so I'm not going to tell you whether to buy it or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will just say, you know, it was kind of neat to see a resurgence of Magic the Gathering.
[SPEAKER_11]: Magic the Gathering
[SPEAKER_11]: You have the card, good old card and table and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or you have Magic the Gathering Online.
[SPEAKER_11]: The interesting thing about Magic the Gathering Online, they have really tried to mirror the card playing experience right on down to what you pay for it.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you weren't aware, if you want to play Magic the Gathering Online, it's essentially free.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to pay $10.
[SPEAKER_11]: I did a little research today.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've never played Magic the Gathering Online, but I did some research.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I wanted to play, what would it take?
[SPEAKER_11]: You pay like a $10 registration fee, but that $10 goes towards a coupon that you use in their store.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you buy decks just like walking into a comic book store and buying a deck.
[SPEAKER_11]: You buy booster packs just like you would buy a booster pack in a store of 12 random cards or what have you.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's the same price with tax and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you literally, but they make it very clear.
[SPEAKER_11]: There is no...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: um and this is from an interview on destructoid.com senior brand manager worth woolport actually was quoted saying a good way to think of it is like the old theme decks or our current intro decks it's that kind of option to add on to your gaming experience and it's all set it's not randomized at all by the way they're also going to have themes play mats like the background you can buy yeah and gamer pictures okay but at
[SPEAKER_01]: But what about for the people that's over it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, what appeal is it going to have for all the people who've moved on?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is there anything that's going to bring anyone back?
[SPEAKER_01]: What about the face-to-face playing with somebody?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, to be honest, Jamie, I think this is it to bring the old people back is that you don't have to put up with the boosters and all these extra little costs here.
[SPEAKER_11]: In a way, I think if I was going to play Magic the Gathering more regularly, this is appealing to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: When I played Magic regularly, I loved being able to collect all the rare cards and to have the collection that other people went, ooh.
[SPEAKER_11]: But wouldn't it bug you when someone, when you were playing, would pull out that effing card that is so rare there's no way in hell you're going to get it?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, that type of thing, and then it's being used in a match.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, one thing you can say about the Microsoft way of doing it on Xbox Live, everybody's on the same page.
[SPEAKER_11]: Everybody's on equal footing.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, that's not fun to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: If I wanted to play, you know, a certain type of match, you know, I would say, hey, do you have a Type 2 deck?
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have a Type 1 deck?
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, do you have old school Type 1?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know what that means.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's for tournament.
[SPEAKER_01]: I used to do tournament play.
[SPEAKER_01]: Back in the day.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I just say like, hey, you know, if you've got this type of deck, then we'll play this kind of game.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to bring out the strong stuff, you know, we would actually set up those parameters first.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it was a much broader scope of play if you had this together.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've seen people take out wimpy ass starter pack decks and beat people with, you know...
[SPEAKER_01]: The Hardcore Expensive Deck Just Because They Were A Better Player Not Everyone Is Going To Be Equal
[SPEAKER_01]: You may be able to match the cards for everybody, but you're never going to match the skill.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I think that that really takes away a lot of the experience and play.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, from what I understand, you still build your own deck.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just that everybody has the same card pool to build from.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a collector by nature, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: You collect video games.
[SPEAKER_11]: You collect systems.
[SPEAKER_11]: You collect lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're a collector by nature.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can see your argument.
[SPEAKER_11]: For me...
[SPEAKER_11]: That's too much money.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will tell you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I spent a lot of money on this as a kid.
[SPEAKER_01]: My first collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, you were a kid, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was playing in college.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wasn't that far behind you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was playing this when I was a sophomore, junior in high school.
[SPEAKER_11]: You were what, two years older than me?
[SPEAKER_11]: So right around the same there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki was a child.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just kidding, I was not a child.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the whole thing is that I actually built up a collection, sold it for about $1,500 of D&D books, which I still have, and then promptly rebuilt my collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just because, you know, it's its own currency.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to be smart with the building and trading.
[SPEAKER_01]: And, you know, my last collection, by that time, I didn't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_01]: Nobody wanted to pay what it was worth.
[SPEAKER_01]: But still, it's a matter of...
[SPEAKER_01]: What are you in it for?
[SPEAKER_01]: For a lot of people, the fun comes not just in the playing, but in the having.
[SPEAKER_11]: Our good friend Marissa is in chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Marissa Congusto says, I was in elementary school for the win.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't I feel like grandpa?
[SPEAKER_11]: We do love Marissa, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we want her to come visit the show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: Marissa!
[SPEAKER_11]: or Jamie and I are just going to have to end up in L.A.
[SPEAKER_11]: the same weekend and make that happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, and Loki somehow is going to have to be talked into making the trip.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do want to say, though, what else I thought was interesting about this whole Magic the Gathering story was that they also, in this interview, the brand manager would not really say how much it's going to cost because he says, as far as price, all that stuff is dictated by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: What some people have spent lots more money on another online gaming platform to have.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's fascinating to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe I'm just weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it's the memories I have.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sure they would have done booster packs and stuff if they had a way to do random cards like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: But because it's pay X amount of points, download this data, done.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can't do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: for them I do want to check out the full version of the game though I think I will probably as soon as I finish up some of this Final Fantasy and other stuff I've been playing I'll probably get a little more into Magic the Gathering and I would love to play Jamie on Xbox Live but I don't know if she'll want to spend the 10 bucks it might be fun though it really has been years me too I have two decks here on my desk Rob
[SPEAKER_11]: When I was going through that tutorial, I was like, oh my god, this is almost too much to remember.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, I have to hit a button to interrupt if I want to actually use this?
[SPEAKER_11]: So, oh my gosh, she really does.
[SPEAKER_11]: She just whipped it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a sealed deck, for god's sake.
[SPEAKER_01]: I challenge you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ready to play 30-card deck and quick start guide.
[SPEAKER_11]: For real, these are two starter decks?
[SPEAKER_01]: Two starter decks.
[SPEAKER_01]: I challenge you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: We should have a battle on this show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it's a special one-off show or something.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have a white deck and a green deck, which means it'll be a fucking long game.
[SPEAKER_11]: We should do this as a special spin-off show or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: And maybe Loki can provide commentary.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what the hell's going on, nor do I care.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be what was funny about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: If this has that phasing bullshit in it, though, I'm out.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell is phasing?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know what that is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I stopped playing when they put in phasing, which means one card is in play for one turn, and then you have to skip the next one with that card, so they phase.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: My deck was black-red.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would spawn thralls and throw fireballs, and people hated it.
[SPEAKER_11]: This battle is happening.
[SPEAKER_11]: This must happen.
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got the white deck.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got the green deck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, you're holding the white deck, so I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need to set a time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sealed deck tourney.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sealed deck tourney.
[SPEAKER_11]: Between you and me.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I haven't played in years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Neither have I. And they are sealed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Completely sealed.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will take a picture and put it on the website so that you can see that they're sealed.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about we do this on... What are you doing on Wednesday, Robb?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to check with the significant other, but I think I will be free.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bring the significant other.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's on.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's going to think it's the dumbest thing you've ever seen in your life.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to get sandwiches and beer.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not beer.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to get sandwiches and lemonade and play Magic.
[SPEAKER_11]: If this weekend wasn't birthday slash pride slash whatever, I would say let's do it this weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then you're going to Las Vegas the next week, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you're going to be gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, we'll make it happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll figure something out behind the scenes.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is going to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will be.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, the chat is very supportive of the whole Magic the Gathering sealed deck tournament.
[SPEAKER_11]: We should turn it into a drinking game.
[SPEAKER_01]: We've got the geekery.
[SPEAKER_11]: Instead of 20 life points, we should have 20 shot glasses.
[SPEAKER_01]: God, Rob, this is so fucking ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially since... How would you get your life back?
[SPEAKER_12]: You just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially since I haven't really wanted to play Magic in forever.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just got the decks because they were freaking free.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought I'd give them to somebody or we'd give them away on the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about this?
[SPEAKER_01]: How about the winning deck is a giveaway?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: A whole crap ton of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: We have on the 23rd, Fallout 3 point lookout.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then we've got on the 26th, a whole bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another code R, Journey into Lost Memories.
[SPEAKER_01]: Arma 2, is that it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dynasty Warriors 6 Empires, Fight Night Round 4, Guitar Hero Greatest Hits.
[SPEAKER_01]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Monster Hunter Freedom Unite, Overlord 2, Overlord Dark Legends, Overlord Minions, and Prinny Can I Really Be a Hero?
[SPEAKER_01]: And Superstars V8 Racing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: In the US, we've actually got a little bit coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Starting off, we've got...
[SPEAKER_12]: Monster Hunter Freedom Unite Dynasty Warriors 6 Empires Transformers Revenge of the Fallen
[SPEAKER_12]: Split up between Autobots and Decepticons to celebrate the new movie coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: My Healthy Cooking Coach for the DS and Enhanced for the DSi with lots of recipes.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, you get some exclusive recipes if you have the DSi system.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is such bullshit.
[SPEAKER_12]: It is crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can thank Ubisoft for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Overlord.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_12]: Overlord 2 coming out on PS3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: Overlord Minions on DS and Overlord Dark Legend on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also this week, Resident Evil Archives.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to be your first, I guess...
[SPEAKER_12]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: Discovery Kids Parrot Pals yet another
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, SimGame.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wonder if you can make the parrots repeat you in their parrot voice.
[SPEAKER_12]: That'd be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: The PlayStation 2 is getting a bundle of two of the PlayStation portable ports for Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_12]: Liberty City Stories and Bite City Stories bundle coming out for $30 retail.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not too bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: And on DS, some more schlock.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fashion Week Junior Designer coming from 505 Games.
[SPEAKER_12]: and Dawn of Discovery, a real-time strategy game that's coming out on the Wii and I believe the DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Classic Word Games, another one from Ubisoft, also enhanced for the DSi.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's coming out on DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just think that's a horrible thing to do to the casual audience.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not that these are games I would ever buy anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just think that's a mean thing to do to the casual audience.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not like you're using the new hardware for this.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just plain and simple.
[SPEAKER_12]: All the enhancements for that cooking game, it was 20 more recipes.
[SPEAKER_12]: and you got to take your picture and put it in as the chef picture or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, if that was the main enhancement, then fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is something that the DSi hardware can do that the DS just simply cannot do.
[SPEAKER_11]: But this whole withholding recipes or mini-games or what have you just sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shimogane Tensei Devil Summoner on DS coming out this week and...
[SPEAKER_12]: and lastly, Hanya Fantasy Golf on PSP will be making out this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that is it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: Mamoru-kun wa Norowaerte Shimata comes out as well, which is a port from the arcades that...
[SPEAKER_11]: Agarest Senki Zero Ideafactory
[SPEAKER_11]: It kind of looks like a sim type of game mixed with a role-playing game, which could be kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that is coming out over there on the PlayStation 3, as well as another version of BlazBlue.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Fight Night Round 4 also making its way to the Asian region, so it pretty much matches the Xbox 360 dates pretty well.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they also have one other game, Rorona no Atelier 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: Arland no Renken Sushi comes out and that is on several different types of box sets and so forth and I do see that this guy is using like magical sushi in a role playing type of format there so I think that's got to be based on some other type of series over there the game looks very stylish though I will give it that it looks kind of neat
[SPEAKER_11]: coming out on some other systems on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wii Sports Resort, by the way, is coming out this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a pretty big deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that is coming out in Japan, and that's really the only thing of note over there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to skip past PlayStation 2 dates and go straight to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fushigi Yugi gets a game on the DS this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's a Fushigi Yugi game?
[SPEAKER_11]: On the DS this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me see it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bringing up some picture in studio to satisfy DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, dear God.
[SPEAKER_11]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, it looks like it's kind of a sim type.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it definitely looks like a sim.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Tusky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fushugi Yugi is two romantic adventures combined into one DS card.
[SPEAKER_11]: Become the Miko destined to save a nation from calamity and meet all the handsome bodyguards along the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: The fans who have read the manga may already know who the heroines end up with, but now with you in the Miko's robes, you don't have to end things the way the anime or manga did.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: That sounds kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Too bad I can't read any of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's kind of like reverse dating sim because now you get to date boys.
[SPEAKER_01]: That'd be fun if that one got a release over here, but I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the game, I like the name of this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a game called Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is the name of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe that'll be the American release.
[SPEAKER_11]: Instead of about two girls, it'll be about an owl.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although that would be a completely different game altogether.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, from what I understand, Scribblenauts has the O'Reilly Owl in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_11]: All the more reason to buy it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember we told Bobby about it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh no, you weren't there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I told him to go try it the last day and I know he talked about it on his show.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I told him, do lolcats.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I guess he tried the O'Reilly Owl and it actually worked.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quickly on the PSP, I want to mention Memories Off After Rain comes out as well as Noko Aozora Ni Yakisuko Tenohira no Rakuun comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: The cover art is this girl kneeling in the beach, reaching for your hand.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's probably another dating sim.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, there's three people in bed together.
[SPEAKER_11]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's probably a family.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not that hot.
[SPEAKER_01]: It looks like a dating sim.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: The best dating sims have three people in bed at once.
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, the Fushugi Yugi got a big rise out of the chat room.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, indeed.
[SPEAKER_11]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, hey, we're going to close out Part A and get into Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: We just had a mention of the Tokimeki Memorial, which is like the big dating sim series.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yeah, there is one for girls.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's called Tokimeki Memorial Girlside.
[SPEAKER_01]: I do believe it's called Girlside.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura is going to pick a game and share it with you all right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: The classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is a very interesting game called Silhouette Mirage.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm surprised I haven't done this one before.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I think I haven't done it because I thought I had done it before.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, cue music?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's some clip from Silhouette Mirage.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is actually from the Saturn version, which is the one that I really want most of all.
[SPEAKER_01]: It has really good music, by the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a game that's put out by Treasure.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it was initially on the Sega Saturn and then had a PlayStation release.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, the Saturn Japanese release was in 1997 and then came out in 98 on PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then Working Designs brought out the PlayStation version.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, later, actually on, um, December 31st, 1999, which I have that version, and honestly, after playing the Saturn version, the Saturn version is better!
[SPEAKER_01]: Um, but that's what happens with a lot of Saturn PlayStation conversions.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, you basically play through the game where you have different sorts of natures.
[SPEAKER_01]: One is Silhouette, one is Mirage.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so you actually play as a character that has both of those attributes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if you can see in the movie file, Rob.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, she's like flipping from blue to red.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, when she moves one way, she's red, and when she moves the other, she's blue.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's very similar to Gunstar Heroes in how it plays, but you have to really make sure that you're the same type matches, which actually in the Japanese version you can't absorb it, but you can in the US one.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then you also have to make sure that you're attacking with the opposite type of whatever the creature you're fighting is.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really, really difficult.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, treasure games are freaking difficult.
[SPEAKER_01]: So basically, the main character is called Shina Nara Shina, which I thought they did something stupid to it in the U.S., so I'm not even going to bother with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So she's very little, and she has both...
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: You actually get beings that will help you out that are based off the seven deadly sins.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sins.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get Sloth.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get Lusty.
[SPEAKER_01]: Angry, Gluttony, Envy, Covetous and Pride
[SPEAKER_01]: Some other things, you have the Reaper and Galoov bosses that are only in the PlayStation version.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so they actually modified the story, added a new dialogue, new levels, another ending.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they were intended for the Saturn version, but the rumor is that they rushed the Saturn version out and all that wasn't in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, they made it harder for the American version, which I'm saying it was really freaking hard.
[SPEAKER_01]: They made it
[SPEAKER_01]: Harder.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, harder.
[SPEAKER_01]: What you're seeing there, Rob, is easy.
[SPEAKER_01]: They made it hard.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really suck at the PlayStation American one.
[SPEAKER_01]: You also have a debug mode.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have Super Core Fighter 2, which you can play between Shaina and Zohar, one of the other characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: They also, of course, edited...
[SPEAKER_01]: Some of the sprites in the game, like one of them, a character, a cigarette was replaced with a gloved hand, you know, instead of holding a cigarette.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a burning cross was replaced with a dragon.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, but that is classic treasure.
[SPEAKER_11]: Another treasure to add to our pile in the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they did do some great games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, if you want to look at the things Treasure's given us, Gunstar Heroes, Doki Doki Mischief Makers, Bangayo, Ikaruga, Radiant Silvergun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Treasure is like, they're aptly named.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well there you go, your classic game of the week, Silhouette Mirage, available on the Saturn, or if you were in for a challenge, the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's going to do it for this Part A of our show, but we've got plenty more show when we come back, including our Part B tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have the Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have some other discussion topics we're going to get into and of course your emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com We will be back right after a quick break with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Stay tuned guys!
[SPEAKER_11]: And welcome back, everybody, here on this lovely Sunday evening, June the 21st of 2009, for Part B of Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 328.
[SPEAKER_11]: We tape live every week on allgames.com, available at radio.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we put out our podcast every week as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: In the same vein of Team Ninja, working with Nintendo to reimagine Metroid, what development group would you like to see partner and collaborate with Nintendo, and what franchise?
[SPEAKER_11]: So basically, to make it short, dream developer, dream franchise, but a Nintendo franchise.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to be getting into that a little later, and if you want to vote and participate in tonight's list list and have a say, chat.orangeloungeradio.com is the place to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, we're getting some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some topics that we're not going to talk a lot about, but we wanted to let you know what's going on anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, what's the rapid fire news tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, for our friends over in the UK, this is actually until July 3rd, you can get a gold subscription to Xbox Live for basically one pound.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, of course...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, afterwards, you can pay regular price if you want to keep it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But seriously, one quid for one month, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good way to get your foot in the door.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty much, see how you like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, some games coming out, WiiWare and DSiWare.
[SPEAKER_01]: We actually have Let's Catch, which is put out by Yuji Naka.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's to go along with Let's Tap, so it's catching a game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then we have Ikarian Kindred Spirits, where you play as a little winged girl called Nyx who is trying to find Icarus.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aren't we all trying to find the sequel to Icarus?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nay, you know, it could... I don't know if it's tied in, but hey, if it is, that would be sweet.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then DSiWare gets a game called A Little Bit of...
[SPEAKER_01]: Dr. Kalashima's Brain Training, Maths Edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, um, it's math.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which means I won't be getting this freaking game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's 800 Nintendo points, by the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, last but not least, we have...
[SPEAKER_01]: Mass Effect for iPhone which is a side story actually there was an NDA leak that came out last month one of the testers blurted out all this crap so basically it's not a bridging story it's just a little side story about one of the Mass Effect 2 characters so it's just like a little fun option game so hey that's it
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, there's some interesting stuff coming out actually on TV.
[SPEAKER_12]: You may remember Penn & Teller's show Bullshit.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they are taking on JT Voldemort and talking about the evils of video games and violence and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're interested in watching it, the episode will be available on July 9th is when it's supposed to air.
[SPEAKER_01]: You were talking about one of my favorite shows ever, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: XBOX Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_12]: Back in Japan in 1999, and in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_12]: as Fatal Fury, Mark of the Wolves.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, it is the final Fatal Fury title.
[SPEAKER_12]: And last week we had a new Wii game come out, and this is talking about a throwback to the old Laserdisc days, but Digital Leisure has a live-action shooter game you may remember as Mad Dog McCree.
[SPEAKER_12]: Little Bird.
[SPEAKER_12]: They had three games in that series, and all three of those are available for $19.99 in one new pack for the Wii, Mad Dog McCree's Gunslinger Pack, which includes Mad Dog McCree, Mad Dog 2, The Lost Gold, and The Last Bounty Hunter.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, very interesting and old-school crappiness.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: Another game that's going to be heading its way to the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can I say though, those Matt Dogg McCree games are really trying to bank in on the nostalgia of those laser gun games and how cool they were at the time because it was like OMG video.
[SPEAKER_11]: But by today's standards, please.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they are $20 for all three games.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you are really willing to buy it, I would suggest waiting for it to really hit the bargain bin.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess that's a cool value, but still...
[SPEAKER_12]: A new Monkey Ball trademark has been discovered, and I guess based on the title, people are assuming it's going to be using the new... God, it just wouldn't be a week if I didn't have the wrong music kick in at the wrong time, huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't stop it!
[SPEAKER_12]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's cursed!
[SPEAKER_12]: The song is cursed!
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_12]: much like the game Super Monkey Ball which now they've got a new one coming out, Step and Roll which people think, oh Step, the Wii balance board and hey, who doesn't like to whore out the Wii balance board so that game will probably be coming soon from Sega and then that's it
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a few stories I want to cover here real quick in Rapid Fire News as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're just going to start off with a story about the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Commodore 64 apparently has been ported over to the iPhone, which isn't much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's other emulators as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently it is Manomio is the folks that put this thing together, a Commodore 64 app on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: They did this together with a Danish studio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently you can actually run this whole thing on your iPhone.
[SPEAKER_11]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Apple has rejected it.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Apparently Space Invaders Extreme is going to be getting some download content.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Xbox Live Arcade's version, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Going to be getting some extra stages and some things.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's 240 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess you get some reimagining of the original Space Invaders and Space Invaders 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a pretty good price.
[SPEAKER_12]: 240 points for two games and some download content?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not much at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought Duke Nukem Forever was cancelled, finally.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if we ever get the final word on that or not.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's still in limbo because somebody could technically still take the code because wouldn't the publisher now own the code?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: And get somebody else to finish it and call it a done deal?
[SPEAKER_11]: It could happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we're going to take some time now to bring up your emails.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every week we let you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com and we respond to them live on air.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, that's what we're going to do right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, take it away.
[SPEAKER_01]: AlphaKananagram must have been bored.
[SPEAKER_01]: We got an email with the title, You Suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then the inside, it says, I love Puyo Puyo Wee.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't drink and... Is Puyo Puyo on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wii.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you refer to yourself and other people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I get it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then, from MisoSky, we have, Hey, I have been noticing that the majority of MMORPGs are either science fiction or medieval fantasy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you ever think we will see MMORPGs that are westerns, 1980s, or even modern era?
[SPEAKER_01]: Dude, we have.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was Matrix.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think that people are attracted... That's sort of sci-fi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that is more sci-fi, but you were in a modern environment.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think people are attracted to an MMORPG that has been done countless times before?
[SPEAKER_01]: There actually are pirate-based MMOs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Puzzle Pirates?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, there actually was one that I played a little bit of at PAX last year.
[SPEAKER_01]: Where you could play a pirate and raid for booty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, what about, did they mention, like, you know, Star Trek has an MMO coming out?
[SPEAKER_11]: Science Fiction.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or Eve.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, it's Science Fiction.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Science Fiction or Medieval Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Something else outside the box.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything Western?
[SPEAKER_11]: Disney has a couple MMOs out there, based on their products, but they're a little...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know Disney stars are genetically engineered in a lab, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't there a Pirates of the Caribbean?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there is.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the thing about those games, you can't type text in them.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have predetermined phrases that you can say because obviously they have to keep it family safe.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you don't have mean people in there typing fuck, shit, piss, cock unless that is a preselected phrase.
[SPEAKER_11]: They also have all the adult MMOs.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can always try to find an adult MMO.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like the Red Light District one?
[SPEAKER_11]: You're going to have to face it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The fantasy and sci-fi ones are by far the most popular, at least right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_01]: Last one, and it comes from Maren.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, ready?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's long.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey guys, I didn't get to call in, but I wanted to touch on two subjects that were discussed during last week's episode.
[SPEAKER_01]: First, Rob mentioned that some people are complaining about how DJ Hero is just a ripoff of Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_01]: I believe that Rob protested the idea, saying they're completely different.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'd like to think it's something like this.
[SPEAKER_01]: DJ Hero is to Beatmania 2DX as Guitar Hero is to Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_01]: You could very well...
[SPEAKER_01]: you could very well say that these two games Beatmania and Guitar Freaks are the original music games and that games like DJ and Guitar Hero are knockoffs but I think it's more than that
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_01]: who play or have played Guitar Freaks but I only have one friend who hasn't played Guitar Hero or Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_01]: Perhaps DJ Hero is similar to Beatmania TDX but it will definitely be something that is more accessible to a Western audience.
[SPEAKER_01]: I for one am happy that DJ Hero is joining the ranks of other music games like Guitar Hero and Rock Band because the success of DJ Hero will only bring us that much closer to having an Americanized keyboard mania game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I personally will be the first person to stand in line to pre-order Piano Hero Elton John.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who's surprised?
[SPEAKER_12]: I would say the better comparison I think would be Guitar Freaks and Guitar Hero and then probably Beat Mania and Kraken DJ.
[SPEAKER_12]: because, you know, Kraken DJ, it's kind of a beat-matching game, but it's very different than Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I have my own thoughts, but let me wait until the email's done.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, also, I did just get a note in saying that AlphaKananagram says that wasn't him, but an imposter.
[SPEAKER_01]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I honestly, I don't really care, I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Finally, I just wanted to touch on the idea of the new PS3 remote.
[SPEAKER_01]: To make a long story short, the idea of the PS3 remote makes me think of the SuperScope 6, pretty nifty idea in theory, complete fail in execution.
[SPEAKER_01]: Take care and have fun gaming, Marin.
[SPEAKER_01]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, if you come to Las Vegas from July 1st through 7th, I will give you a dollar.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to Las Vegas from July 1st through the 7th.
[SPEAKER_11]: You win a dollar.
[SPEAKER_11]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about buy me a soda?
[SPEAKER_11]: You should put that dollar in a slot machine and win a hundred.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't gamble.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm going to play bimbo.
[SPEAKER_11]: I agree with some of the email and I disagree with some of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I agree with the fact that Harmonix has done great things for music games over here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's not forget they did create the original Guitar Hero as well as Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_11]: Harmonix rocks.
[SPEAKER_11]: They did what Konami was too pussy to do, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: For that, they deserve to be commended and get praise lavished upon them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: From a music game fan like myself, you have to understand.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: However, the part I disagree with is the comparison about DJ Hero and the Guitar Freaks, Guitar Hero thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I get that, and here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bet that's the same thing we're going to hear on G4 and for a lot of these networks and stuff, but I don't think it's a real good comparison.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would use the Guitar Hero, Guitar Freaks comparison in trying to describe DDR and In the Groove maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although, you know, both games were guitars where you held down buttons and strummed the thing in time with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The thing that's different for me is that that's not really what's happening with DJ Hero is that because you not only have the buttons, but you have the scratching and the crossfader is really big as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's different than it is in 2DX because the whole crossfading leads to a style of gameplay that to me looks more like amplitude in a way.
[SPEAKER_12]: 2DX was more where the scratching was just a replacement of another button, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: And for me, 2DX just feels like it's just DDR but using buttons instead of your feet, which is ironic because Beatmania came before DDR, but that's really what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's another way of reading music, in a way.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think a better comparison would be to say Street Fighter 2 versus Tekken.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're both fighting games, but they're completely different characters.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Hero and Beat Me at 2DX, they're both music games.
[SPEAKER_11]: They both involve turntables, but they're really different.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're just like Kraken DJ.
[SPEAKER_12]: When games started coming out and stuff, more fighting games, everyone was like, oh, it's a Street Fighter ripoff.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think we're going to kind of go through this phase right now with Guitar Hero and these music games because everyone's going to say, oh, it's a ripoff.
[SPEAKER_12]: But really, it's just another music game.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, I mean, we got into it elsewhere on the show, though, as well, is that, you know, now they're charging a premium price for it, and I think that's going to be a little bit damaging.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's also not forget, though, one thing that is interesting is that DJ Hero is not being made by Harmonix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Something to kind of keep in mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: Harmonix is not making DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's kind of cool that other developers now, it's not just Harmonix has to make all our music games.
[SPEAKER_12]: But they, yeah, another developer, you know, is the one that did, you know, was...
[SPEAKER_12]: B-Boy, they did that game, which is another sort of music rhythm game with dancing involved and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: But they kind of have that whole style that they kind of brought with them and stuff and their influences with that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm willing to check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you might have missed a point, too, is that she wasn't saying that DJ Hero is like 2DX.
[SPEAKER_01]: It pertains to 2DX in the way that Guitar Hero pertained to Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not that they're the same type of game, but they're different.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the Americanized improved version, basically.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's tailored to a different audience and newer.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can see that to a point.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just so different than it felt when we were talking about Guitar Hero or Guitar Freeze.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I think when a lot of us looked at Guitar Hero the first time, a lot of us jumped to that whole, oh, it's Guitar Freeze.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now that we're seeing DJ Hero, I don't see 2DX at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just that the basic influence is there.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Showing the Guitar Hero a game like that would be popular in the first place.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, does that do it for the Mailbag?
[SPEAKER_01]: That be it, sir.
[SPEAKER_01]: Arr.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to send us more emails, Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to send your emails.
[SPEAKER_11]: We do have a segment here every week where we read those.
[SPEAKER_11]: Also, we do some interactive stuff through our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, if you don't have us added on Twitter yet, you should do that at Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: with Netflix on the Xbox 360 plus Microsoft's own video service.
[SPEAKER_12]: Same thing with the PlayStation Network where you can stream movies as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, apparently Instat, a marketing analysis group, published a report this week basically examining how this web-to-TV streaming is consumed by people out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: and they found that the majority of it is coming actually from console owners.
[SPEAKER_12]: They said 29% of U.S.
[SPEAKER_12]: console owners between the ages of 25 and 34 currently use their consoles to stream video to their televisions.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yeah, I can see that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I use it for streaming...
[SPEAKER_12]: Video, and files and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Plus, I've also downloaded TV episodes and stuff like that on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, it is popular.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's convenient.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's my question.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's the competition besides game consoles?
[SPEAKER_11]: Apple TV?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are they comparing it to Apple TV?
[SPEAKER_11]: Or are they comparing it to these Netflix boxes that you can buy that are just standalone Netflix devices that I've heard of?
[SPEAKER_12]: Digital media adapters, set-top boxes like Apple TV, Blu-ray players, web-connected HD TVs, and I guess media center PCs.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's odd that they throw Blu-ray players into that.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess web-enabled stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe they're talking about how you can get those bonuses on Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah, like you can go into the BD Live and get all the user commentary and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't figure out.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's too complicated for a normal person to use.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that BD Live stuff with doing all the custom commentary stuff, too complicated.
[SPEAKER_11]: If they want people to actually use that, they need to make it more...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: WALL-E but it's not really a chat room they don't show messages or anything like that because you know somebody would just be on there typing penis penis penis the whole time but what they do they do these weird like polls like a little thing will pop up on the screen like press this button if you saw WALL-E in the theater or press this button if you didn't see it until it came out on blu-ray or whatever and like people vote and it shows you the results these weird little interactive things that I think just need some time to be good
[SPEAKER_11]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of looked at it going, that's kind of a neat feature.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish they could do something more useful with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's what I think would be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: As you know how with Blu-ray and stuff you can do full Java programming with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interactive board games or TV show things like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Trivia games I think would be pretty cool because you could actually program that stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you know how before with a DVD you'd have some sort of crazy menu system and paths and stuff that would go for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You could actually program a pretty decent game.
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw on chat says, the BD Live stuff is cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: My only gripe is the video extras they offer aren't full screen.
[SPEAKER_11]: I see I've yet to even really figure out how to get the video extras.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know what DVD...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: and I'm being told the Transformers Blu-ray has new BD Live content featuring footage from the new Transformers movie plus some deleted scenes from the first one that just went released this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well that would explain why I don't have it because I don't have the Transformers Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought about the Transformers Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got it on HD.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: We all got screwed for that so there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: SSJ100 Matt makes an interesting comment in chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm buying a Blu-ray player for my dad for his birthday this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really don't see why he would want any of this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Besides, I don't feel like showing him how to use it.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, honestly, I have my Blu-ray player on PS3.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't use any of this extra content.
[SPEAKER_12]: In fact, I could care less about these interactive things where I can go on and chat with the producers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a damn DVD.
[SPEAKER_12]: If I want to chat with producers and stuff, I'll go on the internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_12]: Blu-ray, DVD, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm looking for basically the same content that's on a DVD, but maybe in a higher resolution or more content added on there instead of having to have four discs or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just all on one disc.
[SPEAKER_12]: Would be nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Back to the original part of the story.
[SPEAKER_11]: The whole Netflix thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: What...
[SPEAKER_11]: What is the central part of this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Are they trying to say that this is just showing that game devices are actually becoming entertainment hubs and all these other types of things that will only do entertainment are being rejected?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they're surprised that for something that's streaming from the web that the consoles...
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess they're saying basically that video to television streaming is putting pressure on traditional cable providers and will eventually restructure today's video distribution ecosystem.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they're saying that game consoles are at the forefront of this new direction.
[SPEAKER_12]: So basically they're saying...
[SPEAKER_12]: eventually everything is going to go the kind of digital streaming that physical media is going to go away or at least that's what they're claiming and that leading the way of this transition is game consoles hmm
[SPEAKER_11]: That sounds pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm looking at some comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw talks about the particular Blu-ray player he has.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a Sony BDP-S350 which supports BD Live.
[SPEAKER_11]: The BD Live only works on it as long as you have a USB thumb drive connected on the back.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wonder how many people would even think to do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's so many people that just need it to work right out of the box.
[SPEAKER_11]: TheRobD says, I don't know when the last time I listened to a director commentary was, but TigerClaw follows that up with, I love listening to director's commentary.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I guess it really depends on the person.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: SSJ100Matt closes this thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a gimmick, is what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting story on Netflix kind of turned into this whole Blu-ray discussion, but I think that Blu-ray thing is something that will continue to evolve.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think the smart thing that has been built into it is funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's something I was critical of Sony on earlier.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was critical on Sony about this, and that is that Sony does not manage to evolve usually, and that's why Microsoft's beating them.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: Now it appears they are evolving in where it comes to Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_12]: For more updates, that's what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now you can create a new feature and everybody can now have that feature.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, let's move on to another topic and talk a little bit about something else that's going on on the PlayStation 3 right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was a hamster versus human dance-off in PlayStation Home.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, you heard me right.
[SPEAKER_11]: This Saturday, this past Saturday, there was a hamsters versus humans dance-off that happened.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just want to point out, it's not April 1st, it is the middle of June, and I don't know what the hell this was for, although apparently...
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_11]: And some of them look like furries because they're hamsters.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think the most important information that we got out of this is that there's hamster costumes in home.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's scary now because now there's furries in home.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I think my initial reaction when I watched this video and kind of everything that's going on here is, What the fucking fuck is this fucking bullfuck fuck?
[SPEAKER_11]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is this what we imagined PlayStation Home was going to be when they unveiled it at Gamer Developers Conference last year?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, is this the innovation that they were looking forward to do in Home?
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is just Second Life, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the kind of crap that happens in Second Life.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not that I have a problem with the stupidity of the whole thing...
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was on the official Sony PlayStation blog.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm just kind of like, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: These are the events I have to look forward to at home?
[SPEAKER_11]: What is the fucking point?
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Home being used to broadcast the Sony PlayStation conference during E3?
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a great use of home.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was smart.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: And having everybody in that one place, they could view it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hamsters vs. Humans...
[SPEAKER_12]: and it doesn't look like there was a good turnout for that either I mean it's just like maybe 50 people
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, apparently it was server by server, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: You log into home, there's a lot of people using it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just don't know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have yet to figure that out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Waiting in lines for games?
[SPEAKER_12]: Why do you have to wait in line to play a game?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a fucking virtual world.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can play the game whenever the hell you want.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why do I have to wait in line to play a virtual game?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: TigerClaw says home is also being used for Q&As with the directors and stars of big movies.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, that's neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little unnecessary, but I guess they do it in Second Life, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's something more special than a chat room because you can actually see the director or the special person in front of you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And do the running man as a hamster.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or guinea pig, or whatever the hell.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: SHM100Matt says, why couldn't Jack Trenton talk about this?
[SPEAKER_11]: LOL.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zappy says waiting in lines is very social
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's hard for me to say because I don't know what types of things people say on home.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't pay attention to a lot of the dialogue.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I can't imagine people are going to be as cordial online as they are in real life.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you're standing in line at Disneyland, maybe you'll strike up conversation with people around you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I usually don't because I strike up conversation with the people that are with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: But okay, we are being social because I'm with people.
[SPEAKER_11]: but A, in home you don't really have that everybody goes to home by themselves and B, when people can hide behind their monitors they do stupid shit that they wouldn't do in real life so I don't think people would say hurry the fuck up at Disneyland as much as they would say in Sony Home I don't know I say hurry the fuck up all the time at Disneyland
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but you're not really saying it to a child.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, maybe you are.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, I just... What I wanted to tell some of the parents there is to watch your fucking children, maybe.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just when I saw this whole thing, granted, if I don't like it, I just shouldn't play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm just looking at this going, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is what home has become?
[SPEAKER_12]: I can understand if it was some sort of thing that bloggers or whatever decided, hey, let's do this.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wouldn't have even reported on it in that case.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was on the official PlayStation blog.
[SPEAKER_11]: And with a little poster markup and everything.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I don't know if that's kind of like just giving in or conceding to what home has become.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if you want me to have this be, I turn on my PlayStation and the first thing I see is home.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then I walk up to this if I want to launch a game or I have my trophy case and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, really, this is not the way to sell it to me that this is ever going to be a reality.
[SPEAKER_12]: You'll be able to launch in the home and view your trophy case coming 2010.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's on the horizon, Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have to understand that the pure use of home, it's coming.
[SPEAKER_12]: It'll be there eventually.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't worry, we'll have a firm launch date that we won't stick to, but it'll come.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: How could I ever doubt Sony?
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially after the amazing hardware that was the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: How dare I?
[SPEAKER_11]: How dare I be skeptical?
[SPEAKER_11]: All I have to say is bring on the games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Part of me thinks if I'd seen this earlier, I would have actually logged in to check it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then once I was there, I would have been like, what the hell am I doing with my life?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, slash risk, slash risk.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, oh well.
[SPEAKER_11]: They need PvP at home.
[SPEAKER_11]: or just maybe a game somewhere in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: PvP.
[SPEAKER_11]: PvP would be better.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would be cool if I could actually walk up to somebody and it was very easy to start a game.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: At the same time, maybe finding my friends list in a home would be a place to start.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe a section of home that only my friends list can access or friends of friends can access.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would love that.
[SPEAKER_11]: A section where I only see friends and friends of friends and then can start up really easy, quick games with them.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, as a matter of fact, I do.
[SPEAKER_01]: And this is actually something that I think is really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Namco Museum Essentials is coming to PlayStation Home in July, which looks like we'll be getting Pac-Man, Galaga, Dig Dug, Dragon Spirit, Xevious, and a 1080p quote re-envisioned Xevious Resurrection, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you get your trophies, leaderboards, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it's more Namco, and that's always happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the important thing to note about this is it's in home.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it's in home.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's strange.
[SPEAKER_11]: So am I going to have to buy this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is home going to be the only place I can play this Xevious re-imaging?
[SPEAKER_01]: I doubt it for very long.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you buy the game and then you have to wait in line to play your own game that you just bought?
[SPEAKER_12]: Surely it can't be like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it goes in your own house.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would make sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you buy this game and it goes in the house you own.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can other friends play it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or is it going to be sorry?
[SPEAKER_11]: You can invite friends in your home, can't you?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's just so... Honestly, I have to be honest.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't really know how to do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: One thing Sony could do is make this whole thing easier.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Facebook.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bejeweled.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tons of people play Bejeweled on Facebook, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know about your friends list, but on my friends list, tons of people play.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know why they all play?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because when one person plays...
[SPEAKER_11]: And they get a good score.
[SPEAKER_11]: They click a button and it publishes to their profile.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm playing this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Come play with me by clicking here.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's how easy it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: If they want home to be like this central place that everybody... It needs to be that easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm sure I have listeners that are like, Rob, all you have to do is open up the menu and da-da-da-da-da.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're not hearing what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_11]: It needs to be easier than that.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want...
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know though, as far as the Namco thing goes, I guess that's pretty cool, but I guess this could be the start of where we really start to see now maybe the full intention of home?
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to call it that?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: To cash in on stuff?
[SPEAKER_12]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, I think this would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really wanna play it, actually.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really, really wanna play it, because I love Xevious.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actdeft in our chatroom points out Yaris was free too, and we all know how that turned out.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Marin in chat makes a very good point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Home in real life is where you're lazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Home for PlayStation 3 should be lazy-friendly too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly my point.
[SPEAKER_11]: And RPGKing7 says it has to be stupid-friendly.
[SPEAKER_11]: It does.
[SPEAKER_11]: If we want our parents and some of our friends who aren't as into gaming, you all know this.
[SPEAKER_11]: You all have a friend who thinks video games are kind of fun, but doesn't really play an awful lot of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: But they might own a next-gen system that they play Madden or a role-playing game on once in a while.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: They wouldn't know how to use a lot of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: They need to take, I think, examples.
[SPEAKER_12]: What they need to do is kind of learn from MMOs and what people do in their downtime in MMOs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think home should add fishing because there's plenty of fishing going on in Final Fantasy XI and you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's something you can do by yourself and just kick back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, what about something like item synthesis or professions?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know it sounds stupid but imagine if you could make your own shirts.
[SPEAKER_11]: and things within reason.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like I'm not saying put your own designs on it because everybody will walk around with a shirt saying fuck or topless mods that just pictures of boobs and things like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'm saying like, you know, people could collect items in home and then build stuff and then maybe even like sell them for fake money.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then I'm turning home into an MMO and I guess that's not his intention.
[SPEAKER_11]: But all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's move on to another topic.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we're going to get into some Listless for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm excited because we haven't done Listless in a long time here on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I need to find the music, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shame on me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I didn't have the music queued up already.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we have music that goes with Listless.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's a remake of a familiar tune.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, there we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: The theme music for Listless.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, the way this works, folks, if you've never heard this segment before on Orange Lounge Radio, we've been doing it ever since the very beginning because this is a segment I used to do on my college radio show.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it gives you an idea like how old this is.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to take a topic and then we are each here in studio going to give our top four for that topic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, we've changed things up a little bit since last time we've done this.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're all going to give our top four for the topic.
[SPEAKER_11]: and then we will have made a list of 12 between the list of 4 that both DarkSakura, Loki and myself make then we will each go around and take one item off of the list leaving us with a list of 9 then you guys in chat will vote on the 9, your favorite and you give us your number 1 and number 2 votes and then we should have a definitive list
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: And Reggie Fils-Aim asked, Well, in the same vein of Team Ninja working with Nintendo to reimagine Metroid, what development group would your readers love to see partner and collaborate with Nintendo and on what franchise?
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, let's face it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Metroid Other M was probably the big, big announcement out of Nintendo for us hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_11]: OMG Team Ninja working with Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_11]: So, what do you think could be the next OMG developer working with a Nintendo franchise?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what we're here to put the list together tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: So let's start putting that list together.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, why don't you start us off this week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Give us your number four answer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ah, number four answer.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is kind of a joke answer, so we're going to go with that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Akira Yamaoka and Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Team Silent or just Akira Yamaoka?
[SPEAKER_11]: Team Silent.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Team Silent is going to remake Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: How would that work?
[SPEAKER_12]: It would be extremely intense, but with Luigi.
[SPEAKER_12]: Would Pyramid Head make an appearance in it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Less whimsical, more scary, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see, my answer would be my number four answer tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blizzard, the folks behind World of Warcraft, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Blizzard would make an Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: So now Animal Crossing really would be an MMO.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Blizzard makes an Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so DarkSakura, what is your number four pick and why?
[SPEAKER_01]: God, mine's actually kind of related to that.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Sims team doing a new Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_01]: And actually, you know, make it interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: We both had Animal Crossing answers back to back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Suda51 or Grasshopper Manufacturer and Wario Land
[SPEAKER_12]: And, you know, Suda51 is the, you know, the mind behind Killer7 and No More Heroes and just, like, the insane, crazy shit that's in those games.
[SPEAKER_12]: Put that in Wario Land, because, you know, WarioWare and stuff's really crazy, so it'd just be batshit crazy, just the platformer.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is insane.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is just pure insanity.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_01]: My number three is the Outrun team doing the next Cruisin'.
[SPEAKER_01]: And making that a good game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I haven't thought of Cruisin' for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought Cruisin' was Midway.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_01]: But didn't they, no, that was with Nintendo and Rare.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I think there was something, yeah, Rare had something to do with it too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: So fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what, we'll let it slide.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't even matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Outrun Team makes Cruisin' and brings that series back.
[SPEAKER_11]: It certainly has memories on Nintendo 64 and all that.
[SPEAKER_11]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're halfway through.
[SPEAKER_11]: What would you say?
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see if I should start doing some of my serious ones here.
[SPEAKER_11]: The chat room is clarifying, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was Midway made it, but for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it was really a Nintendo franchise that Midway made.
[SPEAKER_12]: Looks like... I hope I don't mispronounce this.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kaita Takahashi and Yoshi's Island.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Kaito Takahashi, the creator of Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Yoshi's Island.
[SPEAKER_12]: What would this game be like?
[SPEAKER_12]: Touch Fuzzy, Get Dizzy?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, the entire game would be Touch Fuzzy, Get Dizzy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: Then we're going to get into my number two answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Q Entertainment, because I'll buy practically anything Q Entertainment does.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remaking, and I'm kind of stretching it a little bit, kind of like the Cruisin' Answer, but Nintendo does have the rights here to Tetris on their own, and Nintendo obviously put out a lot of the big versions of Tetris.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think Q Entertainment should just give us a new Tetris, infused with all the music and lights and hypnotic stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's what I want.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry for the silence.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm actually typing out a list here as we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, your number two answer, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Silent Hill team doing Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought you did that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_11]: You guys both had the same one?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought you were talking about a different game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, how funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll pick something different.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, shoot.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can do another one if she wants to take mine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, because I completely missed it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, how about the... There's lots of good ideas in chat.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I don't listen to them.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, okay, how about Square doing the next Zelda game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zelda's a beloved franchise, but maybe it's time to turn it over and let some other people who are more experienced at it have a crack at it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Square makes a Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so so far we have Team Silent makes Luigi's Mansion, Blizzard makes Animal Crossing, Sims Team makes Animal Crossing, Suda51 makes Wario Land, Capcom makes Kid Icarus, Outrun Team makes Cruisin', Keita Takahashi makes Yoshi's Island, Q Entertainment makes Tetris, Square makes a Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's get into the number one answers.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, your number one answer, please.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry Rob, this is probably going to take years but Criterion Games does the next F-Zero because Burnout is fucking awesome and it just lends itself perfectly to F-Zero
[SPEAKER_11]: well you read my mind but Criterion Games was not who I actually thought of to take over the F-Zero franchise my number one answer is Sega, Namco, and Nintendo all team up again and finally bring us a fucking sequel to F-Zero GX and yes I phrased it just like that so Sega and Namco once again make F-Zero GX
[SPEAKER_11]: That's two F-Zero GXs as number one answer so far.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if... I'm sorry, just F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess the GX wouldn't really be there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see if DarkSakura has the same answer or something new.
[SPEAKER_01]: Something new.
[SPEAKER_01]: Treasure doing a new Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_01]: Could you imagine how hard that shit would be?
[SPEAKER_11]: That could be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some runner-ups I had.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arc System Works and Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arc System Works, of course, the Guilty Gear franchise.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh god, that would be crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: 2D Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_12]: game would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bethesda and Zelda.
[SPEAKER_12]: Another one that just popped into my head.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kojima Productions and Battalion Wars.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: No Earthbound.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was almost going to say that Square should do the Earthbound game, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Earthbound's very American, even though, yes, I realize.
[SPEAKER_11]: Square's very Japanese-centric.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just don't think it would meld well.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was trying to think of the perfect developer for that, but I couldn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well guess what guys?
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is, the list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now we gotta go around and eliminate.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is gonna be hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so here it is so far.
[SPEAKER_11]: Team Silent makes Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Blizzard makes a new Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Sims team makes a new Animal Crossing game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Suda51 makes Wario Land.
[SPEAKER_11]: Capcom makes Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_11]: Outrun team makes Cruisin'.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keita Takahashi makes Yoshi's Island.
[SPEAKER_11]: Q Entertainment makes Tetris.
[SPEAKER_11]: Square makes a Zelda game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Criterion Games makes F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sega and Namco once again make F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_11]: and Treasure makes Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_11]: Outrun Team makes Cruisin'.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_12]: Boo-hiss.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry, the last few Cruisin' games have really sucked.
[SPEAKER_11]: But this would breathe new life.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am going to take out Suda51 makes Wario Land.
[SPEAKER_11]: Too crazy.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just too weird.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, which one of these is not worthy of the list?
[SPEAKER_01]: Blizzard doing Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_11]: You just want yours to be the only Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, honestly.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Three have been eliminated from the list, leaving us with a list of nine that the chat will now vote on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll get to the answers a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Remember, you need to be in our chat, chat.orangeloungeradio.com, and you can place a private message to Rob Roberts in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: with your number one and number two answers.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, here we go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Team Silent makes Luigi's Mansion, The Sims Team makes a new Animal Crossing game, Capcom makes Kid Icarus, Keita Takahashi makes Yoshi's Island, Q Entertainment makes Tetris, Square makes a Zelda game, Criterion Games makes F-Zero, Sega and Namco once again make F-Zero, or Treasure makes Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we have...
[SPEAKER_11]: 2 F0s and 2 Kid Icarus is on there so we'll see how that plays out if they split the votes or what so remember you can place a vote now to Rob Roberts in the chat room with a private message and indicate your number 1 and your number 2 or it will be assumed that your first answer is your number 1 pick while we tally that up
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to get into another segment here.
[SPEAKER_11]: We like to call the FUs of the week, but in order for our angst to build, we have to have a story that makes it worthy of us building the angst.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I also have to cue the music, which I was completely unprepared for tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not used to this new format yet where everything's in a different order in the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyhow...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Nor could you redeem codes, including your pre-order codes for the Xbox 360 version of Ghostbusters.
[SPEAKER_11]: So the PlayStation 3 users got to jump on that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And look, all I'm going to say is if you're going to take your system down for 24 hours, it should be working by the time you bring it back up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or don't bring it back up.
[SPEAKER_11]: So stories like this make us angry.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, we're going to bring on the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_01]: My FU of the week goes towards sleeping for 12-13 hours because I lost most of my day.
[SPEAKER_12]: My FU goes to Xbox Live Marketplace because Angry Barry is still broken and I still am out 400 Microsoft points and nobody seems to be fixing anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Very convenient, Microsoft, now that you have my money.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, my FU of the week goes to the fact that I just told people to vote for the wrong thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, in chat, it's Rob Roberts, not Sky.
[SPEAKER_11]: Look, three people fixed it all in a row.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm broken and I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess I'm going to say F you to the swine flu for reals.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know there's been a lot of jokes and ha-has made about it, but I actually have a friend suffering from swine flu right now who's in the hospital in ICU and is really not in good shape right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: And a lot of us are actually kind of scared because she had to get put on dialysis this morning.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's how bad it's gotten because her kidneys are failing from all the meds.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, she contracted swine flu.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know where it came from, but Beth, I am thinking of you and I really want you to get better soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: and more.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, let's go ahead and move on to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: While I tally the votes, my God, there's tons of people voting tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, of course, you would think with the Apple iPhone and the iPod Touch, you know, it's a bit limited in what you can do with games on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, of course, and this is actually being listed as one of the features with the iPhone 3.0 firmware, is that third-party accessories are going to now,
[SPEAKER_12]: and this is actually coming from the official iPod Touch software update page and so people are thinking oh goody we're going to get controller add-ons and so that might be actually what's going to happen because with gaming being so popular nowadays and really those touch screen controls suck I mean look at Mega Man 2 they need a new alternative so it might actually be an add-on
[SPEAKER_12]: So what do you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that a good idea?
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you actually play with something like this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, I'm like tallying cage match votes right now, so it's hard for me to totally pay attention, but... It really, I think, would depend on how well executed it is, honestly.
[SPEAKER_01]: They'd really have to do something impressive.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I think it's kind of...
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess it's okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, a lot of people are kind of bitchy about, you know, oh, I don't want to, you know, have some stupid peripheral hanging off of my, you know, iPod to play a game.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, I guess you don't necessarily need to buy it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And some people are saying, hey, now they can do Guitar Hero on iPhone.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be scary.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I mean, the iPhone kind of needs something like that if it's really going to be like the next wave in gaming or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I don't know how seriously Apple's taking gaming right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I've heard about this whole like premium games for the iPhone thing, which I think is silly.
[SPEAKER_11]: The games that are on there right now, I don't see them getting much better than that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why should I pay four times as much?
[SPEAKER_11]: Especially when there's a lot of great indie games that are 99 cents or free.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, definitely.
[SPEAKER_11]: So.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I'm trying to see if there's anything going on in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're still talking about the list list tonight a little bit, which I'm still trying to tally up.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Rob D in chat, though, says, isn't the point of the iPhone 3GS to be better for gaming?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think not necessarily just gaming.
[SPEAKER_01]: How about to be a more efficient multimedia machine?
[SPEAKER_01]: That's what I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, I believe that brings us to the end of our topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we're going to go ahead and open up the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you want to give us a call, if you have any type of topic you want to bring up that we missed tonight, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Meanwhile, do we have any last minute stories or missed rapid fires that we want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, sure, I've got some stuff I can talk about.
[SPEAKER_12]: Apparently, there's a rumor that Michael Jackson is involved with the new video game, and no word on exactly what that is yet, but apparently, there's something that he's working on right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, um...
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is coming out of... It's actually a foreign article.
[SPEAKER_12]: 9lives.be is the website that has the information on it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of hard to determine what exactly they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have gone through an official Xbox rite of passage How so?
[SPEAKER_09]: Red Ring of Death
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, and you've had your Xbox for the past year.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, you know, that's the price you pay for having something early, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and what was funny was that when I went to fire it up, it didn't even have the new Xbox experience so I had to download everything first.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_11]: That is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still have one of the older consoles or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Perhaps, but I don't think they're going to give you the top-of-the-line ones as a replacement.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's probably the hidden text.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I could have asked for a different box if I wanted to, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, because you get to keep your drive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it seems that with Best Buy, you bring it in, you hold onto the hard drive, and they just give you a brand new console.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess, but that's the same thing they do with Microsoft, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I never sent my hard drive back.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's something to do about the actual serial on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't played either of those games in a long time, either, so they might have changed something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because, you know, now there's Geometry Wars 2, and I couldn't tell you the last time I signed on to Xbox Live and played Joust.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I should do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Joust is awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: I should think about that, but most of the time I'm just streaming videos and stuff off my 360 from my computer because I don't like sitting here in front of the 19-inch.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd rather watch it in glorious 32-inch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Size does matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what she said.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, Ranma, anything else before we let you go tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, you take care buddy, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: 877-GAME-OLR, Orange Lounge Radio on Skype.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listless results coming right up, but a few more last minute stories.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do we have any more?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, actually that one thing I was talking about, the Michael Jackson game, he's supposed to be starring in his own game, so no word on exactly what that is, but it's a game that he's actually going to be the lead in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Quick question, chat, anyone interested in a Michael Jackson game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Would you buy it?
[SPEAKER_10]: If Sega did it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's say it's a music game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Pleasure, I'm Zaku.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Zaku, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing much, just spending a rainy weekend here in New York City.
[SPEAKER_05]: If it's Moonwalker 2, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Boone Walker 2, Michael Jackson Boone Walker 2?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, Michael Jackson's Boone Walker 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: You might not have heard it because you were calling in, but I asked the chatters, if Michael Jackson is really making a video game and starring in it, would you buy it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Will that involve, like, you know, Jesus Juice and other sexual accusations?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's not go there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Zakud, what did you want to call in about tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, basically I just wanted to bring up a little gem that I managed to find this weekend.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, I don't know if you heard, but this probably made Kotaku earlier today, but
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently, these developers were making an iPhone Commodore 64 application.
[SPEAKER_11]: We did touch on it during Rapid Fire News and it got shut down, which stinks, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you think about it getting shut down?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I guess on one hand it's Apple's walled garden.
[SPEAKER_05]: You see that they pretty much control what apps make it onto their store.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I guess they ran afoul with the fact that
[SPEAKER_05]: And I can see that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bigo.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could pretty much run any other app, any other music synthesizer, for example.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bingo.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's too much.
[SPEAKER_11]: It leaves it too vulnerable.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kind of actually understand where Apple's coming from for the model they're trying to build.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess Sega basically dodged it by creating a standalone emulator hard-coded for Sonic and Golden Axe.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's no way you would have been able to run an arbitrary code.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I guess if those C64 guys want to make their apps on the App Store, they just got to make drastic changes to the point where they have to bundle the games that they license them from.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's going to be one app for The Last Ninja, one app for...
[SPEAKER_05]: or something like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you could sell the other games as DLC.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then, you know where it's not going to work?
[SPEAKER_11]: Now you have to get all the original publishers involved.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: As opposed to being able to run all your old code
[SPEAKER_11]: I bet I could find my old Commodore 64 floppies and the mass amounts of games I had.
[SPEAKER_11]: I would love to have a night.
[SPEAKER_11]: We seriously need to plan the time we are going to freaking do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just do some seriously hardcore old fucking school gaming on big televisions.
[SPEAKER_05]: well, we've got the vault
[SPEAKER_05]: and just like really old school consoles right there in one particular room out of six game rooms that weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: I really want to figure out, maybe we could do this at a con or something, tag on to some con.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to broadcast it and I want to marathon obscure classic games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to do like Mario Brothers and all that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's some type of charity thing, but it's all obscure shit, like stuff that you may not have played before, like Impossible Mission or other Congress 64 games.
[SPEAKER_05]: What about that Penn & Teller game?
[SPEAKER_05]: That Penn & Teller game we just drive on a bus for hours.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but let's face it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The joke is that the game is stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't want to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, go through our own Classic Game of the Week archive and pick like 10 of those obscure games and play those.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I had my share of obscure games and I had my NES, so I pretty much have a good pig.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ziba says, at PAX, please.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, dude, if we could get a room at PAX somehow like that, I would love that, except we're probably not big enough.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I never thought about it either.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to start with the smaller, you have to start with the con, at the con level, since that's pretty much your domain at the moment.
[SPEAKER_05]: PAX is kind of like major, it's like a major indie thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of like the E3 of indie games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I agree we need to piggyback on a con somewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe I need to talk to the SakAnime people.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need to do a lock-in.
[SPEAKER_11]: We need to rent the Masonic Lodge for a weekend and do a lock-in.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, Zaku, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_11]: But thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, have a good weekend, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mega Man ZX and the EXE Universe
[SPEAKER_12]: And then finally, there's a new record being broken.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Frogger score held by fictional character George Costanda is going to be challenged, I guess, this weekend.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: We got a call.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is RPGKing7.
[SPEAKER_11]: RPGKing7.
[SPEAKER_11]: Are you truly the king of RPGs?
[SPEAKER_11]: I like to think I'm the seventh in line.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are guys above me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Have you played this Final Fantasy IV after years?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I'm all the rage about right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a Wii, so... Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_11]: You've got to figure out a way to play it, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: My parents have a Wii, so I'll probably get it.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know you probably called in to talk about something else, but I've got to ask you a question, because I want to talk about After Years with somebody, and you're the best thing I've got, because you're at least RPG King.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you hear the story about the whole Chrono Trigger fan project getting shut down?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh my god, you're reading my mind.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's exactly what I wanted to bring up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, okay, then you say your thing, and then I'll say mine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I was wondering, you know, why isn't the, I was going to mention it and bring it up, that they were like practically complete, and then Square shut them down.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm wondering, what do you guys think Square is being so anal about it, whereas there's like a million Mario and other fan projects, and the other publishers haven't said boo.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, like, even that...
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I just want to jump into that other project that was a few years ago, where they built up a 3D version of it from the ground up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Square cut them off pretty early.
[SPEAKER_11]: That wasn't that long ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember that, though.
[SPEAKER_11]: Again, I think protecting their rights, because Square's been doing all these remakes on the DS that are in 3D, so maybe they want to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I think they're doing it because they don't want to shut the door on the possibility to do that stuff later on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because I remember years and years ago they copyrighted the name Chrono Break and people were thinking, oh man, they're going to do a new Chrono Trigger, they're going to do a new Chrono Trigger, but they haven't done anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe it's going to be the ace in the hole or whatever, but I know the fans are getting restless.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why are they continuing to shut down all these projects if they're not going to do anything with the Chrono Trigger franchise?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had the whole fan project that did Mother 3 and it looks like we're never ever going to get that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, it's sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I wish we would, because EarthBound's a fun series, and they could put it on WiiWare like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It would be so easy, but for whatever reason, they just don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, I didn't mean to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was saying that the whole DSiWare, and one of the speculations I remember hearing was that they'll put the old Game Boy and Game Boy Advance games on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They put EarthBound 3 on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: They'll get a huge number of people buying that up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but hopefully they're just not afraid of, like, you know, and I remember hearing an argument before that there's too much parody in there that they're worried about getting sued or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just, I hope they just get over that, whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a freaking video game.
[SPEAKER_11]: People need to get over it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, well, RPG King, we gotta let you go to get some more calls, but do you have any other final thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's just, you know, keep the RPG love alive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we will try our best.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, take care.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, the less I play MMOs, the more I can play RPGs, so I will do my best.
[SPEAKER_11]: We can probably get one more call in, 1-877-GAME-OLR or Orange Launch Radio on Skype, but really, really one more call.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways, as I was saying, George Costanza from Seinfeld, his fictional Frogger high score is going to be challenged this weekend for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, apparently Nintendo had another handheld system that they finished.
[SPEAKER_12]: However, they're not going to release it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, apparently, in the history of Nintendo, there are several examples of such devices like this.
[SPEAKER_12]: But when we are launching new hardware, the most important thing is to sustain the momentum.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if introducing new hardware won't do anything to do that, well...
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, it's Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind tonight, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't think you guys were doing a show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surprise!
[SPEAKER_04]: Why wouldn't we do a show tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought last week you said something about being back in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Our anniversary show is in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, maybe that explains our dip in listeners tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: But no, our anniversary show is in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of ironic, because he brought up Month of Three, which is, I think, one of the better RPGs ever made recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyway, there was a fan game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of a prequel to Earthbound, and it's a full RPG.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, it's, granted it's not a ROM pack, uh, it's a, you know, it was done in, like, RPG Maker or something, but, you know, it looks halfway decent, and, you know, it uses a bunch of music and sound effects from EarthBound, and, you know, you don't see Nintendo getting all, you know, butthurt over it.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's no different than logging onto a Harry Potter forum and reading the stories people have invented.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you were going to go by Square's logic, fanfiction.net would not exist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of ridiculous in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe the problem that they have at Square is the ROM hack element of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But then again, I guess, you know, but they also have a 3D... But they did try to make it perfectly clear that the ROM image itself would not be included in this thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was just a patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like the Mother 3 translation was just a patch.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to attain the ROM yourself.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe it was just the whole fact that it was encouraging the altercation of an intellectual property of Square.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think the whole thing's a little silly, and I don't think they stood to lose anything at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: But maybe they just don't want someone out there competing with themselves.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it didn't make sense to me until I played Final Fantasy IV the after years.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you brought that up, I was like, wow, shit, that's a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Really good point.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what that is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It didn't hit me until I played that, and then I was like, oh, I get the lawsuit now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, hey, thank you so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to let you go so we can wrap up the show, but we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: We will be here next week, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's a big show for us.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we'll see you then.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, see you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we're going to go ahead and close up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks to you guys so much for calling in, but I keep cutting Loki off every time he tries to finish the story, because... And it's very rude!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, the callers, we want them to be heard, and I don't like them being on hold for 30 minutes, because then we hear all their background noise, and some of them will start going, Hello?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_11]: And you're trying to do a thing, so we try to get to them quickly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: Rock Band, Metal Track Pack Motorhead, Killed By Death
[SPEAKER_12]: Hawkwind, Master of the Universe, Blue Oyster Cult, TransmaniaConMC, Nazareth, Hair of the Dog Arma 2 looks awesome
[SPEAKER_11]: Operation Flashpoint 2 Dragon Rising
[SPEAKER_12]: PC, Arma 2
[SPEAKER_12]: which is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: So the game needs to be bug tested maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little bit, but hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: You should post that YouTube in chat because it is really funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty funny, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So do that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry to the podcast listeners, you don't get to see that, but you can search for it on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just search for Arma 2 and I'm trying to find the funny video.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll find it.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, since you just picked up the mic, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_11]: We just got the baby potty trained in time.
[SPEAKER_11]: She is talking about a video game, y'all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to play Arma 2 once it comes out.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it hasn't leaked out yet, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_11]: My final thought is candy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want candy.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want sugar.
[SPEAKER_11]: My sweet tooth is bugging me.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can go get us ice cream.
[SPEAKER_11]: Us?
[SPEAKER_01]: Us, yes, us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Us.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, oh, crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: The chatters are reminding me we have not done listless results I can't end the freaking show until we get the listless results God, I almost fired
[SPEAKER_11]: I am really out of it tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a lot on my mind today.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's been a very long week for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I apologize for my amateur radio hostness.
[SPEAKER_11]: But then I remember I don't get paid for this shit, so deal.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: The top three on tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number three.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nintendo franchise you most want to see remade by somebody else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number three answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: You would like to see Square make a Zelda game is the number three answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: There it is tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your number two answer tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Q Entertainment makes a new Tetris game.
[SPEAKER_11]: You kids like your raves.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love this idea, by the way.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want it to happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the number one answer tonight for tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Team Silent makes Luigi's Mansion.
[SPEAKER_11]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your number one answer.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was a joke answer, too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, hey, DarkSakura had it down as a real thing, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is the definitive list, so somebody contact Akira Yamaoka or the folks at Team Silent and let them know.
[SPEAKER_11]: The vacuum heat is strapped to Luigi's back.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's going back in and maybe he'll meet Pyramid Ed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyhow, that is really going to do it for tonight's show, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Change the name of the thing to Luigi Shed His Pants.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mamma Mia!
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my pants!
[SPEAKER_11]: Now that we actually have people regularly reviewing games and talking about gaming music, which is great, we're no IGN.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're no 1UP or GameSpot.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we are three friends who do this show for you guys, and your support keeps us alive.
[SPEAKER_11]: Please continue to tell your friends about the program and join our little family we have here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: We'll see you next week for the seven-year anniversary of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to make sure I can do my class earlier.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oof.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you then
[SPEAKER_07]: See you next week!