[SPEAKER_09]: and I, June 7th, 2009.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're all here in studio with your phone calls and chat romantics to discuss this year's highs and lows of E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
[SPEAKER_05]: I am doing okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was a little worried you weren't going to be here tonight at first, but things pulled through and now you're here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that I had a school orientation, and it turns out that I don't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, that's a good thing though, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: That means I have it next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you can sit here and party with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, it's all parties all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, or you can play Sims 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I can do both at the same time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, no, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, also say hello to the one and only Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki's able to do the show and look at porn at the same time.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you looking at porn?
[SPEAKER_14]: Although my wife is adding bookmarks for porn on my computer, I like to add.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: How very thoughtful of her.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, well, how you doing today, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: You just got back from L.A.
[SPEAKER_13]: today, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, like four hours ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: Most people leave E3 like Friday, but you stayed over till today to do stuff with the wife.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and that reminds me, she wanted me to add a few things about E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: She says...
[SPEAKER_14]: E3 sucked because she had to stay in a hotel room and because the people in the hotel room had open wifi but for whatever reason she couldn't connect to them so she couldn't download the porn fast enough and then she was also pissed off at my computer because it didn't have Yahoo Instant Messenger installed on it anymore that's because a Windows update crashed and I had to reinstall the whole thing so that's her complaint oh and Universal sucks
[SPEAKER_14]: Universal Studios Universal Studios Universal Studios Universal Studios
[SPEAKER_13]: Circling of the Trims.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Mario thing was later in the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, he took over.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe it was the second night.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually watched every night of Conan O'Brien.
[SPEAKER_14]: I saw the sign to go in there and I was like, oh, I want to go in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we couldn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: What day were you at Universal Studios?
[SPEAKER_14]: We were there Thursday afternoon.
[SPEAKER_13]: We went there Friday.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like we kept missing each other the next few days.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Universal Studios sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've never been there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought they had like a Jurassic Park ride and a Simpsons ride.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that a pregnant woman can't ride.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the Simpsons ride, pregnant people can't ride that either.
[SPEAKER_14]: Pregnant women can't ride a lot.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hate to break it to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, but, you know... Violent motions shaking around your belly are not good for twins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, but beside that, though, I mean, they really only have four rides.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have the Jurassic Park ride, the Mummy Returns ride, or whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have the Simpsons ride...
[SPEAKER_14]: and there's maybe one other one I'm not sure but that's all they have at Great America or at not Great America Universal I mean come on for a theme park that's pretty shitty I mean my only bitch is that Universal CityWalk is extremely overpriced and by the way if you don't know what this is
[SPEAKER_13]: LA, they have the Universal Compound right off 101 Freeway.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's where Universal Studios is, where Conan O'Brien tapes his show now.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's where they do a lot of special events.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's where the More Friends concert was a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not Dear Friends, the one More Friends concert they did at E305 was there at the Amphitheater, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I think it was 05, because 04 was the first Dear Friends, 05 was More Friends.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: I know what you're talking about, but I don't remember what it's called.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know someone in chat is going to yell it out in any minute.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com The one episode of that show I saw, they actually taped at Universal CityWalk, so a lot of people know what this place is, but it's extremely overpriced.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I guess, you know, you expect these types of things are going to be.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, enough about theme park rides and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: We have a lot of ground we're going to cover tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the interesting thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I want to say thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chat is now piping up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chase, Chase, Chase.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's called Chase.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: So thank you, chatters.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: So we didn't end up having an outline at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: My husband volunteered.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan volunteered.
[SPEAKER_05]: I volunteered him for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Dan is not used to having to prepare anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dan just comes in here, is funny, and leaves.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's Dan's role in the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds like my marriage.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure he'd be very happy to hear that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can we get him in here to comment on that?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: So tonight we're just, we have no, I mean, I don't know when part A is going to end and part B is going to begin.
[SPEAKER_13]: We just, we're winging it tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: But we know we have a lot of ground to cover with E3 News.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm just warning everybody up front.
[SPEAKER_13]: If the show feels a little weird tonight, it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: It's tough.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: E3 was smaller than it was in 06 when they did the last big one.
[SPEAKER_13]: But this is how I've been describing E3 to people.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was E3 2006 with less Paris Hilton, and that's a great thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Booth Babes are not cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It costs a lot for all that silicone
[SPEAKER_13]: and some companies like Nyko is the one that comes to mind the ones that have the big inflatable Wii controllers they did have some booth babes Nintendo had their I want a big inflatable Wii controller Nintendo didn't have booth babes but they had the educated good looking women that were showing off they just weren't dressed cheaply
[SPEAKER_13]: and a couple, I mean, I'm not saying there weren't any Booth Babes anywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: There were the Trauma Center Babes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think one of the Capcom games or something had some Booth Babes.
[SPEAKER_13]: There just were way less than I saw at E3 2006.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I, in part, blame the economy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see that as a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think the economy cut back on a lot of those types of things this year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Less silicone, more games.
[SPEAKER_13]: And zero booth studs that I saw.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, now that's a travesty.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is a huge travesty.
[SPEAKER_13]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Equal, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Equal opportunity, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Equal representation.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's more and more women going to E3 working and doing, you know, women play games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometimes we want booth babes too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Surprise.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, I happen to be one of those guys who wouldn't mind seeing some of those booth studs.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I've learned to just accept that's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: So whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it is fun harassing the booth babes, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, let's get into your gaming week Besides E3, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did what I'm doing right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which is?
[SPEAKER_13]: Playing Sims.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, not just old school Sims.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you at least played a new game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we've actually had full reviews posted on it on the blog I contribute to that Tiara keeps at AvengersTower.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: She reviewed the game itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I reviewed the exchange in the store and the house mechanics, which, you know me, I love building the houses.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm building the Avengers Mansion right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, give us a little synopsis.
[SPEAKER_13]: What makes this game special compared to previous installments in the franchise?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's new, and really, that's not very special right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, a lot of the play in it is improved.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can put diagonal...
[SPEAKER_05]: Furniture and change a few things.
[SPEAKER_05]: The build a house mode is a lot better.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can definitely customize your body shapes a bit more.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, there's a problem is that the faces are butt ugly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it takes a lot of adjustment to get them not butt ugly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they have no chins.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what are all the other...
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: and you can actually buy points to use in their store and they've got some neat stuff in the store but the only thing that I was actually super excited about was like a lamp and a bathtub because it was a really cool bathtub sounds like a trip to Ikea I want an Ikea pack
[SPEAKER_05]: Sims 2 had Ikea packs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want an Ikea pack.
[SPEAKER_13]: For real?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_13]: There's a huge Sims culture.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think a lot of times, you know, because our show, we try to touch on PC gaming, and I think we do to an extent, but I think, you know, I'll admit it, we stay pretty focused on consoles.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I think sometimes, even the PC gamers, we neglect how huge the Sims franchise is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't the Sims, like, the best-selling PC game ever?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm pretty sure it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there's this huge culture around it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would have never guessed, however, that there was actually Ikea packs for Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I mean, the whole thing about The Sims is that, you know, especially through cheating, like me, you can have all kinds of neat stuff happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, for people...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, speaking of exchange, I don't think Sims 2 had this.
[SPEAKER_13]: This sounds more like what Spore had, where you can publish all your creations to the web, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You could do it with Sims 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had, you know, where you could post up your stuff, but you had to, of course, register your game, and really, they didn't have anything on there that you couldn't get anywhere else, you know, once the big mod forums came out, which, actually, I'll go ahead and plug my favorite right now, modthesims.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're probably the best one out there So overall with Sims 3, all you were hoping for and more?
[SPEAKER_05]: I really had very little in the way of expectation, so I like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not displeased with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that you can, if the floor or something is butt ugly, you can just change it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually go in, in any of the floors that you lay down, you can actually go back in and change the color of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: This little tool that I have here is a palette tool.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you can go in if it will let me and actually change the various colors in it by sliding the little slider and it'll change all the colors and then you can just copy that one and paste it all over the place.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've done a few custom floors myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Reading some chat comments.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chat.OrangeLawnRadio.com Decipher is in chat and wants to clarify Sims 2 had it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just wasn't as intuitive, I believe, talking about the whole web interface.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is actually super easy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, um... Oh, come on, you butthead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I talk to my games all the time, that's right.
[SPEAKER_05]: For example, I'm just going to show you with a piece of furniture.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say that I put this stupidly ugly bed...
[SPEAKER_05]: Right here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hate that this stupidly ugly bed is stupidly ugly.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I want to change it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I hit my little palette thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, it is an ugly bed.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I can go through and say, you know what, I really hate this rose pattern thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want this leaf pattern instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can pick the leaf pattern as soon as all this other crap loads.
[SPEAKER_05]: and my computer's a little taxed of course because I have everything running for the show but it will change the bedspread to
[SPEAKER_13]: It seems to me that you play Sims really for the design element.
[SPEAKER_13]: You really like to design the houses.
[SPEAKER_13]: You like to design the furniture and color every little piece.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there stuff there?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I suck at designing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there something in this game for me?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there actual game to play?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can just pick a house.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can download houses that other people have done.
[SPEAKER_14]: After you've murdered the family.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, you have empty lots and you can evict people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And right now it's still thinking about changing that bedspread to green.
[SPEAKER_05]: But what would happen is I would save it here and then I would pick share.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then when I go in, you have this other thing that's called the launcher.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is the first thing that loads up when you play the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Does that launch Sims?
[SPEAKER_14]: Out of a cannon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, it's modthesims.info by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: The site.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then you go into this and you can actually, those are screenshots up there, but you can select that one of the items that you've saved specifically for sharing and click upload.
[SPEAKER_05]: And almost instantly it's on the exchange for you and everybody else in the universe to see all the crap that you've managed to make.
[SPEAKER_13]: And again, kind of like Spores Creature Creator kind of reminds me of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, everything that you've picked for download.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this also works now for the content that's up on Mod the Sims right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that you just click on the little pack and it loads it into this and you can choose to install it in your game.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, maybe I'll have to check that out a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's worth it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's worthwhile.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, let's move on and talk about more gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: It changed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Finally, it changed to that green pattern.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's camo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, besides the stuff you played at E3, because we'll have plenty of time for that in a little bit, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_14]: I played Fuel, more Fuel at least.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Still driving around, trying to get more stuff unlocked.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really just trying to drive around and collect more Fuel containers to unlock more cars.
[SPEAKER_14]: Man, that game is big.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to spend one of these days actually just trying to drive across the whole map.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it probably will take a whole day.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because it's that big.
[SPEAKER_13]: It seems... I'm looking at some of the reviews for that game because I'm considering picking it up.
[SPEAKER_13]: It seems like it's getting very average reviews.
[SPEAKER_13]: People don't think, I guess, the implementation is good or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know what people's problems is with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's nothing really like it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And...
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, probably the next racing game similar to it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be Dirt 2 and that's not out until September.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, there's no real racing games I think coming out until September other than Fuel, which has already come out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anything else besides the E3 stuff?
[SPEAKER_13]: More Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_13]: My gaming week, obviously with E3 kind of being this week, there wasn't a whole lot I played outside of E3, but I will tell you, once I got home, one of the first things I wanted to do... Well, I did play a little bit of Final Fantasy XI, because I mentioned in a previous show I'd gone back to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't played a whole lot...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh crap!
[SPEAKER_13]: Final Fantasy 4 The After Years came out this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have got to go play that because Final Fantasy 4 is like my favorite Final Fantasy ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least the one I have the most nostalgia with.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because that was my first real in-depth Final Fantasy game that I just got totally immersed with.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean I remember playing the very first one on the NES when I was like 9 or 10 years old.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't even remember how old I was.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I remember playing that very first one on the NES and it was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: But um...
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't really get immersed until Final Fantasy 2 here in the US, which as we all know is really 4.
[SPEAKER_13]: So finally, I'm very excited to hear the sequel came out and it's on cell phones.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I checked out Final Fantasy 4 The After Years on the Wii and yeah, my nostalgia strings were successfully tugged.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was kind of surprised at how...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: But, of course, I had to remind myself, okay, Rob, you are playing a port of a cell phone game.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, I guess if I could compare it to anything, it would be very similar to playing, like, Final Fantasy IV on Game Boy Advance or WonderSwan Color.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you know, that kind of, like, slightly souped-up upgrade from the original Super Nintendo one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ghosts!
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to get the seven other episodes with the spinoff characters, they're like 300 Wii points each.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then the final chapter is supposed to be another 800 points.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I guess they're rolling this out slowly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like there's a side story on Rydia out now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't really played it yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I plan to, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then once you complete all these side stories, you can use the characters from the side stories in the closing chapter is what I hear is supposed to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It plays and feels like Final Fantasy IV on the Super Nintendo, not on the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: No voice acting, nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it plays and feels.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you want an old-school Super Nintendo RPG, if that's what you've been clamoring for, if that's what you miss, much like Mega Man 9 appealed to you because you missed the old-school NES Mega Man games, then you will like Final Fantasy IV The After Years.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a fairly well written story, at least what I've gotten into so far.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just playing it all over again is kind of making me giddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually kind of am having a lot of fun with it, and that's what really games are all about.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you want the nostalgia of Final Fantasy IV all over again, definitely go check this out.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you know what this made me think about as I was playing it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing, what really made me think about this was this whole story that we've been covering on the show the last couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know how Square shut down that Chrono Trigger fan project?
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember how somebody was making this Chrono Trigger ROM for the Super Nintendo that was like, it was like using the old Chrono Trigger data but it was like a new story and all this stuff, remember this?
[SPEAKER_13]: And Square sent them a cease and desist letter and we were like, you bastards, why did you shut down this project?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was just a fan thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I realized this week they shut it down because that's what they did with Final Fantasy IV The After Years.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a reskinned Final Fantasy IV with new dialogue, new stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: It didn't hit me until now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Square is doing... They're like, don't do it before us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're like, don't do it before us.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, in a way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, even though this game's already been out in Japan on cell phones for a while, I think that's why they shut the Chrono Trigger project down.
[SPEAKER_13]: If this Final Fantasy 4 thing is successful, I'll bet you they're going to do one for Chrono Trigger.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's probably cheap to do.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there's your answer, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's why it got shut down.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is cheap to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: All it is is programming scenarios and no real sprite creating since you're using the same sprites.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just creating a few world maps with already sprites.
[SPEAKER_13]: To be fair, and Henry,
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Like Devil's Road, which is the road that connects Mysidia and Baron.
[SPEAKER_13]: You used to just go in there and it would be and you'd appear in Baron.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well now they've actually made, I don't think this is very spoilery and I apologize if you feel it is, but they've made a little dungeon to go with the connection now that you have to work your way through.
[SPEAKER_13]: To say they have just only re-skinned it, that wouldn't be a fair thing to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have done minor tweaks.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm telling you, you're going to play this game and you're going to be like, I feel like I'm playing Final Fantasy 4+.
[SPEAKER_13]: I feel like I've popped in my Final Fantasy 2 cartridge from the Super Nintendo and unlocked a whole secret level that wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what it feels like.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's why this Chrono Trigger fan project got shut down because maybe this is the direction Square is heading in.
[SPEAKER_13]: um let's see uh the Rob D in chat says the translator for Final Fantasy 6 apparently wasn't a Star Wars fan well all the Super Nintendo Final Fantasies yeah I remember it was it was something to do with Star Wars it was always Biggs and Wedge that's right okay so thank you Rob D that's right VIX was a mistranslation in the American Final Fantasy 2 and 3 they did VIX instead of Wedge but but or instead of Biggs so it makes sense I figured it was something like that as well but not in 7 mm-hmm remember
[SPEAKER_04]: BlackWolf, our good buddy who celebrated his 200th episode right before we went live tonight, says in chat, It's really not.
[SPEAKER_13]: 300 points for a couple hours worth of gameplay I think is worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, I just understand.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're going to be spending your money on something old school.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you're spoiled by all these newfangled 3D graphics and things, I don't know if there's a lot here for you.
[SPEAKER_13]: But if you love Final Fantasy 4 as much as I do, you're going to love this, I think.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's definitely worth the price.
[SPEAKER_13]: And quite honestly, I think all the add-ons will probably be worth it too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hell, I saw a great argument the other day on a forum or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: Final Fantasy 2 as a cartridge when it came out was like $70.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: And HendersonManInChat apparently is a fan of the game and says, and that's what I wanted from the after years.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, Rydia's story is $3 for about 4 hours.
[SPEAKER_13]: So yeah, I mean, don't get me wrong, I'm not slamming the game for what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just, you know, know what you're getting into.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was caught a little off guard.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was expecting it to be kind of like newer and fancier, but now that I'm kind of playing it, I'm like, you know, there's a part of me that's kind of glad it's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is kind of neat to revisit that game I loved.
[SPEAKER_13]: Literally loved.
[SPEAKER_13]: 15 years ago, 18 years ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do endorse Final Fantasy IV The After Years if you are a fan of Final Fantasy IV at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rob D in chat says, yes, but times are different now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why should we judge it by antiquated pricing?
[SPEAKER_13]: Not to say it's not worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just don't think that's a good argument.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see your point.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, there's a lot of crap out there.
[SPEAKER_13]: They are trying to charge this $5 and $10 and do some of this episodic money for.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think, you know, again, if you know what you're getting into, if you want that Final Fantasy IV old school nostalgia, you know, not a lot of people complain about Mega Man 9.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's going to be worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did import the Sailor Moon Super S fighting game for $110.
[SPEAKER_05]: My early days of importing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, import game is a whole other story.
[SPEAKER_13]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: So Henderson Mann kind of concludes, this is the last thing I want to say on the Final Fantasy IV After Years.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, think of it like this.
[SPEAKER_13]: The total price for Final Fantasy IV The After Years is $37 for the full game, about the same price as a DS game remake.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: And in the end, when you add up all these hours, it would be what, like 21?
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably about 30 hours of gameplay, which is about what you get out of a DS cartridge anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know,
[SPEAKER_13]: But just again, not going to be your cutting edge graphics.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think Mega Man 9, but Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd pay for it, seriously.
[SPEAKER_13]: My nostalgia strings are extremely tickled by this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Extremely.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I hear the story gets really good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm really avoiding spoilers.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm probably only about an hour and a half, two hours into the main episode.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know I have plenty more to go.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'm squeeing so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you squeeing in a girly manner?
[SPEAKER_13]: A little bit of both.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, let's move on and get into some housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are slowly getting the podcast caught up after our storage drive corruption.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're almost caught up now.
[SPEAKER_13]: We just need last week and this week, and this should all be caught up by the time the next show airs.
[SPEAKER_13]: So sorry again to our faithful who listen to us on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry we have not been more reliable recently.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope you will still stick with us and continue to tell friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is never our intent to make you feel abandoned.
[SPEAKER_13]: So sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, I don't really have a whole lot else, so follow us on Twitter at twitter.com slash OLR or our Facebook is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm pretty much going to stop plugging MySpace because I'm pretty much over MySpace.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does anyone use MySpace anymore?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did last night.
[SPEAKER_13]: To what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Clear out spam?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, to look up a band called Stovacore, which is a band that's all heavy metal that dresses up like Klingons and singing Klingon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, alright, we're on MySpace, and if you want to add us there, you can, but I'm going to be honest, we haven't been doing a whole lot with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But to be honest, we haven't done a lot with Facebook either.
[SPEAKER_13]: We need to tape, like, special shows and things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will say this, though, our YouTube channel, after, like, two or three years, will finally get some new content.
[SPEAKER_13]: We did take video on the E3 show floor.
[SPEAKER_13]: We got me singing Karaoke Revolution, the new DDR games, Split Second, so there will be some stuff going to the Orange Archery.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have me looking incredibly bored playing the new DDR game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it's incredibly boring
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about music games, because there's been some very good music games at E3, some very bad music games at E3, and some very non-existent music games at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's where I want to start.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where the hell was DJ Hero?
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't this game supposed to be out in a couple months?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was shown behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, how nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did they let people play it?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, they had it demoed on a live stage.
[SPEAKER_14]: They had it demoed in front of a crowd, and that was pretty cool, but they didn't let people play it.
[SPEAKER_13]: and I'm very disappointed.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Hero 5, Guitar Hero Van Halen
[SPEAKER_13]: Guitar Hero Van Halen was at Sony's booth
[SPEAKER_14]: But they had it on stage.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were demoing it on stage.
[SPEAKER_14]: And DJ Hero looks sweet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I mean, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Hero looks great.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it looks fun to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to play it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to get my hands on it and see for myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe that's what they're trying to do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe that's what they're trying to do, is leave it a mystery for all of us.
[SPEAKER_13]: I still get frustrated at E3 when I see these millions of dollars spent to do this big DJ hero show.
[SPEAKER_13]: For what?
[SPEAKER_13]: For something behind closed doors for special people.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think people are quite 100% behind it yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Before, they were only showing half the controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_14]: Before, they were probably expecting people to go, Oh my goodness, what is this?
[SPEAKER_14]: This looks so cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to learn more about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But people were just kind of going...
[SPEAKER_14]: How the hell are you going to play this?
[SPEAKER_14]: This looks dumb.
[SPEAKER_14]: What are they doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: And then they finally, just during E3, they finally released the rest of the pictures of what the actual controller was.
[SPEAKER_14]: Besides the fact that it was in Game Informer, but actually having it free to look at outside of Game Informer, they just put out the stuff for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, I mean, it looks cool, and I like watching it being performed, and they did both just, you know, an actual song, and then they did the one that they had the Beastie Boys mashup thing where the guy was playing the guitar.
[SPEAKER_14]: Both of them look pretty cool, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, besides, you know, being able to play it, I mean, it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you hear what they're doing with DDR?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, you're going to love this.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're going to love this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I mini rant?
[SPEAKER_13]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't I do my mini rant, and then you can piss me off even more with what you're about to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Keep in mind, folks, this show would not exist if it weren't for DDR.
[SPEAKER_13]: I love what DDR has done for my life and the people it's introduced me to and all of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: That being said... Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: People were kind of heckling and saying, this is just going to turn into a sports game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the roster update 2009.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just new songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I apologize.
[SPEAKER_13]: You were right.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what the franchise has turned into.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's roster update 2009 with new songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see nothing here to report on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rihanna's in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whoopee!
[SPEAKER_13]: On the Wii One, you can now play on the balance board and shake your hips.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: That is new.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is something legitimately new.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is new and it is stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I agree with the stupid part, but hey, it is new.
[SPEAKER_14]: Then, not only that, not, okay, so, it would piss off fans enough that they didn't really do anything with the song list, that the song list sucks, and that, you know, the songs that they've just brought back a bunch of older songs and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be fine as it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, but they didn't leave it there.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, let's piss people off by taking Dynamite Rave and changing the lyrics to it, making it even worse.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate to tell you, they already did that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Download the DDR for the iPhone, you can download Brilliant to you with lyrics, and it'll make your inner Bomani fanboy cry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it's still sad.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just, I'm just, I've done.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's how long it's been since I pleaded.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've given up on Konami.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've given up on these games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I officially give up.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Rob, how can they possibly innovate this game?
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I, can I read, can I read this comment from chat real fast?
[SPEAKER_13]: Comment from chat, Actdeft, 8 arrows for the 360 and PS3, Alpha Cananogram, did you try PS3 360 version with 8 arrow pad?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it was not on the floor.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they did have that, and Technomotion did it first.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_13]: Technomotion was shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you ever actually played Technomotion, it was fucking garbage, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the one game everybody talked about back in the day, like, hey, I played Technomotion, because nobody had it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because it was fucking garbage.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, okay, fine, if this is how DDR is going to innovate with the 8-arrow pad, whatever, let's see the goods.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe I'll change my mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not convinced adding four more arrows is going to make it any more fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not going to make it any more fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, is that what you were going to tell me?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to piss me off even more?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it's not going to make it more fun because they don't understand.
[SPEAKER_14]: They don't understand what...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: But people aren't doing that anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: And so now you're going after these new people instead of trying to recapture fans.
[SPEAKER_14]: You already had your base right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you kept them happy, you would be selling enough each year.
[SPEAKER_13]: Newsflash.
[SPEAKER_13]: Konami does not care about the DDR fan base because we all got old.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's been 10 years and we're all too old to dance now.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they are going after children.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hate to break it to you folks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Konami does not care.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're all 30 now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Konami does not care about you anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: you're all gonna have kids and they want your kids playing DDR that's that's where it's at they need to remember is that we for all of us who grew up gamers we're not gonna buy shit for our kids we're not gonna buy them crappy games we're gonna buy them stuff that we'll want to play too but the thing I mean I was even thinking about this on the ride over here today like
[SPEAKER_14]: The problem with Konami is they don't get what makes their games sell.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's basically, you know, with DDR, it was all about the music and kind of the surprises.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like with each different mix, they were adding something that was kind of new that was surprising.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like the freeze arrows and stuff, that was kind of surprising for us.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was a new element in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: They don't really want to do any of that, so what they're going to do is... I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't even know what the hell they're calling this game, because it just said Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I don't care either, but... I don't want to tell you what it's called.
[SPEAKER_13]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_13]: As a journalist, or whatever... Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: As a blogger, pod... Whatever the fuck I am.
[SPEAKER_13]: As me, I don't want to tell you what it's called, because I don't care.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the point I've gotten to with these games.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know people work very hard on them.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, they don't work very hard on them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think this chatter is absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sephiroth1215 says, no, they don't care anymore because Jason Enos is gone.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's when DDR went downhill.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is exactly it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I ran into him a few months ago, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: He works at EA now.
[SPEAKER_13]: He doesn't work at EA anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: He also saw the games live.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if I can say what game he's been working on, but it's more casual games, I guess, is what he's doing now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe we'll get him on the show at some point.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll shoot an email or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, yeah, you know, obviously that was huge.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, not just that, but the whole San Francisco office shut down, and that's where a lot of the fans were working during the steps.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, that was huge.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't buy that, oh, well, you know, there's people working hard in this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, that's pretty sad then if this is the best you can do.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, because really, all they did was just recycle the whole engine again, maybe change some assets to it, and just said, okay, what songs are we going to throw in there now?
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here's the licensed songs we want.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, let's see what else we can fill up the song list with.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so, look, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's our game to advertise their music?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dance Dance Revolution, awesome if you're seven.
[SPEAKER_13]: By the way, if you need further proof that Konami does not care about the fans from ten years ago, look at what they did to poppin' music on the Wii, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: They're relaunching poppin' music with this whole new control scheme and I guess song lists and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: They say 150 classic tracks will be downloadable.
[SPEAKER_14]: at launch.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is this the new PS3 one?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: To be fair, I might check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: The nostalgia fanboy in me kind of is curious but it's a thin line with me right now that they're walking.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thin line.
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to see the nature of the train wreck?
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_13]: because I love DDR at its core.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's why I get so impassioned about looking at where it's at now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's really frustrating when it really isn't that hard to turn this thing around, but they just don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, Karaoke Revolution was also at Konami's booth.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was surprised at how current the song list was, because they had, like, My Life Will Suck Without You, Just Dance by Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_13]: They did have some current tracks, but honestly, to me, it felt like the same game we had on the PlayStation 2 without the American Idol stuff now, just with, you know, 720p, slightly souped-up engine.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't see a lot of new stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I imagine they're going to have the download store like every other music game now, but
[SPEAKER_13]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: but I have a feeling Karaoke Revolution is going to be more of a robust jukebox by the time it's done which is kind of sad because Sony owns their own record label but when you look at what's available on SingStar it's very narrow especially when you consider that most of it is UK based music which isn't a bad thing they have some great music over there but not a lot of tunes that are going to be a big hit at parties here in the US because nobody's going to know them so that is a fair point
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, I think that's where Karaoke Revolution may win some people over because I think there's a lot of people who haven't taken the plunge into SingStar or Lips that might still be able to get brought on board with Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do have nice things to say about Konami.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of my favorite games of the show was at their booth.
[SPEAKER_13]: But before we get to that, I want to talk about one of my favorite games of the show, period, which was a music game, Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the trailer for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everybody's talking about that introduction and how amazing it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: And let me tell you, the game itself looks just awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, I don't know, you want to talk about our experience at Beatles Rock Band?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I mean, the thing everybody's harping on, harmonics and both Activision and that kind of stuff, and EA, is that they're taking these...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: But with Beatles Rock Band, they've redone the whole style of the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's kind of this very stylized version of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like the new things that they're doing now with the dreamscapes, which they kind of touched on a little bit in the trailers and the intro where you see some really trippy stuff that goes along with the songs.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's really cool and different.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the three-point harmonies are pretty cool in there and how you don't really have to...
[SPEAKER_13]: Those stages for Here Comes the Sun and Octopus Gardens, those dream skates, that was amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: The three-part harmonies are pretty cool, how you can pick which one you want to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just like the little stuff that they've added, little tweaks to make the game flow better and play better and is more fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: That kind of stuff, focusing on the gameplay was really cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're even going to support it with download content.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously,
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, Luke, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: But they are working on different things Thank you Harmonix though for not putting out a Rock Band 3 this year Can I just say that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for not showing Rock Band 3 However, at the same time you did show Rock Band Lego thing Which is kind of, I guess in a way that's cheating It's more for the pop stuff Like for the family type songs More pop kind of stuff And that was kind of neat looking But they are doing the same thing on the Activision side with Band Hero They just didn't really show much of it
[SPEAKER_13]: Sephiroth 1215 says, Okay, so I say the Beatles can suck it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why should I buy this game?
[SPEAKER_13]: Which is fair.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not everybody respects the classic music stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Music might not be for everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I'll tell you what.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if I overheard this at the booth or somebody told me this.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I apologize if it was you and I'm not giving you credit.
[SPEAKER_13]: But somebody said, You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: No matter...
[SPEAKER_13]: No matter what kind of music you listen to, you hear these songs in the Beatles games.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can't help but hum along or recognize these songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: How often do you play Rock Band or Rock Band 2 and you're like, I've never heard that song before.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't do that song.
[SPEAKER_13]: But with the Beatles songs, there's an awful lot of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: You just know because they are so embedded in our culture.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know a lot of these songs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that's a big part of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plus, for me...
[SPEAKER_13]: The Rock Band Beatles, that's the way to do an artist's game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It makes the Guitar Hero, Aerosmith games, and Van Halen games, and Metallica games look like cheap reskins.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can you imagine if they did a Pink Floyd or something really trippy and stuff with a Rock Band type thing?
[SPEAKER_14]: The same different stylized stuff, or like a Gorillaz game or something like that, same stylized...
[SPEAKER_14]: They should change it up with each artist that they do it and then it would be really cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just think this is the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And by the way, if you don't understand what I meant earlier about how DDR needs to innovate itself and change, this is a perfect example.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_13]: My expectations going into this because of all the other music games I've seen lately were very low going in to look at the Beatles rock band and just kind of seeing that they've really made it like a Beatles experience.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, wow, they know how to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And honestly, I think other companies could be really learning a lot from this, and hopefully they are.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I just, you know, it just, it felt, it's so hard for me to put into words.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's something you have to see for yourself, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it feels, it doesn't feel like a cheap reskinning or a cash-in type game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It feels like a Beatles tribute.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, so we watched some people play that, and it was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Lego Rock Band, since that got brought up a minute ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not as excited about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, that does look like a cheap reskinning of an old game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I gotta be honest.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's gonna have the pop songs and all that stuff, which I suppose is gonna make or break the deal, and it's for the kids or what have you, but I literally was looking at Lego Rock Band going, this just looks like Rock Band 2 with Lego people.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really show off a lot of stuff that they were talking about though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember with Lego Rock Band they said they were going to have kind of an adventure mode type stuff where you battle monsters and whatnot while playing music, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that might be something kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And the soundtrack really kind of...
[SPEAKER_14]: would make or break this game, I think.
[SPEAKER_14]: But right now, it's hard to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: It just looks neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you can rock out into a Lego pirate ship and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's just kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd do that anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the end, really, you don't have to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, it's just optional.
[SPEAKER_14]: If it's something that you think would be cool, cool, pick it up.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't think it's being sold in the bundles, so...
[SPEAKER_13]: BlackWolf
[SPEAKER_13]: in chat also kind of sent me this.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's kind of like a food for thought, and I actually think it's a really interesting theory.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to read this.
[SPEAKER_13]: The conspiracy behind Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_13]: Think about which music company's CEO felt that they aren't getting enough money from licensing for music games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now think about which company is publishing Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now realize that download content for Lego Rock Band is not compatible with Rock Band 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: Connect the dots.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's an amazing thought, actually, and something I think a lot of people are overlooking.
[SPEAKER_13]: It probably has a lot to do with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't Warner putting out this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which record label was having a big stink?
[SPEAKER_13]: Warner.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you've stumbled onto something, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_13]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gold star.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get a Scooby snack.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: We share the radio night with you here on All Games for a reason, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: and those folks that were thinking that, oh, Kensha Hall is lost and gone and what have you, you could still feel their presence there a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: In the space that would have been taken up by Blizzard and some of these other companies that didn't come to E3 this year, they did have some of the old Kensha Hall, like DDR Game, you know, going back to the, you know, they're always there at E3 showing off their hard pads and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were there doing their thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, they still have some of the old Kensha Hall companies are making a showing and the Indiecade, which was, you know, kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, what do we want to do?
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about...
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about some of the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: I know you guys probably have heard all that you wanted to hear on the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just want to recap, give you guys a chance to give your input on the press conferences, what you thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was following Twitter during a lot of this, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Were you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I was at work, and of course I can't get on to watch any of the stuff, but I was getting feedback through Twitter, and there's some very interesting things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I stayed home.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what pissed me off on the Twitter thing?
[SPEAKER_13]: People that declared Microsoft won before Sony was done.
[SPEAKER_13]: Shut up!
[SPEAKER_13]: You know that all the good stuff- I mean, fanboy!
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, fanboy!
[SPEAKER_13]: Sony was not even done yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course they left their feathers in the cap until the end.
[SPEAKER_13]: Call me a Sony fanboy if you want, but go back to the archives of this show.
[SPEAKER_13]: We've been highly critical of it in the past.
[SPEAKER_14]: I left it open-ended.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, you know, Microsoft has won this unless Sony really brings something to the table that's, you know, outstanding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because if they brought what they brought last year-
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: or everybody was a winner it really depended on what you were looking for this year in the games and honestly I think Microsoft had a lot of great ideas I think Sony had a lot of great implementations and I think Nintendo well they'll always have soccer moms Nintendo had a lot of last year oh and then this that's pretty much what we had from Nintendo
[SPEAKER_13]: The chat room is speaking up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bobby, Actdeft, and some other folks saying the winners are gamers.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I was commenting to Loki this as I was walking around the show floor.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't really played a shitty game yet this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: Usually at E3, there's a real stinker of a game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm kind of like, oh, I don't know about this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I take that back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tara said the Beatles won.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, reuniting who Microsoft did on stage, that was an impressive feat for their press conference, so I do give Microsoft props for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you did find a shitty game?
[SPEAKER_14]: I did find a shitty game, and I can't remember what, it's like, it's a Konami game, surprise, but it was actually, it was like Zephyr the Elemental or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was supposed to be, it was the one that they had, it was like Tornado something or other was the working title for it, and it's supposed to be like Katamari where you're this, you know, tornado, and you
[SPEAKER_14]: Knock over things and you get bigger as you collect more things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't this game already on Xbox Live Marketplace?
[SPEAKER_05]: It should be a Vornado game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, basically, and it sucked.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was boring.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, no, I don't like that game.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is my stinker game of V3.
[SPEAKER_13]: I feel the need to say something nice about Konami because we've been giving them a hard time.
[SPEAKER_13]: And to be fair, Konami did show a couple of great things at the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: So before we get into the press conferences, to be fair, I want to say this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, you know, seeing that scene where the guy reaches in the toilet and pulls his hand up and he's got all the needles in it, that's just nasty, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: But there's people out there for the that's just nasty, and I gotta say, if you're a Fangoria-type person, Saw is probably going to appeal to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not terrible.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still would never put any money into it, even if it was the best game on the planet, just so I don't support the franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously, that's how I feel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I'm trying to put the personal thoughts on that aside and just evaluate the game itself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Considering it's a movie tie-in game, it looks like it's raising the bar on those a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just don't think I can in good conscience say anything positive about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well, I do want to say though, a game that was incredible at Konami's booth that I played, and not quite my favorite game of the show, but just about my favorite game of the show was Silent Hill Shattered Memories on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my gosh, this game was great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially, and I hate to say this, but for a Wii game, like it's, it was really, I love the concept.
[SPEAKER_00]: It runs really smooth.
[SPEAKER_13]: It runs smooth, it looks nice, you know, it doesn't look
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: I love the way it controlled.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was definitely kind of scary in parts, like when the things would jump out of the darkness on you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think the game is going to piss off hardcore fans of the Silent Hill because it looks like they've really changed up this first game.
[SPEAKER_13]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: As someone who is casually a Silent Hill fan, I think it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like some of the changes they've made.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's engrossing.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's scary.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to be a lot of fun, and it's a good non-party Wii game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hooray!
[SPEAKER_05]: This is what I have to say for people who fuss just because of changes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Without change, we'd have stagnation, and with stagnation, we'd have death.
[SPEAKER_05]: So if you want the franchise to die, then don't look forward to any changes in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't be...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: She was kind of a hoe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly, whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: The game was fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: The changes are being made based on how you answer some of this personality stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it kind of changes it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's almost like how different things manifest based on the characters' intentions and desires and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's some pretty personal stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember Silent Hill 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: The little girl never saw any of the...
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you ever roleplayed during sex?
[SPEAKER_13]: And all these very personal questions.
[SPEAKER_13]: And of course, as I was taking it, I was trying to make myself sound like the most messed up person on the planet.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't really see what impact that's going to have on the game, but it looked interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: So...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Unfolded Raptor talking about the Saw game.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is one where you have to close stalled doors and read the backwards number in the bloodstained mirror in the room and put in the combination for the lock in order to get to the next room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, that puzzle was in the demo and it was an interesting puzzle.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was kind of a neat little gameplay mechanic.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: GS68 says, well, they didn't show gore, I think he meant to say, but they showed 3D stuff and some disgusting shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's why I don't think in the end I could actually play the Saw game.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, you know, the parts I saw where people weren't losing looked just fine, but I don't think I'd be able to play the game myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Isn't that weird, to kind of say that about a video game?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: It might be nice for those of you that are into that kind of thing, but not me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever sinks your battleship.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, GS68 wasn't talking about the Saw game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh god, he was talking about Faname 2009 Hentai Room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was looking up the notes there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure the Saw game has some pretty disgusting shit in it too.
[SPEAKER_13]: In fact, I know it does.
[SPEAKER_13]: I did see some disgusting shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Real quick, before we go on to the conferences, I was going to mention some of the other announcements from Konami real quick.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, some stuff that actually didn't make the keynotes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kojima Productions announced Metal Gear Solid or Metal Gear Arcade.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they also, you may remember there was that Castlevania type game that they were previewing that wasn't really Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it ended up being Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it's actually being done by Kojima, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Patrick Stewart is a voice in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That makes it infinitely cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, so that was definitely a big yay from Konami.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do you wonder if he's going to be Dracula?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you imagine Patrick Stewart as Dracula?
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope this is a game that's showing up on the floor next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because he can do the scary voice.
[SPEAKER_14]: Patrick Warburton as one of the Belmonts.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope we don't get the die monster.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then of course, to kind of go back to music games, also Konami announced that they are bringing over that poppin' music for Wii with no controller.
[SPEAKER_13]: Once again, really not... Meaning it's not poppin' music like you folks that have been following Konami for 10 years will think it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: So don't... You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: Do yourself a favor, hardcore Bomani fans.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't think of this game as poppin' music because you are just going to be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_13]: And don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it's not fair to say that until I've actually had my hands on it playing it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm not going to say that, but I'm going to say don't think of it as poppy music because you're only going to set yourself up for disappointment.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: But Lorde's a shadow looker.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a Castlevania game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, so let's talk about press conferences here.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're an hour into the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: We haven't even touched on a single press conference yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: So let's talk about the big press conferences so far.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where do we want to start?
[SPEAKER_13]: How about Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess we were ragging on Nintendo a little bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll start with them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay, I like ragging on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the things that they mentioned.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, not all the news was bad out of Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, certainly Metroid Other M. How about this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Team Ninja teams up with Nintendo to put out the next Metroid game.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Team Ninja's lacking.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only good announcement out of
[SPEAKER_14]: Out of their press conference.
[SPEAKER_14]: And seriously, if they hadn't announced this, I would have had no hope for them.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, this was definitely the thing to cater to the hardcore gamers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, it's a good example of how to revitalize your franchise.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have someone else do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But we don't have Itagaki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Samus will have boob mechanics
[SPEAKER_13]: Prime was alright, but yeah, I was missing my 2D Metroid and this is going to give it to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Prime did not do it for me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just couldn't get in the Prime and corruptions, you know, it looked kind of dumb.
[SPEAKER_14]: But this looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: This looks like something I could actually play and would want to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know why it's stupid?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's because it's just porting basically the game from the DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yeah, I know it's a new game and stuff, but really, unless you're really into party games and really into playing this with four people at once, which, that's fine, because the Wii is for a lot of people that want to do party games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I just couldn't see myself breaking this out at a party and playing this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'd be like the regular new Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played through it myself.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: This game, if I play through it myself, I'm not going to really get anything out of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I played this on the show floor, like I said.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it was fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Playing with four people, it was a lot of fun and very competitive.
[SPEAKER_13]: But don't be mistaken, folks.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is another party game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: In Mario's clothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: And don't call this New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: because you just ported this shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not new.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's ported.
[SPEAKER_14]: Slightly recycled.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's not really the focus.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's very nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing that I didn't really get.
[SPEAKER_13]: To be fair, that wasn't really the focus of the demo they were showing or not really the focus of the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: My opinion of what she said was that's not really the focus of the game because if there was a single player mode, they would have shown it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's not what they were showing.
[SPEAKER_13]: They were showing this four player party thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: And strangely enough, it's not online.
[SPEAKER_13]: They had the perfect opportunity to have a fun little online game and it's not online.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love it because, as Bobby was saying in his show, because the processing power of the Wii can't handle online with this type of game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It can't handle online with this type of game.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't Brawl do that?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell was this one they just had on the GameCube?
[SPEAKER_13]: Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brawl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wii, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was online.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was laggy sometimes, so they did it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did this other game have much more than that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: Brawl, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: They can't handle online?
[SPEAKER_14]: Then you need better programmers!
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, but it's a 2D game, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a 2D game with very low polys, and you can't handle four people online?
[SPEAKER_14]: Mario Kart can handle four people online, and that's way more complex than this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why can't you handle four people online?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I know why, because you don't want to embrace online.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's really the reason behind it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not because it's a technical limitation, because if it was a technical limitation, I'm sure you'd find a way around it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's a personal limitation.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's because the person that's going to buy this game isn't probably really into online.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're probably into soccer.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they probably are a mom.
[SPEAKER_13]: AlphaKananaGram in chat says, Rob, they said that is the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: With extra players joining in and leaving at any time.
[SPEAKER_13]: So yeah, that is the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's exactly what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't be fooled.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is a party game.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brawl had a single player mode that was pretty extensive and fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: All I'm saying is that if there is, you know, to be fair to Nintendo, if there is a single player fun bonanza in here, I just have yet to see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you are thinking you're excited about this game, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope you have friends to play it with regularly.
[SPEAKER_14]: When I saw this one, they were like, oh, we have new Super Mario Brothers now on the Wii coming this holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was like, whoop-dee-shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also people, though, that I just hope you have friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, you know, oh, we've been waiting for another Mario Brothers game on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_14]: New Super Mario Brothers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I'm sorry, that wasn't awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: TigerClaw in chat says, yeah, Nintendo's forgetting that there are many of us who don't know people in the neighborhood that own the same system.
[SPEAKER_13]: So yeah, you're pretty much all alone.
[SPEAKER_14]: Super Mario Galaxy 2
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Yoshi's in it now!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, my mistake!
[SPEAKER_14]: Yoshi's in this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, obviously it's a sequel now.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, I mean, really, they didn't do that much to it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, whereas, you know, like Super Mario World, you know, Super Mario World 1 and 2, I mean, those were very different games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, they were really different games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, granted, World 2 was kind of annoying, but, um...
[SPEAKER_13]: Really with the crying baby?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, just mute the damn TV if it gets to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or don't suck so much and keep losing the baby.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then you won't hear it cry.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what Mario Galaxy 2 needs, a crying baby on the back of Yoshi.
[SPEAKER_13]: Touch Fuzzy, Get Dizzy
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interlogic in chat says, okay, there's a lot of yelling going on.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about switching to a subject that can let everyone relax?
[SPEAKER_04]: How about we use our inside voices?
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe 3DO talk.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, just for you, Interlogic, let me ask Loki about this little gem here.
[SPEAKER_13]: One big thing that Nintendo had to unveil at their press conference, the Wii Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_13]: I...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Nintendo, for giving us shit we don't need.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, they're all... It's going to take the gaming to the next level.
[SPEAKER_14]: For geriatrics, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a heart monitor for Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dude, I can give myself an electrocardiogram on the Wii now.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're like, it's going to allow you...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, all they're going to do is come out with another game that's going to have some mini-games based on this accessory, and then that's it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Imagine the WarioWare with the Wii Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_12]: Some of the mini-games stop beating.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry, it's going to be dumb.
[SPEAKER_14]: And what also makes it dumb is they should have done this Bluetooth or something like that so that you can utilize it with...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: How long may I ask before we hear about an injury where someone has inserted their penis into the Wii Vitality Sensor?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I bet you anything someone will do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because if it's got some sort of way to attach to something, someone's going to try to stick their penis in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's immediately what I thought when I saw it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, how long is it going to take before someone sticks their penis in that?
[SPEAKER_14]: I know that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you just made Rob hurt.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hurt.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, Grandma made Jello tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: How long before someone puts their dick in it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mashed potatoes?
[SPEAKER_05]: See, now all we need is to talk about farting and we'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then I'd like to finish off the rest of their wonderful conference.
[SPEAKER_14]: They talked about Wii Sports Resort, and they talked about the new games they're in, which are fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: WeMotionPlus WeFitPlus
[SPEAKER_14]: and some online data sharing or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whoop-dee-doo!
[SPEAKER_14]: But guess what?
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to have new bundles and people are going to be dumb and not realize that it's actually the same game they just bought and they're going to buy it all over again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Frisbee says, now that's what I call touch generation games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although, Rez with the Wii Vitality Sensor might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, other things at a Nintendo's press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wii Sports Resort.
[SPEAKER_13]: I actually played this game on the floor.
[SPEAKER_13]: I played the archery game, which was, you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: What can I say about Wii Sports?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's the type of thing that's fun at a party when I have friends over.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, let's play Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's have a little competition, you know, because we're at a party and drinking, so we can't go outside and play, so let's do some Wii Sports.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't think I would ever play this by myself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, hey, I'm bored.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to shoot archery.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you ever figure out?
[SPEAKER_14]: What exactly would MotionPlus does?
[SPEAKER_13]: It looks like it just allows motion detection in more places.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, to be honest, the archery thing did feel natural, and I think with the controller they have today, it would have been a little bit shaky.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because we remember way back, we did play archery in DECA Sports.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know if you remember that that much.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not really, but I seem to recall there was more, I don't know, it just seemed more precision.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's part of the give and take of E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, so I can't base my entire judgment of this game off of what I played.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, you know, again, I didn't see anything that made me go, oh, you know, I need this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Red Seal 2, though, looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: How so?
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really check that out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It ran really smooth, 60 frames per second.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Wii Motion Plus and sword tracking really worked.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it looked fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unlike Red Seal 1, which...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: More for people who don't already own it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't see myself... I mean, it really depends on the price point.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't see how much they were going to charge for this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't see myself paying a lot of money for it if it's not going to give me anything that special, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just more minigames.
[SPEAKER_05]: What if they make Wii LiPo?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd probably buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or Wii Gastric Bypass.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Depends how good that online functionality is.
[SPEAKER_13]: But based on what I saw, I don't really see anything that justifies $40.
[SPEAKER_13]: $20 maybe, but I highly doubt that's what they're charging for it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not going to be $20.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: What other kind of stuff was announced at Nintendo press conference?
[SPEAKER_13]: That's pretty much all that I have on my list.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other things announced that didn't quite make their press conference.
[SPEAKER_14]: New colors.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was about time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, Japan, during the summer, will be getting a black Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really know what they were.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, other announcements.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously, DSi was getting Facebook support as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to allow you to upload pictures you take with the DSi camera to Facebook.
[SPEAKER_13]: As if there wasn't enough crap on my feed.
[SPEAKER_13]: I hope I can block it.
[SPEAKER_14]: WarioWare DIY WarioWare
[SPEAKER_14]: They've also announced Flipnote Studios for DSi this summer, which is also the motion notepad that they have in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: And New Mario and Luigi RPG, well, was it March of the Minis again?
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to do another Mario vs. Donkey Kong game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that was going to be a DSi-only app or something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that was the one that came out.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's out tomorrow or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't they announce that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Something like that, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's out now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was a download game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't have a DSi.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I say this real quick?
[SPEAKER_13]: The chat room really wants us to mention Golden Sun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I saw a couple other people mentioning that before and SSJ100Mac kind of sums it up here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got excited for a split second when they said at their press conference, an old franchise that was once gone is coming back.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought maybe Mother 3 or Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_14]: I saw that too.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah, they're going to announce Mother 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, nope, they're not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, anything else you want to say about Nintendo's press conference?
[SPEAKER_14]: Um... It still sucked.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, theRobD wants to point out, I'm really excited, I loved Golden Sun, this is a good thing, a very good thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I mean, the Golden Sun games are fun, but you have to admit, there's some folks that are going to feel that huge sense of disappointment, like, oh my god, I've been waiting forever for Kid Icarus, here it is!
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, Golden Sun, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Classic Game of the Week Classic Game of the Week
[SPEAKER_13]: So DarkSakura, amongst all these newfangled games we're talking about, the three, what's an old classic that folks should be revisiting?
[SPEAKER_05]: I went for old and obscure.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually a game I've mentioned on the show before, which is to date one of my favorite shoot-em-up games.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's called Ginga Fukei Densetsu Sapphire, which is one of the last games that came out on the PC Engine, on the Duo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oops, I cut it off accidentally.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here we go again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's a little clip of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love the music in it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it is one of the arcade CD-ROM games that came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that means, of course, with my Turbo Duo, I can't play it, which I do own a copy of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's also one of the few games towards the end of the PC Engine's life that had an actual real 3D in it in the form of the bosses and some of the enemies in the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it actually came out recently on PSP as part of the Galaxy Fraulein Collection, which is actually something I plan on ordering very soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because, again, this is one of my favorite games.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if you want to find it on eBay, good luck.
[SPEAKER_05]: This game will actually end up costing more than Dracula X does.
[SPEAKER_05]: This one will go for easily 400 bucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway, it's basically just a standard, you know, shoot-em-up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can upgrade your weapons, and you have your little option things hanging out with you, and you just basically go through the game and shoot stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, I typed the name of the game in chat, but they would like to hear it pronounced once again, because it is not an easy name, because it is a Japanese game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's Ginga Fuke Densetsu Sapphire.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want a translation of the name, that is Galaxy Policewoman Legend Sapphire.
[SPEAKER_05]: It came out in 1995.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a Hudson Soft game.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of the... Oh god, I love Hudson.
[SPEAKER_05]: But also, one of the things about the game, and this is actually something that I've seen in several reviews, and I'm going to repeat this one from one little review, that says...
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, the game is more of overcoming the game's mechanics rather than mastering them.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, really, a lot of playing in the game is hit or miss, whether or not you make it through.
[SPEAKER_05]: If the game has it out for you, it's going to have it out for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where you have actual real 3D...
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, this boss looks like, imagine one of those giant chemistry molecules they have hanging in chemistry class.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, it's like one of those things, but it's actually like rotating around and spinning around.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, for, you know, a game from 95, that's a pretty cool depth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was, it really is, though, even though it's really a little bit on the hard side, your bosses are so easy in this one because they are so predictable in their patterns.
[SPEAKER_05]: And
[SPEAKER_05]: The whole part, though, is trying to get around how slow your ship really is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the ship, as you'll see, the ship does move really slowly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you have a relatively large hitbox.
[SPEAKER_05]: The area that will count as you being hit.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game really doesn't look easy.
[SPEAKER_13]: It does look very hard.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have you actually had a chance to play this, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, my friend, actually she lives in Japan right now, she has an original of this, which is how I got my copy of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: She, um, she's got a PC Engine Duo and arcade card, so we went over to her house and she said, okay, play this game, okay, play this game, okay, play this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Sapphire was just like, oh my god!
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like, this one and another shooter, Psychic Storm, were the ones that I played the most, but mostly because in Psychic Storm it sounds like they're saying I get pissed off instead of saying Psychic Storm.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's another game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, isn't that... Really, you should post the link to this in the chat room because it's something that you really have to see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a fantastic, fantastic shooter.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, I'm going to actually do an eBay search right now and see if I can find out how much it's going for.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, let me just go ahead and wrap this up and say there it is again, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, Jamie, you might have to correct me here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ginga, Foukei, Densetsu, Sapphire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: There it is, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are going to take a break and come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: When we come back from a quick break, we have not even touched on Sony's press conference and Microsoft's press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: And believe me, there's a lot to talk about there.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're also going to cover some other news.
[SPEAKER_13]: We still need to get the release dates, the FUs of the week, and the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we have a busy Part B still coming up.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to get to it all.
[SPEAKER_13]: And your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: My God, we're going to be here until 11 tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, we'll...
[SPEAKER_13]: we'll try and wrap it all up in just a little bit we're going to take a quick break to rest our voices and so forth we will be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_13]: And welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on our 326th episode for this June the 7th of 2009.
[SPEAKER_13]: As a reminder, we do tape live on Sunday nights over at allgames.com right after the Bobby Blackwolf show, which is about 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time, 9 o'clock Eastern Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_13]: Unless it's a special night, maybe Bobby will go a little longer.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll start more like 6.15 as tonight was because it was Bobby's 200th episode.
[SPEAKER_13]: Quite an accomplishment.
[SPEAKER_13]: So congratulations.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, anyhow, we're going to get back and do some E3 rundown.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, unscripted tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just kind of talking and playing around, talking about some of the various events that have happened at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I guess we're going to talk about Sony's press conference, if that's all right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Before we do that, I was going to mention a few more things about Nintendo stuff that I saw.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got to see Sin and Punishment 2, which looked awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't even know what that looked like.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: But they had some other stuff that they were announcing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fossil Fighters for the DS, which I actually know that's coming out in August.
[SPEAKER_14]: And a new Professor Layton game and Pokemon Mystery Dungeon Explorers of the Sky.
[SPEAKER_14]: All sorts of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that was kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then...
[SPEAKER_14]: I think... Oh yeah, Sin and Punishment 2 is supposed to be coming out quarter one of next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are we okay to move on to Sony now?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk Sony, because Sony definitely had a lot of big news out of their press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: And a very interesting story I have about Sony.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you missed day one of E3, which is when the Sony press conference was going on.
[SPEAKER_13]: From what I understand, day one of E3 was not originally supposed to start until noon, but it ended up starting at 10 a.m.,
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkDeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: And I wanted to check that out But obviously there's some big announcements at Sony What's also cool and a lot of people may not know because they were at Sony's press conference God of War 3 as you know was playable at the show floor in Sony's booth But during the press conference all the monitors were turned off So you actually couldn't play God of War 3 until the walkthrough was done But you knew it was going to be there because they had the God of War 3 sign up And they already had a line forming But just nobody could play it until the press conference was actually over
[SPEAKER_13]: But I did get to see some of Sony's press conference at the booth, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: And to see some of their big announcements.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course, God of War 3 being one of them.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not huge on the God of War series.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I certainly respect what it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just I don't have time to play everything as none of us do.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this is just one of the big series I haven't gotten around to.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, I don't know if you're big on these games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like them.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's nothing really innovative for God of War 3 other than, you know, obviously the nicer graphics now with the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it is a little bit more detailed in the gore.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, there is one point where they had slashed open, I believe, a minotaur and just like his organs were spilling out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you got to see those organs spill out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that was kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like organs.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you're a fan of God of War, you're going to love this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just the same type of gameplay that you can normally expect from them.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Which is kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: For now, they do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you know how usually they dub over the Japanese lips.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you remember when X-2 came out, they re-synced the animation to the voices, too?
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be nice if they did that for XIII, but I'm not counting on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they re-did a lot of the CG to match voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they completely re-did two whole scenes in that game for the American audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it makes sense they do something like that with XIII.
[SPEAKER_13]: So obviously this game's on its way out, and they did confirm this for a 2010 release, and it was nice to see some of it actually getting, you know, some more of it shown to get to know a little more of the story.
[SPEAKER_14]: They showed Odin, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, and some of the summons, which is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: But then a huge bombshell dropped right after that at the show, and what's interesting about it is that then he started talking about how Final Fantasy XIV was exclusive to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Before even showing the trailer, he talked about, I'm here to announce that Final Fantasy XIV is going to be exclusive on the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Final Fantasy XIV Online
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: but different.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, 1UP of all places actually had a pretty in-depth talk on Final Fantasy XIV and some of the things they've talked about, they have learned a lot of their lessons from the prior game.
[SPEAKER_13]: This game is going to be launched globally, Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to be on the PlayStation 3 and the PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's going to be on both.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're also talking about bringing it to the 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I suppose, but nothing's for sure yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll probably be playing it on the PC no matter what.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't imagine playing it on a console.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really wish they hadn't announced this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because you're just watching your life get sucked away, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I seriously wanted to cry standing in the booth watching that trailer.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it wasn't because of the trailer itself, but it's because I just saw the next few years of my life wilting away at this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because we all know that's what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: This will happen to me because I have something far better to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_13]: Star Trek Online
[SPEAKER_13]: So, it's like, it sounds like some of the biggest flaws of Final Fantasy XI have the potential of being addressed in this.
[SPEAKER_13]: This could be huge, but of course, I don't want to set the bar too high, or I might be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I'm... And of course, the chat room wants to know... Whoa.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe this is good music for that question.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Amazatsuma wants to know in chat, Sky, Final Fantasy XIV or Star Trek?
[SPEAKER_13]: What a tough question.
[SPEAKER_13]: and one is about swords and weapons.
[SPEAKER_13]: But they did have those ships that they were flying around and shooting each other and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So you're going to get sucked into this MMO, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't have time.
[SPEAKER_13]: The wife's not going to let you.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've got kids to raise now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_13]: You can get a sitter.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll let them play too.
[SPEAKER_13]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, why can't we have our cake and pie at the same time?
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Haven't you ever heard of getting ice cream and cake?
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, what'll probably end up happening is I don't know if I'll actually play this game because I'll probably just want time.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'll be a time factor.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I am very excited about this.
[SPEAKER_13]: And honestly, I would say that this right here was the biggest surprise of the show.
[SPEAKER_13]: No one saw this coming.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who could imagine that they would have Final Fantasy XIV coming out the same year as XIII, hypothetically?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think they're actually going to make it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bet you anything XIV gets pushed back to 2011.
[SPEAKER_13]: But just the fact that they kind of had the balls to do it, announce the next Final Fantasy game before one's even done, is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Other big things announced at Sony's press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about Mod Nation Racers?
[SPEAKER_13]: That was sweet looking.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was a neat looking game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, tell us a little bit about this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mod Nation Racers is going to be the next of that play, create, share type of game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically like LittleBigPlanet, but with a Mario Kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you've got these characters that you create that kind of look like those money characters...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: So people are going to be able to make their own levels.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously the Mario Kart rip-off levels are going to be in here as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: But basically create whatever they want as far as races have goes and then share it with their friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can't wait to see how levels get moderated in this game for being Mario Kart courses.
[SPEAKER_13]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Space, The Final Frontier,
[SPEAKER_13]: These are the Voyagers of the Starship OLR Prize.
[SPEAKER_13]: And D'Artesuya continues, It's ongoing mission to seek out new life and new civilizations and blow shit up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ranma finishes, To boldly go where no geek has gone before.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very nicely done.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the blow shit up part best.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uncharted 2 Among Thieves.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know there's a lot of folks very excited about this game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not one of them, but it looked neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sitting here and I'm holding in my hand a multiplayer beta code for Uncharted 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, you know, I don't really want to use it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think Loki wants to use it either.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura probably not going to really play it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm thinking we should give this Uncharted 2 Among Thieves code to a listener.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, here's the thing though, is that this listener has to be willing to write something for the website on this.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if we give away this beta code, we want them to write something for the website with their impressions.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's the deal.
[SPEAKER_13]: We give you the code, you give us an article.
[SPEAKER_13]: So how do we give it away?
[SPEAKER_13]: Do we give it away to live?
[SPEAKER_13]: We should let the podcasters have a chance at it too, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Or maybe open it up on Twitter or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it should be a match game prize.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe a match game prize later on?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I think some of you are a little bit more fair.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, a match game is only two people.
[SPEAKER_13]: So let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Send us an email.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I got it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Send us a tweet because you're restricted to 140 characters.
[SPEAKER_13]: Send us a tweet as to why you should get this code.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then we'll pick the ones we like and pick one at random.
[SPEAKER_13]: We don't want to pick our favorite because that's a little too objective.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll take all the ones we like and pull one out at random.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you send us a tweet about... It better be awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: and not direct message.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do not do a direct message.
[SPEAKER_13]: You got to do at OLR and then whatever the message is.
[SPEAKER_13]: So maybe by next show we'll figure out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that too late?
[SPEAKER_13]: Valid June 3rd through June 28th.
[SPEAKER_13]: We probably need to give this away sooner rather than later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: How about tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_05]: We post the reply on Twitter tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_13]: The podcast won't be up tomorrow but maybe I'll post something on the Twitter about the contest tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: By Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thursday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe let's say midweek, Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because Wednesday is when the show should go up.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we're going to say by Wednesday, if you send us a tweet about why you should get this Uncharted 2 beta code, we're going to take our favorites and randomly pick one and give it to you.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then you're going to write something for our website.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: A 140-character essay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So to our favorite tweet at why you should have the Uncharted 2 code.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we'll post a reminder on Twitter a little later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exciting.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Grand Turismo PSP
[SPEAKER_14]: for a PSP game it actually looked pretty good running at 60 frames per second looks very smooth about fucking time that it came out though seeing as it was supposed to be a launch title so they sure take their times on those Gran Turismo games Metal Gear Solid on the PSP as I predicted a game based off the Metal Gear Solid 3 universe there where you're playing as Big Boss what's kind of interesting though is they're going to have like
[SPEAKER_14]: Online co-op or like ad hoc co-op or something like that where you can actually play as each person is like a big boss character which kind of is funny look like clones.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about Assassin's Creed 2?
[SPEAKER_14]: You know it's a neat trailer but I just don't really care about that game unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played the first one didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of file it in the hole don't have time to play everything?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah it's sort of yeah it's a neat game they are doing a little bit more with it I think as far as
[SPEAKER_14]: The Depth of the Game, but, I mean, if you like the first one, you're obviously gonna like this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh, obviously we've been talking a lot about the PSP, but how can we not mention something about the PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_13]: $249 for the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are people gonna pay it, or did they shoot themselves in the foot?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a tough sell for a system that doesn't have a UMD drive on it, and I don't give a crap if it has 16 megs, or 16 gigabytes of storage.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what, I can buy a 16 gigabyte card for cheaper than the difference, so, um...
[SPEAKER_14]: and there's a lot of stuff that we don't know that's like kind of as far as specs goes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is the processor better?
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it the same?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, has it got more RAM in it?
[SPEAKER_14]: What exactly separates this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously now it can't really utilize some of the peripherals I think because of where they've placed different things on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a neat idea I guess but
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: They're not really doing anything with this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, here's what's interesting is that also one of the big things I said, am I going to be able to play my old UMDs on it?
[SPEAKER_13]: And the answer is possibly.
[SPEAKER_13]: We haven't heard the final answer yet, but apparently Sony isn't developing right now a Goodwill program is what they're calling it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And basically they're saying it might be similar to portable copy, which is how you transfer your Blu-ray movies from the PS3 down to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: Users would not be ripping their UMDs,
[SPEAKER_13]: But there'll be some type of digital distribution method on how it's done.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's going to be a code in a manual that you're going to basically be able to download it to your system or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_14]: So what's going to happen is someone's going to basically buy the game, dump the code in, return the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: The end.
[SPEAKER_14]: or you're going to have it where it's your well that might work for new games but what about the games that you have right now see that's the problem is how they're going to be able to do that and if it's a kiosk solution where you basically take it to a kiosk and it dumps it to your system that's a whole nother problem right there it just there's no real way I see this working you know other than you know having it be a code in the manual and even then
[SPEAKER_14]: Sony's Motion Controller
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Really, it is kind of that patent we saw earlier.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember how you talked about how there was this EyeToy patent and that it was going to be red dots and blue dots that the EyeToy could see that would differentiate it and we thought it was something that would go on the regular controller?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it's like this new little motion thing that has the things on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looked dumb.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I'm sorry, but the controller looks retarded.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, you know, the only cool thing that they did with it was the augment of reality stuff where, like, you see yourself and then when you're moving the thing around, it replaces it.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just, it... The thing I worry about with these motion controls is how well are they really going to work?
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, we kind of went through this with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: When the Wii was announced, I think a lot of us, our jaws hit the floor and so forth.
[SPEAKER_13]: And now when we kind of want, you know, sometimes it doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now they're telling us they've got to have Motion Plus because it doesn't work as well as they originally intended.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's what I want to, the main focus I would like to see with this is what are the limitations?
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: The PlayStation Eye Sensors
[SPEAKER_14]: And, you know, the camera's really kind of useless anyways right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I know because I own cameras for both, you know, the Vision camera and the PlayStation Eye and...
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, haven't used either one of them, really.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, other than trying out Totem Ball, which sucked.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, it's just they're kind of useless.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, I mean, Sony is doing a little bit more with the PlayStation Eye camera.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, they have the Eye Pet thing coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've got, you know, some cool implementations for, like, you know, photos and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: And a little Big Planet.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, then the normal face mapping stuff for, like, the EA Sports games and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, I just don't...
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to have to make this controller a lot better looking than it looks.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I know it's a prototype.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I want to read this comment from chat because here, Legend of Zaku in chat says, Jesus Christ, this goddamn prototype.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember that the PS3 controller is still in development, so everything you saw last week is a prototype tech demo, so the final versions will vary once it's released.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, yeah, but at the same time, this is...
[SPEAKER_13]: Sony is in front of the world showing it what is going to be playing in the next year.
[SPEAKER_13]: So while there might be slight variations, I mean, this is what they are planning right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: And unless something freaking major happens, this is going to be what it is next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, this to me looks almost like a copy of a Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_14]: Basically, it's kind of what... They're all, how can we mimic what the Wii Remote does...
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you know, make it a little bit better and, you know, not use the same technology so we don't get sued.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what this seems like, whereas the Microsoft one was like, how can we do something that's motion control, but different and better?
[SPEAKER_13]: And some folks in chat are invoking the PlayStation 3 boomerang, like GSX-H has changed his nickname.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, remember when the PlayStation 3 controller was supposed to look like that boomerang?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, and thank God they didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because of all the negative reaction, they didn't end up doing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, you know, Sony has been known to go back to the drawing board when they get negative reception.
[SPEAKER_13]: So could something like that happen here?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, and I just, I think the whole setup is going to be really, it's going to suck because, you know, once again, going back to the Microsoft one, you're not trying to sound like a fanboy here, but all you need is a camera.
[SPEAKER_14]: Done.
[SPEAKER_14]: You got the camera, you can play four players, 16 players, whatever the game's going to support.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you are the controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: White Knight Chronicles White Knight Chronicles
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a very pretty looking game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had it described as Final Fantasy XII meets Xenogears.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a very pretty looking game.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm definitely interested in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you actually played it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had to watch you play that one.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you think of White Knight Chronicles?
[SPEAKER_14]: How did it control?
[SPEAKER_14]: It controlled fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was just basically target something and then you had macros and pick which macro you want to, you know, which attack you want to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then you can also set up a macro for a combo of attacks and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It seemed easy, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: It was neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: SSJ100Matt, going back to the motion control in chat room, chat.orange.com says, I think the fact that he gave a release date is what's bothering me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Spring 2010 is too soon for that to be out.
[SPEAKER_13]: They never stick to the release dates, ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Home got delayed how long?
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to go grab some more water, so talk more about Sony with us, our listeners, Loki
[SPEAKER_14]: including the PSP of course.
[SPEAKER_14]: Other things, Resident Evil Portable was announced, which is pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_14]: We talked a little bit about Metal Gear Solid, Peace Walker, the PSP version there.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Coming to both the 360 and PS3, and I think we may get into this a little bit more, but they have the new Metal Gear Solid Rising, or the Raiden one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's actually, I wanted to find out if they did anything on that, because I actually like Raiden.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then, um... You know, they announced more stuff coming to, uh... Home.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I kind of zoned out when that happened.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, the biggest announcement, I think, well...
[SPEAKER_14]: they didn't really show anything so it can't be that big of an announcement for me but Rockstar announced a new game franchise that's going to be exclusive to the PS3 called Agent that was going to be about secret agents and stuff like that the problem I have with this though is they also announced that franchise Noir is going to be a Playstation exclusive at one time and we still haven't even seen that yet so let's finish one franchise first before we start announcing another one that's my thing though
[SPEAKER_14]: and then I did actually get to play the Motorstorm Arctic I forget the subtitle on it but the new Arctic themed Motorstorm game on the PSP that was pretty fun like a normal Motorstorm game actually looked pretty good on the PSP I watched other than White Knight Chronicles I watched some of the God of War stuff looks just like normal God of War games
[SPEAKER_14]: They didn't really have... I was hoping to play that... What other PSP games do they have?
[SPEAKER_14]: They have the add-on for Wipeout, HD, Licked OK.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I kind of got a brief overview of everything that they had at Sony's booth, and they've got some pretty good stuff coming.
[SPEAKER_14]: I didn't really see anything, though, on Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, they did announce Gran Turismo 5 is coming.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to have 400 cars.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, great that it has 400 cars, but you know, the same time, Forza 3, they announced the launch date for it, and it's this fall, so you
[SPEAKER_14]: Better hurry, because that looks pretty good too.
[SPEAKER_14]: And honestly, 400 cars sounds good, but do we really need 400 cars?
[SPEAKER_14]: I wouldn't know which one to pick.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wouldn't know either.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, we need to do some of our regular segments here before we get to Microsoft's press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: It wouldn't be a week if we didn't say something angsty.
[SPEAKER_13]: So let's do our FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Folks, how's that sound?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's shout.
[SPEAKER_13]: Even though we haven't had anything angsty to bring this on, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: I could say something angsty to invoke this would be how much stuff we didn't get to see at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: There were way too many booths with way too much stuff behind closed doors.
[SPEAKER_13]: What are you so afraid of?
[SPEAKER_13]: So anyway, bring on the angst.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, F you to not being able to go to E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, that's blanket.
[SPEAKER_05]: And for being somewhat sick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to the Australian family that was eating next to us on Friday night.
[SPEAKER_14]: I forget the restaurant, but they were famous for ribs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyways, apparently they like to yell a lot and talk about how their aunt and uncle have sex right in front of their kids.
[SPEAKER_14]: So F you to them because they were loud and obnoxious and we were making fun of them all weekend long.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, yeah, they suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't really have a lot of FUs.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, I had the week off of work, and that's always something to be excited about.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, FU to the fact that I have to go back to the old work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I got one more.
[SPEAKER_14]: FU to my work for not actually finalizing my payment for my hotel that I stayed at in downtown LA.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sticking me with an $800 bill.
[SPEAKER_14]: because they didn't, either they screwed up or E3 Housing screwed up and my company, which was supposed to have, you know, faxed an authorization for their credit card, that didn't happen and so I had to pay like $600 more than I was expecting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, screw them.
[SPEAKER_14]: You should really get reimbursed, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: I better fucking get reimbursed.
[SPEAKER_13]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take it to man.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: One of our other segments we always have to do here every week on the show is the part where you get to interact with us.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's where you send us emails at Mailbag at OrangeLoungeReader.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: And every week, the lovely Dark Sakura jumps into the mailbag headfirst and lands with a few emails on her forehead.
[SPEAKER_13]: So she's going to pick out some of her favorites and read them for you right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mailbag at OrangeLoungeReader.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first one comes from Taz.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, Loki, you called it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seeing how the LEGO games have been in the past year, this one probably is going to turn out to be better than the rest of the Harry Potter games out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is supposedly from years 1 through 4, and I guess we will see years 5 through 7 and then some perhaps when movie 8 comes out in 2011.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm wondering if the game will follow the same LEGO Star Wars formula, or would it go all new on us?
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyways, I know have game for my soon-to-be wife, which I'm probably going to enjoy as well, the game you pervs.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think he's talking, obviously he's talking about like a Harry Potter that got announced that was coming out, big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: The only good thing about that is that means that toys are coming back.
[SPEAKER_14]: My wife was asking about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: We actually went to the Lego store that was on Downtown Disney.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_14]: But no Lego Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_14]: No weird stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: They hopefully will re-release toys when that comes out.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would not bet they're going to do anything new.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think they have to stay pretty true to the books.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that might be some type of agreement.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think he was saying as far as new as gameplay-wise compared to the other Lego Indiana Jones stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wouldn't expect anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe the magic element, but that's probably as far as you're going to get.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The next one is from Cheeseburger.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey guys, you've been talking about your iTunes ranking and how people leaving negative reviews pushes you back a few pages.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I've been thinking that when people subscribe to a podcast, that podcast rank will go up.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is everyone unsubscribed and then resubscribed to OLR in one week, your rank would skyrocket?
[SPEAKER_05]: Am I right or is this just a load of crap?
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess we could just test it out this week, like set a date for the and then resubscription to OLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and he wanted you to verify your email address.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's two ways that iTunes ranks shows, and the one where it has like five pages of featured shows, quote-unquote.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're not even on it anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: Five pages of video game shows, we're not even there anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just like I said, word of mouth is all we got, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I've kind of given up on the whole iTunes thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: There's an email that I don't think I can read.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, skip it, do the next one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It doesn't have punctuation.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's do the next one then.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't have to read them all.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, but I usually like to read them as much as I can.
[SPEAKER_05]: But someone who really likes Pepsi Throwback, which I've had, me who does not like soda.
[SPEAKER_13]: I still haven't had it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's good.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It tastes like old, except it still has that, oh my god, I just sucked a spoonful of sugar aftertaste, which is like honey.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where can I get it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Walmart?
[SPEAKER_13]: Everywhere?
[SPEAKER_13]: I haven't seen it, I swear.
[SPEAKER_05]: The gas station down the street from my house?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll check that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is the last one and it's a bit long.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it is from, I think, Spazinator?
[SPEAKER_05]: Spazinator?
[SPEAKER_05]: So I will just hop right on in and read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi everyone!
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought that I'd write in in order to bring up a few interrelated topics for today's show, being today's, assuming there is a show today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, there is, you're listening to it, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_05]: Before I get to the topics at hand, I'd like to apologize in advance if this email runs unusually long, as I am combining two weeks worth of topics into one email.
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, in regards to what Sky mentioned on the previous week's show, coming back to Final Fantasy XI, I'd like to say congrats.
[SPEAKER_05]: You had made a fine choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I may, I'd at least like to think that I may have possibly played a small role in influencing you in returning to the game, considering that I'm always talking about LLR.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's your return to Vanadiel so far?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you happen to be on either Odin or Alexander and see a Taru-Taru named Derwunch...
[SPEAKER_05]: Dariwa Hyunjiwa
[SPEAKER_05]: on a Final Fantasy related note what are your impressions of the announcement trailer from E3 regarding the previous unannounced Final Fantasy I think we've been over this personally I have mixed feelings about it on one hand being a big old Final Fantasy experience fan that I am I'm rather excited about any upcoming Final Fantasy game and new story experience points that each game brings
[SPEAKER_05]: On the other hand, I'm concerned that Final Fantasy XIV being an MMO will cannibalize Final Fantasy XI's user base.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell, for all I know, Final Fantasy XI may, and I stress the word may, shut down as a result.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though I do plan to play XIV, I still don't want to leave XI or see any aspect of it suffer as a result.
[SPEAKER_05]: The game has a damn good storyline and community.
[SPEAKER_13]: There will always be people out there wanting to play XI.
[SPEAKER_13]: You just might see some of the server consolidations and those types of things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, inevitably some of the user base is going to go over to XIV.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's just what happens.
[SPEAKER_13]: But then again, look at EverQuest and EverQuest 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: When EverQuest 2 came out, not a lot of people wanted to leave EverQuest 1.
[SPEAKER_13]: And EverQuest 2 kind of suffered because of that.
[SPEAKER_13]: However...
[SPEAKER_13]: I think there's a lot different going on here.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, for one, it's Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_13]: For another, you have a lot of people, and I can't stress this enough, you have a lot of people who used to play XI and left because things weren't fixed, but I think they're going to want to give XIV a try.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, is it possible for both games to coexist?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but I think XI will probably shrink down significantly in size, but I think there'll always be people playing XI somewhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Final Fantasy XIV Final Fantasy XIV
[SPEAKER_05]: As a broader question, what's everyone's impressions of this year's E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you feel are the high points as well as the low points?
[SPEAKER_05]: Additionally, do you feel that there was a clear-cut winner between Microsoft, Nintendo, or Sony's conferences?
[SPEAKER_05]: As a result of E3, would you say there's anything coming out between now and early next year that you're particularly psyched about?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I think this show is going to kind of hit on all those points.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's kind of what we built the show around tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I will say I will address the conference question between is there a clear winner between Microsoft, Sony, and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I'm going to say no, there is no clear winner between the three.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the Twitter conference wins.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess, I guess.
[SPEAKER_13]: But there is no winner in my opinion because not enough is out there right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Microsoft had a really good showing.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only thing I think holding me back from Sony as far as grading them as high as Microsoft is a lot of their stuff that they announced, and granted Microsoft is capable of this as well, a lot of it is not coming out anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: Microsoft, they had Crackdown 2 and stuff that they announced, which we'll be getting into more of that stuff, 2010 stuff, but a lot of it they did announce with dates and time frames like this is coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: October.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is coming out then instead of Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not coming out until next year.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is part of our 10-year strategy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not coming out until next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or God of War 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Really, the only games that they showed that were coming out this year were Uncharted 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So a lot of the stuff that they're talking about, maybe White Knight Chronicles, I'm not sure about that, but a lot of it is all next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's that 10-year plan.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's great that you're announcing stuff that's coming out, but Microsoft is announcing stuff that's coming out this year and stuff that's coming out next year.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: When it comes to next year, they will have more stuff to announce that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what separates those two companies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sony likes to...
[SPEAKER_14]: promise a lot but it takes a long time for them to come through with what they promise and you know Microsoft does the same thing to a lesser extent I think but I've just gotten tired of listening to what Sony has to say and promise and know really what's going to happen like you know Final Fantasy 14 and granted that's not really up to Sony but probably not coming out in 2010.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was that it for emails?
[SPEAKER_13]: Any others?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there was more to that one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you that care, there's been some interesting stuff happening in the PSN store within the last two weeks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony's been continuing to put more PS1 classics on there, most of which are pretty damn good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Two noticeable ones are Resident Evil Director's Cut, complete with Jill's sandwiches, and wait for it at Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_13]: I sure did and I have yet to play it because then I literally as Final Fantasy 7 was downloading I remembered that Final Fantasy 4 After Years had come out on Wii and I was like no I want to play that so I haven't gotten back to playing 7 yet keep in mind I was gone most of the week and that's good that they have stuff to download now some of their older Playstation 1 classics because they sure as hell aren't filling up their store full of new Playstation Network games
[SPEAKER_13]: True.
[SPEAKER_13]: I guess they need something to keep them afloat.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's more to this email.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where was I?
[SPEAKER_05]: Once Jack Trenton mentioned that Final Fantasy VII was coming to the US PSN store, nearly... This is nearly, I guess, supposed to say every Final Fantasy fan collectively just their pants.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: They also added a bunch of other stuff on the game side too numerous to mention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Additionally, they have expanded their offerings on the video side of the store to include somewhere in the ballpark of 10-15 more supported TV networks including Showtime and G4.
[SPEAKER_05]: Additionally, they're giving away for free two TV show pilots, Dexter from Showtime as well as Voltron.
[SPEAKER_05]: On a side note, although it's been on the video store
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thanks for taking the time to read my email.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's appreciated.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, sorry, especially to DarkSakura, who usually ends up reading the emails.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for such a long email.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do like how they are adding more anime studios to that, because I think that's something that diversifies them a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not sure what their anime coverage is for the 360, but I know... I don't think there's that much on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that's kind of cool to diversify themselves a little bit with that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: Are we going to get episodes of Cops and Cheaters?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, is that going to be part of the lineup?
[SPEAKER_13]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want the Excuse My Beauty transsexual episode, which I believe was Albuquerque Police.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would pay for that episode.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would so I could watch that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Excuse My Beauty, officer.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll go back to Arizona, I swear.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you haven't seen it, YouTube, Excuse My Beauty.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Starcade, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Xlink in chat wants to point out G4 is free on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brad from PopCulture says Cops is on Hulu.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I didn't realize that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sephiroth1215 says, speaking about the Sony press conference, I mean, we have to think of the years as fiscal.
[SPEAKER_13]: A lot of companies end their fiscal years in March so they can release games up until that point and be keeping the truth of coming out this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes and no.
[SPEAKER_13]: I still think a lot of this stuff when they say 2010, they don't mean March.
[SPEAKER_13]: They mean like October.
[SPEAKER_14]: They should say this fiscal year instead of this year because that, I'm sorry, that's,
[SPEAKER_13]: I think the only games that might come out before holiday 2010 are Final Fantasy XIII at least in Japan and that's why I don't think XIV is going to come out in 2010 because I think XIII is going to barely make the holidays but it's a different team working on it so I could see that happening that would be so weird if that happened and then God of War 3 I think will come out early no you don't think so?
[SPEAKER_14]: March for sure
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, March.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not.
[SPEAKER_14]: They already announced it's March.
[SPEAKER_13]: I see.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, well, okay, then that's before the holidays.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uncharted 2 will be the big holiday game for them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mag was another game that they were showing off that I don't know if it's going to be out this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looked cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I watched people playing it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, if you're into Call of Duty and stuff, you're really going to enjoy that game because it's a massive battleground, basically, of everything that you've seen in Call of Duty and
[SPEAKER_14]: all your multiplayer first person shooter games so that'd be kind of cool if that comes out this year I'm not sure if it is I would hope that they put out Gran Turismo 5 this year because I think they kind of have to you know with Forza 3 coming out I mean
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then as far as what they're going to fill in the rest of the year with, that's a good question.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, Heavy Rain is supposed to be coming out this year, I thought.
[SPEAKER_14]: That wasn't even there at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: No mention of it at all.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: I believe that was all the emails we got.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you want to send us more, mailbag at orangelandredo.com.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's move on to Microsoft, and then we'll let Loki throw in anything else he wants to, because I know he's probably got some other games he wants to talk about, and then wrap up with just a couple phone calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: Probably not going to take a lot of phone calls tonight, just because we've been chatting a long time tonight, but we'll do what we can.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, I want to talk about Microsoft and some of the things they talked about at their press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's just start with the big one, which is Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_13]: which obviously you know I'm pretty sure you guys are all aware it's the motion controller that's camera only there is no controller with it I don't know if you've watched the trailer that goes with it but it's very interesting because the scene that struck me specifically was when the girl walks into the room and the Xbox 360 know who she is and she gets a phone call from her friend or whatever on the 360 and her friend says hey I picked out this cute new outfit for you you should try it on
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyhow, all that aside, let's just talk about Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, Loki, what were your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's really cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought, wow, this is really good, and it set them apart from Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_14]: They can do a lot more with this if it actually lives up to all the stuff that they say it can do.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, I mean, they have kind of demonstrated, you know, their live demonstration of how, like, playing that giant breakout game, which...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: It looked easy to use, looked very intuitive, and I like some of the... I mean, it's very unnecessary as far as browsing your menus and stuff by swishing your hand around.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's cool and all, but I'll just use the controller because it's a lot faster.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, you have the option.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, you don't have to do it that way.
[SPEAKER_14]: But then again, if I'm trying to shoo away my cat, I don't want it moving through menus.
[SPEAKER_14]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see how that ends up.
[SPEAKER_14]: It could be really cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: If they could come up with maybe like a one-handed controller or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Something really small, almost like the Nunchuck or something, so you can, you know, say like you're playing... The Buzz controller.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not Buzz, sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Scenic controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, very small, so you can have some of that, you know, controller stuff and then doing your motion stuff with your other hands or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, some of the things I think were unnecessary, like they showed in the video, like the driving.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't want to have to hold my hands out like a steering wheel.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's not for me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I'd rather...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds like a prescription drugs name, by the way.
[SPEAKER_13]: I am extremely, extremely skeptical about this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think it's going to work as nice as they're showing it in these trailers and things.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this whole concept of people don't want to have buttons and stuff, that's just not true.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, but I don't think that's true.
[SPEAKER_13]: And the whole thing about, well, people get intimidated by all these buttons and things.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't buy it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: There's one device everybody knows how to use.
[SPEAKER_13]: Everybody fights over it all the time.
[SPEAKER_13]: When somebody loses it, people...
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: Hub.
[SPEAKER_13]: I get it, I get it.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're gonna have that, but I just, you know, the fanboys are going crazy with this 360 thing, and I'm sorry, you know, call me whatever name you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm extremely skeptical about this whole thing, and I have a right to be, because the Xbox Vision camera sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: What can you do with that camera?
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: Especially compared to what they showed us years ago.
[SPEAKER_13]: When they first showed us the camera, we were promised all these games that were going to integrate the camera.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what do you have?
[SPEAKER_13]: You have Uno and some of the other Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_13]: And a couple third-party developers threw us a few bones there with the EA.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have the Burnout license plate.
[SPEAKER_13]: Big fucking deal.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then you have the You're in the Movies.
[SPEAKER_13]: and then Totem Ball.
[SPEAKER_13]: And remember when Totem Ball kind of looked fun from the previews that we were shown at that E3 when the vision camera was announced?
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, Totem Ball might have actually been kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: and the way you controlled that whole thing it doesn't the same thing with the eye toy it is never picking up your body correctly it doesn't see your motion right if you don't have exactly the right lighting in your house the thing sucks and if you don't believe me check out some of those eye toy games on the Playstation 2 they're terrible so I think seeing this whole you know motion and movement is how we're going to control our games I am extremely skeptical about it I have a right to be I've seen this before and it sucks why should I feel any different?
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Microsoft bought the company and now they're working exclusively with them to put out this technology.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I do understand, you know, trust me, I bought cameras for all those systems and they all piss me off.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yes, I'm very skeptical on buying another camera that...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Johnny Chung Lee, the guy who did head tracking with the Wii, is working on Natal.
[SPEAKER_14]: It has to work because he is pure genius.
[SPEAKER_13]: TigerClaw says, in order for it to pick up the entire room, it's got to be a widescreen view of the area so that everyone can be involved, insinuating that it's probably a widescreen camera.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, it's a camera, but it's also got other sensors on it, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's not just, you know, it's going to be infrared.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it's infrared, because it looks like there's two infrared sensors on it or something, unless those are just indicator lights for different stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, the camera's really wide, and it...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to keep reading comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Great stuff from chat tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sephiroth1215 says, I feel more satisfied with the Sony Wiimote because while it might just be practically the same, it will be nice to play games with it that are meant for the core gamer, which Nintendo doesn't do.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ziba says, and in all the videos I've seen with it, their living rooms have so much room in front of the TV.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know any house that has that much room in front of the TV like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's also a set.
[SPEAKER_13]: True, but I mean, that makes a good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: Will this work in close quarters as well as far away?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can tell you for certain, my living room is really small.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, how do you play Wii Sports and Wii Bowling?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I know that takes up some space.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I know when we're playing Wii Bowling and Wii Sports and stuff like that, we push out the coffee table, move it out of the way.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yeah, I know it's just one of the requirements.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've got to have space.
[SPEAKER_13]: And guys, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_13]: When I say I'm skeptical, that doesn't mean I hate it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's a great idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: If they pull off everything they're promising, I will bow down and suck Xbox's cock.
[SPEAKER_13]: It truly is one of the greatest things I've ever seen in that case.
[SPEAKER_13]: But excuse me if I'm a little bit skeptical.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think I have a right based on some of the crap we've seen before.
[SPEAKER_13]: Right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I fully agree.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm just cautiously optimistic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, that's fair.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cautiously optimistic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Optimistic to the point of if this ends up being crap, then yes, I'm not going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I need to see it actually being utilized.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I trust that Microsoft would probably understand that, you know what, this isn't going to be just for the casual gamer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's implement this and maybe some other stuff and see what we can do with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, moving on to some other topics because we have a lot of ground to cover.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure some of the callers are going to want to revisit this because probably Natal is the thing that's got the biggest buzz out of E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do want to mention this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Speaking of buzz, my Twitter has filled up with blah blah blah about 1 versus 100.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I feel completely out of the loop because I have yet to play it because I've not been home when all these beta tests have been going on or what have you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a freaking game show.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: If so many people are saying good things about it, there must be something good about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: People are having fun with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's what games are supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're welcome to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, you just got home today.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course you haven't tried it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_13]: I definitely want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's so freaking popular on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm surprised it's not in the trending topics so many people talk about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, some of the other things that were mentioned at Microsoft's press conference.
[SPEAKER_13]: Left 4 Dead 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's got a lot of people pissed off.
[SPEAKER_14]: It looked cool, I thought, to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: When I first saw it, I thought there was this one game that was supposed to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was like Voodoo something or other that had Samuel L. Jackson doing the voice of the main character.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought that's what that was, and then they were all left for dead too.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, oh, I guess it could be that too.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, um...
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot of people are just shouting too soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, there's a petition already with 13,000 people on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Petitions online don't really do anything, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: That are saying it's too soon, that they didn't support the first game enough, and that Valve's cashing in.
[SPEAKER_14]: Honestly, if you ask me, I think that you've been spoiled by Valve.
[SPEAKER_14]: And so now they're actually putting out another game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what?
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't pick it up if you don't want to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait for it to go on sale.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, wait for it to go on sale.
[SPEAKER_13]: They always have these crazy ass sales six months, a year later.
[SPEAKER_14]: No one's forcing you to buy it, but people are pissed off because they've been spoiled with all Team Fortress 2 updates on PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not on 360, but on PC and all the other stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whatever, dude.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just, it's in a different setting, okay?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Different setting, you've got a little bit different game modes in there.
[SPEAKER_14]: If that's enough for you to buy another game, then buy it.
[SPEAKER_14]: If not, then don't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but Left 4 Dead has hugely rabid fans in it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sure there's tons of people.
[SPEAKER_13]: This thing's going to sell like crazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rabid indicates disease.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: The fact that Left 4 Dead 2 is nearly identical to Left 4 Dead 1 and will decimate the community of both games.
[SPEAKER_14]: The announced date is not nearly enough time to polish content or make significant gameplay changes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Which, all these are really assumptions on the development process, and since none of these people actually work for Valve, then I don't really know where they're actually, you know, how they're able to make these comments actually, you know, with... I seem to recall Left 4 Dead got some pretty awesome support after it came out, like there was a free pack that came out afterwards with some new stuff, you know...
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, I think you guys have it pretty good.
[SPEAKER_14]: or not 4, 5 taking place in Africa and guess what?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was bright and cheery but there's zombies.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did anyone bitch about that?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: The fiddle based horde music is extremely disliked though differently orchestrated music is otherwise welcome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Left 4 Dead 2's release will result in a drop of quality and frequency of Left 4 Dead 1 content even compared to before and the community has lost faith in Valve's former reputation for commitment to their games post-release.
[SPEAKER_14]: is what I hear because you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: When I went to Microsoft's booth and EA's booth, guess where the lines were?
[SPEAKER_14]: For Left 4 Dead 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: So go suck it because enough people out there fucking love that game.
[SPEAKER_14]: At least wait until the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's way too early to start.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_13]: The Halo series has Halo Reach and Halo ODST Talk about milking a franchise Holy shit Oh, Halo's done Oh, no it's not We need to put out some more prequels
[SPEAKER_14]: There won't be a Halo 4, but damn it.
[SPEAKER_14]: ODST looks kind of okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gameplay-wise, I don't know what they're really going to do different than Halo 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: And just to make sure that you're a sucker and buy ODST, they're throwing in a bunch of freebies, and they're also going to throw in a beta to Halo Reach, which we don't even know what the hell it is yet, other than it's going to be another prequel.
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not interested in it one bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, and they're going to have a collector's edition, as they have to do with every Halo game.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're going to include another Xbox 360 controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, just an Xbox 360 controller that has special painting on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow, are you a... Do you have a functional D-pad?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, but it's camo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Brad from PodCulture in chat comments, ODST has Nathan Fillion.
[SPEAKER_14]: So... Oh, well then that's perfect for all those fanboys out there who love Nathan Fillion.
[SPEAKER_14]: Crackdown 2 Crackdown 2 Crackdown 2
[SPEAKER_14]: and they're also going to have 16 player deathmatch in it which is awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: How about Shadow Complex?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is the one that Cliffy B came out and you all think it's going to be Gears of War 3 but nope, it's a game called Shadow Complex which is an Xbox Live Arcade game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of looks like Bionic Commando Rearmed.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it was supposed to be more like Castlevania and Metroid is kind of what they were comparing it to and it looked neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: Not really my cup of tea, but it's a neat feature.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then also kind of including the same stuff that they had in Forza 2 with all the designing cars.
[SPEAKER_14]: They kind of spent a little bit much, a lot of time on the whole designing cars thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, oh, it's a way for me to express myself and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was a little bit of, I don't know, ridiculous if you ask me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because, dude, just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Draw something on paper or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Seriously, there's other ways to express yourself, not this game.
[SPEAKER_14]: This game didn't just come out and go, oh my god, now I can actually express myself for the first time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I express myself through playing The Sims.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, maybe you can upload some of these high-def videos and pictures to the brand new Facebook integration on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_13]: But wait, wait, it doesn't stop there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Twitter on Xbox Live as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Facebook thing actually looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only reason it looked cool is because you can actually... Upcoming games are going to support this in-game screenshot thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know about Facebook and Twitter.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I don't use Twitter that much.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Facebook, I really don't use that much.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, it'll be neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm glad that they're adding more things.
[SPEAKER_14]: web browser, please just add a web browser don't need all these things, just add a web browser guess what, I can go to facebook.com or I can go to twitter.com and add tweets that way I have facebook on my iphone so I don't need anything else
[SPEAKER_13]: at a web browser.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, and, and, not just that, Last.fm was another integration they announced.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that you'll be able to, I guess, stream the Last.fm radio, I'm assuming, to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kind of took that assumption.
[SPEAKER_13]: Or it's going to track your plays from the 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not sure exactly how that's working.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't really use Last.fm, so exactly what kind of stations are we talking like music hosted on servers and we can stream stations based on artists?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: On Last.fm, it basically tracks everything you play using a scrabbler, everything that you play.
[SPEAKER_13]: So what you can do once you've tracked some of your listening things...
[SPEAKER_13]: Podcasts
[SPEAKER_13]: Funny enough, if you listen to podcasts on iTunes, they get scrabbled.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's an entry for Orange Lounge Radio on Last.fm because people listen to our show, and so it goes into there.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I wouldn't think that this integration is going to mean that the podcasts are suddenly going to be listed.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think it's going to do anything for us.
[SPEAKER_13]: But yeah, podcasts are a small part of Last.fm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very small.
[SPEAKER_13]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, it could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not sure, you know, we need to kind of hear more about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that was kind of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_13]: Some of the other things that they talked about at the press conference, Final Fantasy XIII actually running on the Xbox 360, which looked fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Big deal, looked like the PlayStation 3 one.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, not a big surprise there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which we all knew it kind of should.
[SPEAKER_14]: Metal Gear Solid Rising.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not 4, Rising.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, we knew that the Raiden Metal Gear Solid was coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, that's...
[SPEAKER_14]: We already knew that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It wasn't a big surprise.
[SPEAKER_13]: But boy, when Kojima walked out on that stage, I bet there were a lot of people thinking, here it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, they were thinking, oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I love the way they worded it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now the Metal Gear franchise has come to the 360.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they made it sound like it was exclusive.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Metal Gear Solid Rising is not.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, and I think this just cements, and I better not hear it ever again.
[SPEAKER_13]: Metal Gear Solid 4 is not coming to the 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: If it was, you would have heard it this year at E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is done.
[SPEAKER_13]: They have moved on.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is how they're getting Metal Gear Solid on the 360 is moving forward.
[SPEAKER_14]: There is a new Metal Gear Solid PlayStation Network and live game that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's using the Metal Gear Solid 4 engine.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: What game is that?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't remember what it's called, but I remember hearing about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe that's that Metal Gear Solid arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably what that is.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was thinking an arcade game, but it's actually for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go, Metal Gear Solid 4.
360.
[SPEAKER_13]: A couple other games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if you are into this, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, not my thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, again, this kind of falls in the category of, hey, it looks neat for the people that are into that sort of game, but I can't play everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alan Wake.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's close with Alan Wake.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you think of this one?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's nice to actually see the game being played.
[SPEAKER_14]: A little...
[SPEAKER_14]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: The whole light-dark thing is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: Reminds me of that WiiWare game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to know about that one because I wasn't sure on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, here's a little trailer I can actually play here, except there's a lot to this.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a very lengthy trailer.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me see if I can skip ahead a little.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually try to show some of the... Yeah, I don't like the previously on Alan Wake because it reminds me of...
[SPEAKER_14]: A Little in the Dark
[SPEAKER_05]: X-Link in chat says it looks like Silent Hill meets Supernatural.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would be like Jamie's dream game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that would really be my dream game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I would have to check this one out after all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, what did you want to add?
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to add there was one thing that didn't get announced.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, a few things that they announced and touched on.
[SPEAKER_14]: One, some new enhancements to Netflix.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now you're going to be able to actually add stuff to your streaming queue straight from the 360, not having to go back to your PC, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'll be able to also browse through different categories on there.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're also doing...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: The Xbox video marketplace is being relaunched at the Zune video this fall to kind of integrate it with their Zune HD stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which did not come up at the conference at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then also this one was a really big surprise.
[SPEAKER_14]: It didn't come up at the conference at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're going to be able to download full Xbox 360 games starting in August.
[SPEAKER_14]: on their service and you're going to be able to basically buy brand new games including like Mass Effect, Assassin's Creed, Civilization Revolution it's going to be you can use Microsoft points or actually use a credit card to buy these games and they're full retail games that do not require a disc at all and they will store it on your hard drive that just sounds a bit bizarre yeah kind of interesting the whole digital distribution thing huh
[SPEAKER_05]: Just like full... The whole damn game.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, so that pretty much wraps it up for everything I wanted to say about the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, I know you had a few stories you wanted to talk about tonight that weren't really necessarily tied in completely to E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: But some of it was touched on a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me pull up.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then I'm going to probably just turn it back to Loki, see if there's anything else he wants to mention about E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: We need to cover release dates at some point too, don't we?
[SPEAKER_13]: So we'll cover release dates as well and get into those.
[SPEAKER_05]: I unfortunately accidentally closed my release date page.
[SPEAKER_13]: We are going to go to the Skype line tonight, but since we anticipate there's going to be a lot of calls tonight, we're going to institute our two-minute rule tonight, which means no call is going to go longer than two minutes.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to be asking everyone the same questions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who are you, and what did you think of E3?
[SPEAKER_13]: So we'll give everyone their two minutes, but since we want to get through a lot of calls tonight, just so you know, that's going to be the rule tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know that might be sad, but at the same time, that means we get more people on the phone, and that's happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, there we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Be happy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, what we have is, for the 10th, this is UK releases, by the way, we have Draconica on PC, and then on the 12th we have EA Sports Grand Chellum Tennis, Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings on a bunch of systems, Prototype on PC, PS3, Xbox 360, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Going over to Japan, you might have heard me mention last week, there really is not a lot to look forward to in Japan this month.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a very slow release over in Japan, and that continues to be true this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: There really isn't anything out on the Xbox 360 or the PlayStation 3, although a big game's getting a price drop next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll have to tell you about that next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: But going to some of the other systems, again, going to Japan, on the PlayStation 2...
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is literally nothing coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me see if the DS is any different.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, on the DS you get Infinite Space is a new game from Sega coming out.
[SPEAKER_13]: That comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: That is really the only big release on the DS.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's a new Platinum Games game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Trying to see if there's anything on the Wii to mention this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Chibi-Robo, the Wii version comes out in Japan this week as well as Metroid Prime 2 with Wii controls but of course as you know it's coming out here in the US pretty soon as a combined one and then quickly looking at the PSP for Japanese release dates I really don't think
[SPEAKER_13]: There's anything this week either.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh no, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Of course there is another Neon Genesis Evangelion game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kotsetsu no Girlfriend 2nd Portable Limited Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, they're doing... I've played that game too.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Girlfriend of Steel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fate Unlimited Codes Portable is now coming to the PSP in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a PS2 game that's been ported.
[SPEAKER_13]: A 3D fight for the Holy Grail.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it for Japanese releases.
[SPEAKER_14]: In the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: there wasn't a whole lot this coming week here, but today we had Legendary Starfy.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a 2D platforming franchise from Nintendo that's finally made its way over to the United States.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, next week we'll be getting Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2010 on all platforms.
[SPEAKER_14]: A lot more games you're going to see coming out supporting Wii Motion Plus since that's also coming out on the 9th.
[SPEAKER_14]: including EA's Grand Slam Tennis of course there's also the Tiger Woods PGA Tour Wii Bundle with Wii Motion Plus and then finally also coming out that
[SPEAKER_14]: I think there was one other Wii Motion Plus game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yes!
[SPEAKER_14]: Virtua Tennis 2009 on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then other games other than Wii Motion Plus stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Prototype coming out on PS3 and Xbox 360 and I believe PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also we've got some really crappy games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Diva Girls, Divas on Ice on the DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I think on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: Indiana Jones and the Staff of Kings on PlayStation 2, the Wii, the PSP, and I believe the DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: Vertigo, which is a...
[SPEAKER_14]: Marble Blast type of game that's going to be coming out on the Wii it's a budget title also this week Rock Band Unplugged coming out on PSP and also the bundle to go along with that and back to crappy games Pets Fashion Dogs and Cats yes a game where you can dress up both dogs and cats to look absolutely ridiculous and on the Wii we have Go Play Lumberjacks Lumberjack themed games and Go Play Circus Star I'm a lumberjack and I don't care
[SPEAKER_14]: seriously and then let's see here oh and then how could I forget Guitar Hero On Tour Modern Hits the third DS game not supporting the DSi Pool Hall Pro another budget Wii billiards game and then finally on the DS Lego Battles the real time strategy game for DS alright sounds fascinating
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, I don't know if you had anything else you wanted to mention.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it's about Tekken.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I love Tekken.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Loki, we'll go to you with any other E3 things you want to report on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, it's just a report from E3 about Tekken 6.
[SPEAKER_05]: It has a beat-em-up mode.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can go around beating stuff up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stomp them, smash them, and it has a story with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can use guns and have giant robots.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, hooray for giant robots.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that like the whole Tekken 3 had its beat-em-up mode in it?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I mean, I think it's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: At least it's not like the crazy RPG mode.
[SPEAKER_13]: True.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love me some Tekken.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, and some other things that were kind of E3 related.
[SPEAKER_14]: Another part of the Microsoft press conference that they talked about, the new game from Big Park, Joyride.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a free-to-download kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: In fact, to kind of go along with all that stuff, Microsoft has announced their new Summer of Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: And with that, a bunch of games coming out, including Splosion Man, which I believe they had a trailer for a while ago, which looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: The game from Epic Shadow Complex.
[SPEAKER_14]: TMNT, Turtles in Time, reshelled, the remake of Turtles in Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's happy, happy, happy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_14]: The HD port of Marvel vs. Capcom 2 coming.
[SPEAKER_14]: Trials HD, which is based off of a Steam game, Trials 2, second edition, that's going to be coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And also, to go along with the more telltale games, adventure games...
[SPEAKER_14]: Monkey Island Special Edition, coming out with both remixed and original graphics.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that was a huge thing announced at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who played Monkey Island?
[SPEAKER_13]: I played Monkey Island.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was a huge PC game, the LucasArts series.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, I just wanted to know if either of you guys actually played it, because I actually didn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't play that one, but I played Loom and some of the other ones that LucasArts... Well, Loom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Loom.
[SPEAKER_14]: I love me some Monkey Island there.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I also... Something else that made me kind of happy is not only are they releasing the original Monkey Island and the remixed version, but Telltale is working on
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Avatar's are going to get some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're going to be able to get unlockable clothing and props for Avatar's based on achievements.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're showing off some of the ones for ODST which unlocks a costume for your character.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of cool that they're utilizing them in that sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: And yet still no trophy cabinets in Home.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although I will say I did play Home this week and they are slowly making upgrades to what we all thought Home was going to be a year ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, you can finally put pictures in home.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can import pictures into your home.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's special.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Going back to Microsoft again.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some features they were talking about when they originally were showing off the new Xbox experience.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now you will be able to watch movies with your friends and also do the photo slideshows and stuff like that with your friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think you can actually already do the photo slideshows now.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you'll be able to listen to music and stuff with your friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, some other random stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Xbox Live Arcade on June 17th will be getting Magic the Gathering as their downloadable title.
[SPEAKER_14]: Magic the Gathering, Duels of Planeswalker will be coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you're a Magic fan, that's probably pretty exciting news.
[SPEAKER_14]: On the Wii, actually, WiiWare in Japan is getting a new four-player Pokemon fighting game that's coming out on June 16th.
[SPEAKER_14]: No word on exactly how that's going to play, but it looks like gameplay is real-time like Zelda or Ys-type action RPG.
[SPEAKER_14]: And, of course, four players can face off in the game's Battle Royale Arena mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Team Ico.
[SPEAKER_14]: Remember, I think we talked a little bit last week that they were teasing that there's going to be some Ico download content for LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did they say what it is?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, they have some more teaser stuff that go along with it, but apparently it looks like it might actually be a level pack like the Metal Gear Solid stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_13]: I love the Metal Gear Solid level pack.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so they have some stuff from Media Molecule.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's on their website.
[SPEAKER_14]: Doesn't really show... It says it's Shadow Colossus stuff, I guess, is what it's supposed to be.
[SPEAKER_14]: They don't really... It's just like kind of teaser stuff right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Trying to pull up their video, see if it actually shows...
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, but it looks like it's just going to be Shadow of the Colossus stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know if it's actual levels or stuff, but it's at least going to be stickers and costumes.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they have like a Colossus costume and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tatsunoko vs. Capcom was shown at E3 this year, and they've announced that there's going to be five new characters for North America since they've removed one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're taking out the Genie character.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that'll be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Perfect Dark being remade for Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: We kind of knew that because of all the leaked icons and images and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it has been confirmed now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's actually being redone or kind of updated, I guess, to run in 1080p.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'll be coming out this fall on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were showing off this game called Cop.
[SPEAKER_14]: The recruit for the DS actually looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: It actually looked like kind of the PSP Grand Theft Auto games.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's coming out from Ubisoft I think later this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that looked kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_13]: Why don't we take some calls real quick?
[SPEAKER_13]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're going to open up the Skype line because, yeah, we're already running into about three hours worth of show.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's about 9.30 here on the West Coast, very late on the East Coast.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I'm going to go ahead and open up the Skype line tonight, try to get some calls out of the way, and then we'll see if Loki has anything else he wants to bring up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Again, if you guys want to share your E3 stories so we can wrap up and get out of here tonight, try to get done before 10 o'clock tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, but I kind of have to work really early tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_13]: So we're going to start taking some calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, two-minute rules in effect tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, this is DSMaster26.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, was that DSMaster26?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell us about your E3 thoughts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I watched it online, and of course I also watched the Sony conference.
[SPEAKER_11]: The Microsoft and Nintendo ones blew me away, but Sony?
[SPEAKER_11]: Boring.
[SPEAKER_11]: The biggest disappointment was, okay, you know how they had Chewbacca come out with the PSP 2000 Star Wars pack, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't believe how they did not schedule Miley Cyrus aka Hannah Montana to bring out the Hannah bundle.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seeing as that it got such a huge reception, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: But what was it that impressed you more with Microsoft and Nintendo that Sony wasn't delivering on?
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, they showed actual gameplay for Final Fantasy XIII.
[SPEAKER_11]: They showed off, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: A few songs from Beatles Rock Band, which that was actually kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the Nintendo conference was actually really kind of cool when they showed off the other M, Metroid.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm like, this is freaking awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was there more than just the Metroid that you enjoyed at a Nintendo's press conference?
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty much, well, other than the Resident Evil stuff, but, well, yeah, and Cop.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I'm like, come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rockstar, if Ubisoft can pull off full 3D sandbox game for DS that's similar to GTA, why can't you?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, 20 seconds left.
[SPEAKER_13]: Any other thoughts about E3 you want to share?
[SPEAKER_11]: Basically, when I was talking about before my PSP went wonky...
[SPEAKER_11]: If Rock Band's dealing with Lego, I'm betting you full on, somewhere down the line, Guitar Hero's going to pick up on Disney.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's bound to happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, time's up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Batav, good one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for calling in.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, peace out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Foodie Monster.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, long time no see, Foodie Monster.
[SPEAKER_13]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: How are you doing guys?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've actually moved countries, which is why I've been kind of able or something, MIA and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where are you now?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm in Chile, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, congratulations on the move.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, so tell us E3 thoughts, quickly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, well, I actually wrote it down so I make it faster for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Splinter Cell Conviction, oh my god, that looked incredible, and I'm so happy with the direction they're taking that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Assassin's Creed 2, love the first one, they promised to give us more diversity and that's exactly what I wanted Project Natal, kind of fucking wait, day one purchase for sure Scribblenauts, amazing, God vs. Kraken, I mean really, that's all you need PSP, excited about Sony, because they're really proving that they can support the platform this way
[SPEAKER_08]: They're showing more stuff, more games, Little Planet, a lot of things, RPGs, and I'm really excited about that Definitely interested about The Last Guardian, that might actually get me to buy a PS3 because that looks great And definitely my best of E3 thing, the best thing that happened in E3 Secret of Monkey Island Special Edition and Telltale's version of Tales from Monkey Island which is going to be the best thing since sliced bread
[SPEAKER_13]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, actually, I just want to say to all non-believers of point-and-click adventures, fuck you, they're back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, Woody, thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a pleasure as always.
[SPEAKER_13]: Call back again when we have more time, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Will do.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Use name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: This is Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_13]: You got two minutes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Three thoughts.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I was impressed by both Microsoft and Sony's conferences.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's too much stuff to really list out, but both the NATO and the Sony motion controller do look promising.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't see whether they're going to be good or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm also kind of excited about the Final Fantasy release stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: What do you think, since you're really excited about the motion control, how do you think Nintendo can catch up, or do they need to?
[SPEAKER_10]: I honestly don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really haven't been following Nintendo at all for the past 10 years.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really don't know enough about the Wii to really comment on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, is there any other E3 thoughts you want to comment on tonight, then?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for taking my call.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not a problem.
[SPEAKER_13]: Take care, Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep, you too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to give us a call, please make sure if you do use Skype, you want to test with Echo 123 first before you call, or else your call might sound like crap, and we don't want to have that now, do we?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, it's me, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_13]: Two minutes.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did you think of E3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Initially, it looks like Microsoft took it, but then again, Sony actually came out and tried very, very close to top them.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Nintendo pretty much came in third.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least it was better than last year's Nintendo Presser, since that was a downer at best.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything that they may have not thought of into the development process, well, they still can because they still got, like, what, at least less than a year before they even release it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they should have plenty of time to work out any final kicks before they market this thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: No one's answered this question yet, and you've got about 40 seconds left.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who do you think is going to be the first one out there, Microsoft or Sony?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and this is the issue with First to Market.
[SPEAKER_07]: It all depends on whether Sony can get it, can outdo Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, if Natal is going to get sidelined and delayed, then that works in Sony's favor.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we'll see that Natal is nothing more than a crock of hyped up shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: Quickly, do you think anyone might rush this and screw up?
[SPEAKER_07]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Sony has done a lot to the point where they could rush this, but they should have a decent product.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm more worried about Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: We haven't even seen the real thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: We haven't seen the real unit on E3.
[SPEAKER_07]: We only saw pictures of it and trailers and demos that didn't even use the unit itself.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've got to let you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Time's up.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for sharing your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_13]: Later.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, it's SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, hello SSJ100 Matt.
[SPEAKER_13]: Two minutes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_13]: Go!
[SPEAKER_01]: E3 overall, I enjoyed it quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I enjoyed Sony's conference the most.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, not really the most, but I enjoyed the, you know, Last Guardian, which actually made me cum a little, not going to lie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thanks for your honesty.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're listening to KTMI.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I like Mag, and then I could...
[SPEAKER_01]: That's all I could think of at the time.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the thing I wanted to call in about was Natal.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I mentioned this on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_01]: I 100% agree with you.
[SPEAKER_01]: We should be skeptical of this thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they talk pretty big with tech demo videos.
[SPEAKER_01]: But until we get something tangible, because they didn't really show us anything hands-on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I would like to see what the third party developers are going to do with this and whether or not they can pull something off quick enough that's
[SPEAKER_13]: Now that they have their development kits, which apparently they just got.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's why I think this thing still weighs out.
[SPEAKER_13]: But quickly, since you don't have a lot of time left, any other thoughts you wanted to share, SSJ?
[SPEAKER_01]: Two things I was kind of disappointed that weren't at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm disappointed that Microsoft didn't mention anything about X and A, what they plan on doing with that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's a damn good point.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_13]: There wasn't anything on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because they didn't mention anything about it, and you know... Ah, they're going to kick it to the curb and treat it like the bastard child it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: What's the other thing?
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was wondering, where's Final Fantasy XIII Versus?
[SPEAKER_13]: Good question!
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, nowhere to be seen.
[SPEAKER_13]: 2011, if we're lucky.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, SJ100Mal, we've got to let you go, but thanks for your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yep, Boba Fett.
[SPEAKER_13]: The Microsoft seems to be closed down a little more to the community.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Coincidence?
[SPEAKER_14]: I was looking at... They have a really close-up picture of the Natal camera.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it looks like it's got two...
[SPEAKER_14]: Sensors on it or two actual cameras on it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Almost like I think they're going to detect depth the same way as a human would detect depth.
[SPEAKER_14]: With the differences between the two images and figuring out where you are based on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think that's exactly what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you're right on track.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's like those stereo images where you stare at it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know where the two dots come together and you're supposed to see the sail ship and all that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to be able to see the sailboat?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll try.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's do one more call, guys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Marissa.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi Marissa, how are you my friend?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm alright, how are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, I just had to leave the house for all of these sounds of Call of Duty right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well awesome, we're talking about E3 but you've only got two minutes hun, so what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just called to say hello, and the biggest disappointment of E3 was that you did not call me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, I'm so sorry, Marissa.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got so busy down there.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was my first trip with my boyfriend and everything, who's from L.A., and we had all this other stuff planned.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just teasing you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, the only relevant gamer news to me is that I just found out they're coming out with a C4.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's completely irrelevant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, we will definitely get on that now that all the craziness of our expo is over and we're bored again, at least until PAX.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, it sounded wonderful.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was fabulous to hear all the updates.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was in town, but all we LA-ers knew about it was that it kind of fucked up traffic.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all we know about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, hey, I will be back.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have a pass for Disneyland now, so I'll definitely be back.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will definitely let you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe an OLR LA meetup.
[SPEAKER_13]: But Marissa, we're going to let you go so we can wrap up our show, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Absolutely, and love to Jamie too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Marissa, come up here and hang out with me.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, come to Sacramento and be on the show, please.
[SPEAKER_13]: Make it happen.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, we're going to go ahead and have that be the last call.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think all the people that were dying to get through got through.
[SPEAKER_13]: We want to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're already like three hours and counting tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a Marissa.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, it was very nice to hear from her.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, did you have anything else you wanted to get out there before we wrap up tonight?
[SPEAKER_14]: Mel, your arcade is actually an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I see images of the cabinet now.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, there is another Xbox Live Arcade game then.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Smash Brothers Brawl, the user online service is ending.
[SPEAKER_14]: That not being the multiplayer online service, but the service to upload user-generated snapshots, stage designs, and replay data will no longer be available.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_14]: No word.
[SPEAKER_14]: No word at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Something else interesting Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: Brawl related.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently there's a flaw or an exploit that's been discovered in the stage builder.
[SPEAKER_14]: That will allow you to run... Oh yes, you know it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Arbitrary homebrew code.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is why it's getting closed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Another exploit just like Twilight Princess.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then, um, let's see here.
[SPEAKER_14]: And apparently Sony says that E3 is not a proper venue to announce any PS3 price drops.
[SPEAKER_14]: Excuses, excuses.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm having a change of heart.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm opening up the phone line one more time.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if we want to get a couple more calls in, we'll give it just a minute to see if anyone else calls.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we'll give it, again, two-minute rules in effect.
[SPEAKER_13]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then we're going to wrap up.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know if we're going to do much of an afterbirth tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: I really want to.
[SPEAKER_13]: Deathwishing
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, okay, first of all, everyone, get feel, it's a, like, for me, if you're not gonna like it, rent it, because it's just so massive, it's 5,000 square miles of just racing, and it's just...
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've heard a lot of negative things about Fuel on the game review sites, but that's now two people.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, like Edge and IGN, but those sites suck anyways.
[SPEAKER_13]: True enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, here we go with E3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Assassin's Creed 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to show you.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I say, ugh, that means it's good.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I go, aw, that means no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Assassin's Creed 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Splinter Cell Conviction.
[SPEAKER_02]: I shit my pants.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Halo Reach, I'm actually excited because it's a Halo based on the book Fallout Reach, which is going to explain why there are Spartans and why there's only four.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm sorry, but the PS3 motion control looks like a sex toy.
[SPEAKER_02]: You say this like it's a problem.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a sex toy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why do we have a problem with this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, it's gonna give little kids ideas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, that's just because their mommy and daddy didn't teach them right.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's just going to encourage people to put glowing balls on their penis and then try to get the thing to follow their penis.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_13]: For boys, you can put the Wii Vitalize on your wiener.
[SPEAKER_13]: For the girls, you can put the PS3 motion control on your pussy.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not finished.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Project Natal.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how with Rainbow Six Vegas you could do the facial scan and put your face in the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now think of Project Assault putting your whole body in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, remember they showed that little tech demo with Peter Monono and that little child?
[SPEAKER_14]: And remember he needed a drawing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_14]: Someone's going to put their penis on there!
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to happen!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait to scan my nude body.
[SPEAKER_02]: When you use that in a first person shooter, what's going to happen to the fat guy?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's going to have a bigger hitbox.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, quickly, because we talked over your call.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll give you 15 more seconds to wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing 1 vs. 100.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to join in, Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: This Tuesday, I think they're having another live episode, the 12th, and I would join in if I were you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will try to play.
[SPEAKER_13]: I will do my best.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, we gotta let you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have fun.
Bye!
[SPEAKER_13]: I liked his whole uh and buh scale that he didn't even really use.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was fascinating.
[SPEAKER_13]: Marissa asked in chat, what is it with guys and putting their penis everywhere?
[SPEAKER_13]: And Frisbee has the right answer, because they can.
[SPEAKER_13]: We talked about this a little earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, I don't do it, but I just report it how I see it.
[SPEAKER_14]: History has proven itself.
[SPEAKER_14]: If it can have a penis put in on it, a penis will be put on it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Folks, we do not make the news.
[SPEAKER_13]: We merely report on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: The cock always wins, huh?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, on that thought, we've got to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're on out of here for tonight.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm glad to be back.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_13]: My final thought is sleep is awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, do you have any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_05]: My husband didn't bring me a milkshake.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm disappointed.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's so fired for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you guys so much for tuning into and downloading our show.
[SPEAKER_13]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for supporting independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_13]: You guys are amazing.
[SPEAKER_13]: And thank you for staying up late with us tonight and putting up with our crap if you're listening to it on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Getting all the way here to the end.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you guys again so much.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you like what you hear, please tell two friends about our show.
[SPEAKER_13]: Word of mouth is how we sell it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you guys so much.
[SPEAKER_13]: Have a wonderful night.
[SPEAKER_13]: We will see you next week with more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, just because E3's over doesn't mean the video game news is stopping.
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll be back next week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe since we'll probably have a lull in the news next week since everybody shot their wad this week, maybe next week we'll be able to play some good old-fashioned OLR games.
[SPEAKER_13]: So look forward to that next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that sounds like a stupendous idea.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, then stay tuned to next week in another stupendous show.
[SPEAKER_13]: In the meantime, I am the stupendous Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the amazing Jamie Summers, and he's the OK Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: And we'll see you next week here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_09]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next week!