[SPEAKER_10]: ... ... ... ...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I'm laughing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll explain myself in a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, we're live and I'm here, myself, Rob Roberts, joined by my incredible co-host tonight, July 27th, 2025, for episode number 1056 of our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: First off, the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: We were talking about his drive because, you know, he's recording on the road right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was talking about the town of Winnemucca, Nevada as a place to stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess I was saying things about – and Alan at some point just went –
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop saying that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you can't stand the sound of the name of that town.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I was like, oh, yeah, I once had to stop there because I had to have Porta Subs, which is an amazing Nevada sandwich chain.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's on the way to Boise when I was going to see friends there and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's just the way Alan was.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now it's become a joke between Jason and I. So he sent me a picture.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: He sent me a picture from a casino in Winnemucca where the sign just, like, brightly is lit up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says Winnemucca.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's just making this...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they all can't be Sly Dell, Louisiana.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least Fly Adele has a Waffle House and some trees.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think there are any Waffle Houses in Nevada.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think there are.
[SPEAKER_05]: There are not.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's not in Arizona.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Arizona, but not Nevada.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, the furthest west I have eaten at a Waffle House was, I think, St.
[SPEAKER_05]: Louis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, the first Waffle House I ever went to was in Tucson.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or was it the second?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe Atlanta did beat it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I literally do not know the first Waffle House that I went to because I probably could not form proper memories at that time.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know the first Waffle House Alan went to was in Tucson.
[SPEAKER_07]: But maybe I did go at one point in the DragonCon years before I actually was at the Tucson one.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a Waffle House.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know when you go to a Waffle House when you're out there, you have to go behind the counter and order me some grits.
Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_05]: A Bag of Grits.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, it's the thing you miss most.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a dollar.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long does A Bag of Grits last you?
[SPEAKER_05]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't finished my last one and I got it a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to make sure that it's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a little bit hard to do their grits at home because they're saltier when I make them for some reason and I don't add salt.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think, I don't know, but I freaking love good... I mean, these are like instant grits almost.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're really quick and very fluffy and dense and delicious.
[SPEAKER_07]: So since we're Orange Lounge Foodio a little bit, I will say this because, you know, when you're from California and you say we don't have Waffle House here, it's like, oh, well, we have Denny's.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to that one downtown.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's not Waffle House.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we have Waffle House knockoffs or Denny's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's why we don't have Waffle House here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tech Master Loki wants to talk about food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blue.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they have like Waffle Squares and things like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all knockoffs.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all knockoffs of what... But the actual Waffle House chain will not play with our wage laws.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why they won't build them here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I heard that directly from a franchisor.
[SPEAKER_07]: People say, well, you have Denny's.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Denny's is everywhere here in California.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's my take.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're sleeping on what I think is the better West Coast cafe, diner type of place, and that's Black Bear Diner.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's the place that I would much rather go there than Denny's any day of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's marginally better.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the thing I think people on the East Coast are missing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Black Bear was kind of like what we would do for... I would go with Danielle's family, part of my ballet group, because we never wanted to go to Chevy's.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we would always go to Black Bear, although this time we went to Red Robin after Swan Lake.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's just like comfort food, and they have decent mimosas, and they will give you the bottle.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, yeah, but I still, like, if you, you know, could teleport me into any one of those, I would always choose the Waffle House first.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, Rama in chat says, hey, hey, Japanese Denny's is amazing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you can't compare international versions to American versions because they're never the same.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that goes, that's good and bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm sure Japanese Denny's is better.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, they also have, like,
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw an article on that today Finally
[SPEAKER_02]: There's almost no Sears left, but yeah, I think that one is also closing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say there's something like 90 of them in Mexico, but it's because it's not the same thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Woolworths is still a thing in some countries, but not here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woolworths overseas was quite a bit different than the Woolworths here, and we had a Woolworths in Mobile, Florida.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the way up through when I was in high school.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I remember Woolworths also had a little lunch counter or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Target in Australia is also a bit different.
[SPEAKER_07]: So tell me one thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is going way back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you remember when Howard Johnson's had an ice cream parlor?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not the Hojo's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember the ones here ever having them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not in the inns.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mean like a standalone ice cream parlor?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know that I ever saw one out here, because it used to be all about the thrifty ice cream counter at the thrifty drugstore, which became the Rite Aid drugstore, which became the Walgreens drugstore, which I think are going out of business.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if there's any thrifty ice cream counters left, but that used to be the big ice cream thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a sign for one in the Folsom one, but I don't know if that's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Still the case.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last time I went into one, which was in Citrus Heights, which is closed now, they did have an ice cream counter, but no one was there.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one in Pocket had one, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if that's still open or not, but I used to go there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know that the Howard Johnson and Mobile had one all the way up through the 80s, and I think it finally closed out like right before the 90s.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they had like a peppermint stick flavor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wait, because Howard Johnson's is actually a restaurant, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Howard Johnson was their restaurant, but they were primarily, their ice cream was the big thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I associate that name with a hotel.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's, like, there's one by Disneyland, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or there was, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and it's the same company in general, but they had, like, their big thing was 28 flavors of ice cream, and that was their thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what that makes me think of?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, we do talk about video games, I promise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fry's Electronics and Fry's Groceries.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're like... Okay, I never knew Fry's Groceries.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, because I want to say that's a thing in Arizona, is Fry's Groceries.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was in the Bay Area, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was in the Bay Area, too?
[SPEAKER_07]: See, and now Fry's Electronics.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if Fry's Groceries is still there, but obviously Fry's Electronics isn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, no, I'm going to take that back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fry's... I remember we had a Fry's in Antioch, California.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I can't remember if that one was also fries in San Jose one of those used to be in Alpha Beta and then it became a fries actually I have seen a fries grocery when my mom lived in Phoenix so yeah that's the other thing that comes to mind when I think of like a name that was in multiple things yeah so anyway alright just bring me back some Puddin' Pops they're probably all Kroger anyways I mean it's everything's Kroger
[SPEAKER_05]: and open a Whataburger around the corner from my house and I'll be happy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whataburger or Waterburger?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Whataburger.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm all southern right now, Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: A Whataburger from Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't think that place was very good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, you heathens.
[SPEAKER_05]: You heathens.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: When somebody says they don't like food, when somebody says they don't like food, you say, more for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Except there's not one here!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on, I want to get to the gaming news, or in this case, maybe news affecting the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, quite a bunch of hubba-baloo going on this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And actually, leaving people wondering if you were caught up in the crossfire, Loki, with this story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was not.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think my game's marked NSFW anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby did some investigative journalism during his show, and it was discovered that, yes, you still can find pixel poops.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us what this is all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're getting ahead of ourselves.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so there's a group, I think it's out of Australia, the Collective Shout group.
[SPEAKER_02]: um that basically has been putting pressure on payment processors we talked about this last week with Steam and how they were cracking down on certain um not safe for work games or with adult themes and stuff I think one that they were cracking down on even was like like furry games because they were saying oh it's bestiality or something like that
[SPEAKER_02]: whatever the case may be they were cracking down on a bunch of stuff and now that has spread to itch.io as well which has also cracked down on a bunch of games and even some that aren't necessarily they're not necessarily adult in that sense obviously overreach with LGBTQ plus games that have been affected by it as well
[SPEAKER_02]: but yeah so there's a lot of games that have been shadow banned and also they have blocked payments for those games as well so if you're making money on those games all of a sudden now you're not able to access those funds which is stupid because those rules weren't in place to begin with and now they are it's like well hold on like you should be able to have some sort of grace period or something like that
[SPEAKER_02]: but also we shouldn't just let you know these watchdog groups or whatever like pressure everybody into doing things um
[SPEAKER_02]: So you have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, we even had some larger developers calling this out as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the director of Nier Automata, Yoko Taro, was talking about this is basically censorship because we are allowing these companies to essentially bypass the normal regulations to now crack down on free speech.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically saying, you know, it implies that by controlling the payment processing companies, you can even censor another country's free speech.
[SPEAKER_02]: I feel it's not just a matter of censoring adult content or jeopardizing freedom of expression, but rather a security hold and dangerous democracy itself.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I think he was more talking about Manga Library Z which also got hit with this as well because essentially anything with an NSFW tag on HIO was delisted I think you can still get to it if you have the page directly but you can't search for it which effectively kills the discovery of games outside of social media platforms and things of that sort so obviously there was some
[SPEAKER_07]: Really gross shit out there on these marketplaces that did have a reason to be dealt with.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now this is a case of a massive overcorrection.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think truly what it seems to me truly a case of a activist group not working in our best interest.
[SPEAKER_07]: You give them an inch and they take a mile.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is basically I think how we've ended up in this situation.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it sounds like these payment processors have too much power anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, can I say something about all that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really going to regret saying this, but I have to call it like I see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: This whole thing, I know, brace yourselves, I'm going to wince when these words leave my mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: This whole thing is the first good argument I've heard for cryptocurrency.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gross.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think that speaks to the nature of these big payment... Let's not jump to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Y'all put the pitchfork and torches down.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's still a lot about it that bothers me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think it definitely says something about the fact that these folks, these payment processors, control way too much in the room.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so I can see why people are turning to these alternative forms as a way to go around these payment processors.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's really no... What is the worry here that I'm going to think poorly of Visa or MasterCard?
[SPEAKER_02]: I already think poorly of Visa and MasterCard.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's not any amount of goodwill that they could do to have a positive... You are just a means to the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one is like, oh, that family company Visa, I love them.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one's saying that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting that we are talking about how companies are different in other countries, because correct me if I'm wrong, I swear I was reading somewhere, and it might have been in relation to all this, I don't remember, but they were talking about how, like, in Japan, you can pay for something online online.
[SPEAKER_07]: and print.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of using Visa or MasterCard, you basically get a barcode or a receipt number of some type, which you take to a 7-Eleven or an ITO or one of those stores that are very different in Japan than they are.
[SPEAKER_07]: 7-Eleven Japan is nothing like it is here.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no one's examples, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: You take the barcode of one of those stores and you pay for it there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so it provides a payment alternative to Visa, MasterCard.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not something that's in our culture.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't really have the means to set up.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's also just going in and buying stuff in the konbini.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like you recharge your Suika card and your other type of travel cards and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But a lot of stuff, like you buy tickets at a konbini.
[SPEAKER_02]: I kind of like that though I mean assuming that you could build it in a way that wouldn't be exploited because that's essentially almost like a VPN for payment processing in the sense because you essentially decouple it from the website now you just have this thing that's a transaction number essentially and you just take care of the transaction and Visa, MasterCard they don't know what it's for
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the big brain idea you gamers need to get on because, you know, right now I understand.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, Loki, if you're going to get to this, but I understand there's a big telephone call campaign to Visa and stuff, which I understand that for, you know, trying to protest to get the message out there and so forth.
[SPEAKER_07]: But like the big brain idea would be to launch that million dollar idea that's going to beat Visa, MasterCard at their own game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I thought something like Venmo is halfway there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really feel like, especially amongst younger folks, Venmo is a very standard method of payment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Venmo and MasterCard tied together?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Venmo tied to one of the banks?
[SPEAKER_07]: It has to be, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: It has to be something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Apple Pay or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's PayPal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Venmo is PayPal, but PayPal is Wells Fargo, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Apple Card is Goldman Sachs.
[SPEAKER_07]: But Apple Pay is not, I don't think.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I do, to some extent, think some things are starting to move away from traditional payment processors.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just not moving as fast as we need to for something to happen about this particular story.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I do think some of that culture is changing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it also gets complicated in the sense of, like, I don't know how refunding or anything, like, would work with all that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so that's a whole other bag of worms.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, was there anything else with the thought there was one more?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, just just that there's also obviously because folks aren't really enjoying this thing happening.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are, of course, launching a petition to tell MasterCard, Visa and activist groups stop controlling what we can watch, read or play.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it describes it basically that this is corporate overreach and censorship of legal fictional content and of course it's already received 77,700 petitions as of about a week ago July 17th but
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, I don't know if it's going to do much, but at least, you know, you can let them know that you're not happy with this, and maybe they'll consider changing their mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's still weird, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I don't think payment processors should say anything about speech.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, block illegal activity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know, you can try doing that, if you will.
[SPEAKER_02]: But once again, even with that, that's kind of overreach as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just...
[SPEAKER_02]: function as an ATM or a transaction machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: We don't need personality opinions in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just do your function and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's funny because some of you in chat are like, PayPal wants to know your location if you mention sex in your transaction messages.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it really never occurred to me that these payment companies are looking at transaction messages because I have some people that I will go out to brunch with once in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I usually will put it on my card and have people Venmo me.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they send me the most disgusting Venmo messages possible as to why they're paying me money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to try to show you one without doxing somebody here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I can do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Y'all aren't seeing nothing here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to show you like an actual payment message I got.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you see that?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a bottle of lotion.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the thing is that a lot of other people can see these messages.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why they do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why they leave those types of things.
[SPEAKER_02]: it's for the lotion that you bought at Bed Bath & Beyond or Bed & Body Works it was for fucking chilaquiles it was not for foot lotion, god your pedicure and you went out for eggplant parmesan afterwards so I mean that's, yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Rage against customer service, but when I say that, I hope y'all are keeping it in the back of your mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: The people that are taking your call are not the ones that are setting the policy at Visa.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if y'all act foolish, that's just going to be what this movement is going to look like, is foolish.
[SPEAKER_07]: But
[SPEAKER_07]: If you act professional in being on the phone and expressing your distaste to this, all of those calls are logged.
[SPEAKER_07]: They may tell you to email a thing, which you could do as well, but make sure that your distaste, your grievance, we shall say the formal term, the grievance is logged.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that way Visa has a record of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, Ranmari in chat says emails can be filtered out, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I think legally they have to still track them, but that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're a stat.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're a stat at that point.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you're on the phone, now that's impacting their call volume, the amount of time, the amount of calls come in, the other calls that aren't getting picked up because they're having to answer to this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a very interesting method of protest.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, yeah, I agree again with Ranmari's perspective in chat over Twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I don't think I said it earlier because we do tape live at twitch.tv slash VOG Network, the Voice Geeks Network, every Sunday night at 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific, right after the Bobby Blackwell show.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, 20 years old this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our baby cousin turned 20 this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Congratulations, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ranmari live in chat says, kill them with kindness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, they have... They log their calls.
[SPEAKER_02]: They usually, like, will... Any call center will usually tag their calls based off of whatever the criteria is about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have, like, what they call, like, kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: not heat reports but it's basically something to the sense of like they're trying to get a like pick up on trends that are happening with you know the call center what type of calls are coming in so they you do want to be polite to obviously the people doing it because most of the time it's even like probably with visas call centers are not even associated with visa they're just using those employees to kind of take those calls but they still track that stuff for metrics so that they can
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, Ranmari says, I worked in customer service.
[SPEAKER_07]: I currently work in medical billing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get the occasional call of people yelling at me for things that aren't my fault.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, please, please don't be foolish on the phone with these folks that are not the people that are coming up with policy.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are paid to take the calls from angry people.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to be one of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, I would argue you're going to get noticed more
[SPEAKER_07]: by folks.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you call in, you're actually nice about it because people, they're going to talk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Those reps are going to talk about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: You getting those people that called today talking about the payment thing on Steam?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they're really nice, but there's a lot of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to talk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just remember, call centers, a lot of times they're like, you know, entry-level jobs.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people that are of that age play video games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, maybe even aware of what's going on at the company and aren't happy about it too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Start a revolt from within.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you hear the people sing?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the goal.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's certainly... We're seeing, not just with payment processors, there's a lot of things that are attacking free speech and trying to censor things across the entire world.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, it's just... I wonder if that's not how this ultimately ends.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't think on the itch.io front, but, you know, say a game like a Grand Theft Auto gets banned by this whole thing in the future, because you know Grand Theft Auto is going to be a big fucking deal when it comes out, and it's going to catch the attention of one of these, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: Anti-free speech organizations that will be trying to get the payment processors to not take money for Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then a big company basically sues the payment processors over their rights to what they can sell.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, I know free speech does not apply to private corporations, but nothing in this country makes any legal sense anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're suing people over everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's starting at the highest office in the land.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I...
[SPEAKER_07]: If you ask me to say what's going to happen, I think it ends in a lawsuit because that's where everything is going these days.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did watch that South Park, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was so good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you know the way they were able to get away with showing that on TV was that they put two little eyeballs on it, like little Michael's craft eyeballs on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That whole part was AI anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, which I don't agree with using AI, but It's their own company.
[SPEAKER_02]: They own an AI company.
[SPEAKER_07]: A point was made
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, but I will say I will never hear the Billy Idol song Eyes Without a Face the same way ever again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby Blackwell says Comedy Central TTP.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to say, though, because I thought this was an interesting comment from SSJ100 Matt in chat who says, So you get fired from your big game studio job and you try to make your games on the indie market, but your game gets taken down because it's offensive to some troll group.
[SPEAKER_07]: This industry isn't fun right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is what I'm also worried about.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, and it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It is not... If a drag queen wants to read books to kids at the library, like when I was young, a clown would do at the library.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, but that's what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for some reason, the right has a problem with one and not the other.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's just...
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, that's what I worry about is that they're going to try to say, well, because the game has drag queens in it, it's NSFW, it's an adult game, which then is because trans people are represented, it's NSFW.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, oh, gay people are in it, it's NSFW, which anything LGBTQIA+, it's NSFW.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: If Tammy Faye can wear all of that amount of makeup and cry on public TV reading fiction as well, I think that drag queens can wear all that makeup and cry in public and read fiction.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're preaching to the choir.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that's a religion I can get behind.
[SPEAKER_07]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Preach.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tammy Faye was a drag queen.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was.
[SPEAKER_07]: Elvira was really one of the earliest as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Tammy Faye did turn herself around a bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Tami had a very interesting life anyway all right uh let's move on let's get into i mean we could we could talk all about Tami Faye uh for three hours but we're gonna talk about our gaming weeks instead and the types of video games that we have been playing this week so DarkSakura i'll start with you how was your gaming week um Mass Effect Dead by Daylight i'm trying to recapture my pig era again um Palia i've been doing quests in Palia um
[SPEAKER_05]: Playing the Suika game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't really had time to do much more than my usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just because I went back to my Friday ballet class.
[SPEAKER_05]: My whole schedule is going to be changing pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not in a bad way.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll go to Loki then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your game of the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much just Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still working on coding the data pack for my stuff and then I've been working on other things as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just playing around in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yep, still Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's always the name Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: For me, I'm still getting my dailies done in Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still play a little bit of Diablo 4, but not as much because I've just been playing other stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I will say I was doing, you know, some classic games this week, but I will say the one classic rabbit hole I fell down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you'll appreciate this, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I started playing Final Fantasy XI again, but this one is one of those private servers.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't do a very good job keeping this a secret.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called Horizon, Horizon XI, which launched in...
[SPEAKER_07]: Dune's Parties Warcraft Classic
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be interesting if Square Enix, because you know how we got official World of Warcraft Classic, was Blizzard finally shut down all the servers because they were going to do something official.
[SPEAKER_07]: They sent cease and desist to all the private servers and started their own official thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if someday Square Enix doesn't do something official.
[SPEAKER_07]: It still blows my mind that they charge money for Eleven and that it's not just grouped in like a Squeenix Pass event.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: and uh but level syncing is there so if you want you could take your level 30 character sync it down to level 17 or whatever and go do a Valkyrm Dunes party you can do that and still gain most of the XP there is some penalties to the XP depending on how many people are signed on and all this all these other factors I'm not going to bore you with the stats but um it's interesting that they have put some of those quality of life because level sync was
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: It's slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I've been playing for a couple hours and I may be level 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it just took me forever to remember how to do shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's so much fun though.
[SPEAKER_07]: The nice thing about Horizon though, like everything is built in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like in the launcher, there's a lot of great add-ons.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's one called Balloon that makes all the quest text look like Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it will support 4K and all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm pretty impressed by the Horizon stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So kudos to everybody because that's a labor of love from Final Fantasy XI fans making those servers work with those tweaks that mostly keep it frozen in time but add the quality of life stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do believe they are adding Treasures of Ottergon pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: because you can't even do like Blue Mage, Corsair, any of the jobs they added in Otter Gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's something they're looking at adding in the relatively near future.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, otherwise, that was my game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to get into some gaming news, just some quick notes of weeks we will not be here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to be absent a couple weeks in August, so I will not be here on August the 17th, and I will not be here August the 31st.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm on a personal trip on the 17th, and on the 31st, I will be at DragonCon in Atlanta, as I have been for the past decade plus.
[SPEAKER_07]: So as I usually say, and I hope I will see some of you there, if you're in the area, best time to catch me at DragonCon,
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know my full panel lineup yet and I won't until the app is released, which is like two weeks before the convention-ish.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the one thing I do know will happen, I can promise, Thursday night we will have a mixer for the digital media track at...
[SPEAKER_07]: 7 o'clock?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I don't have it in front of me.
[SPEAKER_07]: But look for that on Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby and I will be there and that is the best place to catch us during the frenzy of DragonCon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So come have a nice chill Thursday night with us at the Digital Media Track on Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everything else I will mention closer to probably that show right before is when I will be able to talk about anything else I'm doing at the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we had a Pokemon Presents showcase that showed off a bunch of Pokemon updates.
[SPEAKER_02]: Starting things off, of course, they had a DJ Pikachu animation thing, which is neat, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I watched some of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was not the music I thought they'd be playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's that news?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, that's not news.
[SPEAKER_07]: That affects nothing in the Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cute!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what's news about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be new episodes of Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got a Pikachu that's so old back there he's deflating.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that cute?
[SPEAKER_07]: My little Pikachu pillow?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemon Concierge is going to be getting some new episodes starting September 4th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that'll be coming to Netflix.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have the Pokemon Tales, The Misadventures of Sirfetch'd and Pichu, which is coming in 2027.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a new stop-motion series.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing a lot of animation stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that'll be... We're probably going to forget about it by the time it comes out in 2027.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poke Park Kanto, a new outdoor attraction that is opening up in Japan that's made to look like a real forest.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that is set to open up in 2026.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pokemon Go.
[SPEAKER_07]: It didn't look like it had rides or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like it's an Instagram park.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an Instagram park is what that place looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instagram park?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemon Go Fest 2025 Max Finale is going to be coming soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to take place August 23rd and 24th and will feature Max Pokemon including Eternatus.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat, I haven't been in Pokemon Go in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eternatus, I think, might be?
[SPEAKER_07]: Eternatus, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Emprisonatus?
[SPEAKER_07]: Empanadas?
[SPEAKER_07]: Empanadas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's empanadas.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, well, that Pokemon is a pretty big one from Sword and Shield.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still am playing Pokemon Go pretty regularly, at least to incentivize my walk.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do mostly Bluetooth catching, but I'll catch the most random fucking shinies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, just in the last week, I got a shiny Aeron.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Pokemon Masters EX Pokemon Masters X Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's what everybody's wanted, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is going to be getting Carmine and Sinestra as a sync pair on July 29th, or at least starting July 29th through September 6th.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you'll be able to participate with that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, Pokemon Cafe Remix.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, are you glitching?
[SPEAKER_07]: Am I?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you disappearing into the Matrix?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, you keep blinking, which I'm like, what the hell is happening?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm actually looking at... Well, it stopped now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, now that I said something, it stopped.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, go ahead, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a bunch of pirate-themed characters and cosmetics coming to the game Pokemon Cafe Remix, including Captain Outfits for Lapras, Lone Mouth, Toadtodile, and Messino.
[SPEAKER_02]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they also have a summer-themed Jigglypuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, what else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Pokemon Sleep!
[SPEAKER_02]: Legendary beasts are coming to Pokemon Sleep, but you'll never see them because you'll be asleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's coming out in August.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not how the game works, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not how the game works?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not how the game works.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know anything about Pokemon Sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: It measures your sleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a game where you try to play Pokemon, but every time you bring out your Pokemon, they're asleep.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're just like, I don't know what to do here, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, do we fight now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: When that game first came out, I failed to see the point completely.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I played it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pogo Plus Pokemon Unite Lataius
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know these Pokemon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, join the roster.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's going to be coming, I guess, August 8th.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then they have a new battle mode called Electrode Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's going to be, I guess, available now in the game as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: More Pokemon TCG stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed off some new full art Mega Evolution cards, including Lucario, Gardevoir...
[SPEAKER_02]: Kangaskhan and Venusaur so cool there we have Pokemon Friends is going to be let's see Pokemon Friends which was released on the App Store it's getting a they're also a new puzzle game I guess called Pokemon Friends and I'm not really sure what it is it says you get plushies by solving short puzzles in a variety of classic traditional brain teaser formats
[SPEAKER_02]: and I think that's the game you can do you can do one puzzle and then you gotta pay for it free to play free to play technically true um and then we had what was it Pokemon Scarlet and Violet talking about the Switch 2 upgrades for that as well as they're gonna be getting new terror raids for the Treasures of Ruin um
[SPEAKER_02]: But you'll only be able to capture them after the raids have been completed 1 million times.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of stuff just makes you think it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have the first footage of Pokemon Champions, the battle simulator game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to include ranked, private battles, new training mode, and it's coming to Switch and Mobile 2026.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then finally we got some more footage of Pokemon ZA Legends or Pokemon Legends ZA and yeah they showed off some gameplay on the Nintendo Switch too which thankfully doesn't look like ass so that's good it's gonna be it looks like fun I'm actually really hyped for this game I'm really excited to get it yeah and yeah games are supposed to be coming out October 16th that's gonna be here before we know it
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry for that, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta say, yeah, I gotta say, I wasn't, like, blown away by this Pokemon Presents.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, obviously, Legends Z through A is great, and so I know they gotta do a little bit of the hype machine for that, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought maybe there'd be something kinda new in it, or maybe...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, maybe I just set the bar too high in my mind I'm still really disappointed we don't really have decent ways to play the old Pokemon games considering the fact that Nintendo's really pivoted away from the 3DS and the DS and so those ports of Pokemon Yellow and all that stuff not that I need to necessarily play Pokemon Yellow again but it would be nice to have some of those older Pokemon games maybe in the Switch library maybe just to hear about some other games that are coming out for Switch 2
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, you've talked plenty about Dear Esther.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was another one of their titles as well, kind of the OG game in that genre.
[SPEAKER_05]: Both, they were great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Little Orpheus, another game they made.
[SPEAKER_07]: I missed this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: They made a game recently called Still Wakes the Deep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't checked that game out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks very different from some of their other titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I've not played this yet, so maybe I need to wake up.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you may or may not know, the Chinese room at some point was acquired by Sumo Group.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then Tencent bought Sumo in 2021 for $1.27 billion.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this really was a case of fish gets eaten by bigger fish gets eaten by biggest fish.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, apparently what has happened is that the Chinese room has now bought back its independence.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: which is the British way of saying that.
[SPEAKER_07]: The specifics are confidential but the studio is currently 55 developers.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was a very difficult process as we saw a future for the studio outside of Sumo.
[SPEAKER_07]: No more layoffs are planned as the studio moves forward.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess take that for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they are going to be independent.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are also working on Vampire the Masquerade Bloodlines 2 in conjunction with Paradox.
[SPEAKER_07]: That title is supposed to be launching in October.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are also, they meaning the Chinese room, is developing two other games that are not yet announced.
[SPEAKER_07]: In a quote on this whole thing, the studio ahead, Ed Daly, said, This management buyout allows us to scratch the creative itch of continuing to work on new, original intellectual property, but also to partner with other studios on projects when they fit in with our vision.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what we're doing, and we want to carry on doing it, so we're happy to carry on in this vein.
[SPEAKER_07]: So kind of a mixed bag of news there is that, you know, hooray for the independents, but at what cost?
[SPEAKER_07]: So it'll be...
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Questbuster points out Still Wakes the Deep was really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how I missed that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I usually try to follow and see if that studio's got anything coming out, but I guess that just kind of missed my radar.
[SPEAKER_07]: How'd that happen?
[SPEAKER_07]: I must have been asleep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I can find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: When did that game actually come out?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the other kind of question I have.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long have I been officially sleeping on this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, 2024, it was released.
[SPEAKER_07]: June 18th, it's about a year old at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting, I gotta get on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Windows, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a psychological horror game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm, sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: The producer of the game, Lee Cocker, said that they were going to introduce Pokemon characters in Street Fighter, Mega Man, go in the Dragon Ball franchise, Metal Gear Solid, Legend of Zelda, some Sony and Microsoft properties.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that never happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a licensing nightmare.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they just stuck with what they had.
[SPEAKER_07]: Always fun to hear about the stuff that got cut from games, as frustrating as it can be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but honestly, don't overcomplicate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Keep it simple.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And building off of the old rivalry was a smart move, keeping it that way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: True.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, and then the whole 2020 Olympic Games kind of got screwed up anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange right in chat says, Super Smash Olympics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, kind of.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of what it was going towards, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Complaining works, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: So everybody was unhappy with the fact that, well, Nintendo kicked off this whole $80 brand new game thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, you know, the next studio to announce that their game was going to be $80 was Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Obsidian with the Outer Worlds 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, everyone complained about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And now they've walked it back.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they put out a social media post saying, Dear Galactic Citizens, we have received your SOS via skip drone and are about the pricing as an organization devoted to make sure that corporations do not go unfettered.
[SPEAKER_02]: We here at Earth Dictorate have worked with Redacted to revise the price of Outer Worlds 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: and essentially dropped it down to $69.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll call it $70 because that's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: $70, yes, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: Along with that, we also have news that Call of Duty Black Ops 7 is also only going to be $70 and not...
[SPEAKER_02]: The price point for the game itself will be $70.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's not kid ourselves that it's only going to be $70.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your limited editions, your special editions, your early access editions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so $70 as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for right now, they've walked it back and the price point of $70 that people didn't like before now is a little bit easier to digest, I guess, because it's not $80.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, this really seems like a case of the internet getting what it wants, which I think is very interesting because it seems to indicate that, I mean, I don't, the only logical reason I can see that they are retreating from this, not just from one game, but all of, because all those games are Microsoft first party at this point with everything Microsoft's acquired in the last five years.
[SPEAKER_07]: All those games are Microsoft first party.
[SPEAKER_07]: This shows that Microsoft is retreating from that $80, which indicates to me the only reason you do that, the pre-orders weren't pre-ordering.
[SPEAKER_07]: People were pushing back and voting with your wallet actually worked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, of course, we don't have the stats to back that up.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not going to say pre-orders are at an all-time low.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I guess we could investigate with some retail outlets out there, but we probably are not going to get the full story on the why.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it would seem to indicate that people were not willing to pay $80 for a video game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most likely, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Most people got it as a pack-in for their Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I realize it was still the number one selling game outside of that, but I think that is... Once again, I think that's limited by who buys a Switch 2 and then buys the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who would be buying that separately unless you got...
[SPEAKER_07]: People that were desperate to get that day one so they could play with their friends or just the status of it or otherwise.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think at the end of the day, you can explain it a hundred different ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not an accurate barometer for the rest of the gaming industry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the accurate check for Nintendo will be if they decide to price something else at $80 because they didn't do it with Donkey Kong Bonanza.
[SPEAKER_07]: and good thing they didn't because Donkey Kong Bonanza is a pretty good game and I worry the only thing in that conversation would be the $80 price tag if it had been $80 because it's a good game but it isn't exactly anything...
[SPEAKER_07]: Prime 4 at $80.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, now that I'm thinking about it, I hope they don't because they're going to set that game up for failure.
[SPEAKER_02]: A new Zelda game, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Metroid, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: ZA isn't at 80, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that was in the news recently because I think that surprised a lot of us that Pokemon ZA is not going to be 80, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that would be the game I would think they would do it with a mainline Pokemon game.
[SPEAKER_07]: would make sense for them to try at $80 but again that's going to be the more accurate barometer of where the $80 price tag is going to be effective for Nintendo but very clearly the others are retreating for it which is not a good sign for Nintendo leaning into this for a future game of theirs.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's no need to be disrespectful about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, $80 price tag?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll wait for a sale.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a very effective... Because I think for... And God, that's probably a true statement for a large percentage of people who don't buy games on day one anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they know they're going to be on sale, on Game Pass, something.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's going to be another way to acquire it for far less cheaper later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just for those fans that really want to be in there day one for whatever reason that are willing to... Which...
[SPEAKER_07]: is me with a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm willing to admit that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm sure we all have franchises we would do that sort of thing for.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's interesting to see what games boardrooms think are worth $80 that then people go back and say, no, this is not something I'm going to take a gamble on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a whole other thing, too, is that there's no guarantee an $80 game is going to be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know Ubisoft is itching to charge $80 for games and that's a whole other issue.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're stupid and delusional and think that their games are AAA games and then they put out some pirate game that sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just awful.
[SPEAKER_02]: That did real well for your Assassin's Creed game that you delayed again because it wasn't up to snuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you can, if Rockstar Games came out and said, yeah, we're a quadruple A studio, I would be able to, you know, that would be something, you know, okay, maybe, yeah, okay, yeah, I'd get, I'd buy that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, like, Ubisoft, come on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Come on, Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Look in the mirror.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_02]: You've made Far Cry how many times now?
[SPEAKER_02]: And while I'm talking about Far Cry, I'm talking about every other game that you've made while Far Cry has existed has basically been Far Cry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, how many times have you made Far Cry?
[SPEAKER_02]: Too many.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to get to another comment in our chat room, kind of tying this back to the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw in chat at twitch.tv slash VOG Network says, do you think those bullying tactics will work against Visa?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, technically they sent out a general response.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I think it's going to take something bigger in that case.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do think it is worth calling and voicing your opinion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it tactfully...
[SPEAKER_07]: It is worth calling and voicing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And all of this has to be done tactfully because if you just give ammunition to the gamers or trash and they like nothing but trash file, then people are going to use that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So don't be trash.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think anybody listening to this show, I don't think needs to hear that, but maybe some of the people you know need to hear it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be what I would think about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do think, you know, Itch.io is not a very large publisher when all is said and done, or I should say storefront of games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Steam kind of is though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet if Steam said we are now only going to take payments through Venmo or something like that, I bet they would do well enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: They could weather the storm for a bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think they'll do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think they will.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think they have a little bit more negotiating power when it comes to Visa and MasterCard to be able to say no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think right now, because what the demands are from the payment processors is it's not impacting sales enough, but if they started saying, oh, we're going to crack down on all violent games, we've got to protect the children or something like that, where it would affect more of their library than they may have some pushback.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think that they're going to just be like, oh, yeah, we're going to take off all the M-rated games off this platform.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, no, they're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think the optics, if they do delist something that isn't really adult because of the whole thing I was talking about before with LGBTQ or other types of themes, I think the optics of that would be so bad for Valve that they can't have that happening to them.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be very, very bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they have a little more leverage to push back against the payment processors.
[SPEAKER_07]: When all is said and done,
[SPEAKER_07]: Itch.io is, I guarantee you Itch.io is not a large organization.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guarantee you Itch.io does not have a large legal staff ready to deal with these sorts of situations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Valve probably has more, but you know who'd have a ton?
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if they try to start to, you know, I mean, do this, but already the consoles are pretty limiting in what they offer.
[SPEAKER_07]: The consoles don't list AO games.
[SPEAKER_00]: You don't have adult games like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Itch just does not have the staff to be able to push back against this at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_07]: They don't have a legal team.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they are more looking at, in order for us to not have to hire a lawyer and stay solvent, how do we get around this?
[SPEAKER_07]: And now the baby got thrown out with the bathwater, which I really hate that expression, but it applies here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what happened with Itch.io.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now they're going to have to backtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: But blame the organization that's starting all this shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: They know what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: mm-hmm all right which is weird though like because how many people does that organization actually have why does one person complaining to payment processors cause I think they rallied a thousand I think they rallied a thousand okay but in 77,000 they're like oh well you know forget them but like a thousand people mad at us oh no like
[SPEAKER_02]: What they should be doing is they should be like, listen, man, we're Visa.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're a thousand people.
[SPEAKER_02]: You mean nothing to us.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're in Australia.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't even have the right time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your seasons are backwards.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your toilets swim the other way.
[SPEAKER_05]: With all these 30-minute increments, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have folks that listen to Australia.
[SPEAKER_07]: You all are great.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know this organization is nutso, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about other things going on with Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the Steam client beta is testing a new design for the storefront, which is to try to make it a little easier to find games that you might be interested because this is the age-old problem, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Steam is so full of games, it is hard to find things that you might actually be interested in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Discoverability is a problem on any storefront these days, whether it's mobile, Steam...
[SPEAKER_07]: All of it is in the same boat.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're trying new things to see what might be able to break through with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the latest beta update, instead of having a bunch of text links and menu buttons, this remodel will have everything into an organized menu at the top.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what happens is that you will get, quote, easier access to the places Steam users most frequently visit.
[SPEAKER_07]: A browse feature lets you go into games based on top sellers, new releases, or sales.
[SPEAKER_07]: The recommendations will let you explore what Steam thinks you're going to be into based on the things that you've played, the things that you've acquired in your library, or even things that maybe communities that you're in have recommended.
[SPEAKER_07]: The categories menu button will let you look at the top genres of games that you're playing and then give you tags that are kind of along those same lines to find similar games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Things like Great on Steam Deck, Immersive Sim, Demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Adult Video Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, Steam will also show the most popular searches, your games that you've viewed, and top genres.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there is a button for advanced search if you want to go through all the filters and tags and all of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: None of these are new features.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is just a way for them to reorganize the features that are already there to try to make the button bloat of the menu on Steam today a little less popular.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that could be interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, if you want to check that out, you could just opt into the Steam Client Beta and take a look at it for yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that will probably just be a matter of time before it shows up for everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, for people, this is actually, I'm going to put this in the realm of better news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if anyone is familiar with Project FX's, sorry, SideFX Project Elderwood.
[SPEAKER_05]: is a sort of a demonstration of some of their rendering tools meant for creating video game assets, including in-game vegetation and scenery, all sorts of things like that, all procedural tools for generating these things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they have released their custom Houdini tools for use in
[SPEAKER_05]: For anyone who will be interested in using it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's based off of a custom tool called Natsura, which is like a new tree plugin thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I remember correctly, I do believe this is going to be for Unreal Engine 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: but um but yeah i mean it is it is something you know you got to pay for licensing but um but it's a lot of assets and i know that we've got people um and actually the project elderwood files themselves are free um so you can get uh get that and see how everything is put together
[SPEAKER_05]: But, yeah, I think that if anyone out there is into a little bit more higher end game design, this is something I'd say we're thinking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't make a lot of games, so it's hard for you to put that in that context, but I think it's neat that the accessibility and information, I guess, is out there for everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, yep.
Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: If any of our designer friends out there are using stuff like this, let us know.
[SPEAKER_02]: let's move on just a few more stories before we get to the classic game of the week but this is an interesting meeting of the minds collaboration of the century we had the developers of Claire Obscure Expedition 33 visiting Square Enix and visiting the Final Fantasy dev offices as well for an exchange of ideas so collaborating with them and
[SPEAKER_02]: Does this mean that we'll get a turn-based Final Fantasy game in the future?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we can have the Claire Obscure folks put out a Final Fantasy game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would jump to that conclusion, but it is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's very interesting that
[SPEAKER_07]: with all the talk of this is what we want in our Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is what Final Fantasy should have been.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the direction that Final Fantasy should be going.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's very interesting that they are meeting with them because it actually shows a willingness to listen on Square Enix's part.
[SPEAKER_07]: That, to me, is the news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Y'all need to stop with the jump into the, oh, they're going to collaborate, they're going to offer...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I mean, it's all wishful thinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not saying that to you, Loki, but, you know, just the internet in general.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I think it's just a show that Square Enix is willing to listen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, hey, in this day and age, is a gift.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because there's a lot of people out there who don't want to listen.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also visited Kojima Productions as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder what they might be cooking up over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, taking it back to a classic era in gaming, we have some news this week on a brand new Atari 2600+.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might remember this was the retro console that came out last year, but the little, or maybe it was two years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Time is a construct that has lost all meaning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Time is fleeting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Madness definitely takes its toll.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the 2600 Plus, it was a classic console, but it would actually play your Atari 2600 cartridges.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I believe it plays your 50...
[SPEAKER_07]: 200 and your 7800s.
[SPEAKER_07]: It plays more as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're coming out with a new 2600 plus that is all about Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I love the look of this thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: But for those that are listening live, you can take a look at what this looks like there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like a yellow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take that wooden concept of an Atari 2600 and make it yellow, which I just don't like.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like the color.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that might be neat for people that missed it the first time around, but I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love the look of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it is celebrating 45 years of Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is coming out October 31st.
[SPEAKER_07]: The price in British pounds is $128.09.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know what that's going to translate to over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe $129.99?
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is...
[SPEAKER_07]: Just the same as the basic model that came out previously, but it will have a Pac-Man themed joystick, also yellow, and a double feature Pac-Man Atari 7800 cartridge.
[SPEAKER_07]: It has an all new arcade game, Pac-Man 7800, and it has the very first Pac-Man Atari 2600 as if anybody needs to revisit that.
[SPEAKER_02]: No one wants to see that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, but that's kind of neat that it has both the reimagining.
[SPEAKER_07]: There also are Ghost Edition wireless joysticks coming in the color of the various ghosts, which is kind of a cute idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, that's coming.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, that's not really the news that caught my eye.
[SPEAKER_07]: The news that did catch my eye was that Atari 50...
[SPEAKER_07]: The retro collection that came out for the modern consoles a few years ago now at this point is getting yet more DLC.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is after the Intellivision.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had some other stuff recently.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they are getting a Namco Legendary Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to tell the story about Atari and Namco's partnership.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, Pac-Man for the Atari 2600 will be in this collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where that game belongs?
[SPEAKER_07]: In a museum.
[SPEAKER_07]: A virtual museum.
[SPEAKER_02]: The 2600 plus is $169.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, thank you, tariffs.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, tariffs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, where were we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Atari 2600, 5200, 7800 will all be represented.
[SPEAKER_07]: Galaga, Dig Dug, Xevious, Galaxian.
[SPEAKER_07]: All going to be represented in this, which I think is really cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love this idea of the Namco collaboration.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, this leads to a lot of people, including myself, asking, could there be an Activision collaboration, which means a Microsoft collaboration, which I would think on the Xbox version of the game would be easy peasy, even though now there's their own Xbox Classics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I got to come back to that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be neat to see Activision represented at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just think the licensing is going to make that very difficult.
[SPEAKER_07]: But never say never.
[SPEAKER_07]: After all, you can play a lot of those games now on Xbox Classics.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I will say this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft is doing a terrible job supporting that Xbox Classics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Show of hands in the room, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: How many of you know that the legendary game Gabriel Knight is now accessible on Xbox Classics?
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have an Xbox that I would play it on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gabriel Knight was a classic CD-ROM game by Sierra that had Tim Curry as one of the voices.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe had some other A-list actors involved in that game as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gabriel Knight released on Xbox Classics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, the publicity and the system behind that is so bad, it's not getting any coverage that these games are actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it seems like they're adding new games maybe once a month.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and that was before Gabriel Knight that was the last one with Cosmic Commander and some of the other releases this or Cosmic Commuter this time I didn't bother looking and I was just like I'm sure they're probably not because I should have seen I should have seen this somewhere else than actually just logging into the game on a whim and seeing oh they added Gabriel Knight at some point to Xbox Classics nobody's talking about it for what a legendary fucking game that is from the 90s so anyway
[SPEAKER_07]: That was my tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the classic talk isn't done yet, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to the bump.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn, Jamie, this game's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is an old game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I was specifically looking up vector games and I was like, oh yeah, this game existed and I haven't done it before.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's Omega Race.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is a shooter that came out in 1981 designed by Ron Halliburton and it was released by Midway.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was an arcade video game, and it was the only arcade vector graphic game that Midway created.
[SPEAKER_05]: It had some ports.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get into that for a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the way that the game is set is it's set in 2003!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_05]: and you control an Omegan fighter spaceship to destroy enemy droid ships around a track and you use a spinner to control the ship and you have a button to thrust and a button to fire lasers and so the enemies that you destroy
[SPEAKER_05]: Have to destroy or avoid, this is different ones you have, are drone ships, commander ships, two types of space mines, and shooting star ships.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you bounce off an invisible barrier on the edge of the screen that briefly shows up when you're hit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course you get extra ships, they're awarded at 40,000 points and 100,000 points respectively, by default.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: The port that came out... Alright, let me actually get into the port.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was ported to the VIC-20 in Commodore 64, published by Commodore in 1982.
[SPEAKER_05]: In 1983, we had the ColecoVision and Atari 2600 versions that were released by CBS Electronics.
[SPEAKER_05]: So the Atari 2600 version came with a booster grip controller that converted the button on the Atari CX-40 joystick into having separate buttons for thrusting and shooting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was also one of the few CBS games that came out on the 2600 that had an additional 256 bytes of RAM in each cartridge, and they called it RAM+.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Consumer's Guide How to Win at Video Games stated that any unskilled player can pop a quarter into the machine and stay up there for up to 20,000 points.
[SPEAKER_05]: They said that more than 35,000 machines were created and the average machine brings in $181 per week as of the publication in 1982.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was one of the best money-making machines at the time because it was deceptive and actually pretty frustrating.
[SPEAKER_05]: Compute magazine called Omega Race, quote, a real winner for the VIC.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that it was fast-paced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, Byte Magazine said it was fast-paced, had colorful graphics and featured good sound effects.
[SPEAKER_05]: The quote says Omega Race is a fun game that retains all the best characteristics of the arcade version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ahoy also called the VIC-20 version fairly faithful to the game and very exciting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it won a certificate of merit in the category Best Solitaire Computer Game at the 4th Annual ARKI Awards.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was cloned for the TRS-80 Color Computer, a space race in 1982.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now here's the fun one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was going to be... In fact, it was pitched for the Atari Jaguar as an update.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it didn't get further than the proposal.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a document that exists about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is in the hands of someone named...
[SPEAKER_07]: Joe Corrale on Atariage and that's it that's Omega Race it's vector-tastic it is I'm trying to remember if I ever actually played this game because it does look super familiar I know I played this at some point but I'm like was it an actual arcade version or where I don't know
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, DarkTetsu just said what I was just thinking.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you imagine an updated multiplayer version of this sort of in the style of, say, Tempest 2000?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh, that's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, great classic.
[SPEAKER_05]: And SSU100 Matt adds, apparently there was a sight-down version in the arcade that was rare.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But this game is math.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, definitely a classic pick there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank you, DarkSakura, for that pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to get to some other headlines right now in a segment called Rapid Fire News.
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk about some other things going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so starting things off, of course, we got some cool new games coming, homebrew games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Fallout Bakersfield, which is a Doom... I'm just imagining and it's making me laugh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that a prequel or a sequel to Fallout Buttonwillow?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just wondering.
[SPEAKER_02]: it is a non-commercial Doom 1993 total conversion built using GZ Doom and it's being worked on currently right now it's estimated to be out in 2027 but it looks pretty impressive so far definitely has Fallout 1 and 2 vibes which I think is supposed to be around the time period that takes place but yeah, Fallout Bakersfield look forward to that something exciting needs to happen there
[SPEAKER_02]: and then we got the announcement of and I knew we knew it was coming but they finally showed off the set now and you can pre-order it but the Lego Game Boy which is I think almost a one-to-one model it's gonna retail for $60 and
[SPEAKER_02]: and it basically comes with some mock cartridges for Zelda and Super Mario Land and it also has lenticular little displays that you can slide in there but it looks really cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's coming out October 1st.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it's actual size and actually not super expensive so that's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 60 bucks, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really not.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kusama, The Awakening, Orion the Orange
[SPEAKER_05]: Nightlings, 1slash, Ito There's Blindsided Labs Some of these are actually both Mac PC and some of them are available for Steam Deck Some of the other games on the list is Blood Quest from Hell
[SPEAKER_05]: Sinkers Space Ace but it is not the Space Ace this is a different game called Space Ace a 2D down top shooter it's a game called Hold Me Still where you're trying to investigate your friend's disappearance Tiris, Digging Dogs which looks really cute, Flush Fall which is a toilet battle royale Cube One versus Cube Two Track Racing, The Holy Rosary, Zombie Murder 3
[SPEAKER_05]: Dreamlocked SRA
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a few more on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bling, Fortune Memories, Enflamed, Realm Runner.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Population Must Grow, which is a city builder.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, that sounds like something up your alley.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a game called A Pig Game, a Pee Wee premiere, and you play as a ceramic pig looking for toothpicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Simple Zombie Survival, which looks like a PS1 game.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Going to updates to the Nintendo Music app.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo Music got a pretty big drop of songs this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's 26 new games from the NES and Famicom era.
[SPEAKER_07]: I won't name them all, but essentially it's all of the black box release titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, things from like Clue Clue Land, Excitebike, Ice Climber, you know, sort of that initial launch era of games released.
[SPEAKER_07]: Famicom, Mahjong, Gomoku, Narabe, Renju Devil World
[SPEAKER_07]: and turning them into 10-hour loops, which is something you can do in the Nintendo Music app.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want to go slowly crazy by listening to the Clu Clu Land background music over and over and over and over again while you work, you can do that thanks to your Nintendo Music app.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, now let's check out some release dates of some games coming out all these years later after the Famicom's release.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's start in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: with release dates, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a game called One-Eyed Liko that is coming out on PC.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's see, Achilles Survivor coming out of early access on PC, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Tales of the Shire, Lord of the Rings game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: on the Nintendo Switch 2, Earthian on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got, let's see, Haikyuu Fly High on iOS and Android, Harvest Moon, The Lost Valley, and Harvest Moon Skytree Village on Nintendo Switch, Mashina on PC,
[SPEAKER_02]: We've got Ninja Gaiden Ragebound on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series Noctuary on Nintendo Switch and PlayStation 5 Spy Drops on PC and Nintendo Switch Time Flies on PC, Mac, Nintendo Switch, and PlayStation 5
[SPEAKER_02]: and let's see, WanderStars on PC and Nintendo Switch.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, traveling to Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty busy week on the Nintendo Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: On July 31st, we have Steel Empire Chronicles, Cotton Reboot, High Tension.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know Jamie's going to be there for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: In a regular and a limited edition coming out on the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mononoke Chigiri, also coming out in a regular and a special edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Halolive, Holo's Hanafuda, also in a regular and special edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Furukai 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I was just saying, Hanahura game sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Furukai 5 is also out in a regular and limited edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ys X, Proud Nordics, is also out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: But heads up, it's on a game key cart.
[SPEAKER_07]: uh Noctuary is also out in Japan on the 31st of July and then we have Kirameki and Nurse Diary Mina Wo Sukeru Tenshi no Ishigo uh is out as well on the 31st of July uh we have oh Japanese Rail Sim fuck yeah Journey to Kyoto oh that's a price reduction that's good I wish that was the name what oh fuck you Journey to Kyoto fuck yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: That should be the title.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would get more attention, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: And it doesn't end there, because on the 1st of August, we have Demon Slayer, Kimetsu no Yaiba, Hinokami Kapitan 2 coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's everywhere, because that is in like four different editions in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that is also something to look forward to on the 1st of August.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all the Switch 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looking at the PlayStation 5, Cotton Reboot is also on PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_07]: Furukai 5, regular and limited edition, Ys VIII and IX, also getting looks like re-released in anticipation of X. Noctuary, also out on the PlayStation 5, that Demon Slayer game I mentioned.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, busy week in Japan, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remari says Journey to Kyoto got delisted because Dispatch is a fucking disgrace to game localization.
[SPEAKER_07]: They took people's limited print pre-order money and ran.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds like drama.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, maybe we do need the release of the... Yeah, fuck yeah, Train Sim!
[SPEAKER_07]: But see, then payment processors wouldn't want to let people buy my game, so what can I do?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's go to the UK, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_05]: Madomonogatari, Thea and the Wondrous Academy for PlayStation and Switch, on the 30th, Terminal Brigade, T-E-R-M-I-N-U-L-L, Earthian for Switch PlayStation Xboxes, on the 31st, Gold Gold Adventure Gold for PC, Atomic Owl for PC, Hell Galaxy for PC, and Hungry Meme, M-E-E-M.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, Nine Years of Shadows for PlayStation and Xbox Ninja Gaiden, Ragebound for PlayStation, Xbox, Switch, and PC Alright Well, just one more quick update What about Madoka Magica for PS5?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't think I said that Or was it the Madomonogatari?
[SPEAKER_01]: Sorry, Ranma asked.
[SPEAKER_01]: I should have said something.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we'll look it up later.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, we'll go to you for one more story before we go to Listener Roundtable.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so we have news now that apparently Station Eleven, their showrunner, is going to be leading the upcoming live-action series based on Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the director of Fallout, because Fallout's done so well for itself, it's already garnered a second and now third season.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now they're like, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Fallout worked out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's do Wolfenstein.
[SPEAKER_02]: And so now that's going to be a thing that's being worked on as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we'll have to see how this turns out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fallout was great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't wait for the season two.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's later this year, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, lots of stuff happening on the TV front.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to say something real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Madomodogatari, I should have known because it's the game that PioPio was based off of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and I'm a silly bean.
[SPEAKER_05]: I should have remembered that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, don't let us get four of you in a row or you'll disappear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been a hot minute since I played some Puyo Puyo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should play it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they have the Puyo Puyo in Tetris 2 on Switch 2 because that was very controversial because it's not a free upgrade.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I didn't own it on Switch 1, so, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: You realize that right now I am literally looking at a Super Famicom copy of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Curbys Avalanche
[SPEAKER_07]: I do love that game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what Puyo Da was, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was the dancing music game that came out on Dreamcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought it was cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wispy Woods.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was how they said it in Kirby's Avalanche.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how they said it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wispy Woods.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get to the Lister Roundtable and invite you to do your Kirby impressions here on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to call us, you sure can on our Discord, vognetwork.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, new feature on the VOG Network Discord server, we now have one of them cute little tags you can have by your name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby says Rob's boost goes towards cleaner voice chat rooms.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: The original two went to having us as actual.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this whole little getup is a little bit cleaner and has better audio thanks to... I haven't seen a single cobweb.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the one thing I do keep clean, unlike the mailbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of which, do we have an email this week?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't see any, but okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Participate at OrangeSongsRadio.com if you wish to throw some things at Jamie to read in a future week.
[SPEAKER_07]: or if you want to keep sending me promo codes some of y'all are so nice and send me promo codes keep it up keep up the yes keep up the good work send Rob promo codes I'm very interested in free shit in Pokemon Go if you get any codes for that or you know any any good game I'll probably take them I appreciate it
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, how about any, oh yeah, S. Jonah Matt says, don't throw any actual things at Jamie unless they are tacos.
[SPEAKER_07]: And even then I would recommend a soft shell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or a Garris Vicarian body pillow.
[SPEAKER_07]: What, you know, one of my friends had a birthday this last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might have been the same birthday as the Bobby Blackwolf show, actually, now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyway, one of my friends had a birthday this weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was texting me pictures today from the Mass Effect ride at Great America.
[SPEAKER_07]: He went to Great America for his birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to go!
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, I keep forgetting the Mass Effect ride exists, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you would have thought they would have closed it years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what caught my eye is that I was looking at the pictures and I was noticing that the host...
[SPEAKER_07]: Did not appear to be a guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's not... What's his name?
[SPEAKER_07]: The fanboy from Mass Effect that usually is the mascot on the ride.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, usually the person introduces themselves as Conrad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a joke to the games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I've never seen...
[SPEAKER_07]: A lady or theydy hosting the ride.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it does look like this picture is so far back.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now that I'm looking at it, they might have green skin.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm wondering... I'm wondering if it's just weird lighting.
[SPEAKER_05]: The sorry lady that turned green from the Dorian?
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if it's that.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was her name?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I asked.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who did she introduce herself as?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's not Conrad.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the first time I've seen...
[SPEAKER_07]: A different gender up front.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was like, what did he couldn't remember?
[SPEAKER_05]: Shiala.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was her name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I wonder.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if that's like the the other character they can have.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, very random, but just a reminder to those, if you go through the Bay Area, you have maybe, I don't know, they're saying, they're threatening like two years left to go check out that ride before they close Great America forever and turn it into condos because billionaires are terrible people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want a taco now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except for Dolly Parton, who might not actually be a billionaire.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is Dolly Parton a billionaire?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure, but I mean... She's excluded.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's some ethical people out there, but she also does a lot of good with her money.
[SPEAKER_07]: When the billionaires... She's just a billionaire with karma.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a few other folks out there who use their money for good.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be fair, Bill Gates does a lot of good stuff with his money.
[SPEAKER_07]: More than most.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's on Trey Parker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, $500 million.
[SPEAKER_05]: Still, that's probably because she's giving away a bunch of money.
[SPEAKER_07]: The funniest thing about that South Park was before that little AI thing was shown, and y'all know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: It said one of 50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of 50, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they renewed for 50 episodes, which makes me think they're gonna do this shit every single week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which...
[SPEAKER_07]: I never thought I would be sitting here going, South Park is really funny, but everything from the 90s is back, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, then people want to say, oh, well, South Park only wasn't funny because they were making fun of liberals.
[SPEAKER_07]: South Park has always made fun of everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just got to a point where it was like...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it was just so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: But now they're making fun of the Republican bros.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't like it anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're pushing an envelope that hasn't really been pushed in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: It needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm hoping for an aneurysm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't say who, I didn't say when, I didn't say anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just hoping for an aneurysm.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have a joke about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: He was pretty metal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Ozzy Osbourne, of course, Malcolm Jamal Warner passed away.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I said, you know, these death things, they usually come in threes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think for a minute there, we were all thinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said, no, I don't have to say the name.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have to say anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, the room's laughing, giggle, giggle, giggle.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I said, and then we all realized we need to be more specific because God took the wrong racist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I believe I ended that joke with, and if that joke is too soon for you, too bad, brother.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and DT also points out that the Ozzy concert with Black Sabbath raised a lot of money for charity, and yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It did, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to joke about Ozzy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think it's metal as fuck that the first thing Ozzy does when he dies is murder Hulk Hogan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, this is so metal.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go back and say another thing, because I actually said the same thing about when my dad passed, is that it's all something that he brought on himself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, for my dad, it was lots and lots of drugs and alcohol when he was younger, and probably for Hogan, it was very similar, compounded with roids.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know?
[SPEAKER_05]: Still taking them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rough week to have done cocaine in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rough week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, yep, yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to ask if we had any last minute stories, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, we do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sony is hiring a new role, which is the Senior Director of Multi-Platform and Account Management.
[SPEAKER_02]: What does that job do, you may ask?
[SPEAKER_02]: They specifically say that it will play a critical leadership role in shaping and executing the global commercial strategy for PlayStation Studios software titles across all digital platforms beyond PlayStation hardware, including Steam, Epic Game Store, Xbox, Nintendo, and mobile.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, the games are not going to be platform specific anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the world's coming to an end.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, obviously they're going to try doing that and pivot that way because they can make more money.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, too bad, fanboys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anything else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, if you enjoyed the game that had behind me during this live stream, which is Boltgun, I have a free key for you because unfortunately they
[SPEAKER_02]: You pick it up and then all of a sudden it becomes part of a bundle that you get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free key.
[SPEAKER_07]: Free Steam key for Boltgun.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a great game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that looks fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, holler out in chat if you're the one to redeem it so we know it got redeemed.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you want more instant freebies like that, check out live as we broadcast Sunday nights, 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, with that, I think we're going to move to wrap it up for the night.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to go around and get final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, I want to thank you for listening to Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for checking out our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice, but we need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: So tell a friend or two about the show, because we are the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you liked what you heard, a nice five-star review on a site like Apple Podcasts, YouTube, Spotify, wherever it is you found this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: It goes an awful long way, and we really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: With that, we'll get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, we'll go to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you're streaming tonight, yes?
[SPEAKER_05]: I am, I am, and I'm trying to get my stupid avatar hands to make a heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll just do this one instead.
[SPEAKER_05]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, at any rate... Congrats, OrangeRite, got the code.
[SPEAKER_07]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to be playing Mass Effect 2, and I've got some announcements to make, so, you know, stick around.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: But I am going to be working out when I can actually throw in another ballet class and still keep my stream schedule.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will see you next time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have fun, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye-bye.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, that takes us to you then.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if you didn't get a key, it is half off right now on Steam as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, just letting you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can pick it up for $10.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: My final thought is, hopefully I can get to finishing my data pack this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been saying that every week.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been taking a very long time, but it is a very complex thing that I'm doing for the first time.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that'll be... Yeah, it's going to be tricky.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I'm looking forward to getting that done.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make good content.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is Alan is going to be out of town for like four days for work.
[SPEAKER_07]: So good thing Oreo likes to cuddle.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love my cats.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's going to do it for another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you so much.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be back next week to do it all over again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until then, good night.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is a production of OLR Studios.
[SPEAKER_10]: To join us for our live show, tune in to vognetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern.
[SPEAKER_10]: The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio nor VOG Network, but you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_10]: See you next week.