[SPEAKER_06]: Quote, an advocacy group made up of AAA publishers.
[SPEAKER_06]: In addition, many titles are designed from the ground up to be online only.
[SPEAKER_06]: These proposals would curtail developer choice by making these video games prohibitively expensive to create.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm pretty sure games have only gotten more expensive since the era of GameSpy, and taking on 100% of the server costs makes it cost more than the alternative, not less.
[SPEAKER_06]: This intro has not been brought to you by a Mind's Eye Saboteur.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's time for your hosts, Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers, and Loki to tell you more about this initiative and the rest of the week's gaming news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting right now on the show, where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hello, my friends out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is Orange Lounge Radio, and we are live once again tonight with episode number 1053 for tonight, July the 6th of 2025.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't believe we're already in July.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think as I saw in a post the other day that was very hateful, we are now closer to 2050.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I think okay I guess so yeah cool I mean I'm hoping I can go kind of we sort of blip didn't blip it on the radar I think so right now it is what it is yeah I gotcha I gotcha uh all right well we'll go say hello uh next off to the one and only Techmaster Loki hello hi Loki how are you
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, apparently I have a splinter in my finger.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even know where it came from.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've touched no wood at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: The closest thing to wood was I picked up my... Can't say the same, but I'm bummed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that better not be splintering.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm playing Fantasy Life and I'm working on crafting.
[SPEAKER_03]: What on earth are you talking about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was referring to my playthrough of Fantasy Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, well, I hope I'm sorry to hear you got a splinter.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just blame it on the cat.
[SPEAKER_03]: When in doubt, blame it on the cat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get it out?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's super tiny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like one of those ones that doesn't hurt, but occasionally you'll brush it, and then you feel that it's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like it's painful, it's just like it's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what it tends to be a lot of the times?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not a splinter, it ends up being a beard hair that gets jammed into my...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why you trim.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why you trim the murder mittens.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're going to need to get one of those freaking slings where they can't do anything until they get you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because that's the only way we're going to be able to train them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or the vet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you want to come?
[SPEAKER_03]: May the odds be ever in your favor.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will show you how to two-person cut the death mittens.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd be curious to see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do mittens on my own.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Midna probably cooperates a little more than ours.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, she doesn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's a hissy little bitch, and she bats her paws around, and she doesn't try to eat my arm, bite me, but she'll snap.
[SPEAKER_03]: What I'm curious about besides cat grooming tips is Loki has a video game playing behind him tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because we do tape live, of course, every Sunday night at the Voice of Geeks Network at 9 o'clock Eastern, 6 o'clock Pacific.
[SPEAKER_03]: Twitch.tv slash VOG Network right after the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except Bobby Blackwolf's not on tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is already out at Summer Games Done Quick, which we'll bring up again later in the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if you...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty Warzone, clearly
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the Beavis and Butthead Super Nintendo or Genesis?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Super Nintendo because I just saw it do the pixelation effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: I maybe rented this game once.
[SPEAKER_03]: I do not remember it.
[SPEAKER_03]: What brought this game to mind tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: Call of Duty Warzone Beavis and Butthead
[SPEAKER_07]: Skydance
[SPEAKER_03]: I just know they've been talking about that stuff but I don't know I can't follow the drama in my own life let alone the South Park creators over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network we do tape live of course on Sunday nights and Ranmari in chat bringing up an old reference saying Super Metroid greater than and then cut off there with Chrono Trigger and I hope you all know by now the real answer is
[SPEAKER_03]: There's room in my heart for both.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there's this long-running, I don't even know if I'd call it an in-joke because jokes are funny, but that Super Metroid is better than Chrono Trigger or vice versa.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bobby strongly believes the other.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can just call it a meme by now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's a meme.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I guess a meme is a good way to put it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I do find the humor in the fact that Bobby Blackwolf is hosting the Super Metroid speed run because in that argument, he would always say, no, Chrono Trigger is the best Super Nintendo game ever made.
[SPEAKER_03]: I always said Super Metroid.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I do find it funny that with all that back and forth, now he gets to do the Super Metroid run and has to be the hype guy for that run.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there is, you know, I'm enjoying this even sitting at home.
[SPEAKER_03]: Summer Games done quick so far.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rinmari also says in chat, clearly we need a ROM hack that mashes both games up.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that could totally be a thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do those randomizers.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was playing that one once upon a time that was Metroid and The Legend of Zelda, the original, where you would go into a dungeon in Zelda and you'd turn up in Metroid and then you'd go down an elevator in Metroid and now you're back in Zelda.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a cool concept, but my brain could not handle the randomy.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm making up a new word, the randomy in those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, let's get into our kickoff topic tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's a lot of interesting stuff going on with this petition around the Stop Killing Games movement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, are you up to speed on what's going on with this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a lot of drama involved with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Taking the drama out of it, there was another push by a lot of content creators and whatnot to get the petition over the line.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they've essentially had a petition with the UK and I think the EU regarding...
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess in their process with Parliament, you put a petition together, it reaches a million signers, that then they discuss it on the floor of Parliament or just bring up the topic essentially.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't mean it's going into law, it's more of like bringing it before them to discuss whether...
[SPEAKER_07]: They have to talk about the issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can't just avoid it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is the one that got associated with the crew, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ubisoft sunsetted the original crew, and this petition started going around for, you know, which is labeled Stop Killing Games, which is essentially to...
[SPEAKER_03]: hold companies liable to when they sell these games, they need to keep servers open or they need to allow people to have their own private servers.
[SPEAKER_03]: There needs to be a way for the game to be able to be able to be continued.
[SPEAKER_03]: Essentially, you shouldn't be buying a game you can only play for three years or in the case of some games, a lot less time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's that's at the root of all this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just in case you're not aware of what this petition is all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and so they did manage to get over the one million signature mark, but because there is a risk that people might be spoofing signatures on the internet, even though these these are government forms, though, so that is a crime.
[SPEAKER_03]: People signing things, see more butts on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you kidding?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, so... Or Cord Holio, I'm on theme, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're looking to get more signatures than what's required just to account for any that may be thrown out for not being correctly signed or invalid stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're working on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the EU one has crossed.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're still waiting for more signatures on the UK one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, yeah, and so there's been kind of back and forth with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that there was an advocacy group for major gaming studios that have basically pushed back on it, saying private servers are not always viable alternatives, options for players, the protections we put in place to secure players' data, remove illegal content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Combat Unsafe Community, blah, blah, blah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the UK's version of the ESA speaking.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're pushing back on it saying, basically what I'm hearing is, one, it's too hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: Two, it's too expensive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Three, it would cause game publishers to not do this anymore, which is kind of, I think, I thought what people wanted.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I, you know, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: As an advocacy group, they're going to respond.
[SPEAKER_07]: Live service game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you're the ones doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, I have a hard time believing that companies that make billions of dollars off of microtransactions can't afford to create an end of life plan for their game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, okay, so what's interesting is there is some sort of prominent streamer out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know these streamers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's Thor.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Pirate Software.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's big in the scene.
[SPEAKER_07]: He ex-Blizzard dev.
[SPEAKER_07]: His dad was the WoW guy from the South Park episode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, his dad was at Blizzard before Blizzard was Blizzard, so that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So he's been outspoken about it because he is a game developer, and he has said that for smaller indie studios...
[SPEAKER_07]: These requirements may be too much for them to handle, and so also pushing back on some of the more finer details.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, though, I mean, I'm trying to just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I was just thinking about this earlier over dinner, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, not only would stop, you know, protecting games and stuff like that and just layoffs and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like...
[SPEAKER_07]: more and more in the world like it's hard to find joy in things that we're doing like the world around us seems to be a chaotic mess that is just ever so crushing us down by it and then now we have like the game industry stuff where
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just treating people as disposable.
[SPEAKER_07]: Corporations treating people like nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of it down for the bottom line of their shareholders.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really their only concern about anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's the fun?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we find the fun again?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I would like.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I get it that there could be some challenges, but once again, I think that would be more something that's hammered out when they consider that as a law.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe there are some exceptions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's only for certain size companies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe it's for whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: typically though I find that a lot of folks see or understand a bit more that if a smaller game studio is unable to keep a title going it's a little more understandable versus like
[SPEAKER_07]: and EA that keeps releasing games year after year after year and then they shut the servers off after a few years because that fight night wasn't doing well or whatever the case may be.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's
[SPEAKER_07]: it's a little bit more understandable there but once again any smaller indie game studios I don't think necessarily are making these big always online games always online games anyways so like I don't know well and I see
[SPEAKER_03]: chat over at twitch.tv slash VOG Network.
[SPEAKER_03]: TigerClaw says, Pirate Software, he's earned the ire of the gaming community out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I did notice that, too, that this guy's been getting a lot of hate.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's also a bit rude as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and I don't know the guy, and if he has an unpopular opinion, then so be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But people on the internet need to calm the fuck down sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not everybody's going to agree with you all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like him.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't necessarily agree with his opinion.
[SPEAKER_07]: But once again, it's fine to have differing opinions.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think the how does this affect indie and small developers is a fair counterpoint.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a fair counterpoint.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think it changes my feelings that something has to be done, especially with large shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have an idea, but I'll let you finish, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have an idea, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, essentially though, they're blaming him for the stalling of the movement in the first place because he's such a prominent figure.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I get it, it's fine to have differing opinions.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's also, maybe people may not be on board with your opinion as much when you tell them to eat your entire ass when it comes to these things.
[SPEAKER_03]: You are going to get what you give, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's a little, you know, I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, and this would directly affect you if it were to go into place.
[SPEAKER_07]: But let's like realistically look at this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this going to happen?
[SPEAKER_07]: God, no, nothing good ever happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: So like, of course, it's never going to go through.
[SPEAKER_07]: But like, it's still nice to try to at least show these, you know, game companies that we're not going to put up with this crap.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Here's kind of where my brain is going with, like, how do we resolve this whole thing?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm going to fully admit, I'm speaking off the cuff here, and I haven't fully thought these out, and I'm sure y'all are ready to poke holes in this, but this is the direction my brain is kind of going in, because I'm thinking that what tends to happen is that you have these large companies, especially a Nintendo out there, that really likes to legally sort of
[SPEAKER_03]: claim the protections on games, even if they're games that are no longer sold, no longer out there or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And usually in Nintendo's case, at least, it happens to do with trademark because they don't want Mario to end up in porn and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they have to protect their trademark, I guess, on Mario and things like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I think that's kind of what the other bigger companies lean on.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I don't think smaller companies or indie companies as much are going to be
[SPEAKER_03]: leaning on intellectual property to sort of save themselves as a game doesn't do very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would think most Indian small studios are of the mindset that if, you know, a fan movement wants to try to save the game, then so be it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And to me, I think the answer sort of lies in the
[SPEAKER_03]: is that when you take these games offline that you have been selling, they should not really have the same types of enforceable sort of copyright and trademark protections on them that would allow people who legally own the game to do things like put the discs in a PC, decompile, do what they need to do to be able to run a private server on their own terms.
[SPEAKER_03]: They should be able to do that without those sorts of fear of repercussions.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of a similar concept to what I've said before on this program about, you know, Hollywood's been doing this a lot, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like Zaslav and Warner Brothers, you know, that Catwoman movie that, no, it wasn't Cat, no, it was Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Catwoman.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Batgirl.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was Batgirl.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, the Catwoman movie came out, it was terrible, it was Batgirl.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was supposed to come out and was...
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently not bad, but the whole thing ended up being a tax write-off.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then there was the Coyote and Acme, which I guess is now actually getting released.
[SPEAKER_03]: The same company that did the recent Porky Pay.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was in limbo for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they get to write that off still?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then they sold it?
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds like fraud.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I have always said if you are a company like that and you are writing off on your taxes, you are paying less taxes, you are not giving the public, you are saying we're not using this piece of media so essentially that piece of media ought to belong to the public.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is my long-handed way of saying Batgirl ought to be a public domain film.
[SPEAKER_03]: at this point because it was a tax write-off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Batgirl ought to be a public domain film.
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be the cause and the effect so it really causes companies like Warner Brothers to think about should we be doing these as tax write-offs because this will be something that is in the hands of the public domain.
[SPEAKER_07]: They shouldn't even be getting tax write-offs anyways for that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, in my opinion, why are we bailing out these billion-dollar companies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, because... I mean...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, E3VL says actors and those that work on it don't get the royalties though, but they're not getting it with the tax write-offs either.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not getting anything right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And again, I fully realize these are theories.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not the type to throw something out on a social media site and say that's all there is to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's nuance in everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are ideas that have to be baked out a little more, but I think the answer is rooted in that, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think the answer to this is somewhat rooted in that too.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what I mean is, let's say that you have a large studio that puts out a big game, a Concord, let's say.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you sign that, you digitally sign the EULA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whenever you connect to one of these games as a service game, anytime you do it, you're accepting some type of agreement, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're accepting an online agreement and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it basically says, you won't try to hack the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You won't try to do your own servers.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're only allowed to play on their servers only, da-da-da-da-da, and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: When the servers for a game get pulled, that online agreement should be null and void.
[SPEAKER_03]: That should be the first thing that happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because the corporation has not held up their end of the bargain.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that agreement that you agreed to should be null and void.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so that would include at that point that if you want to run your own pirate servers, decompile whatever needs to be done, I think that's what should happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I understand with this whole effort, they want...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and with Phantasy Star Online Blue Burst when they when Sega shut it down and they shut down the servers they put out a tool so that your characters could be exported and they basically they didn't I don't think they put out the software correct me if I'm wrong Jamie because I don't remember I didn't follow the ins and outs of it I don't think they put out the software for people to run their own servers but they basically said if you run your own server we're gonna turn a blind eye to the whole thing we're not gonna look at it and they did you know some tools
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there was a character export tool.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was the main thing I remember.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to this day, there are still Blue Burst servers running on out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what else is out there?
[SPEAKER_03]: And this is funny because this ties into my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what I've been playing?
[SPEAKER_03]: On a GameCube emulator, I've been playing Phantasy Star Online Volume 1 and 2 because you can actually, in the config files, you route the broadband adapter to a different IP and there are PSO private servers for that as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can do that with my Dreamcast version.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, that's a really good question.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet there's documentation on those sites how to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet you could.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, it's probably something to do with setting up the DNS servers or something to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, TigerClaw points out in chat, Sega's the only company that doesn't mind modders and fan games based on their IPs.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm saying that Sega did kind of put a blueprint out there for, I think, what gamers are really looking for the companies to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you're folding, if you're throwing in the cards, then you should release some of those, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: And if they're not going to, I mean, I guess I can see where they shouldn't be compelled to or obligated to, especially if these companies end up laying off employees and stuff that would, you know, be putting that stuff out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think it should be open so that if people do that on their own means, there should be no ability for the company to have legal recourse against that.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I'm saying at the end of the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Basically, if a company shuts the game down, they have no legal recourse to go after people trying to protect their investments.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the long and the short of what I'm trying to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think... I'm trying to remember what...
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of the scenarios that they were proposing are like how it could be abused.
[SPEAKER_07]: Once again, though, like you're putting the cart before the horse as far as like trying to figure out how a system like this would be before the system's even in place.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know one thing the video game, you know, group in the UK said was that, oh, it would it would lead to like bullying, harassment and those types.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like that shit already happens in games.
[SPEAKER_07]: that kind of felt a little bit like reaching to me you know what I mean like they can't protect the integrity of the servers and things like that and it's like you're right you can't and I mean like okay so after it's offline and I get it so they'll be like oh well if someone gets bullied on like say uh
[SPEAKER_07]: on an Ubisoft game that's discontinued.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then it makes the game look bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying that makes our game look bad because now that headline runs on Fox News that says a six-year-old child was bullied playing the crew.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to do it anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's dumb to assume that people are so brain-dead that they're going to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, then fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't have it both ways then.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they're too brain dead to be able to realize that the game that's discontinued that they have to play through a private server is not the same game as when it was running, but also they are intelligent enough to be able to set up their game so they can connect to a private server to play said game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, you can't have it both ways.
[SPEAKER_07]: They can't be...
[SPEAKER_07]: Smart enough, but not also dumb.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it's silly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to say at the end of the day, I support this movement.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the reason why is because I think for years and years and years, the corporations have been setting the rules.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Ubisofts, the EAs, hell, the Square Enixes, the, you know, the Nintendos have been setting the rules because they put out these user agreements and you have to agree to it to play the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: And there's, that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You don't, you don't have a choice.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't get a say on what's in that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: To me, this is the people saying, all right, for years you have said this is what you want and you've set the rules.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: This is what we want.
[SPEAKER_03]: And these are our rules that you need to agree to.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why my youngest son agreed to all of those terms so it doesn't bind legally.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now that's outside the box thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: but yes, I think it's time for us to have the corporations sign some agreements quite honestly and if it means that they need to follow any of those agreements if it means they need to think twice before they decide a game needs to always be online, then so be it
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they should eat themselves and what I mean by that is because right now in the court system we have a battle between AI generators and the data, totally legal that they've trained their stuff off of and then we have
[SPEAKER_07]: These companies where they've clearly been inspired by and totally not stolen all of the data from.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you had, what was it, already legally, there was a court case that allowed physical books to be scanned in and used for training data completely 100% legally.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I can go to my library and
[SPEAKER_07]: Borrow all these books, scan them in for my training data, and just create AI off of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Totally legal.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's another thing that's going to keep coming to a head in courts.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I know there's some court cases that have already been decided, but I think that's a whole other issue.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it does all come down to copyright ownership issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, usage rights, all of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I feel like all of that was written in an era before the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's been struggling to catch up ever since.
[SPEAKER_03]: As Joe and Hunter Matt in chat says it at twitch.tv slash VOG Network, consumer protection is still trying to catch up to gaming, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: 100%.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot of other types of new media, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still trying to catch up with AI.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's still trying to catch up with streaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll get to a point where it's too much for people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gamers, especially gamers of long-running franchises, Madden, FIFA, essentially just get beaten down every year with the microtransactions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And some people are completely...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, well on that note, let's continue on because obviously we have some other big headlines we need to get to.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, we always like to start off in talking about our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we have been playing this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, DarkSakura's back, so I will start with DarkSakura and go, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you're good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Got some real life stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: All good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just the usual stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mass Effect, Dead by Daylight, trying to get through the event.
[SPEAKER_02]: Palia, that's about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, we'll go to you then.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been playing mainly Minecraft.
[SPEAKER_07]: As usual, I know it's shocking.
[SPEAKER_07]: We updated to 121.6 this week, so we have the happy gas now and just kind of messing with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been building a massive battle arena for our sleep game.
[SPEAKER_07]: that will be participating in here pretty soon so I've been just kind of designing and now gathering materials for that thing working on my mega game stuff as well to start the whole early design process part of that and then aside from that a tiny bit of Bellatro and yeah just looking at my Steam library it's like yeah I could play all these games I'll buy more but I'm not going to play them
[SPEAKER_07]: that's a problem I have a problem, I will admit I have the same problem but you know what though, I like it I like having that library because it does give me the option that I can go in there someday and play that stuff it's kind of like realistically, if I were to collect physical games I have no place to put that stuff I don't know anything about that of course you wouldn't
[SPEAKER_07]: but like yeah it's just not all over my kitchen and the offices and under pinball tables it's just like even my collection that I have I don't actually play them um
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know I like to support smaller game studios I like to purchase games that look interesting I get it I will eventually get to them at some point I can't say that about my whole library because there's like 1200 now someday when I give up Minecraft I'll dig into the Steam library but until then I'm going to consume more and how and how
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, before we get to my gaming week... Now with more sodium.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before we get to my gaming week, Jamie, let me know... Go ahead and do your gaming week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then for my gaming week, let me think.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been a lot of the same sorts of things.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm still playing Fantasy Life, still very addicted to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo 4 started a new season, so Season 9, which does this new twist with Nightmare Dungeons.
[SPEAKER_03]: Diablo IV Diablo VIII
[SPEAKER_03]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: D.A.B.O.
[SPEAKER_03]: 4
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, I know PSO2 is still a thing, and I tried to do PSO2, but I feel like PSO2 has like a content overload problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: But to be fair, I haven't visited it in a long time since it first came out on Xbox, and maybe it's a little better now.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I should try to check it out again just to make sure I give it a fair shot.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that was kind of the issue I had with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Compartmentalized, if that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, like PSO is really easy to kind of, I think something about maybe the simplification.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although I keep, I'm trying to always use the right stick on my controller, which didn't exist, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Like you always had to hit the L button to like reset your view.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm just having to get used to that again.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the thing where I'm like, oh yeah, I forgot that this was a thing on the old PSO.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, I love it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, SS200Matt says, gotta soup up the computer just to play Space Cadet Pinball on Windows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dude, that's what I feel like I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like brand new video card
[SPEAKER_03]: GameCube emulators.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, I could totally play too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, you should.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be a fun stream to do sometime.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have the means.
[SPEAKER_03]: Play some PSO.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: What else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that all for my gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, if there's something else, I can't think of it in the moment.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, okay, then with that, before we get to the news, Jamie, you said you need to cut out a little early tonight because you have some stuff going on IRL, which happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to fast forward a little bit and get to your segment because, you know, once a month, you don't just do a classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do a classic game that is going to go to the arcades or has gone to the arcades.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's roll the bump.
[SPEAKER_02]: Console first, arcade second.
[SPEAKER_00]: And now it's time to travel back to a simpler time where I'll dive into the vault and pull out a classic and tell you about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's time for the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, Jamie, what is the console to arcade game of this month?
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so I mean we know Guitar Hero, the franchise has been out for a while and then died and then there were hints of it coming back and I mean the first one was out in 2005 so it is more than a classic game but the one that I am talking about is the...
[SPEAKER_02]: After a number of expansions mined, Activision and Red Octane put in some work with a company called Basic Fun Inc.
[SPEAKER_02]: to do guitar... I said the wrong words.
[SPEAKER_02]: Activision and Konami...
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero Arcade
[SPEAKER_02]: but it reduced some of the features like the whammy bar, star power button you can only activate it by lifting the guitar so you have limited use there and practice modes but you could still download new songs for the cabinet from the internet
[SPEAKER_02]: and the game though did come under some scrutiny by the American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers, the ASCAP who thought that it qualified as the equivalent of public performances and that the game operators needed to pay royalties, additional fees and
[SPEAKER_02]: Alas, it was not meant to be Alas
[SPEAKER_03]: All asked.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is one of those games where you knew it had to come up eventually, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't love it in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, neither did I. But it's worth the mention.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, we...
[SPEAKER_02]: We did have a ton of Guitadora, and we had the Triumvirate, you remember?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, sure, but it was never going to catch on mainstream until they got... But they didn't do it in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: They tried to do Guitar Freaks in the U.S., remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, Rock Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did not...
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm talking about in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, they did.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_03]: They did do one version in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: But then, you know, there's that and then there's like these actual like, you know, guitar songs that everybody heard growing up, you know?
[SPEAKER_02]: As Ranmari points out, Round 1 USA just got the new Gitarra cabs and fancy new 3-screen deluxe cabinets in their U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: region.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, that is true, because the nice thing is that Round 1 has sort of brought back, or at least kind of opened the door, I guess, to...
[SPEAKER_03]: The Japanese games being imported, you know, legally, quote unquote, although it was like it was always a gray area.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, the thing that I wanted to go back to was that, you know, especially in bringing up Guitadora is that they were originally arcade that went to the home, you know, the home consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Guitar Hero came out for the home consoles as we tested in my living room at my old house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I wasn't there, but you guys were.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then to arcade after that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's sort of like it went full circle from there.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, the way things are, people want to play these things in their home and make a party out of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't necessarily want to go to an arcade where people try to change their baby's diaper on the keyboard mania table.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that story is still on YouTube, by the way, for some of our newer OLR fans.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think if you dig on the...
[SPEAKER_02]: Told the woman off?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Playing Guitar Hero at your house.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't there, but you and Loki were on one of the local news stations because didn't they bring the fucking guy from Red Octane to your house?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they made me hide all my Bimani stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You had to hide all your Konami stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just the Bimani stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that's so funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think we had a guy from here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, yeah, so it's out there on YouTube somewhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm almost positive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tiger Claw is probably looking for it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we had all this stuff in the corner of my living room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it's on our Orange Lounge Radio YouTube channel, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that one and the old KCRA clip of Dave Walker, who retired years ago, introducing the story of podcasting.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's the infamous, oh, it's so much fun, clip of you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still have our newspaper.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, the newspaper article too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember when we were famous?
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we're infamous.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did get the Guinness book.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess I can't complain because we did get the Guinness book last year, so I can't bitch too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even chat GPT recognizes it now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just going to say that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I guess that's... I never thought to ask, but it's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I will put the clip in chat.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you found it!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on our YouTube channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I knew it was on our YouTube somewhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have the original KCRA thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's my old TV!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, it's my chin!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just fast-forwarding through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, Matt, you look so young.
[SPEAKER_03]: How old was this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Now you're going to make me bring it up while we're live here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now I got to look at this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see my drum mania.
[SPEAKER_02]: It behind the TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was coming from work, that's why I had a work shirt on.
[SPEAKER_01]: And my 2DX stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wasn't there because, oh yeah, that's the old Red Octane guy.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's... I wasn't able to go at all because I was working that night.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or that day.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is an old, old clip.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm so glad I had my surgery.
[SPEAKER_03]: The end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's enough of Walk Down Memory Lane.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, podcast.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just have to... It is on the Orange Nose Radio YouTube channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You just have to go way back.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sort by oldest.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just put DarkSakura, Loki, Guitar Hero, you'll find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not in it, so don't search me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just go to the Orange Lounge Radio YouTube channel.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's three buttons on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Click oldest.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll sort by oldest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was going to say, because all the actual podcast episodes are mixed in now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Be right.
[SPEAKER_03]: You sort oldest.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be there.
[SPEAKER_03]: How to internet one-on-one.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: We also have Dance Dance Revolution Wii on there.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know you have to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have a final thought for us?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ugh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, just... Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna eat this lovely muffin that Alan brought for me while Loki gets into our news story today.
[SPEAKER_03]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh!
[SPEAKER_03]: Muffin!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna go have a protein shake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, have fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, so Loki, we're gonna go over to you with... Oops, not that one, this one.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're gonna go over to you with the news for tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get to our top headline, which unfortunately is not something to consume a muffin to.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually really shitty news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it not time for muffins?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's time for depression and sadness.
[SPEAKER_03]: Depression muffin!
[SPEAKER_03]: Video game industry layoff muffin!
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it was confirmed that Microsoft was laying off about 9,000 jobs, 9,100 jobs if you want to be more ballpark about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is hitting a wide variety of their different studios.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a memo that they put out to staff, which...
[SPEAKER_07]: wasn't even directed towards staff it was directed towards shareholders which is just some bullshit right there which they made but I'm not even gonna read it because it's just just just imagine PR speak about how we need to make these cuts but also we're super you know we're doing really well we're doing so well this is the best time ever but we also have to make these cuts
[SPEAKER_07]: Because of reasons, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just, you know, how shareholders work.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there was a lot of cuts that was done at King, of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: They lost 200 employees, or roughly 10% of their workforce.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have closed down, cut off a lot of different studios as well, cancelled many projects.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's talk about some of those cancellations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perfect Dark reboot not coming out anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: That has been cancelled and they've also not only have they cancelled Perfect Dark but also the other rare project Everwild which has been in production for well
[SPEAKER_07]: A very long time, over 10 years at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that is also disappointing.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was some cuts at the Elder Scrolls Online Studios as well, at Bethesda Online, ZeniMax Online, that's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a new looter shooter game that they said was Blade Runner meets Destiny 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds just like Destiny 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: That also got cancelled as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, I mean, I wonder if it's because of some of this, you know,
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard there was some game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Zenimax was working on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was something that he liked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It basically said that it was a good game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why he canceled.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure it's because it was a good game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you remember the old Iwata quote, a bad game is bad forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: A good game is good forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Phil Spencer kills it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think that's how the Iwata Club went, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you know what games could possibly never be good, of course, would be a new John Romero game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, let's kill that as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there's another Romero game studio game that is not coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, they made a
[SPEAKER_07]: Statement about that as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently it was they said they were working on new FPS in Unreal 5 and three years later it was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's been in development for at least three years.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great.
[SPEAKER_07]: What else?
[SPEAKER_07]: So I know that this is all very shocking and you're probably thinking like god damn what the hell are they thinking?
[SPEAKER_07]: What are those C-suite people thinking?
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell are they doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, Phil Spencer wants you to know that despite the fact there's been all these massive layoffs, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not retiring anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So he'll be helping more of this bullshit for the near future as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So thank God for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't continue to defend the man after this and I truly really believe that if he is making losses this big, if the impact on the workforce is this large and this many projects are going, that is a lack of leadership and he should have been one of the ones that left.
[SPEAKER_03]: Period.
[SPEAKER_03]: Full stop.
[SPEAKER_03]: If this is a sign of misdirection, or these are games that should not have been made, he should be one to take the fall as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: He should be dismissed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry to say, but not sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought he was doing... I'm sitting here going... The parts that make no sense here, I thought Microsoft was in a place, Xbox, that was better than ever...
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Pass is doing Gangbusters recently with a lot of the games that are on it right now even King I'm surprised that there was layoffs there because Candy Crush is doing Gangbusters as well so like
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand that there are some redundancies post-mergers, but they already did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They already did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They've already claimed that one before.
[SPEAKER_03]: So now what are we talking about?
[SPEAKER_03]: And these are like canceled projects.
[SPEAKER_03]: These are games that apparently were fun that they don't want to put out at all for whatever, you know, whether it's market conditions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't fucking know why if a game is really fun, you don't put it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there was an investment they didn't feel they needed to take, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I'm disappointed, obviously, with all that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here's another fun one that I saw as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forza Motorsport is no more, following the cuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: That blew my mind, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why are all those people at Take-10 getting laid off?
[SPEAKER_03]: Forza Horizon is the reason to be an Xbox gamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's one of the best exclusive franchises they have.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're working on the Fable game, which I realize it's taken a long time to cook, and maybe that's the problem with a lot of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, keep in mind, folks, there is a difference between Forza Motorsport and Forza Horizon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Forza Motorsport was kind of that mainline Forza series that I think was up to seven games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Was seven the most recent release?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then I think what happened, Horizon... Or it was just Forza Motorsport.
[SPEAKER_07]: They didn't even have like a...
[SPEAKER_03]: But what happened along the way is that Horizon eclipsed it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, Horizon is the more... Because it's the more palpable one.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the one that you can pick up and run with.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the one with all of the accessibility features where all you have to do is fucking accelerate if that's what you need to do for the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, like, that's... Horizon is just the bigger franchise at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm still shocked... Right, and that's the big clarify with that, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: That the studios still open to support the Horizon side, but...
[SPEAKER_03]: Right, Jvmon in chat says Horizon is more casual friendly.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can take on the Mario Karts of the world.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would agree that Forza Motorsport, I mean, there's an audience for it, but the bang probably wasn't worth the buck there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But laying off that entire team, why wouldn't you shift a really good chunk of those resources into pumping more into Horizon?
[SPEAKER_03]: or putting out Horizon games more frequently or making them more robust or putting a little bit of that professionalism into Horizon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why would you not do that?
[SPEAKER_07]: So on top of all that, so they also canceled or they've laid off a lot of different developers also working on Call of Duty because God forbid there's like there's I don't even know how many studios are working on Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they did lay off a lot there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's across the entire
[SPEAKER_07]: you know, games division as is and I think a lot of it has to do with the focus on Microsoft not necessarily Xbox, but Microsoft spending I think they're going to be spending 80 billion dollars on AI development over the course of this entire year which now brings us to the other fuck you that's part of this as well so after all these people were laid off they got an email um
[SPEAKER_07]: for people that are going to Gamescom.
[SPEAKER_07]: They said, we're excited to be heading to Gamescom 2025.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, we'll be contending.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're offering an AI roundtable where you can provide us feedback on how you'd like to see us use AI tools and processes to make game development and publishing experience more efficient.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like the...
[SPEAKER_07]: The icing on the cake, or the shit cake that it is with the layoffs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like you're pushing all this generative AI stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nobody wants it, but you're going all in on it because you're trying to be the next Google of this tech space that is brand new.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just... This AI thing drives me bonkers because these companies are about to learn the hard way.
[SPEAKER_03]: You get what you pay for with this AI stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't... AI can make your current employees better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It can't replace your current employees.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a lesson that these companies are going to learn in an explosively negative way, which unfortunately, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They need to learn the lesson in a negative way.
[SPEAKER_03]: People that have been advocating for this on the inside, the CEOs, the board, the upper managers, need to be held accountable when this all goes to shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: They won't be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: it's because they're they're making money for their shareholders and unfortunately the lesson won't be learned by them it'll be learned by employees that they lay off and then oh hey this this was absolute dog shit let's close this studio now because we used AI tools and no one's ever going to learn the lesson it's just going to be
[SPEAKER_07]: As consumers, you just have to be vigilant and, once again, not pre-ordering your games so that you can be aware of what AI nonsense is being put into your games because they certainly like to seem to slip it in without anybody knowing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is so weird because, you know, when you think that AI is so good and everybody loves it that, you know, you'd be proud to announce that, like, AI is in shit because, God forbid, like, all the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Appliance manufacturers and everything else I don't want AI in are so proud to announce that AI is part of my refrigerator or some bullshit like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're purposely hiding it because it's sloppy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cheap bullshit that they're trying to pass off as actual artistic work.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's just going to be slop.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to get slop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Slop in, slop out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not going to be good.
[SPEAKER_07]: but just they have to learn that lesson and well like I said unfortunately it's not them learning the lesson the C-suite people no one's going to hold them to account it's going to be you know maybe the shareholders will if they don't make as much money but I mean they'll fire more people I guess
[SPEAKER_03]: This is the world we live in.
[SPEAKER_03]: That talks about a LinkedIn, which I believe is another Microsoft property, by the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Matt Turnbull, who is an executive producer at Xbox Game Studios, made a post on LinkedIn basically saying, These are really challenging times, and if you're navigating a layoff or quietly preparing for one, you're not alone and don't have to go it alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been experimenting with ways to use LLM AI tools to help reduce the emotional and cognitive load that comes with job loss.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you could do career planning prompts, resume and LinkedIn help.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, here's my current resume.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give me three tailored versions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Networking and outreach, emotional clarity and confidence.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm struggling with imposter syndrome after being laid off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can you help me reframe this experience in a way that reminds me what I'm good at?
[SPEAKER_03]: But no, here's the kicker, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then at the end of his LinkedIn post, he says, no AI tool is a replacement for your voice or your lived experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: See, this is the only context I feel out of all of this and all of everything that we've talked about so far to which the proper response is to eat my entire ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Plus, can we just talk about LinkedIn in general?
[SPEAKER_07]: LinkedIn is a bunch of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember my company wanted me to set up a LinkedIn page for God knows what reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: They wanted something.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like, you have to be on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so important.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll network.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, I...
[SPEAKER_03]: so it is such a useless piece of shit if you just want to see people gassing themselves up that they're the smartest people on the fucking planet look no further than LinkedIn oh my god now look I there's things I like about LinkedIn my last two jobs I have found through LinkedIn so I will say something nice about LinkedIn I mean that that's that's the job search side of the the coin if you look at the social feed and the things that people post on there Jesus Christ
[SPEAKER_07]: it's unreal but it's real but it's unreal anyway and not unreal because that's that's a game engine that's right that's a game engine that's way better than LinkedIn
[SPEAKER_07]: But hey, that's okay, because LinkedIn, you're going to find lots of AI there, lots of prompts and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure that there's probably a course on how to just have generative AI just post a bunch of bullshit to your page, and you'll become super popular then.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'll make it as a CEO eventually, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: that's that have a have co-pilot replace Phil Spencer then if AI is so fucking good have it run your have it make your decisions at your company then if it's so well no no no we we can't be replaced we are too too smart for that yeah it's just it's dumb
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if there is some good news to be had on the Xbox front this week, Helldivers 2, which was a big hit on the PlayStation 5, is coming to Xbox and all the Microsoft platforms this August because the exclusive window has basically is closing.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, the Sony published Helldivers 2 will no longer be exclusive as of August.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, Arrowhead Game Studios, Johan
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope I said that right.
[SPEAKER_03]: The chief creative officer said during a live stream, you've asked for more dudes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're sending more dudes.
[SPEAKER_03]: For one and a half years, you've been fighting the enemies of democracy.
[SPEAKER_03]: And one of the requests that you've always had is for us to send more dudes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the best way for us to be able to do that is to bring another platform into the fight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Xbox Series X and S will get the game August 26, $40.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not trying to charge $70 for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was always a lower price.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's always been $40.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is probably another reason why it's doing so well.
[SPEAKER_03]: so there you go 18 months after launch uh more content to catch up on so good luck to the Xbox players um I don't know if there's a lot of people that are gonna be jumping in but I don't I mean it is a really good game I've heard nothing but really good things about it so I'm sure um I'm sure it's a good time so for those that are kind of confined to their gaming on Xbox now you have a chance to join in so good luck all right Loki what do you have uh talk about like
[SPEAKER_07]: The wrong timeline, but okay, let's talk about how...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, you know, you're playing Fortnite and stuff, and you're like, wow, I really want those skins, but they're just ridiculously expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're charging $50.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I should finance this, said nobody ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's what they're planning on doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, a payment provider, Affirm, has said they partnered with Xsolla to allow people to pay off in-game purchases of $50 or more via payment plans.
[SPEAKER_07]: It goes without saying, and I shouldn't have to tell anybody, and I'm sure everybody is an adult here and understands, there is no reason whatsoever that you should purchase an in-game purchase on a payment plan.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is clearly a scam.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is clearly predatory in the sense that they're trying to get pre-owned people that have no financial responsibility.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that they just, you know, impulsively buy, buy, buy, buy, buy, buy, buy And then they won't be able to make their payments They charge them the late fees, so on and so forth And it's only going to get worse, Loki With everything going on in the world You have a pair of eyes and ears You see what's going on in the news And you know that there's people that are going to be losing a lot And this type of predatory shit is only going to get worse I really need people And again, I think you are right I think most of the people...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: and I think y'all know better than you don't need a fucking $40 skin in Fortnite you don't need the Ariana Grande skin that bad to finance it
[SPEAKER_03]: because the amount that you end up paying but this goes to things like and this is the reality of the world and there's there are a lot of people out there that are financing DoorDash meals because there's so much in advertising and things like that that encourage it and I am so worried that this shit is only going to get worse and these types of companies are only going to get more predatory because when somebody is fucking hungry and it's push at tap
[SPEAKER_03]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm really frightened to see what it does to people.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to have a chat button that says click to taco a representative.
[SPEAKER_03]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're leaving.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, just don't participate with this at all, I would say.
[SPEAKER_07]: In-game purchases shouldn't be that expensive in the first place, like any of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before you push the button to finance these skins, why don't you work on hacking the server to get them for free?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and I should be noted that it's not necessarily in Fortnite.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just Xsolla has partnered with Epic Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Xsolla, I think, is the payment processor, but they also offer these services separately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which means the Epic Games store will be part of this as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's not tied into that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: You shouldn't be financing...
[SPEAKER_07]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're looking to finance a brand new game or something like that, just wait for it to go on sale.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can wait to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, with the DoorDash stuff, assuming that you're able to do it,
[SPEAKER_07]: like and and you're you're you'll have the mobility to be able to leave your house and do all that stuff it's a lot cheaper just to go pick it up yourself like i get it it's the convenience but they're charging you a fee on top of a fee on charge on top of raising the prices on all the items like it's just just do it yourself
[SPEAKER_03]: and then put the $10 that would have cost you a DoorDash in some type of account that has dividends.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I know I'm talking like a, you know, but like the reality is, people, you got to save whatever you can, especially in these times, you know, and I know it's hard, but it's just, it's crazy out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rimari in chat says, I have a friend who's disabled.
[SPEAKER_03]: He's dependent on delivery apps to get food.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's different.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's very different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's completely different and completely understandable.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would also wonder what type of social and public services, well, used to be available a year ago, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who fucking knows now in 2025?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully they may have some friends willing to help out once in a while or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully there are some other options to mix in with that, but that is a completely different scenario.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and with that, I would say also, too, like sometimes it may not be like, say you want to get pizza delivered or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't go through DoorDash to get that pizza delivered.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go through the actual pizza company's website.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some of them you don't have a choice anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of them you don't have a choice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of them they just use that as their delivery option.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then that's, I mean, obviously that's going to be your only option.
[SPEAKER_07]: But a lot of them don't do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of them have their own drivers.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so if you pay that way, it's going to be significantly cheaper than it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You just have to do your research, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to do your due diligence to make sure that you're not getting ripped off.
[SPEAKER_03]: And just so chat understands, I'm not saying never use DoorDash.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a luxury.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I DoorDash food today, so I'll be like... Treat it like a luxury.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: But recognize what you're really paying for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Recognize that, okay, I'm spending $20 to...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is a whole other conversation.
[SPEAKER_03]: We were just talking about this the other day because we were  I went out for Indian food with some friends.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ironically, some friends that play Ingress.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's all some video gaming stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: I went out and met some friends for Indian food and we were kind of mentioning like, oh, the Indian food place, we see so many DoorDash people.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like we were the only people in the restaurant but we saw so many DoorDash and those people going in and out, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's that whole like
[SPEAKER_03]: But now you have restaurants like Red Lobster, TGI Fridays, they're all going under.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, it's like, why?
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, people, I think people are failing to see the reason is people are door dashing better food now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're door dashing more local, smaller cuisines, like Chinese food, Mexican food, Indian food, you name it, your favorite, you know, more mom and pop smaller store cuisine that like, who sits there and goes, I'm going to door dash TGI Fridays.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you want TGI Friday's mozzarella stick, they sell them in a bag in the freezer section at the store.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's why those types of places are going under because nobody really craves the food.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hooters, that's another great example.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who door dashed Hooters?
[SPEAKER_03]: Did anybody ever door dash Hooters?
[SPEAKER_03]: Unless it was a meme?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen it on DoorDash.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, then that's a meme.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a fucking meme.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen it on DoorDash.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would never eat their food because I've had their food many times and I don't like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I don't know why I got on that tangent.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was in Rancho, and now it's a better chicken place.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma says, Rob, I would if I had one nearby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, they had a different place.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had a place called Twin Peaks, which sadly has nothing to do with the David Lynchian masterpiece and everything to do with Twin Peaks on a lady's chest, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's that sort of thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: That restaurant is gone now, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I found out recently that we have a local bikini coffee shop
[SPEAKER_07]: Over Here By, like in Carmichael.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's right next to a place, a Japanese sushi restaurant that my wife goes to all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I know we were leaving there one day, I'm like, wait, that looks like one of those bikini restaurant things, or like, because the name, it's like, you know, a double entendre name, you know, something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Baristas in bikinis, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I guess we have the weather here to support something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So work, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're way on a tangent.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what else do you expect here at Orange Launch Radio?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's talk a little bit about Amazon and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: You probably noticed you were not able to get a Switch 2 through Amazon, and it was a pretty glaring omission of the different retailers that you could pick up a Switch from.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Bloomberg has run a report this week that has talked about the recent issues between the two companies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently, Nintendo of America was not happy that third-party sellers on Amazon were selling video games for lower prices than what Nintendo had advertised.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what they would do, they would buy the games in bulk from Southeast Asia, export them to the United States, and then turn them around cheaper than the recommended retail price.
[SPEAKER_03]: Honestly?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Smart Strategy, I guess, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: But Amazon did not stop this from happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Nintendo said, fuck you, Amazon.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm paraphrasing, but essentially that's what happened.
[SPEAKER_03]: Both companies are denying what Bloomberg has said, by the way, which I think is interesting as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: In a quote here, Amazon tried to assuage Nintendo by offering to attach labels to products that guarantee they're authentic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amazon uses the technique to assure shoppers products aren't counterfeits and to help track merchandise.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the offer wasn't sufficient, the person said, and Nintendo ultimately opted to pull its products from Amazon in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_03]: My how times have changed.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're talking about an Amazon seal of quality.
[SPEAKER_03]: on a Nintendo product.
[SPEAKER_07]: How times have changed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's just pause for a second and understand the irony of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Amazon seal of quality on a Nintendo product.
[SPEAKER_07]: With all the Chinese knockoff fake stuff that's in their marketplace.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or Amazon Basic where they rip off other people by stealing their designs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: XBOX Game Pass
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: Game Pass Game Pass Game Pass
[SPEAKER_03]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, well, then they added five games that did nothing to advertise or bring eyesight to that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I posted on Blue Sky about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: The AntStream account, nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Xbox account, nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, hello, do you want these products to succeed or no?
No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yeah, it could be interesting to see what the effect is that this has on Game Pass because now there's not going to be an Everwild, there's not going to be a Perfect Dark, there's not going to be an MMO from Zenimax.
[SPEAKER_03]: It'll be interesting to see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Speaking of things that layoffs have unfortunately impacted, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, let's talk about another game that's getting cancelled as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Outriders 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently it was cancelled over issues with Square Enix.
[SPEAKER_07]: People Can Fly was working on a game called Codename Gemini, which has of course now been suspended.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they reported that the sequel was nearly finished.
[SPEAKER_07]: Before Square Enix decided to... I don't know what they're disputing over.
[SPEAKER_07]: But basically, yeah, it's not coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So sorry, no Outriders 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I know maybe because the first game didn't do as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says it didn't turn a profit within its first year.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought there were quite a few people playing that game at first.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess it didn't sustain itself or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, DJ Ranma S says Outriders was a fun game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like a third person Borderlands.
[SPEAKER_03]: I even played Outriders in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was on Game Pass, so it was easy to, you know, kind of get into.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it's kind of a bummer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anthem will officially shut down January 12, 2026
[SPEAKER_03]: EA has made it very clear, once the servers go offline, the game will no longer be playable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anthem is being delisted from EA Play as of August 15th, 2025.
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe none of the money in-game can be spent, like you can't buy stuff for money in-game and all that stuff anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's on its way out, which probably isn't surprising.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know, there are...
[SPEAKER_03]: Still a handful of people that are playing that, I'm sure, that are devastated by this news.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so I don't mean to like shit on the fans of this game, but this is exactly to bring it full circle why people want to be able to run their own Anthem servers then, or, you know, pay to have, you know, something going on in the cloud or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jvmon in chat says, Anthem was still around?
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it closed down like two years ago.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I did too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But just because it's, you know, somebody out there still playing it, obviously.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it is, it is...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sad in that regard to see it go, but to me, Anthem is a symbol of every bad decision that Bioware has made under EA's control in the last few years, so I'm not exactly sorry to see it go, but that doesn't mean that people shouldn't still be able to play it if they don't want to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Questbuster says that content support ended, but they still kept the game alive, and says it was fun being a magic-wielding Iron Man.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Since we already did our classic game of the week, we're going to skip on ahead to rapid fire news and talk about some other headlines going on a little quickly here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, we'll go to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So Hades 2, they've got... Basically, it's last patch before launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so I guess they're talking about coming out early access because I was like reading that.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been in early access for a while now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's been in early access for a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I was like before how patch before launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, so basically it's getting its last major update before I guess going to be version 1.0 at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't wait to see how it turns out, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't played Hades or Hades 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you're missing out.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's some good games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hades is good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played a little bit of Hades 2, but I'm kind of waiting for the library.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kind of waiting for Hades 2 to be done before I jump back in.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was I really enjoyed what I played.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, SNK has delisted a bunch of games from its Google Play Store.
[SPEAKER_07]: I forget that they have games on the Google Play Store because I don't really think about playing Metal Slug on my phone, but apparently they've delisted their ports of Blazing Star, Metal Slug, Metal Slug 2, Metal Slug X, Fail Fury Special, Garou Mark of the Wolves, King of Fighters 97, King of Fighters 98, and Samurai Shodown 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: um yeah so that sucks but I mean I'm guessing they've been on there for a long time
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, let's move on to talking about what's coming out for Arcade Archives Series 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a game, I must admit, I'm not super familiar with this game, but some of you out there probably know it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Super Dimension Fortress Macross 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: I certainly know Macross, but I don't remember this particular arcade game, but this is probably something that Jamie played.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's a schmucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Dimension Fortress.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it's Macross.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, it's,
[SPEAKER_07]: I just never played this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Macross is the full name.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I guess probably some of you in chat play this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It definitely looks a lot like kind of Gradius with the power-ups and stuff, but it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'd check this out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen... We're going to go on the tangent train now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen that... It's not new, but it's an emulator that's for the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like the old 3DS NES games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember how they had the 3D 3DS games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can we come back to that?
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, which allows the emulation of, I guess, some stronger systems because it's only available on certain platforms.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there is that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, of course, one other headline, and we already kind of referenced this earlier in the show, and that is the fact that, um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Summer Games Done Quick is underway.
[SPEAKER_03]: Summer Games Done Quick 2025 Raising Money for Doctors Without Borders running starting today on July 6th and running through the rest of the week through the 13th.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: If nothing else, check it out.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're raising money for charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: VOG Network's own Bobby Blackwolf will be there on Thursday and Saturday, helping out with reading some donations and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: But just remember, you can't do any type of shout-out for VOG, Bobby, OLR.
[SPEAKER_03]: They will not get read.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is not about people's egos.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is about the speedrunners.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is about the charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's about the event.
[SPEAKER_03]: So keep your comments on your donations about those sorts of things would be my advice because...
[SPEAKER_03]: Even I tried to send in a donation once that was from Mr. Smush and they didn't read it because they thought it was some type of R-rated joke.
[SPEAKER_03]: It didn't even make its way to Bobby's desk.
[SPEAKER_03]: The screeners cut it out beforehand.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which makes, I mean, in retrospect, makes sense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, if you don't know that Mr. Smush is my cat, you're not going to know what the hell that is and so you're going to throw it out because you don't want something coded to make it out on stream.
[SPEAKER_03]: So be very careful what you write with those donations.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Or just donate.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just donate.
[SPEAKER_03]: In chat...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkTetsuya says it's actually Arcade Archives 1 is Macross.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arcade Archives 2 got Air Combat 22 this week, if I recall correctly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, let's go back to what you were talking about, Loki, when we were doing Rapid Fire News, because we have some time anyway here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have a little extra time with Jamie cutting out early.
Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: One other thing I played this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's this big trend online lately of Nintendo games getting ported to Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: We had a story on this last week, the week before.
[SPEAKER_03]: Life Force, or Salamander, but Life Force here in the US was one of these games that was recently ported.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you might go, well, why do they put the NES game on the Super Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they don't change the graphics.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like it's completely different.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They do that so that it helps to reduce flicker, slow down, and sometimes they can add different types of music types of stuff to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: One game that I actually played this week is I actually played a Kid Icarus port of Kid Icarus ported to the Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Part of what the Super Nintendo port does is it brings in the backgrounds from the 3DS version.
[SPEAKER_03]: which is very interesting although I gotta be honest I didn't find that it really like ran any better to me but look I found this random YouTube video and I'm going to bring this up for folks that are watching live but you can see what this looks like it kind of adds a lot to it it really is just the NES version of Kid Icarus but it's using the backgrounds from the 3DS version of the game and you'll notice they they scroll at kind of a different rate you know um
[SPEAKER_03]: I was talking about...
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember how they had the 3D Excite bike and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: How it was actually three-dimensional with the particular display?
[SPEAKER_07]: So they have an actual emulator that is on Steam.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to remember what it's called.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically a 3D emulator that 3D-ifies games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if people have to add a configuration, but it supports a lot of games already.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it makes everything look voxel-y, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it... Okay, I'm looking at a YouTube, but this is dated three years ago, so maybe it's not this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is... That's...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could be.
[SPEAKER_03]: This looks kind of funky to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it could be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you can adjust the camera and everything on it because it's fully 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know if I like that, though.
[SPEAKER_03]: That just seems... But, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's called 3D Sen, is what it's called.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's a paid emulator on PC.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah, 3D Sen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also supports VR and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, it looked pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was curious to see what Pixel Poop's number two would look like in that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably pretty terrible because I don't think it's set up.
[SPEAKER_07]: You mean pretty poopy?
[SPEAKER_07]: It would look pretty poopy, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't even know if it would run in that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd have to check and see.
[SPEAKER_07]: But some of the demos that they were showing look pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you know I have this fancy new video card, and if nothing else, I can run 3D emulators on it, so let's go, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's travel around the world and check out some release dates.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's check out some games that are coming out, you know, 3D emulated or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Obviously not, because these are all new games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you should support games when they come out and not pirate them, because that's why we have layoffs.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, starting in the US, what do you have coming out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I had to check to make sure this wasn't a typo, but Backyard Baseball 01.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, from 2001.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_07]: PC, iOS, and Android I don't know why that's being ported.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is so old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Missile Command Delta on PC, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_07]: We have Bad End Theater on Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series EA Sports College Football 26 on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series Everdeep Aurora on PC and Nintendo Switch Islanders New Shores on PC, Mac, Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 5, and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_07]: System Shock 2 25th Anniversary Remaster on Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One and Xbox Series Bendy and the Dark Revival on Nintendo Switch, PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_07]: Patsapon 1 and 2 replay on PC, Nintendo Switch, and PlayStation 5 And last but not least, Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 and 4 on PC, Nintendo Switch, Nintendo Switch 2, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Going to Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the Switch 2 this week in Japan, Split Fiction gets its Japanese release.
[SPEAKER_03]: Please recognize that it's just a code in a box.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know that's those types of releases.
[SPEAKER_03]: Code in a box.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those releases have been somewhat controversial, but that is what they're putting on the shelves this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the original Switch, though, there's a lot more going on, which, of course, Switch 2 plays a lot of these.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legacy of Kain, Soul Reaver 1 and 2 Remastered is out this week, as well as the game Uta Tomori no Yokai Yashiki is also out this week on the original Switch.
[SPEAKER_03]: We also have a game called the Irem Collection Volume 3, the Irem Collections.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've had a few of these recently.
[SPEAKER_03]: This one has Mystic Riders, Dragon Breed, and Mr. Heli Battle Chopper.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think
[SPEAKER_03]: Patapon 1 and 2 Natsuman 20th Century Summer Vacation Plus Broadcast Over Sunset
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep, that's the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's childhood adventures in 3D recreations of quaint shopping districts and single car trains.
[SPEAKER_03]: By the way, our pal Shane is over in Japan right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: and rode the Oshawott train today for the first time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you know there's a whole fucking train that's themed Oshawott?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was looking at that on this blue sky.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but I'm not surprised that you wrote it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was just like, oh my god, it literally looks like Shane designed the train.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Oshawott seats, little plush Oshawotts they leave on the seats, little Oshawott designs on the carpet, on the side of the train.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just like, Oshawott threw up all over the inside of this thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But look, hey, look.
[SPEAKER_03]: If it was Bad Bats Maru, I'd want to go on the train as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not going to yuck somebody's yum, but it was just a lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the PlayStation 5, that same Iram Collection Volume 3 is coming out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legacy of Kain, Soul Reaver 1 and 2 Remastered, also out on PlayStation 5.
[SPEAKER_03]: Police Simulator Patrol Officers at Cab includes Police Simulator players.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's it for Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, how about the UK?
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got College Football 26 on PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series, Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 and 4 on PC, PlayStation, Xbox, and Switch, and Patapon 1 and 2 replay on Switch.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry, I just realized this whole time my mic was off.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I was I was wondering why you weren't responding.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's OK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's try again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think we've got one more story for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it has to do with this something we were talking about last week with Mind's Eyes release.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, interesting follow up, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like when... It's not even just necessarily this company.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't like when, for example, what was it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ghostbusters 2016.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of these other Marvel series and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where if you don't like it, it's because of this reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not because it's bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's because, oh, well, you're racist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or, oh, you just...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, you are... Clearly, the bad reviews for this game that, with my own eyes, can see is bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I don't need someone to tell me it's bad, they just show me, here's some gameplay from the game, and I'm like, yeah, that looks bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Clearly, this is sabotage.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least, that's what Leslie Benzies is trying to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Convince everybody that rough launch on Saboteurs and that they are promising the relaunch of Mind's Eye in the future.
[SPEAKER_07]: The saboteurs, or people that were talking bad about the game, didn't make the game bad to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: You made the game bad to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I have a hard time believing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they said that there is a concerted effort by someone to ruin the game's reputation before release.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this someone in the room?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like...
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_07]: We didn't know what the game was because you were showing us weird cinematic trailers all the time and then you release the game and it's absolute garbage.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you remember when the people in charge used to take accountability?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you remember Iwata?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you remember people that take accountability?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I mean, it's been a while.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, I think suffice to say it's yeah, you could you could throw whatever reasons you want out there, buddy.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the call is coming from inside the house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like it's just it's bad looking like it looks bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: The reviews like when people show reviews for a game, like especially a video review, like you're seeing the gameplay.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can see it with my own eyes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not that someone's telling me, oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: and I look at that gameplay I'm like well it looks fine to me but if they're saying it's bad it must be bad no it looks like trash it looks like a game that is not cooked enough that you need to spend a lot more time on that somebody who used to be in charge of like the Grand Theft Auto franchise should do better it's dated it has dated gameplay mechanics it's
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one of these games where you have, you know, somebody that is the top of their game for this one series and then they strike out on their own and you're like, well, I mean, they did a great job with Mega Man, so Mighty No.
[SPEAKER_07]: 9 should be great, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because some people on the internet are ridiculous all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yeah, Ironheart, you know, some people have a problem with diversity.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some people have a problem with it and will go out of their way to say so.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there's a lot of people that will discount something strictly because of diversity or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: That said though, there's also people that will use that claim to mask actual hate for the stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, She-Hulk.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hated that series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it was stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just poorly written.
[SPEAKER_07]: The concept sounded like it would be really cool, and then they just went and twisted it around and like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Just made it some cringe fest thing and they're like, well, you just hate it because you're a chauvinistic pig or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, no, it's poorly written.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, now we're going to get to the listener roundtable.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we're going to take your questions in chat and then your emails and maybe some calls in our Discord server over in the green room.
[SPEAKER_03]: I forgot I need to pull up the mailbag because DarkSakura isn't here and I know there was at least one email tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I need just a minute here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you have any last minute stories, Loki, while I try to pull up the email?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, I, I, I forgot to mention when I said that Romero, the Romero game, uh, game was canceled.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, the studio has been closed down.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's a little bit worse that their whole studio went down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, you know, speaking of that Marvel series, like what I was going to say, there's a lot of their TV series have not been good.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's, it's surprising because a lot of that stuff, like I love She-Hulk as a character.
[SPEAKER_07]: This isn't like the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought the show was awful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, Echo, God damn.
[SPEAKER_03]: We hope this email finds you well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy belated pride from a listener and friend who's plural, one side demi-masculine, one side trans-feminine.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bisexual, polyamorous, demiromantic, and autistic And also, since it's July 4th as we write this And there's a quote here, a screenshot saying This whole thing smacks of gender, I holler As I overturn my uncle's barbecue grill And turn the 4th of July into the 4th of shit I think most people that are not interested in celebrating the 4th of July figured this out But July the 4th happens to be the birthday of the Caesar salad
[SPEAKER_03]: So when I was at a local bar which has an outdoor section and they were lighting off fireworks, I made sure to proclaim happy birthday to the Caesar salad because that is the only thing we are celebrating today.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So happy birthday, Caesar salad.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you all had a great celebration celebrating the anniversary of such a yummy dish, which, by the way, I think you all know by now, but it was not invented in Italy.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a casino in Tijuana.
[SPEAKER_03]: that I think was named Caesar's or the guy that ran it was named Caesar.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's why it's called that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was the Caesar salad was invented in Tijuana.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, first of all, an analogy to express my thoughts on a certain console maker's nonsense.
[SPEAKER_03]: Spillfencer demolishes half of his house, leaving only the kitchen and living room, then tells his family that he had to make difficult decisions, but that their house is looking better than ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: Look at all that place.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can extend the garden.
[SPEAKER_03]: Think of all that garden we can have now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Second, with the Stop Killing Games initiative back in full force after a harassment counter campaign, I often think about this as of late because I play a lot of modern rhythm games, i.e.
[SPEAKER_03]: those made within the last 10 years, like Chunathim, Mai Mai, Archaea, and Easy 2 On.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a lot of modern rhythm games have some form of DRM or another to prevent playing if you're offline, or at least debuffing a lot of the functionality in the case of Archaea.
[SPEAKER_07]: or Dance Dance Revolution nowadays.
[SPEAKER_03]: That is an interesting one.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think that's because of the music rights.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that puts a whole other twist on things where when you have the music rights that come into play, now you sort of have to protect that
[SPEAKER_03]: Game, or else they're not going to license those songs to you from being able to do a lot with that offline or strip the music out, especially if we're talking about like in some of the old, you know, 2DX actually had like the master cuts to an extent because, you know, the instrumentation was actually tied to the buttons.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they actually had to have like the master recordings to strip out certain sound effects of the vocals and isolate those.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if that can get dumped on
[SPEAKER_03]: or Get Out There Somehow, it can cause people to do whatever they want with those songs, which, you know, the record labels don't really like, even though, you know, all this time later, that's all out there for all those old 2DX games.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I digress.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think with the music games in particular, they have to put the walls up a little bit higher because that's the only way they're going to convince the record labels to give them the licenses.
[SPEAKER_03]: But even with those games...
[SPEAKER_03]: I think once they pull them offline, anything that you bought, you should still be able to play, licensed or not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, only a scant few rhythm games, at least on PC and mobile, made in the last 10 or so years don't have online DRM, most notably Fygros and Orzmic, both of which are non-profit games.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's the huge twist.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arcade rhythm games, at least many of them going out of service, get offline patches so they can be played even after cessation of service, albeit in reduced forms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can't save scores, can't save options, some songs are missing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But what happens to mobile-based rhythm games when they reach end of service?
[SPEAKER_03]: One notorious example is Love Live Live.
[SPEAKER_03]: Love Live School Idol Festival, a somewhat infamous hybrid of gacha game and rhythm game, with all the your scores depend on how powerful and rare your cards are that entails.
[SPEAKER_03]: The original game shut down after a little over 10 years and can no longer be played.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then came Love Live School Idol Festival 2, which was shut down after only one year in Japan, and perhaps even more notoriously had its global version release date 8th.
[SPEAKER_03]: and Shutdown announced at the same time.
[SPEAKER_03]: The poor thing lived only three months.
[SPEAKER_03]: And in this screenshot of an announcement that says, this is wild.
[SPEAKER_03]: How do I show this without showing the whole damn mailbox?
[SPEAKER_03]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can show it this way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me show this on the other screen without the token visible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: Global launch notice.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are excited to break the news to you that the global version of Love Live!
[SPEAKER_03]: School Idol Festival 2 Miracle Live is launching soon in February 2024.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, we also want to inform you that the global version will close its doors on May 31st and cease in-app purchases accordingly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember when that came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember something about that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: .
[SPEAKER_03]: very infamously had that partnership with a different drum, that synth pop label out of Salt Lake City that gave us some bangers, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how we got Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's how we got, you know, we got a lot of great artists from that in those games.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they, my, I don't know if this is true, so do not quote me in an article somewhere, but I thought I remember hearing those songs were licensed for 50 bucks a pop.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought I remember hearing that somewhere along the way that it was like 50 bucks but think about but also but like on the flip side think about like they're kind of getting paid in exposure right like Echo Image made you know they sold albums based off that and and probably we were to help a little bit because we hyped the shit out of them but deserved I love Echo Image that's still Compufonics one of my favorite albums to this day quite honestly so um you know I I think you
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, they are probably able to license some songs very cheap because, yeah, it's...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're getting paid in exposure, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, all of this has me concerned for the sustainability of rhythm games, along with the constant demand for new content.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're always having to add new songs every month or two, or else the spoiled players will slam their fists at the metaphorical dinner table demanding, where's content?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's content, dead game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Move on, and then the game loses revenue and dies.
[SPEAKER_03]: In 10 years, let alone 20, will I still be able to play games like...
[SPEAKER_03]: Roteno, The Funny Gyroscope Rhythm Game, and D4DJ.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also hope gacha game players will think about the Stop Killing Games initiative because gacha games by their nature require online DRM so that people can't save scum their roles.
[SPEAKER_03]: I understand that a lot of gacha game players enjoy these games because they are often free to start and can be played on a device they probably already have as opposed to having a good enough PC or console for it, especially in Southeast Asia where people like anime stuff or
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I get that there's more to consider but even in the gacha space if you paid money to get that song then you should have that song and you should be able to play it in that game in perpetuity I do believe that but it's going to be one of those things it's a hard nut to crack and I think at the end of the day it's probably just going to have to do with a lot of those agreements that you sign off on
[SPEAKER_03]: The companies have been writing them for forever.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's time for us to write ours.
[SPEAKER_03]: So on that note, if you want to send us an email for a future week, participate at orangelaunchradio.com is the place to do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Any other last minute stories for us tonight, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then with that, we're going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks as always for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Appreciate you all.
[SPEAKER_03]: We are the place where every gamer has a voice, but we need more voices to put out on air.
[SPEAKER_03]: Help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_03]: A nice comment on social media.
[SPEAKER_03]: A nice five-star review on a site like Apple Podcasts, Spotify.
[SPEAKER_03]: YouTube, wherever you found this going off a long way.
[SPEAKER_03]: So thank you to everybody that sends and goes the extra mile and participates with the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you to those of you that turned out here live on Twitch this evening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you to those that listen to us on the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope you all have a wonderful week gaming and we'll be back in seven days to wrap up the news once again.
[SPEAKER_03]: Until then, DarkSakura's not here, so she won't be streaming after the show tonight, but I'm sure she would have something to say here at the end.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I think she already said FAC earlier on in the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: She'll be streaming throughout the week on her channel.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can check her out on Twitch at DarkSakuraTTV.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll give her a nice plug there in absence of a final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Loki, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is that I'd like to get working on my modded series already.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: And my final thought is I need to beat the main story in Fantasy Life already.
[SPEAKER_03]: I keep getting distracted by crafting and leveling up jobs, but literally everybody who's in Endgame in that game says stop getting distracted by that.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can catch up and do that stuff later after the story.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's hard.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to level everything up equally.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything leveling equally.
[SPEAKER_03]: And why won't the game drop a goddamn woodcutter strangling?
[SPEAKER_03]: I need a woodcutter in my party.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's the one thing I'm missing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Give me a woodcutter, Fantasy Life.
[SPEAKER_03]: Damn you.
[SPEAKER_03]: On that note, have a wonderful night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Goodbye.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know they were all still true.
[SPEAKER_06]: See you next week.