I've always envied the difference of music culture in Japan. Since I started playing
imported games, I also learned about the number of albums they release. Everything from official
OSTs, remix or remake OSTs like the Final Fantasy piano and vocal collections to doujin
released by the producers themselves. But here in the States and on the internet at
large the story is very different and I don't wish the legal hassle on anyone. Join your
hosts Rob Roberts, Jamie Summers and Loki as they explain this and the rest of the week's
news starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio Live. Once again tonight episode
number 843 of our show for this November the 15th of 2020. My name is Rob Roberts and
I'm joined here as I am live every Sunday night at the Voice Geeks Network with my co-hosts
say hello first and foremost to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers.
Hello.
Hi Jamie, how are you doing?
Oh I'm on week four but I'm finally starting to feel better. I'll put it this way my tests
are negative but my doctor hasn't ruled out COVID.
Oh interesting. I've heard of false negatives and things like that so.
Well the thing is is that I also did the serology test and the serology test is pretty much
useless because a good portion of the population doesn't create antibodies.
Well hang in there I'm glad to hear you're at least on the mend and doing better.
Yeah I basically have one more week of recovery and then I'm clear so.
Sounds good.
It's just my voice has been cutting out so but I can talk a little bit longer just it
still is kind of like sounding like you know that fry.
I'm really looking forward to the day when all of us can be in the same studio again
I know it's still several months out but just really looking forward to that day so.
Just wait until we have a competent administration.
I know 65 days anyway before I introduce everybody else it's no secret obviously this
week new game console release week it's a big week and dark soccer we've talked before
on the show about how you guys are kind of waiting for a little bit so I thought since
you are the queen of classic games I thought I'd put you on the spot with a different question
here and I'm going to open this up to our chat as well because of course we do tape
live every Sunday night at the voice geeks network twitch.tv slash a vog network Sunday
night at six o'clock Pacific nine o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwell show
so the question is we're going to be talking about some launch games that came out and
you know some other things too but looking back on all of the systems throughout history
and all of the various launch titles we've had like you know.
Games that have launched consoles there's been some good ones there's been some terrible
ones I'm kind of curious dark soccer if you have a particular favorite or maybe memorable
launch title in your heart.
I am putting her on the spot I didn't warn her about this question so she might need
a little time to think but I'm putting you all on the spot in our chat room as well if
you guys have any questions or any any questions of course you have questions.
There were definitely ones that I like but I think the one that really just stuck itself
out as memorable for me actually I've got two that I can name because I just remember
how how cool it felt you know was a I'm pretty sure Super Mario World was a launch title
it was yeah I mean I remembered Super Mario Brothers wasn't initially so I kind of was
getting into a little bit mixed but yeah Super Mario World was like one of the big ones for
me we had gotten my mom's like that year should we get your brother a Super Nintendo or Genesis
and I'm like you're getting them Super Nintendo and it's for me so I told her what games to
get I was like I don't care what else you get but you have to get you know a link to
the past you know but Super Mario World was for me just the big thing that made me super
super excited about having a Super Nintendo I played the shit out of it my brother sucked
at it but you know they were like 10 something like that and I probably played it so much more
than they did I've beaten it completely by myself when the game first came out and when I dedicated
a lot of time to link to the past after that but that really stuck out for me and then another one
was Sonic Adventure because remember we had our our Dreamcast pretty much right after the
Japanese launch and we played so much Sonic Adventure and you know looked for all the
glitchy stuff and everything I really really enjoyed Sonic Adventure I was really into it
of course it had some of my favorite Japanese voice actors in it like for Knuckles at this
time okay I have to also explain I had a minor obsession with with Hayashi Nobutoshi who was also
he was Tatsuki in Fushigi Yugi he was Basara in Macross 7 got a really amazing singing voice
and you know so and he was you know he he was in the game and I he was Knuckles he was Knuckles
voice actor and so I was really really just enamored with the game I liked playing Amy even
though she was a little bit annoying I liked the music in it I was so enamored so when the US
Dreamcast launch happened so I actually have to rewind a little bit more for that because there
was the rental before launch and we did rent a US one yeah yeah and that demo version that was the
US one and then after that when we got our our US Dreamcast we just played through Sonic Adventure
again of course I had to switch the voices back to Japanese because after playing it so long in
Japanese the US voices were disjointed to me it was just not saying the voice actor was bad I'm
just saying that I was still used I mean I have the same problem with anime today like if I go
watch any Dragon Ball I have to watch it in Japanese because those are the voices I heard
first right um I still prefer Ranma in Japanese because I watched it that way first Sailor Moon
same thing you know um so uh the one of the few anime that I'm not like that with is those who
hunt elves because I first watched it in English and I got used to those voice actors so it's kind
of um but but going back to it um you know I I those two were probably the big ones that stick
out in my head as far as um some of the more memorable ones all right um great yeah I really
loved it great answers um let me add some stuff in chat and then I've got to introduce uh the
other folks on tonight's show who've been waiting patiently uh so uh let me see uh act def says
breath of the wild is definitely one of the best launch titles ever yeah nintendo certainly knows
how to launch a console huh I like this answer from bobby blackwolf my favorite xbox 360 launch
title was geometry wars and she hulk 10 says dead rising 3 for xbox one was and is awesome I forgot
that was a launch title and yeah the dead rising series that was a good one all right uh waiting
patiently and with us every week say hello of course to tech master loki joining us tonight
hello hey loki how are you doing I'm doing okay what are you running behind you tonight is that
is that final fight like a sequel not the first one what is that no it's cadillacs and dinosaurs
I have an idea for like I've seen that for um a game I was supposed to put behind me and like
I had it like earlier this week I was like oh yeah I saw a game like yeah I need to do that one and
completely forgot it today oh no like mo wiki was it that I saw like it was something that I saw out
there I was like oh yeah I totally remember that I need to put that behind me but nope completely
forgot so my memory has always been terrible it's been getting worse as I get older and now it's
getting even worse because this whole quarantine situation and they actually say that like you
know it's it's contributing to people having the brain fog and all that stuff so it's uh
welcome to old age loki yeah I don't know if it's that it's just there's you know different things
going on this week so I I'm sure whatever it was that I saw you know I thought it might have been
like um sam and max I can't remember if I've done that already because of all the like sam max news
we'll be talking about but um I don't know if it was that it was something else but like I saw it
and I was like oh yeah I need to do that and then immediately like today I was like okay wait what
game was that I was thinking of so I have it really quickly come up with something all right
well we'll come back to you in a minute because I want to talk about how launch week has been
going for the new consoles uh I want to know did you well okay I'm gonna even guess did you even
get your xbox you were worried about that with walmart no it came right when they said it was
going to so yeah I actually earlier than they said it was going to so they originally said it
was going to be here on the 12th but it ended up being here on launch day so it was fine um
but yeah yeah I have it sitting right here under my monitor I think I got my got my controller
and everything but yeah it's sitting here I got a brand new 4k monitor um for it so it's looking
nice all right well I'm gonna come back to you in a minute because we're gonna talk all about the
new xbox but um he's been waiting there so patiently and you guys on twitch uh that are
watching live can see that he's back tonight and I've got to introduce say hello everybody to
shane or shad starzik on twitch if you will who's joining us again tonight hi shane
hello and I gotta say shane you are looking so much better than the last time you were here
yeah I feel better good still run down I'm actually feeling run down but that's okay
I've got dr pepper and I have to study for a test tomorrow so I'm gonna be up all night
yeah and for those um that missed uh the episode you were here what about like four or five weeks
ago um on the show and you were right in the midst of three was it wow time flies uh you were
right in the midst of battling covid last time you were on the show but you came here anyway to talk
about I think it was the pokemon dlc you were talking about that night so um and you you were
kind of like lying in bed still but tonight you're you're propped up you've got you know that light
effect I know I'm in my I'm in my computer chair my little corner in the living room and I'm using
my brand new iphone 12 pro math oh rub it in why don't you shaky I don't have a web so this is just
what has to work no honestly the phone works I'm using the phone for this particular shot here
that's going out on twitch right now so it works all right um but uh part of the reason I brought
you here tonight was because uh if you've been listening to orange launch radio then you know
that I want to get an or I've gotten an xbox pre-ordered one of those uh we'll talk about
how that went because it wasn't so smooth loki got an xbox none of us really have playstation
5 represented here uh so shane you got a playstation 5 this week right and so so you've
got both so I want to talk to you about how this week went so obviously um this is a big week uh
last week our show got cut short abruptly unfortunately thanks to the internet which
I'm hoping is holding in there more steady tonight knock on wood but I've had less problems this week
which is good um but um last week we were still able to talk for an hour and a half we talked a
good chunk about how we are on the dawn of a new generation with playstation and xbox launching
new consoles you know and we were kind of wondering you know is it too early for them to
be doing it is it going to be worth it and all this and now we have a lot of answers to many of
those questions um echoing something that bobby said uh he goes on of course before us here at the
voice geeks network echoing something that he said uh is that well clearly the launch went
great because they're selling out so no these consoles didn't go or I'm sorry no these consoles
didn't come out too early because they're selling out so it's going very well and yeah the consoles
have been very hard to obtain um loki I'll start with you uh on the xbox series x so tell us how
that went for you the ordering process and kind of what you've been playing on it I figured we
usually do a kickoff topic here on tonight's show and then we do our gaming weeks but this week the
big topic is our gaming weeks so we're just going to kind of jump into it so loki I'm going to kind
of ask you about your gaming week with the xbox series x sure so like the ordering process it was
basically when those orders were opened up originally back in september I just had all
the different you know retailers online uh all their sites open and walmart happened to be the
first one that let me put something in my cart and submit the order so that's what I went with
and so I was always I was kind of worried that it may not arrive on time or at all because I
had issues with my mario kart live where came to be launch day and they hadn't even shipped yet
so I had to cancel that one but thankfully I was able to get that in store um I knew that wouldn't
be the case with the xbox series x so um other than that I mean it was fine it arrived on time
like I said you know I was worried that it would be here late um because originally they were
estimating the 12th but it arrived on the 10th and I was like cool and uh
uh so really what I've been playing on I don't really have a ton of stuff so I haven't had an
xbox since the 360 so I finally got games pass ultimate and I just was downloading some stuff
on there actually I was looking at all my xbox stuff I have on there like 94 games because of
my old 360 games of gold stuff um so there's quite a bit old 360 games I have but I don't
really have a lot of um xbox one games I guess I have a few with like crackdown and uh forza
because I purchased those on pc uh which is nice but um so I ended up getting yakuza like a dragon
because I wasn't really sure of what launch games I really wanted there was nothing really kind of
standing out and I was trying to look at look for something that was really showing off the series
x and really the only thing they have is like forza horizon 4 and I already have that so I
started downloading that it's taken a long time but I think it's finally downloaded now I've been
mainly playing yakuza um which is interesting because I've never played a yakuza game before
and this one is more like a um an rpg so they've they actually set up because the main character
is a huge fan of dragon quest and so it's all turn-based combat which I I love it it's great
cool um the story is a bit slow but it's just like it really feels like playing like a dragon
quest or final fantasy game it's just kind of funny in that sense I I heard that I heard that
that was um like that that it was more like an old school rpg so it's kind of more of a spin-off
game so you know and I've had people for years telling me you need to get into yakuza you need
to get into that series I wonder if the fans of the series would think this is a good one to start
with or no don't start here definitely different because the other ones are brawlers I mean this is
still a brawler but it's turn-based so it's different um it's all right I mean it's certainly
not like a huge powerhouse like pretty looking game I mean it does look um not like it's pushing
the high-end graphics or anything like that but I don't know it's all right I I've enjoyed it a
little bit I haven't been playing a whole ton because I've been working on my game but I did
play like a probably like five hours of it so far and it's all right it's just there's so much story
and we're like I'm still like in the tutorial section of the game haven't even gotten very far
and it's just it's so much dialogue like I get it but there's like some of it doesn't really
it's just like dragging out so long like oh my god and they have options to skip past dialogue
but I'm like worried I'm missing something but I'm really not missing anything um so I don't
know it's just it's really slow to get started but it is somewhat interesting the story is
interesting enough it's just it's like oh my god when are we going to get to like the actual like
game um but the action's cool so there are some action sequences and stuff in the game um I don't
know I I enjoy it so far we'll we'll see how long I play through it and everything um aside from
that I did try Minecraft a little bit because my kid wanted me to play it and honestly I can't say
that it looks any different that's definitely not a game that would uh benefit from the series x now
saying that once they do push out the ray tracing stuff which I have played on pc uh that does
look really great like if they can do that on a series x then that would be definitely one to
revisit because it looks really good when they do that um but right now obviously it doesn't
look any different than it did before um I saw it in the list I haven't downloaded it yet but
lost odysseys on games pass since I was like we should go back to lost odyssey um but no I've
been really kind of just going through there to see you know what really um showcase the system
I know Ori um might be a good one um fours horizon like I said I've already downloaded that but like
I'm worried I don't want to fill up the hard drive already with this all the games out and stuff and
I mean hopefully still uh we have uh cyberpunk coming out in you know a little less than a month
yeah we definitely definitely don't want another delay on that for sure yeah so hopefully that
comes out but yeah I'm gonna jump in here because I I forgot we have a time constraint with shane
so I want to make sure he's able to um get his impressions especially with the playstation 5
and so forth so I'll come back to you though loki if you have more to add um but shane how
was your week with the new consoles how did that go for you um so pretty easy for me in terms of
getting them we've talked about like the magical powers I have for things like persuasion for
people to get stuff done and I'm also an expert at getting in line for things which is kind of how I
got at least one of these consoles um so xbox whatever you guys are going to talk about that
I haven't really done much with it to be completely honest um real quick why why is
the xbox taking a back seat for you because it wasn't the console I was originally getting I
only got it under a weird circumstance so um okay ps5 I went to best buy because I had gotten a
pre-order there and I went at six in the morning because that was my time slots because they were
doing time slots to pick up uh your system and literally there were probably about 20 people 20
25 people that were there for the same time slot like they were all people that had it pre-ordered
it was a pretty smooth process except I saw if you haven't seen the box I can't really reach it
right so whatever it has a little handle on top so you can carry it it's one of those like cheap
little plastic handles isn't it it's really flimsy and I saw three people hold it by the
handle and the handle snapped while they were holding it and the console come crashing down
to the floor as they were walking out of the store yike so yeah that wasn't good um otherwise
I I don't want to say I'm a Sony fanboy but I tend to just play on their products mostly besides
Nintendo and uh I love my ps5 the controller is fantastic it's just basically the same as
what the joy cons were trying to do but a little more advanced feeling um for launch games I've
I got four I got Demon's Souls which I haven't played yet I just installed it I got the Miles
Morales game that came with Spider-Man 1 and so I played a little bit of Spider-Man but not Miles
Morales yet uh I got the Sackboy game haven't even opened it yet or installed it and I got
Godfall I did install that and I played that for probably a good hour and a half pretty fun little
like hack and slash loot game um and it's really pretty and that's what I guess I didn't realize
I was missing on my um on my consoles was like a really nice high definition 60 frames per second
experience and that's what I'm getting with these new games I don't I don't switch it to oh no I
don't switch Godfall into the pretty fancy ray tracing mode because it just chugs if you do that
but if you keep it on performance it's beautiful and really fast Spider-Man though super cool
looking at 60 frames a second but I keep it on the visual fidelity mode because it's really
really nice looking I can deal with 30 frames a second problem and Astrobot to me Astrobot is so
good I don't care if it's just like Playstation propaganda throughout the entire game it's such
a nostalgic trip for some of the things I've seen I love it I've heard a lot of good things
about Astro Boy considering you know I think most people are kind of I'm sorry Astrobot
Astro Boy is a different thing considering so many people were um like overlooking it as just
just kind of writing it off as oh the tech demo game that you know they're just kind of throwing
in there because it's cheap but it really seems like a lot of social media is really taking to
this game like no it is it's a strong game on its own just for like you're saying the nostalgia
features and being able to kind of show everything off like it's it seems like it's a much better
kind of deal than one two switch same oh yeah for sure and it really gets you acquainted with
the controller and all the things that are uh available to to uh be used for that fancy new
controller um we'll see if in even six months time if other games are taking advantage of it
Godfall didn't really feel that special um in terms of like fun controller things neither did
uh regular Spider-Man so uh we'll see maybe maybe more people will look to Astrobot now that it's
out more developers will and really see what they can do with that um just tell me if you have to
go by the way but um I I want to ask you this question kind of about the since I don't you know
you're kind of like our PlayStation 5 voice tonight what do you kind of think like do you
feel like this console is like a huge step up from the four like what is this like really bringing to
the table for you that's exciting so the load time and that's something I can like even speak
to on the Series X the load times make all the difference in the world it feels like for example
besides Astrobot probably the game I played most on the PS5 is Fuser um from Harmonix I
wondered when you were gonna bring that up yeah because these are so good um so I just downloaded
it all I was playing a little bit on PS4 when it launched then I was like screw it I'm not even
going to keep my PS4 out here anymore so let's just move everything to PS5 and just I can't
believe how I was sitting through load times before this these systems it's just I never
want load times again but the trade-off is at least for now I'm already onto like maybe 400
under 400 gigs left on my PS5 for storage space and that sucks that like Spider-Man both of them
together were already 100 gigs that's like almost under just under a seventh of the entire hard
drive that you get or no just under about a six yeah it sucks like I don't know what they need
to do I don't know what the industry needs to do to make these things cheaper but that's I guess
I guess beautiful graphics fast loading ridiculous face constraints that's what the new generation
feels like um at least we know the space stuff is upgradeable later on um if but it's kind of
expensive those I mean at least the official like solid state drives are kind of expensive
I mean a regular USB drive not so much but then you're missing that perk of the loading time which
yeah over on Series X which I'll talk about in a minute I'm definitely noticing like wow this
really changes things with the loading time it's pretty impressive I don't even have time to switch
to like the right input on my Series X before it's already up like I'll hit the button on the
controller to turn on the system and I hear the noise and then I reach for the remote and turn it
to the right input and it's already there it's instant it's pretty amazing um tell us quickly
before I let you go about about Fusor like what is it about that game you love so much
I love drop mix and Fusor is just drop mix without physical cards and you get to make a character
and you get a weird camp mode and it has like rhythm based mechanic like timing and it's so
much fun I just just hope it's not like I hope it gets supported for longer than six months
because that feels like the average harmonics game or even that might be stretching it um but
I already want more dlc I went all in on it got the big fancy pack uh I pre-ordered so I got three
more songs and literally uh you make like your own sort of deck thing your own box of different like
music cards and every single box I make like there's three songs I keep in there I don't care
if it has to be like if they're focusing on like uh rock music or if they're focusing this box on
uh rap and r&b and stuff like that or country like I always keep freaking ghosts and stuff
by deadmau5 and rob swire eyes by rufus soul and the other one keep in there oh where's your head
at my basement those three are always in every box I make because I refuse to let them go because I
I always throw the vocals on over uh with one of those songs I can't stop um are they gonna uh
I thought I was reading this might be a thing but let's say you wanted to so obviously shared play
is the thing in the sony universe if you wanted to share play your playstation 5 but I'm only
on playstation 4 am I going to be able to see that or does that not work interesting we'll have
to try it because I haven't tried any like I haven't really done a lot okay so here's how it
is oh I got two new fancy consoles what do I do last night I play pokemon it's just you know like
I'm sitting 15 feet away from them looking at them and I'm like oh but I should probably go shiny
in pokemon that's a good idea I get it though because like you know I have shiny new consoles
and we're still signing on to play final fantasy 14 and do dungeons so you know I will not put
that on my ps there is no space for that game yeah I'm good with keeping that on my computer
all right uh shane I know I I gotta let you go because you have another uh thing you gotta do
but um thanks sorry I know you had to sit there for a long time but uh we have a lot to say sorry
about it um but I'm sure we'll have you back again soon okay okay take care buddy bye all right um
so while I fix the camera settings here live on twitch um loki anything else you want to see on
the xbox because I had to cut you off a little bit sorry no it's fine so it's funny enough like
I was looking at uh some of the playstation 5 games that have come out like especially like
the footage of um spider-man miles morales and even like uh sack boy and um astro bots and stuff
kind of makes me want to playstation 5 but I'm certainly waiting until next year when um I don't
think they're gonna go down in price but when there's um more availability and maybe when
playstation vr2 gets announced or is coming out um so we'll see when that happens but um definitely
in the short run like I think there's more um interesting games on the launch end for
playstation 5 but the reason I picked an xbox series x is because I feel especially with all
these company acquisitions and bethesda and everything that there's gonna be a lot more games
exclusive games coming to the xbox side of things um it's definitely a game pass machine and that's
not a bad thing yeah yeah and what's cool though like too like with yakuza like say for example if
I don't want to have that on my uh like I feel that this game's kind of a grind fest I was like
man if I could really run this with like trainers and stuff on pc it'd be great and I can because
it's all cross by so I have it on pc too when I make a purchase on xbox um series x or on the
xbox marketplace so like I could essentially download it to my pc if I have not enough space
on my series x interesting um yeah because they've been doing the cross by thing for a little bit
because like I remember forza horizon on xbox one and there's been several titles on xbox one
a lot of especially like the real first party microsoft stuff was cross by and that's why
there's a lot of people that are like why do I need to get an xbox if I have a pc I don't need
to get which is fine sorry I shouldn't do a voice with that but for some people it's what I hear
because I feel like they're trying to take a dig at xbox but I realize some people have that very
measured approach to where it's like I've got a top of the line pc there's not really anything
micro the xbox going to do for me and I do kind of get that but like if you sign up for game pass
microsoft still got your money yeah I don't think they care whether you get a system or not I think
it's long as you're playing their games they don't really care and and that's the thing it's
like if you don't want to get you know an xbox series x right now maybe there's not something
that you want to play on it you can always get games pass or whatever and play their games and
they come out you don't have to pay any additional money for it so it's not too bad I honestly so
this is going to be a really weird statement but I'm gonna this is my early thought like and I I
think the series x is great I'm gonna get my impressions in a minute but I almost feel like
what game pass is bringing to the table and eventually what sony is going to have to respond
with their with their own you know playstation plus library sorry I always get the name wrong
of that but you know they're they're equivalent essentially I almost feel like the next generation
in some ways is more about that and the transition to that kind of ecosystem than necessarily about
more bigger graphics and ray tracing and okay the loading times yeah I mean that is that is certainly
a big difference but I almost feel like that other transition is going to be more representative of
what we went through in this generation from the last generation if that makes sense so all right
yeah so anyway um let me talk a little bit about my uh story with the series x so it actually is
a little bit interesting because um what ended up happening is that I got the um series x on
amazon I pre-ordered it there the day it went live for everybody and um I got that email on
monday that a lot of people got that said oh uh you're not going to be getting that console until
december 31st you know at some point until then some so I knew I wasn't going to be getting it
tuesday so um I was like crap I've got to go find somewhere that I can actually like try to
find one of these on shelves so shane said he heard that best buy and target were doing things
so he was on best buys website I was on target's website and I was able to get one long story short
at target so I went into a store and picked one up at target um and you could I had to go to the
other side of town to do it but I was I was like hey I got one whatever I'm good so that process
honestly was pretty easy um they didn't shrink wrap the box or anything they didn't even put it
in a bag they and there's no handle on that box so the dude just kind of brought it out was like here
you go and like handed me the box which I had to take take this xbox series x out to the parking
lot to my car like just no way to hide it but you're mugging yeah I know right thankfully it
was still light out and there's signs at target they're everywhere that are like security cameras
still in use uh that whole thing but I made it home um and again a big reason why I opted for
series x as opposed to playstation 5 is because I have a playstation 4 pro I don't have an xbox 1x
so I figured the jump from xbox one the xbox series x was going to be a bigger jump and I
really think I was right um so one of the games I've been playing a lot of on series x is no man
sky yep I never shut up about that game and I've started that game probably over like seven times
well guess what bitches I started my eighth playthrough thanks to a game pass and having
that on series x you will notice if you have xbox the new one if you go into the game pass library
it has a little icon in the corner that says enhanced for xbox series x or s has a little logo
for that so you can actually see the games and uh no man's sky of course is one of them we talked
about on last week's show that it was going to be getting that and um there's a bunch of others too
dead by daylight forza horizon the new ori game um and so forth so there's there's plenty of games
that have gotten the upgrades and did I notice the upgrades for no man's sky on series x um compared
to playstation 4 pro yes I did um it number one is the loading times my god like I used to have
to sit there for a minute and a half you know while it's loading into the galaxy in my plate
that now it's down to seconds it's like 20 seconds 30 seconds um something like that it's
it's crazy um and um I I notice the graphics um I I do notice a little bit of pop in um but I
noticed that on any of the consoles or I've I've noticed pop in on pc I just think it's part of how
the algorithm is in that game um but the thing that kind of strikes me is that I notice the high
definition textures even on things that are in the distance and that's probably the biggest thing
that I noticed playing on series x versus playing on any other system I've played on I've played
that game on a lot of systems um especially I will say I played no man's sky just a little bit
on xbox one when it first went to game pass it's it's garbage on the original xbox one compared to
what it is now like the game the game hasn't changed but the graphics like night and day
night and day it looks so much better so um I uh yeah I enjoy uh I enjoy I'm enjoying uh
no man's sky again I've probably dropped easily like 10 hours on the latest playthrough
I am blowing up my twitter with screenshots because that's one of my favorite things to do
in that game because I just like you know I people say no man's sky is kind of like minecraft and
there is it's it's definitely crafting is the backbone of the game um but minecraft to me
everything looks very samezy you're either overground you're underground you're in the
nether you know but there's only so many different environments that's the thing about no man's sky
that really strikes me is that every time you go to this new planet it's going to look a lot
different from where you were at before yes there's there's some basic types that they all
kind of fit into but there's definitely enough variety and enough rare stuff that happens to
kind of keep things exciting and that's that's part of why I really enjoy no man's sky um here's
the other interesting thing I noticed with series x though is that because I didn't do xbox 1x
there's some games that were already enhanced for xbox 1x that I kind of missed so I went to
go check some of those out too so some of the other games I played this week I played skyrim
the definitive edition whatever the they call the remaster one because alan is back into playing
that on pc so he's playing that a lot so I was like oh I'll download this to show it to him on
xbox and we were both kind of taken with wow this looks really good like you know it's like playing
max settings on a pc but it's on my tv and the frame rate very good like when you're looking
around and stuff that whole opening when you're in the back of the cart and everything sometimes
you know the frame rate could get a little weird there if you're looking around a lot of pop in on
the trees and stuff looks very fluid on the xbox series x you definitely notice it so I think
that's another thing that you know it's very similar to how if you're playing playstation
4 games on playstation 5 it's like oh like god of war is like 60 frames a second now like
everything's like running better a lot of that is happening with the xbox one games too I think
even on things they're not advertising our xbox series s or x the other one that I played a little
bit of that I was like wow this looks so good was final fantasy 15 and you know that game has
its pluses and it has its minuses but I will say it looks great in 4k um but you know I I that was
the first time I'd really gotten to play that in true 4k so um kind of interesting uh other games
I checked out on the series x this week uh I checked out tetris effect connected I did not
like that multiplayer is only restricted to ranked or play with friends so there's no casual
mode that's unranked I was a little disappointed in that otherwise it's um tetris effect without
the vr part which is still a great game and worth uh you taking a look at if you have a game pass or
what have you um and then forza horizon 4 I looked at briefly for a little bit and of course that
game looks great too and it's just one of those things where how fast that game moves that game
moves so fast and it looks so good while it's doing it so I I definitely am noticing like
the fluid like you get more constant 60 frames a second things look really good in the distance
as well as they do close up I am noticing some of those like subtleties in this new generation but
are the games themselves different yet well no because most of the launch games are all bumped
back especially on the xbox side we barely got anything on the xbox side you got the yakuza you
got assassin's creed and stuff but nothing that really feels distinctly next generation and I'm
imagining it not until the new halo game or something really strong first party or really
going to see that but that being said I'm very I'm very happy with the xbox series x it's like
getting a brand new video card in the computer and a new chip and like getting that upgrade that
really gives it a kick in the pants and now you want to go back and play all your old favorites
to see how smooth they run again it's very that and that's that phase we're in right now while we
wait for these other big launch titles so um some comments from chat I'm sorry I've been ignoring
you guys um Bobby Blackwell says yeah I've been playing Final Fantasy 15 on my xbox 1x and it's
beautiful um let's see uh bonds 006 says I'm playing Tetris Effect with a girlfriend on xbox
she will learn the ways of Tetris well Tetris is for for everybody boys and girls and
everything uh all the peoples um let's see um sj100 matt says I'm really getting a series x
first to play game pass and at some point cyberpunk I will be getting uh enjoying
forest horizon 4 when I eventually do get my series x which will be some time week of thanksgiving
um act def says which of these will rob end up with more of no man's sky playthroughs or copies
of mass effect 3 uh this would be like my eighth no man's sky playthrough but it's not my eighth
copy of no man's sky uh it's just I've started a new playthrough every time they do a big patch so
I think no man's sky is gonna have a beat Bobby Blackwell says I think no man's sky also got a
playstation 5 upgrade yes it did uh and I would fully expect all the nice things I said about
xbox excuse me all the nice things I said about no man's sky on xbox series x are probably going
to apply to the playstation 5 as well and anybody jumping up from an original playstation 4 version
I'm I'm fairly positive you're going to think all those same things um so there is that um
I will say I've noticed a few bugs in no man's sky I tweeted one of them I died instantly on
loading one of my saves that was a bummer but you know things happen um and uh sometimes when the
aliens tend to hold objects or they're talking to you and the objects kind of vibrate and shake
and move everywhere like they're not staying in one place um I feel like these are things that
we're gonna see a patch from hello games in a week or two the only thing that broke the game was that
loading bug and I feel like that may not be I feel like that may just happen in that game and it may
not be exclusive to an xbox thing I feel like you can probably get that on pc honestly so there is
that um okay um I think that's pretty much all I need to say on my gaming week uh Loki any anything
else on the xbox that I missed no not really I can't think of anything are you happy with your
purchase so far do you think are you glad you got one now um yeah I'm happy that I got it I'm gonna
be really happy once cyberpunk comes out even though I already have it purchased on pc um I'll
get it twice I guess um I don't know I mean I probably didn't need it right away but
you know it's it's better just to get it now and then instead of trying to fight to get it later
on I guess all right well let's see if anybody wants to add anything to their gaming weeks outside
of these new consoles so dark soccer I'll start with you because I'm sure your gaming oh you just
popped up you good to go okay uh and you just I didn't you might be muted still but um how was
your oh there you go okay how was your gaming week dark soccer outside of new consoles well we
picked up a thing for um Dan's birthday that's a new console oh what but I'm not talking about it
yet okay I have a story about it later uh oh okay I know where this is going okay okay got it a
thing that ign ranked above the xbox and the playstation 5 okay I'm curious all right we'll
talk about that in a minute then yeah so I so I actually played some of it today uh again that
will come up later um I played a little bit of pinball um it's been kind of hard to play anything
else and playing animal crossing we just had our driveway done so it was really loud outside and I
could hardly hear anything and on top of that anytime I tried to play something that like would
get me excited um well my heart would start racing really badly and I would almost have
an asthma attack so I'm keeping it calm just keeping it calm lots of wordscapes and lots of
animal crossing and a little bit of pinball but you know it gets the heart racing a bit much
is it was basically coming off of the prednisone anything that I was playing that would kind of you
know kick me up into into overdrive would uh get my heart rate racing too fast because the
prednisone so now that I'm off of it I can play some stuff again so yay no scary games for a
little bit oh no scary games are fine because they don't really scare me it's just things that are
more like actiony you know okay so um but uh I've uh I've got a few few things coming up on my plate
and I'm finally once uh all of this is behind me I'm gonna do my charity stream
so you get to see uh I think that um dream daddy went out on my pole
so I'm gonna gonna get me a daddy let's see which daddy I go for might get myself a nice bear
oh it's not the first time I've heard that all right probably not from an ace girl
uh loki anything you wanted to add to your gaming week outside of the new stuff
um well just you know I did like I said I did play a little bit of Minecraft I played a lot
more Minecraft though on pc and I was working on our realm that um myself and my kids have so I was
finishing up this giant roller coaster with like tons of redstone stuff in it um so I finished up
the actual like coaster part of that still need to decorate it but it's our our giant um
creeper mine type roller coaster thing it's kind of fun because we actually have like a creeper in
a minecart that we have triggered to go at certain times so you see him like zoom by
if I have to add some more of that stuff in there have to probably shoot some video for it at some
point and then also uh my youngest son wanted me to play egg wards with him on one of the
Minecraft servers out there so I tried that today as well and unfortunately it's hard to play with
people that you don't know that there's no strategy or anything and no one's talking
and everybody's just kind of doing their own thing or just idling there so that was fun um
but yeah he was really excited about it so oh and Orna played more Orna yep that's about it yeah I
don't think I have a lot to add to my gaming week outside of the consoles except you know continuing
my uh my paladin in final fantasy 14 hit 80 so there's another class at 80. I will say to answer
act f's earlier question I have more jobs at max level in final fantasy 14 than I do playthroughs
of no man's sky if you want to know the game I really play too much of there's your answer there
but I also did a live stream of that earlier this week because I was like I haven't done a stream in
a long time um my some aspects of my mental health are actually improving um I can't imagine why um
but I was in a place where I felt like I could I could do a stream earlier this week so I did
um and uh yeah it felt pretty good I'll have to do more I I've been directly asked on twitter by
multiple people if I will do no man's sky on the xbox series x as a stream yes I just don't know
what night yet so um stay tuned for that on my personal channel at rob roberts um and then uh
you know kind of the gps stuff um I'm a little irritated with the niantic gps stuff but I'm
gonna save that for another week I want to I want to marinate on that and see how I feel in seven
days um but I have been playing orna still so that's um that's pretty good so yeah um I'm
looking for other suggestions of gps games that I haven't like I I thought I was on top of all of
them but I think there's some that I've missed out on so um I I was writing a tweet about that
so I'm kind of curious if I might discover anything new this week we'll see so uh yeah
act deaf to chat says that's true final fantasy 14 is the game you're always playing yes that is
very true but it's kind of the social element of that game for sure but a lot of people like for
some people call of duty is that game because they get online with their friends and play that game
for some people um destiny is that game because they get online or destiny 2 whatever get online
and play you know what I mean a lot of people have that kind of game that their friends get
together and play for some people um it's dungeons and dragons you know before the
pandemic people were getting together and playing dnd during the pandemic they're doing it on zoom
you know and other alternative board game types of things so there's always game night for something
to run a game what's that I'm just looking for someone to run a game for me to be in
oh you should you should run second edition for me you should uh get a podcast type thing
together dm I'm a shitty dm no no but you don't have to dm it you can be the one that records it
and publishes it if you want but I need someone to run it and I need someone to run second edition
dnd for me all right well y'all y'all heard her y'all heard dark soccer's request get in touch
with her on twitter you're a twitter person now you you weren't using the site very much at all
for a long time and now just in the past few months your twitter's been on fire I'm pretty
exclusive on it now I mean I need like this is a stupid ego thing but I really wish that I had
like the eight more followers to hit a thousand because I did ignore it for a while you know yeah
and now I've got two of them don't forget I have gen x geeks because of course my blog and which
my blog is actually I feel like it's starting to to do better I found my flow on it oh good so um
but but I mean yeah okay so you have two twitter accounts on your phone
do you know how do you know how many I have I have this I'm just showing it from a distance
I have one so I have my okay one two three four five six seven eight nine I have nine accounts
on my phone nine twitter accounts because yeah and no there's no after dark alt we're gonna rule
that out right now that is not one of them okay but I have me olr horde house I haven't used this
in 2014 uh my very secret day job twitter account that nobody knows about nobody's going to know
about that is not an invitation to go find it um because that is that is me separating day and
night stuff vog network guys on a show reading his fundamental podcast pokey stop podcast and shaking
and crying I have nine twitter accounts now granted I only use maybe three of those
with any regularity anymore but it's just funny so soon soon you'll have more of them because I mean
I made one for the sisters a long ass time ago I had like another personal one that
was going to be super private that I never used and I had lady 99 for a while when I was doing my
sort of uh protest stuff and I just said fuck it I'll just be public about my protesting gotcha
so I mean I've got I've got maybe about that many just that I've had for different purposes
and different organizations that I'm in but right now I'm focusing on those two because um I want
to have something dedicated for my blog um and then um something that's just like my thing that
I can complain at everybody about and uh get overwhelmed with people posting about
chipping on supernatural I've noticed a lot of supernatural chat on your twitter this week but
I get it because the show I know is winding down and hey you know what Stacey Abrams is talking
about supernatural on her twitter so you're in good company oh yeah no that's cool she's been
getting some love from the cast uh as well um and I've actually been I've had a couple of just
little quick chats with with some of the some of the folks who do some good things I've actually
really started getting involved I know this is completely different started getting involved
with random acts.org um that uh some of the people who have been or associated with the cast um
organized for doing basically good charity work but also just encouraging everyone to be a little
kinder so be kind and run me a dnd game well I I have lots of kind things I could say about Stacey
Abrams I'm not even going to make it a political thing I mean yes I I love her politics but just
even outside of that and even if you are you know in a different political mind
spot I will say I love the fact that she is like an out nerd in politics and she's very you know
she talks about supernatural did you see that video where she was ranking all the star tracks
and she wasn't sitting there going well I always like she like she had her facts she's like I like
this one because of this story and what it does is I was like okay okay not not that anyone should
ever have to prove I wasn't top on there though I don't want to hear it ds9 was not top sorry
uh what did she put on top maybe she did no no she put voyager on top because I was like yes
yes me too I was like I that's another reason I love her she put voyager on top
voyager wasn't didn't deserve the bad rap that it got yeah I I still say deep space nine is the
best of them all yeah but no I mean she she not and I was gonna say not that anyone should ever
have to prove her fandom but there is something extra special about the fact that she had like she
had deep answers anyway I'm sorry this isn't the Stacey Abrams fan club podcast I mean it could be
but it's uh it's OLR let's talk about other video games uh anything else for our gaming weeks I
think we got it all out let's then move on to some news there's been a lot that's been going on in
the news um about new consoles and other stuff as well right Loki uh yes so of course more
information coming out about the consoles and what they support and don't support
so one bit of um information that we have is right now the playstation 5 doesn't support
1440p resolutions so if you have a monitor that's 1440p well you're just gonna have to play it at
1080p instead um which is unfortunate because I know a lot of people that are getting high
refresh rate monitors may only be able to get 1440p like the one I got right now I was hoping
to get an hdmi 2.1 because that's what all these new consoles are um but there aren't any monitors
or hdmi 2.1 right now so that's basically what you need to be able to do 120 frames per second
and 4k at the same time so now I can only do 4k and 60 fps or I could do 1440p at 120 so that's
kind of what I'm sticking with at least on the Xbox side but the Xbox series x does support 1440p
so that's always good um now whether that may be coming to the playstation 5 later possibly because
right now according to the VP of platform management uh Hideki Nishino basically said that
they wanted to prioritize tv support that's why that 1440p isn't currently supported because
that's mainly a monitor format and not a tv um but later on there's um no reason no technical reasons
to be able to support that later on so that may be something that's coming if demand um requires
it to um along with that there are some issues with some of the games that are backwards
compatible that may have um problems playing now we talked about last week how there are some of
the assassins creed games that were not being supported 100 and actually one of those assassins
creed syndicate I believe is one of those that does have an issue playing it does actually run
but their shadows are kind of like strobing a bit it's all glitched out but up the 4000 plus titles
that are backwards compatible they said about 115 of those are tagged as um you may experience game
behavior or unexpected game behavior while playing this playstation 4 game on your ps5 console
so is that why ubisoft had it remember that story a couple weeks ago and we were like
maybe ubisoft wasn't running the same version emulator at least that was my theory and ubisoft
outed all these games it's not backwards compatible and they pulled it so it sounds
like there may have been some like a truthiness in that because okay assassins creed is backwards
compatible but or syndicate specifically is backwards compatible but it's got some flaws
yeah like for example they talked about some of the other um annoyances that you may run into grip
for example you can um it says that there's issues but nothing's really been noticeable
everybody's golf there's some flick you're a flickering scenery graphics mainly the trees
it could be like how that stuff is being rendered and certain engines um and emulators even going
back to like nes emulators have had this issue like um i remember castlevania 3
the vertical scrolling levels were the biggest pain to get emulated for the longest time
because they're the way those were being kind of like done was very different and the emulators
didn't know how to do it so if you tried to play castlevania 3 early on back in my day in the nes
emulator days this was college so yes i was using emulators and playing all sorts of stuff in them
um but like you couldn't get past you know the like second part of the first level of
castlevania 3 because it was a vertical scrolling part anyway just it's just emulators have always
had these problems because they're emulating they're not perfectly the hardware right so
just you know um keep in mind that you know you may run into some issues they have a backwards
compatibility page that talks about um some of the issues that you may run into but you know it's
it's not to say that they are always going to be broken it could be that they fix them down the
line but at launch i mean four thousand out of you know um and only having like a hundred of
those kind of broken that's not bad so um yeah and then on top of that though um i i don't know if
anyone's really asked the question about region locking but apparently the playstation 5 games
are also going to be region free which i believe it was the same with the playstation 4 i i'm kind
of glad that we've moved past the whole region locking with video games um so hopefully that
stays the same but yeah apparently it is been confirmed via their faq's that yes it is still
region free so that's good i would assume though the same might not be able to be said about
uh all uh placey or i should say uh 4k blu-rays i'm not sure if those are still region locked
but at least the games themselves are not
hmm how where so i mean region locking thing thing of the past right well yeah we haven't
really seen it since uh the playstation 3 i think um on sony side yes nintendo
i think 3d wasn't 3ds or ds i feel like it was more recent on the xbox no the xbox 360 was
region locked the playstation 3 i cannot remember if that was region locked the thing maybe there
might have been some games that were some that weren't um nintendo side i want to say
probably the wii u i know that their cartridge games weren't but i don't know if the wii u discs
were region locked um obviously i don't think the switch games are but i know 3ds and nintendo ds
games were not locked all right well um let's move on then and let's oh actually let me get
some quick chat messages here because uh bobby blackwolf says uh note that there's no dolby
vision or atmos in playstation 5 and there never will be it seems um he does say it going to say
though that 4k uhd blu-rays will pass through fine if you turn on bitstream audio output in
the dvd player settings menu and that has to do with a like a licensing thing for that technology
probably right i'm assuming well yeah because i know with atmos like i have my headphones i'm
wearing right now actually are adobe atmos um and i had to download the app because i had to do that
on pc as well i download the app um and put in a serial number that i got with my headphones
to be able to use the atmos part of that or the seven one surround sound um but yeah i did the
same thing on the series x thankfully it worked without having any troubles like because i was
like oh no enter a serial number i don't have that anymore um but thankfully because i purchased it
on pc that it remembered it all right well moving on let's talk about something that was all over
social media earlier this week when it was happening because this was unfortunately one
of those things that was kind of playing out live um and you know that can be both a good thing and
a bad thing um good because you can follow along but bad because a lot of stuff kind of gets thrown
in that isn't necessarily true and that is the situation that happened with ubisoft montreal
earlier this week um a couple days ago uh in the afternoon uh there was a really scary situation
that happened there um that uh there was talk on social media about oh my gosh there's like an
armed gunman that went into the building and was shooting and all of this well yes and that's the
part that social media thankfully got incorrect apparently that was the type of thing that had
been called in however the whole thing if you hadn't heard by this point it ended up being a
fake 911 call that triggered all these events that happened on friday um so there was a bunch
of stuff that was uploaded to twitter and that's why all this kind of like you know talk about what
was going on um had happened from um so yeah some folks had been working from home because uh you
know the pandemic some were still in the office so some people were tweeting like i know those
people on the roof because those are you know my co-workers and stuff um it was it was unfortunately
a fake 911 call that appears to be some type of swatting event um that happened which definitely
just makes us go like uh it's just it's kind of just disgusting that these swatting events still
happen um you know and why was ubisoft montreal targeted um it is very easy to tie that to gaming
culture because we've seen the swatting thing happen with you know twitch streams and and
things of that sort um and you know it's it's i i shouldn't make that assumption that it's because
they're a gaming company and somebody was upset about games that they did this unfortunately
track record kind of makes that a safe assumption that it probably was some type of weird
somebody trying to prove a point um and you might look at this and go well nobody was hurt
um uh do you know the psychological trauma this type of shit can put on people
seriously like read the accounts of some people who have gone through this on their social media
and stuff like this um there was definitely damage done so this is not an ever oh nobody got hurt
hahaha type of situation um when you do this type of swatting stuff i i know i appreciate the choir
here with this audience and you guys that are tuning in here are decent enough to know this
but i'm gonna say it anyway um you know when you're doing that swatting stuff to you know
haha get a rise out of people you are hurting you're intending to hurt and harm people
and it's about time that the law really caught up with that and had some really severe punishments
um on a on a on a national or at least state level scale um of how that's dealt with now
because i'm sure somebody will jump in there and say oh this happened in canada um
again i don't i don't know how to eloquently phrase this um but if i am to make any sort of
lemonade out of the the lemons that is this news the fact that it happened in canada makes me go
well maybe somebody will do something about this swatting thing now you know maybe something will
happen from the canadian government to really take a look at this issue how it happened why
it happened and look at never making it happen again and then hopefully the u.s can you know
use it as a blueprint and other countries too we don't want to just you know focus on north america
but this this swatting shit is dangerous and it has to stop um and um yeah i don't know what
else to say about that anybody want to add to that i can go to our chat too um act efton chat says uh
we know that ubisoft isn't the best company out there but this shouldn't happen to anyone at all
yeah no the the reputation and all that stuff if if this had happened to ea comcast
whatever like worst company you can think of i would say the exact same thing this is unacceptable
period um no one special 77 says plus since the police were tied up in a fake call that was fewer
cops that were unavailable for a legit call and in a legit situation where cops weren't there
folks could have been easily hurt um you know say a car accident had happened where people were
seriously injured somewhere you know you're right that takes police away from the availability to
do something like that um so it's um it's gross pod culture says even evil g even evil g absolutely
anybody anybody meant anybody so anyway it's an attempt for a party to show power over another
party and really it's not just for the recipient um you know who is uh definitely going to be
suffering um you know trauma from this but the person themselves it's indicative of serious uh
mental health problems that need to be addressed and people have died from it yeah oh yeah oh yeah
yeah we heard about the guy that got shot it was horrible it was like the neighbor or something i
don't know but it was it was horrible i'm sure that wasn't the only one it's so anyway sorry
i don't mean to drag things down i mean at least we can say okay at least it wasn't a shooting
situation but it's it's not really honest is it it's not right down yeah it's not really good news
so anyway not all news is good it doesn't have to be yeah so the the news doesn't care how it
makes you feel it's true the news is news just like science is science no matter what you believe
that's true so i'm gonna i'm gonna hope this had nothing to do with gaming culture but i'm gonna
know in the back of my mind i'm wrong and it is so anyway we'll see we'll see let's move on how
about something that is good news dark soccer how about something a little more light-hearted well
this is what i was referring to earlier um my husband's birthday is coming up a couple of days
after thanksgiving um we often have to deal with this and i've been racking my brain what am i
gonna get him what am i gonna get him and he's like i found myself something and i bought it
for myself from you for my birthday okay thanks oops so we have the uh the game and watch handheld
the new one um it is basically um in the semblance of the old game and watch it actually isn't
doesn't feel as as hefty as an old game and watch you know um but it's got like the color scheme
the branding and everything on it but it comes with um a uh uh built-in uh uh lcd screen um
that uh hat that will play three different games uh one of them is of course super mario brothers
um i had to get i had to like re-familiarize myself with the controller because it feels
different than playing it with the nes controller um and then there's super mario brothers 2 which
as we know it is lost levels which is basically the i bet you want to cry while playing mario
the game um and then the um uh there's ball you remember ball it was i believe the first game and
watch game um that uh i don't know i said lcd going back it was the the juggling game with
the balls but this time it's got mario's face on it although honestly it looks more like luigi but
does it the way they have like the little plates or something like that it's kind of moving back
and forth and the different okay it's just little balls and you get them from hand to hand yeah
well to be to be honest it is one of the easter eggs but there is a way to get luigi and ball
anyway yeah there there's actually video now that shows uh every one of the easter eggs including
the uh the image galleries and uh uh the oshi screen and how to you know get a warp pipe and
everything and the bowser fights um but at any rate because it is a game and watch it also has
the clock built in and the clock has different uh super mario brothers uh scenery uh playing through
it i don't know why why is then i'm just sorry i got like a little tongue tied for a moment
but basically um you know the time gives you the super mario theme clock and it kind of ticks along
with it um and it changes from day to night um with the with the you know with the hours
um and is that something that's kind of just meant to be running like on your shelf full time
since they have like the clock thing okay well was your was your game and watch meant to run
all the time no but it's been 30 years yeah but the with the game and watch is you know if you
didn't have a watch with you you could use the watch on your game and watch
oh okay i see the game and a watch but at any rate um you know i'm going to say this you know
it's it's it's neat you know it actually is a fun little nod it's definitely a novelty sort of thing
um and i still thought it was hilarious that ign ranked it higher than the uh
than the ps5 and the xbox um why did they do that besides for clicks why what was their
what was their justification in that i think fun factor okay yeah but at any at any rate you know
it's a really cool little thing it's got some nods you can look at it you know it's it's fun
you can play super mario brothers the screen is bigger than the gameboy micro so i mean hey
um it honestly though and this is just me um maybe it felt like it was
that was a good word for it i guess not super hefty does that make sense yeah like it felt
really lightweight i'm not gonna say cheap but it did feel really lightweight and the uh
you know the the buttons were you know light everything was just light about it um and and
i mean it is pretty much a a gimmick it's a fun gimmick but honestly i kind of want one of those
little game gears more than this but dan wanted this and dan got this and it's his birthday so
what i want doesn't matter um but i think it is uh pretty pretty cool i'm waiting to see what
the hackers do to it you know it's funny you bring that up because bob coffee and chat says
it'll be interesting to see if someone hacks it to play other nes games my understanding is and
i said it already was yeah i was gonna say i think i saw this on our discord over at vog
network.com slash discord i think that's where i saw it um somebody had um posted that it already
has been somebody got the like a hacked mario rom on there that actually will show the message hacked
so um it's happening i wasn't even looking at chat until you said that bob coffee said something
yeah but um but i mean um it's it's a really neat little thing you know i'm glad i'm glad we have it
you know it's it's really cute and it's definitely you know we're we're sort of stuck in our hardcore
nintendo uh fandomism right now you know i mean dan just the other day says i don't want another
system that isn't a nintendo system i'm like oh yeah same kind of right now but and so he
was right the next system he bought was a nintendo system a little gimmicky tiny nintendo system but
it's cute and it's great and it's a little fun thing and it was kind of fun playing super mario
brothers on a game and watch you know even though it's not quite the same size as an old game and
watch but um but yeah that's cool and you know if you want you know just something kind of fun to
have on the go with a little nostalgia i mean you could do worse yeah i have to admit i totally
forgot that that thing was even coming out with you know all the hysteria around the new consoles
and trying to order them until i saw like a couple of people on twitter were posting their pictures
in the box saying look what i got instead and this is kind of like the same type of thing i'm like oh
yeah nintendo was launching a console this week too uh i'll put a picture on my twitter but um
yeah i mean in in all kidding aside about nintendo's big console entry into the next
generation uh i obviously the switch is still gonna sell like crazy this this holiday because
not only is it the switch but it's got a pretty robust library of games so there's still going
to be an audience of people that you're going to want to play things like uh breath of the wild
mario kart and so forth and now of course the mario kart live as we've seen is is going to
probably be a big toy that a lot of kids want and so forth so um yeah and then the game and watch
is a nice little entry to the collectibles um kind of interesting to see that that's where nintendo
is going from the nes classic and the snes classic everybody was like where's the 64
classic or the game boy classic well we got a game and watch classic which maybe isn't
on the top of people's lists but it's maybe something to hold us over for another year or
two until one of those other things we talked about are going so thinking that they're really
trying to use that nostalgia to bank of course it's almost like and maybe i'm a little bit off
base on this one but i'm wondering if it's sort of like nintendo's fundraising right now
um well no we just i i think our show got cut off right before this story came up last week but we
did have a story on the list about how the switch no i think you might have got to it i don't
remember but there was a story about how the switch has outsold the nes already yeah we we
were about to get cut off so i just threw it in okay yeah so um that that whole thing was was
there so the switch is still selling like crazy so i don't think they need to fundraise but certainly
there's going to be the question of well we are a publicly traded company how can we make our
investors more money and that's the answer more money if if they did a kirby one i would buy it
they'd have to have like a lot of kirby games on it i just want the the the game in kirby um tiger
claw and chat says you think they'll do another game and watch of another game um and orange
right echoes the kirby answer but also says i think they're definitely going to make more game
and watches isn't a major zelda anniversary coming up yes i believe next year would be 30
because this year is 35 for mario right so next year's 35 for zelda or something like that i could
i could be off but um i i think uh yeah zelda's zelda's coming up and i wouldn't i wouldn't be
surprised though honestly you know what they want to release for zelda's 35th anniversary
breath of the wild 2 that's probably going to be next holiday's game and i i think
that that's plenty big enough of a zelda anniversary treat so yeah all right well
anyhow let's move on we have more stories and uh loki a big one in gaming culture right now right
oh yes fun times when we when we're talking about the um the rights of music industry
or music holders so the ria and mpa um so anyways twitch you may remember they had
a whole dmca fiasco where they were um taking down people's channels um because they had
you know copyrighted music in their clips and of course they had really terrible tools for um not
even necessarily identifying which you know video you may have had that had that but basically kind
of like this nuclear delete everything option was one of the ways to go or you know you could
possibly face you know copyright strikes and your channel being deleted so it's really it was only
like a mass deletion tool and they only really gave folks you know a few days notice about that
so of course they came out and apologized you know saying you know it's basically you know we
understand that you're rightly upset with the only option we provided was a mass deletion tool for
clips and that we only gave you three days notice to use this tool we could have developed more
sophisticated user-friendly tools a while ago that we didn't is on us yeah no kidding you think you
live in the same universe that youtube's in you see all the stories about how you know all the
copyright stuff they have to go through and you thought that sucks for them and not thinking at
all about your own company it's kind of stupid and so of course they said it that was a mistake
is or um and we could have provided creators with a longer time period to address their vod and clip
libraries that was a miss as well we're truly sorry for these mistakes and we'll do better
except you know they're not because that's never going to be the case it's never going to be the
end so of course what's going on now well the same stuff you normally see on youtube so for example
there was um someone by the name of um makal ronan who said that they had only music they've
had on their streams was in-game world of warcraft music played by the game itself yet they've got
muted audio on their latest vod because apparently in senjin village um there is the copyrighted
music banger called medium windstorm with gus whistles and low rumble from sound effects from
hollywood edge sound effects library first off i don't think that those should ever be part of the
copyright dmca you know system anyways it's sound effects especially if well okay i i i don't want
to spoil but i have to say there is another story in the news this week that is exactly this
and for the record sound effects actually do require a bit of engineering and design
so yes it is somebody's intellectual property yeah i i can't support it's it's a weird thing
i i don't think i can support the fact that you know the sound effects people shouldn't be
entitled to their thing but but if it's like i i feel like if it's already in the umbrella of
the game that you license especially when the game has said we do not care if you broadcast our game
then at some point there's got to be a happy medium there where the streamer is absolved of
those incidental sound effects that have happened in the background now if a streamer brings in
their own sound board and their own sound effects and starts playing that stuff different that's
different and absolutely i think that's fine because and this is why honestly like i'm gonna
be honest and this isn't what you guys want to hear but i have always been like i'm not gonna
play spotify in the background of my streams and i i i i'll watch streams where people do it and
i don't care what other people do but i feel like y'all are on borrowed time like they're gonna come
in and stop that and sure enough here we are and people are like what i couldn't play spotify about
i couldn't play i couldn't play Madonna while i was playing my games no like i felt like that
whole stuff was on borrowed time well however i do think that if the game says you can stream us
online then this stuff is in the game and it makes that stuff like guitar hero and music based games
in this really weird gray area i get it but i i'm not surprised at the music part of it the sound
effect stuff gets a little bit tricky and we've seen on youtube where this gets abused so i also
because i don't want to see us make it sound like oh i agree in every single instance no no there's
cases where somebody is you know in some third party comes in and sound matches that this happened
to one of my youtube videos and um i contested it and it took forever but it was one of those things
where it's the principle of the thing you know right i feel like there has to be a way to strike
back against incorrect claims well i've seen i've seen some where they've actually there's been a
guy whispering or something like that was the clip they made it a private clip and it got copyright
claimed for something he's like dude that was my own voice like yeah i don't understand that's why
when i'm getting ready to start doing mine i'm going to be doing all the music myself
and with my own copyright uh notice on on my youtube channel well that's what's funny it's
like there was a thing i saw a video talking about like the copyright system and youtube and stuff
and apparently the way someone's gotten around is they make a really terrible and you well not
necessarily terrible but like a really unique intro or extro song or outro song and you copy
you actually submit that to one of those copyright claim um companies that will actually go out there
and flag that and so all of your videos are technically copyright claimed by yourself so
it's like huh they can't two companies can't claim the same video allegedly or like it the way the
money system works it doesn't allow it to flag it or something like that but basically it would
it's not demonetizing and actually this works also for allegedly um monetizing unmonetizable
things because you're basically a copyright claiming yourself so you're kind of abusing the
system i don't feel so bad for the system to be honest considering how broken it is but that is
one way around it that you could do um which i thought was interesting uh also the copyright
deadlock that uh jim sterling of course uh famously created was pretty funny uh where two
companies fight over the copyright claim for one video and technically two different companies
can't claim the same content because no one is the owner then you can't say it's my content and then
the other company says oh but that's my content as well it doesn't work that way um the the
government is going to have to step in and fix this and modernize these rules and um you know i
i don't think that necessarily suddenly happens just because we're going to have a change in the
administration because you know there's just there's so many other things i think they're
they're looking at and so forth however i will say this one thing we talked about at length a
couple weeks ago was the whole like alexandria ocasio-cortez got into live streaming and was
doing that among us stream that essentially became a huge like political awareness rally
that happened on twitch right and there were other people from other political parties watching that
like justin amash who wanted to kind of leverage something like that for himself and so on and so
on so i think as you start to see more politicians get into this just wait wait for the day that aoc
gets a copyright strike on one of her things that's what it's gonna take the whole copyright
system needs to be like redone it's just been abused the hell by disney and other companies
ria it they have like these i mean they really should be accounting for fair use um like for
example one of the examples of another music thing that was taken down was a cover of a song
that someone was covering and they they copyright strike it for the original or um someone using
like a five second clip to make a remix or something like that or five second clip of a song
for some sort of you know uh comedic effect or something and it gets the whole video gets
copyrighted for a five second clip that just seems ridiculous um phoenix 7726 says they won't in the
same way twitter never banned trump they can see that coming a mile away except well this when
they're running bots and automated shit wait until one of them gets caught up in it like the
twitter situation's very different because twitter has had to put a flag on the account that basically
says you know never never disable or ban this although somebody did remember that yeah for like
three hours well it's just temporarily and it's feeling because it's you know an official channel
well not really supposed to be an official channel but it's basically it's a government um
communication media or something like that now oh so could the army recruitment twitch get struck
um well no because see basically like for example they can't ban people from their channels because
it's it's technically like a government entity uh no i'm saying if they play the wrong game could
the army get a copyright strike i don't know that's i'm telling you do you really want to
anger the army i mean that that's how this and i in in a way i kind of do hope it happens and
not in the way you think i'm saying that i'm helping it happens because that is what's going
to get the government to move on this stuff and you know modernize the the copyright law and all
that stuff so anyway all right but we can't fix copyright law tonight on our uh but just be
careful on twitch um i i i don't know what else to say about that um the sound effect thing is
really scary and i because you know you don't know what games you thought the the creators
are totally cool with you playing on stream and then it's like gotcha you know it's that part's
a little bit scary i i that doesn't make any sense it doesn't i i get it like it just seems like a
stretch like you know like if you're licensing sound effects like that you you know that you're
dealing with certain types of clientele it's not like i don't see how it's wind sounds so obviously
you know an ai is not gonna it it's not gonna know if that exactly matches that like i i don't know i
just feel like it makes mistakes and even like i've seen stuff you know on youtube for example
where they're just filming something outside in the park and it gets copyrighted claim for the
wind sounds it's like dude like yeah it's too much too much they're there there needs to be
and honestly the my idea you know i'm not a politician my idea is and i've been saying this
since the very beginning there needs to be a way to have an effective counter claim where the
claimant gets striped so that if they are filing too many claims and they do it overdo it too many
times they lose the ability to be able to do it or that's what needs to be in there or better yet
that they should basically if you're claiming something you can only claim the section of the
video that it's in so if i play a five second clip you're not claiming the whole video you're claiming
the five second portion of that video and right now even with youtube and sometimes youtube is a
little more specific about what it is that someone's claiming a lot of times those claims
could be it's supposed to be specific like this is the section where there's the offending material
but it's not a lot of times they're missing that and that is i think something that's supposed to
be important about the dmca there's it's supposed to those strikes are supposed to include that and
they're also supposed to consider fair use but because these corporations know that
there's nothing that you're going to be able to do they you know they don't necessarily have to
use fair use i mean we've seen people use dmca strikes to take down vias they just don't like
yeah you know yeah and use it as an excuse so it's it's a broken system all right well let me move on
i'm gonna get to our next story because i don't want the show to go all night but um let's talk
about a bunch of money changing hands somewhere else and that is because take two who of course
is the publisher behind you know grand theft auto borderlands you might have heard of them i think
loki's a little bit of a fan um take two has acquired code masters code masters of course
is a big company out of britain uh that makes a lot of like racing games i believe dirt five is
kind of their latest and greatest big title um so uh yeah they're gonna uh join the other labels
that take two oversees like 2k games which is you know like the the 2k sports and the civilization
and all that rock star games uh and private division so code masters is going to be there
uh no words yet as to is there going to be any restructuring or any moving around and things
like that um but uh in a comment uh to business wire the boss at take two straus zelnick said
that the racing output the code master does is going to fit well with the publishing giant's
existing sports fair um and then code masters will benefit from the distribution and marketing at
take two so it does kind of sound like it could be a mutually beneficial situation and i don't
really see that like these games are going to go anywhere they're going to suddenly put code masters
on like a different type of game but i mean we'll see what happens well you know it is take two
let's not let's not confuse things i like rockstar games i don't necessarily like take two okay two
is just about as bad as ea and activision they are going to monetize the crap out of this stuff
um well good for code masters at least you know that's a little bit more exposure i guess for
their games but it's just going to be a mess i mean just look at wwe and you know mba 2k
to get an idea of what take two likes to do with their franchises i mean so it's
uh best of luck to them all right good luck and may the odds be ever in your favor all right
moving on on a different note dar sakura
well you know i like to talk about um video games being used for for good um and cambridge uh the
cambridge researchers um actually put together a um a game that's supposed to help people online
learn how to debunk uh fake news i hate using the term fake news but meant to debunk disinformation
um how to recognize uh you know legitimate information versus misinformation um game is
called harmony square and it's just a simple web game um you basically are uh shown a a news story
um it it has like four different decision-based chapters to help you master these different
techniques um on how to spread fake news and troll and then you will can you will master those
techniques and learn then what it is that's prompting people to believe these things and
for you to evaluate your own feelings and your own triggers to make yourself think more critically
and it actually works um they tested it with 700 participants and then um you know they had them
rate headlines and social media posts prior to this um and then they had half of them play
harmony square and they have a half to play tetris and after it was huh no i'm just laughing
giggling at the the control group in that case and so they they had them do it again with different
headlines and then with their conclusion um that i'm going to quote the perceived reliability of
misinformation of the participants who played harmony square reduced to 16 um and their
willingness to share those things reduced by 11 and and even so i mean that's you know saying
that if that with that population split down the middle um 63 of that half that played it would
find misinformation significantly less reliable this is actually from the report um compared to
237 of the left half to navigate online information without the inoculation of harmony square
and you can um go to harmony square dot game and try it for yourself interesting and i'm
sorry i might have missed it at the beginning is this is this a game for kids or adults or like
all ages everybody okay it's just i i you know when i hear something like this i'm kind of like
this is the type of stuff i hope they're teaching kids in like high school or junior high you know
this is this is stuff like unfortunately that's where our society has evolved and um i know we
were playing things like oregon trail and number munchers and math blasters and stuff when we were
younger and i think there's still room for games like that um but like this is the type of thing
i hope they're using in school because unfortunately in this day and age uh that is not a skill that
is learned by everybody is how to not fall for bullshit uh and there's a lot of bullshit on
facebook and insert social media platform here so some yeah um no one special 77 in chat makes
a little joke saying cambridge needs to make 13 games to teach folks how to point out clickbait
articles game number seven will surprise you that's that's pretty good no one special in
in your uh history of joke making here on this program that's that's one of the better ones
so kudos to you all right but i i i i do love and dark soccer i'm glad you brought that story up
because i do love that idea of gamification or gamifying and gamification of a topic uh we need
to be educating more about and talking about for sure so whether whether whatever term you want to
use for it you know bullshit on social media is something we need to as a society get stronger in
dealing with so the the other thing too is that i i think of it like this that maybe it's a little
bit sad that we have to use a game to teach because people won't by themselves educate
themselves does that make sense people don't want to be educated they want to be entertained right
and that is honestly a social disease um since i have i think no well i'll just say since i've
done a lot with educating over the years i can see how games can sometimes work as an application
method because you know some people are going to learn by listening to the lecture some people are
going to learn by visually but with pretty charts and graphs or reading in a book something with
their eyes but a lot of people learn by doing and i kind of feel like games i mean yes they're games
but they're a way to learn by doing um especially when it comes to things that are more like soft
skills as opposed to put widget a on top of widget b you know in that type of application
like a game of this sort can be an application of it when you present a game with the purpose
of educating covertly people aren't going into it expecting to learn something but when you are in
you know a classroom environment and you're doing supplemental you know exercises or games people
are there knowing that they're there to learn and that this is i'll be honest i hate in class games
i just want you to give me the information let me learn it let me go um you know it is so funny
because all of my trainers where i work know this about me now and they're just like did you already
finish the modules like i finished all the days modules can i can i finish um but uh but back to
that you know it's some people do need it but when they know that they're being educated it's
a different thing if it is a game presented hey play this it's fun and then they learn something
from it that it's not what they think the primary purpose of it is then and you know if you if you
like hey this thing is is a problem and we need to learn how not to do it if you give that to them
they're gonna be like i guess i don't care versus hey here's this game to play oh wow i learned
something from this game i didn't expect it to happen you know what i mean yeah that's a
completely different thing like yeah i i am by the way i'm alert by doing myself i just hate those
exercises because i know that that's all it is i would rather you just give me the information and
let me figure it out i get the perspective of the i might pleasantly learn something while playing
a game like take a game like civilization you might actually learn something about history and
world leaders playing that game but that's not not why you signed up to play does that make sense so
yeah all right all right well let's move on and let's um go to loki with our next story
yeah so this is pretty cool like i know uh they did the similar things with different valve games
i can remember like portal and portal 2 had these in-game commentaries but now half-life alex also
shares that as they've now received um three hours of commentary in that game so you can actually
check it out within the game itself and it kind of talks about the behind the scenes and a
development process of the game itself including 147 points of interest to find and uh talking
about the hands-on nature of uh their narration and it's also available in several different
uh languages if you want subtitles so that's pretty awesome as well um pretty cool i i
still haven't finished this game so i really do need to go back and play more half-life alex
because it's pretty awesome but i do like the commentaries that were in there as well they're
always very interesting okay i was gonna ask because i have to admit i don't know if i've
played a video game with the commentary on and i was kind of curious and opening it that this
question of the chat as well how many of you have played through video games with the commentary on
so you you have done this loki yeah i played through a little bit of portal i think and i think
that they had portal 2 had the same thing but you can actually go through that and uh check it out
and they have these like little icons on the screen you go up to and it talks about like
especially with the original portal like different puzzle designs and stuff like that so it's pretty
cool i've watched a couple of movies with commentary tracks but very few and i've always
found that they're almost always better if there's more than one person when there's just one person
it's not always the most exciting thing in the world it depends on who it is and i feel like
some people don't want to be there but others do so it really um kind of changes that uh no one
special 77 says when i still had a ps3 and the orange box for that i tried the commentary for
that like i've probably like tried it but i don't think i've ever like actually said oh
there's a commentary track out for this game i want to try it so it's interesting um sg100 matt
says i haven't experienced this enough i get the sense i would do that on a second playthrough
you know what if something like mass effect had a commentary track i'd probably play through with
it but there's so much that that game is so long i'm not sure if a commentary track would really
work but it'd be interesting so all right it'd be cool if like games like that let you create
a custom commentary track like we could create one in game and like store different like clips
here like hey you probably don't want to go around the corners jump scare over there just
just beware jump scare right there well that's what you do in demon souls you leave the little
pieces of paper at least i think you still do that anyway all right uh moving on uh i'm sure
a lot of you saw this floating around social media this week and it's it's like the ridiculous like
what the hell are you doing with these consoles and um so in this case did everybody see that
video of the xbox series x where smoke was coming out of the top of the vent and it was that
youtube that was like omg my xbox series x on launch day caught fire well you can very clearly
see in the corner there's smoke going into the xbox that then comes out of the holes on the top
because yes somebody actually was blowing vape smoke into the vent at the bottom which of course
smoke rises fun fact science and it came well at the top it's also because they developed that
console to have nice airflow so it just sucks it up and spits it right out which is why the
playstation 5 is also shaped the way it is is that it's to help with the airflow so you know
both these consoles with their you know beefy parts that are doing all the fancy ray tracing
and everything have to have really good airflow in it so honestly the vape smoke technique is
showing wow the airflow is really good on these systems um yeah and i like i like the comment
though that they had on like i can't believe i have to tell you this but yeah don't blow vape
smoke into your xbox series x xbox actually put out a tweet uh a few days ago on november the 11th
so i was actually the day before uh the day after the launch where they said we can't believe we
have to say this but please do not blow vape smoke into your xbox series x
but that just goes that also goes all into like the fake news type of thing we were just bringing
up is that this person only did it to get clicks on omg and that that can have a negative impact
on xbox because somebody's going to believe it like you got to see this video where a dude's
micro thing caught fire people like chasing clout yeah i know yeah and as and as mentioned in chat
by bobby yeah and also vape smoke can hurt your xbox like let's you know let's let's not forget
that part is that you know there's what makes the vape smoke there's a little bit of water in there
and stuff right you should not be putting those on computer parts and and i mean we should probably
also ignore obviously i didn't watch any videos like this but i'm it they're always out there
there's always the people that are smashing these new systems when they came out because
you know four clicks because haha you can't get one i got one and now i'm gonna break it you know
it's like i don't know whatever people are dumb whatever happened to the video where here's my
brand new xbox series x but here's my knife uh-huh it's a cake like i thought that's where
we were at in 2020 where's my xbox series x is actually a cake like where's that or playstation
five i'll take that would have been a twist like oh hey look my xbox series x is on fire it's
because it's a cake uh no unfortunately we're not there yet i don't know why i'm obsessed with those
cake videos that are like surprise it's a case that i know it's a cake going in but i'm always
kind of like wow these are like really well done cakes you know all right let's go let's go back
to a simpler time when in fact it was not a cake it was it was just a game the classic game of the
week it wasn't a cake it was a lie uh dark soccer is gonna step into the gaming vault and find a
game that she thinks hey uh you should be checking out this game this week uh and this is oh man
you've got a classic tonight it's one of those ones where it's like how has this never been
picked before yet again here we are what i texted you yeah it is it is and that's why i'm saying it
again what's funny as i was describing this to dan is the game where you run around in pajamas and
shoot people's livers and spleens because that's kind of what they look like that is so the classic
game of the week is uh alien syndrome so uh it is a running gun it was developed by sega and it came
out in the arcades in 1987 um so basically you uh have two soldiers that you play as one named ricky
and one mary and they go through this levels that will have a way scrolling and you have to rescue
your comrades who are being held by aliens who uh well they look like spleens and livers to me green
and and pink very pink looking organ meat um anyway um so uh after you rescue a certain number
of hostages uh an exit will open and you can go through to fight you know the boss for the level
the the end of level guardian as this likes to say and then when you've defeated it then you're able
to go on to the next stage um and it does allow two players simultaneous um and you can do pickups
to assist the character get different weapons get maps of the level um and you know it's it's a very
very simple game that people can be kind of all up in arms about versions of it um so um the game
uh had different ports um in 1988 its first series of ports were on the sega master system the msx
the amiga atari st the amstrad cpc commodore 64 and the uh famicon or nes that was published by
tangen because nintendo would grant the license um there were later ports there was the zx spectrum
in 1989 game gear in 1992 and oh gosh i wish i owned one of these a sharp x68000 in 1992 which
was the only arcade perfect port because i mean it was fucking sharp x6800 what you by sixty
eight thousand what would you expect um so and honestly it was just like it was sort of that
era of you know of games right where it kind of had just like that almost minimalist kind of
music to it and it was kind of simple but a little bit more complex than the other things you know it
was it was just a really cool game um it was uh listed as uh one of as the third most successful
arcade unit um by a game machine in japan it was listed that um in 1987 in their article on it
um the original version was also uh reviewed by computer and video games uh magazine in 87
it was called one of the most gripping games they've been playing for months um and it was
very reminiscent of of alien or uh you know or aliens i should say i mean i i honestly see more
in common with alien than aliens but um you know and it also uh the master system version was
actually given really really high ratings as well um so the game did get um uh an upgrade um for the
ps2 uh sega ages 2500 uh series um and uh it was brought over in the us in the sega classics
collection um however it was ruined for the european version to get a lower age certificate
they upgraded controls they uh gave it polygon graphics um analog controls um and they did
include the original game as an unlockable in sonic's ultimate genesis collection um the thing
is is that the sadly the sega ages version is not very good it really is not very good
um there was a sequel also called alien syndrome that was released on wii and psp in 2007 and so
there you go alien syndrome you know shoot shoot the alien headed thing shoot the livers and you
know spleens that try to come at you it's kind of gauntlet-y you know with with aliens and spleens
so there you go all right sorry i stepped away for a second but i'm back
uh yes alien syndrome uh a game that uh i played this on the nes i think i remember the tengan
cart for this uh and playing that so uh and it was hard i remember but maybe i'm better at games now
i don't know i think that we may be now this is actually something i'm gonna go a little bit into
it um i think that um it may not necessarily be a better or worse our perception's different
and we're gonna try to do one thing one way when we're a kid but when you go back and play it when
you're older you sometimes try to follow that old instinct but you think something else is gonna
make sense and i think that's just a difference in a gaming as a mature gamer that's very true
you know something like like mega man is very much a game about patterns right like you've
often talked about your um ability to play a certain section of mega man to all of us ability
yeah like blindfolded because it's really it's really just a game about memorizing patterns
if you think about it but being able to execute those patterns perfectly um and i think some of
that is probably true with what i'm watching here on aliens it's been a long time since i
played this game but um i and what i'm watching in the footage here is i'm like it's really just it
seems like it's just patterns like this person knows exactly where they're running exactly what
they're shooting um and there's like a pattern thing to it before i didn't say if it was a task
play yeah uh um maybe but but i mean this is still the thing too is that with the older games like
this they're a lot of them more patterns are you know there's not really as much i'd say uh
programming real estate to have a more complicated ai in games like this good point
yeah so and it doesn't look like and as far as i'm aware i don't think this particular
game has a whole lot of rng to deal with short of boss battles
so all right well a real classic there uh your classic game of the week alien syndrome
uh originally in the arcade and then pretty much everywhere else at the time
and that large list the dark sakura read us earlier all right well let's get into some
rapid fire news and travel around the world and uh we'll look at world release dates right after
but first some rapid fire news uh loki we'll start with you uh yes so there's lots of fun
news regarding sam and max's week including a brand new uh remaster that's going to be coming to
pc and switch uh this december so sam and max save the world remastered uh looks pretty awesome
and um yeah i'd like some more sam max and with that i'm probably gonna get some more sam and max
because they're gonna be uh coming to vr as well with sam and max uh this time it's virtual and
it's a brand new vr game that's coming out as well in early 2021 so i am definitely gonna be
picking that up um and i believe bobby blackwolf is a big fan of this news too yes yes these are
some of his favorite things all coming together um and then of course like a lot of news i'm
going to bring up another game title and of course it's going to be um well actually this time not
delayed but we at least know when it's coming out so that's going to be a death loop which is going
to be coming out may 21st 2021 and they are charging uh sixty dollars instead of seventy
i didn't really realize that was a thing that originally they were going to charge seventy
for it i know that activision and take two two of the evilest companies known to man are charging
seventy dollars watches and say sony is doing the same thing as well um charging seventy dollars for
their games hopefully that doesn't stick but at least we know that it's gonna be um you know
not that it's gonna be sixty dollars instead it looks like a great game uh it's still only on
uh playstation though that's it all right well let's talk about fall guys are y'all still playing
fall guys um well some new costumes might bring you back to take another look and it's a tie-in
with the untitled goose game or asshole goose game as i still call it uh honk uh the crossover
event is going to be happening on november 13th uh and they did a whole twitch stream where you
could actually see the costumes early and i think they actually had like staff people like dressed
up as the geese so that's really silly but um yeah so that actually i'm sorry november 13th would
have been friday so it's already in the game now um so you can check that out that is also the
launch of season 2.5 that just happened this past week uh there is now a big fan level for that uh
there's some uh mixed up rounds as well and now a hammer called lil yeety because the hammer if it
hits you you're gonna go i haven't played this in a while i haven't had to go back they've been doing
some cute little upgrades to it it's it's it's probably something worth checking out if you
haven't seen it in a while so uh check that out do your kids do that yeet i hear that's a big
thing with kids uh yes yes the kids do that do they play fall guys no they're on to among us
well at least um my oldest son's on among us and still roblox his thing now what he's been doing
is he's been making um like i don't know if they're youtube intros but like intros for people
using scratch so he's making animations and scratch now which is kind of cool
wow your kids doing that yeah that's what he's been doing on his free time does your kid want
to make a new olr intro at least the visuals we have the music but i am i don't know but like
that's it's better than just me panning the camera around the studio
i'm i'm sure we can get someone to do that no i want your kid to do it it'll be funny
why not grow grow everything else in house here all right anyhow uh moving on uh let's get into
oh this is a great follow-up uh from a previous episode so sometimes we discover amazing games
through reading through the release dates and i have an update for you on alpaca ball
alpaca ball all stars is going to be getting a physical release here on this side of the pond
it came out already in like hong kong taiwan sinapore and so forth um but uh we're going to
be getting a release here as well badland publishing is going to do it uh you can get
a collector's edition with a cap a game soundtrack in cd format and of course you better have this in
a game called alpaca ball a little stuffed alpaca alpaca so uh march 2021 is when that's coming out
amazing all right let's move on uh pixel pakas says thank you for keeping us updated on alpaca
ball news you're welcome we are orange lounge radio your source for alpaca ball news um and
then uh phoenix 77 26 says we need president cat too you know as an aside you might remember years
ago it was four years ago during the last election i think we had the guy on who made cat president
which is on steam um we had him on the show uh because we thought it was funny that somebody
actually made a game about cats and presidents though of course he'd never heard this show i
mean who can blame him hardly anyone has so uh what i want to say though is that he did come
out with just in the past couple months cat president too which just in time for the 2020
election was out and i want to say because i follow him on twitter i want to say his twitter
just said that they did like a an extra update recently was it to add the four seasons landscaping
thing i think it might have been i think they added some type of parody on the land yeah so it
yeah cat president to a per political revolution yes so the free plug for that guy what was i i
can't the guy's name i think was paul it was oh oh a rock i remember yeah oh a rock i remember
that was funny but uh free plug for cat president too uh we love our indie developers um
dark tetsuya says you know jordan got out of the gaming industry so i don't know what even
happened to president cat ip uh olr is willing to buy the president cat ip just i want to throw
that out there um we don't have a lot but you guys have been very generous with your bits and
subs so i'll tell you what i'm willing to pay twenty dollars for the president cat license
um i'll just give it to yyr or even uh oh a rock if they want it but uh yes we're looking we're
looking for that please um or wouldn't that wouldn't that specifically be renna because
we we were the ones that said jamie specifically was one that said president cat because it's
really like it was boss cat it was a joke yeah it's it's more like like the delinquent girl
girl leader boss yeah and i was like i was trying to wrap my knee my head around what it meant
i was like president president cat no because i need to stick him on you know i because
it's like a whole subculture no i'm it was beautiful the way it was it's the only time
the show has ever been famous jamie so kudos to you oh that and the katamari thing so you know
we need a stunt it's been like 14 years can't we where's our fucking stunt to get us famous again
hold on let me go get my vape pen
all right all the can't also think of something i guess all right yeah
oh yeah yeah yeah make a game loki okay i'll get right on that thank you it's about time
a stunt game all right let's bring us notoriety all that from the alpaca ball moving on dark
soccer's got some rapid fire news for us
hold on yeah i do um so i'm sorry sorry to interrupt so this is important it's it's it's
yes the patch 105 for the fur seasons all right thank you for that all right sorry jamie
so uh konami style which is konami's record label is doing a tennis compilation
a series called music from konami arcade shooting god i want this um it's got um
10 discs and the first one is morning music twin b gradius salamander life force flak attack
this too is ajax gradius 2 thundercross 3 is bradius 3 proteus 4 is trigon detana twin b
thundercross 2 disc 5 is sexist uh gokujo parodius 6 is twin b yahoo salamander 2
7 is sexy parodius 8 is uh tobe poly stars and solar assault revised 9 is gradius 4
ultimatius and finalizer and 10 disc is bonus tracks and range tracks um yes somebody buy that
for me please i specifically wanted you to talk about that tonight because i wanted that reaction
of i want it well and the other thing is that people go oh why is it digital because
digital music does not sell as well in japan as physical media
so okay also um for people who are still into pokemon sapphire a fish beat pokemon sapphire
after 3195 hours so um basically they have fish swimming around um and they use motion tracking
on them so uh these fish uh beat beat pokemon why are we reporting this because it's that
awkward moment when a fish has more gamer credibility than i do well basically i think
it's also to demonstrate you know i like actually this particular article brings it up because it
was the first thing i was thinking of was the uh the infinite monkey theorem that states if you
have a monkey hitting keys on a typewriter for an infinite amount of time it'll eventually type out
a shakespeare play um that was all that that also goes back to the twitch place pokemon phenomenon
from a few years ago was in that exact same thing was cited the whole and i've heard it also as the
broken clock is right twice a day type of thing it's that same type of theory but on a much larger
scale so interesting all right uh let's move on and travel around the world and check out some
release dates of some games that your fish might beat very soon or in 3000 days or whatever it took
uh loki let's start in the us all right so in the us we've got bubble bobble for friends the
baron is back on playstation 4 and nintendo switch mortal combat 11 ultimate on pc nintendo
switch playstation 4 playstation 5 xbox one and xbox series x uh we have serious sam collection
on nintendo switch playstation 4 and xbox one sniper elite 4 on nintendo switch bridge
construction bridge constructor the walking dead on ios android uh pc mac and linux i'm sorry i'm
gonna cut loki off because he cut jamie off earlier but this chat comment is worth reading
see a tiberian chat says it was the best of times it was the blurst of times that's a simpsons joke
isn't it i know it there and it's that whole thing with the monkey and the typewriter they're typing
something and that's that's what he pulls out it was the best of times it was the blurst of times
oh yeah i remember that look i don't even really i probably haven't watched simpsons in like 20
years and yet i recognize that so there's that okay sorry loki you can continue all right uh
let's see where were we so um it's also coming out on nintendo switch playstation 4 xbox one
xbox series x uh we also have um some more uh looks like the bubble games also coming out on
uh playstation 4 as well even though i said playstation 4 previously i'm guessing maybe
one's a physical version one's not uh we have also uh moral combat 11 coming out on stadia
uh star renegades on nintendo switch and xbox one hyrule warriors age of calamity on nintendo switch
katamari damasi reroll on playstation 4 and xbox one and that would be it
all right let's go to japan virtually uh and check out the release dates over there
on november 19th on nintendo switch we have momotaro densetsu showa he say reiwa mo taiwan
comes out as well as oh my god i should really look at these in advance there is legit
there is legit a game coming out on the nintendo switch called
panty party perfect body that's right yeah panty party and i you know guess guess what's on the box
art school girls and guess what one of them is showing just a little flash of see the game's
title uh that's great now it does come with a warning there is no warning no hentai content
in this game all you get is funny and stupid pennies
okay i think that's a review somebody wrote about olr on itunes um you know apparently according to
this um it has been released over here as well um that's it really last year what was it called
panty party it's also called panty party yeah it's uh fifteen dollars on your switch
all right then this must be some type of like if it's called perfect body it must be like a
remaster or something that's on the switch so anyway all right let me try to just i just
i was i there was nothing that could have prepared me for that uh moving on
neko tomo smile mashimashi comes out this week uh gal gun 2 gets a price reduction as it goes
into the best hits um looking at some of the other systems oh i have playstation 5 to look
at in japan now huh um so let's see so the console itself already released we we didn't get to this
part of the show last week i don't think we have any games this week just that the playstation 5
itself is coming to other regions in asia because remember there was the weak delay um and uh jamie
will get to it because it affects europe as well uh but it also impacted asia um otherwise
playstation 5 has nothing this week i imagine they've uh you know kind of put out all the stuff
the week the system came out uh for a little while uh looking at the playstation 4 though
just because they're still going to release things on that for a little while yep katamari
damasi reroll gets a release in japan uh this week on the 19th uh sniper elite 4 is also out in japan
and a new edition of black desert the prestige edition oh bubble bobble for friends also out in
japan this week there you go that was a lot dark soccer how about the uk oh in the uk we have um
on the 17th mortal combat 11 ultimate um sniper elite 4 fortnite the last laugh bundle truck
driver for switch um on the 19th warhammer chaos bane slayer edition wrc 9 for ps5 um man eater for
ps5 um professor uh rubik's brain fitness uh monster trunk championship uh dirt 5 for ps5
and the ps5 um we have watchdogs legion we have on the 20th we have
eldridor creatures theme park simulator uh not extended uh edition code in a box
hyrule warriors age of calamity uh sakuna of rice and ruin that's what's coming out
all right let's move on we have some more stories for you guys i think it's very important that we
elaborate on that game one more time um oh boy so taking a look at it so it's literally like flying
underwear that you're fighting as it is a 3d like fighting like action game where you play as
sentient underwear apparently it looks ridiculous uh phoenix 77 26 wants to know is chris hanson an
unlockable character well no it's it's not really people there's no people in the game it's just
flying underwear all right uh well let's move on loki why don't you uh start us off with some more
actual news all right let's talk about it um so apparently there japan uh sony is gonna stop
servicing the original playstation 4 which seems quite surprising considering that um
i mean we just got the playstation 5 apparently they're what they're talking about is the original
version of the playstation 4 that launched back in 2014 they are gonna stop servicing but the slim
and pro series they're gonna still do repairs and whatnot on those um it's just the original model
which still though it seems like it's a pretty soon to stop um supporting that but you can do
whatever they want at least they know what a playstation 4 is and having completely forgot
about it thank you vita the headlines on this i think were a little deceptive too because it
was saying like playstation 4 is no longer services well it's some it's the launch so but
it definitely uh it does seem pretty aggressive to be on its way out the door you know what i mean
like the five just came out you know exactly i i think it's a bit soon and considering that you
know people are probably getting rid of their playstation fours for playstation fives i mean
they don't want to deal with the second hand maybe maybe i don't know but
i haven't i haven't decided if i want to keep my xbox one or maybe get rid of it um i just don't
know who won it this one you you want do you not have an xbox one dark sakura
oh i thought you guys had one no we got ps4 let's talk if i mean i at least want to borrow it yeah
if you know what honestly yes i would be fine with you in this way you don't have to give me money
because i would be fine with it having a long-term home um because when we move eventually i'll
probably set it up as a secondary media player but i don't really have the space right now
so i'll be honest our ps3 and ps4 are both connected we use the ps4 for youtube and we
use the ps3 for uh the few times we actually watch physical disc um not just oh bobby says i know
some parents who want an xbox one because i can play minecraft well jamie if you if you really
want let's let's talk because i i can uh do that i'm a cat parent that wants to play minecraft
well to be fair everything plays minecraft nowadays so it's fine that's true too um
anyways just speaking of which jamie um i guess uh you're gonna go ahead and bow out for the night
just to take care of yourself and because you've been a little under the weather so uh
and we could hear we could hear it you're starting to go during the release dates so um
uh thank you of course for sticking it out and being here tonight glad glad you got to have a
full show tonight sort of sorta i mean without the i'm referring to the power drops last week
or god internet drops last week the goal is with uh another week of resting my voice that i will be
100 so fingers crossed but i i would also still like to take the opportunity to tell people
pay the fuck attention to what cdc is telling you wear your mask social distance don't fucking go
to anybody's house for thanksgiving just saying yeah unless you've all been tested
we're doing we're doing the two-week stay at home thing so we can see my dad but that is it we are
only seeing my dad so but like i can't let him be alone i can't so yeah i understand i'm taking
i'm actually taking a test on uh monday to to test myself again they sent me three boxes of tests
from work i'm like why you already tested me yeah all right take care of yourself jamie we'll talk
to you in a week thanks bye all right moving on let's get to our next story where we talk about
youtube premium and i gotta fix the cameras here real quick though sorry
awkward transition all right there we go all right um let's talk about a free google stadia
but the catch is you have to be a youtube premium member so you get the 99 bundle that features a
chromecast ultra and a gamepad if you are a youtube premium member this is for members in
the us and the uk you get the stadia premiere edition a 99 bundle with the chromecast ultra
and stadia controller and uh yeah you get that and then you get a free month of stadia pro with
that but you have to remember to cancel that or they're gonna get you on that um so i'm sure this
is where people want to insert the joke that they can't even give it away well you know what like i
well for one stadia is supposed to be free anyway so like you know what are you getting you're
getting the chromecast ultra that's kind of like the first level of doing this but the weird thing
is um alan has been like a youtube subscriber for a long time um and he couldn't get one it said he
wasn't eligible for it i didn't get that but google has also given away quite a few things
both alan and i have google homes well we have obviously we have two in the house one in the
bedroom in the living room because of our spotify subscriptions and they gave away a free google
with that or his might have even come from a cell phone i don't remember but google has definitely
given their stuff away before i don't know what do you what do you think about them giving away
stadia chromecast and all that for free loki i mean i guess they figured if you're buying
their youtube premium service that you're probably ripe to you know be interested in
such a terrible service as stadia um no i i don't know it's it sounds like a last ditch effort to
try to get people either hooked on youtube premium or stadia i i just think they're gonna have to
change their model at some point to make it more like games pass but i don't know we'll see um
it sucks that he's not able to redeem that considering he would be a subscriber to
you know um yeah i don't know what your premium the weird hold up is i have to look into what
kind of error message he's getting or whatever but anyway um and some comments here uh did you
rama s in chat over twitch.tv slash vog network says damn google is desperate to get rid of them
um maybe but remember here's the thing stadia is supposed to be free anyway but the weird the
missing part here is that how how far are we into the launch of stadia and we still don't have that
version that you just sign on to the web and play unless you are a pro subscriber right or am i
mixing that up can you just go on with any old gmail account and do it now on the web i don't
know you could do it with pro but i don't think you could do it with just like a free one
um so it's it's just the whole thing's a little weird um i just feel like google just
flood this launch so bad i don't know um pixel pocket says i'm very sad about google play music
i downloaded all my stuff and put it on my plex server instead i forgot they just recently shut
that down that's right um i think i had a bunch of olr episodes on there a bunch of old ones
so um yeah uh st100 matt says they want to get folks to get it so they can release that
gotta have stadia game which they don't have yet so it'll be interesting to see the effect this
has i know people that are cashing in on it because hey free chrome cast right it's not
just a stadia it's a chrome cast so i know people that are cashing in on it is it some type of maybe
trojan horse trick i don't know especially when they talk about signing you up for a free month
the stadia pro i i don't know but it'll be interesting to see what kind of impact this
might have on stadia if any so i would i still think it's just their core service isn't worth
paying for i mean it just doesn't paying for the service and then i have to also buy the games on
the service doesn't make any sense it's just especially when there's other companies offering
stuff it it's just cheaper and like i i don't get what the the value proposition is that they're
saying especially since there's not new really i mean aside from there's nothing really exclusive
to that platform either like i just don't get what they are hoping to do with this like i i don't
know oh now this is a service again die dgrms says alan couldn't get it because the promotion
for it ran out so people in chat are asking how do i get in on this it sounds like you might it's
all have been claimed the end so interesting brilliant i wonder if this was all just a trick
to get out get us all to talk about it i don't know but it would be great if they could put out
like that killer game that would i know i'm totally getting stadia now that i've talked
about it yeah all right uh moving on to another story and uh this has to do with uh the the not
twitch con is going on right now the glitch con or whatever um and this is some i i didn't really
catch a lot of big twitch news out of that i i like a big new feature coming or anything like
that maybe you guys did and can correct me in chat and that feature is that they're gonna start
flagging your games for wins besides all of that besides all of that letting that go for a minute
um well one of the big stories that came out of it was that um the co why can't i read this article
here okay the co of able gamers who's uh pretty popular on social media uh steven spon i hope i
said his last name right sorry um but he's the co of able gamers and this charity has been around
a while it's actually um the charity that my amazon smile is set to for what it's worth
and they're they do a lot of great things for gamers with disabilities um in in video games
and one of the cool things that happened uh out of glitch con was that uh the co steven had wanted
to for his birthday because he just hit his 40th birthday i believe wanted to raise one million
dollars for the able gamers charity and um twitch just said here you go here's a million bucks for
able gamers so there's your goal and then some so that's pretty awesome uh and that all happened
during a stream with dr lupo and the ceo of twitch uh emmett shear uh and that twitch is
going to donate one million dollars to able gamers that is pretty awesome uh and it's interesting
because uh steven has said on twitter i've talked to the rock i've talked to ryan reynolds i'm
paraphrasing this is not exact words i've talked to the rock i've talked to ryan reynolds but
that is the one that caught me caught me off guard so that is cool
great charity good news we like gaming good news all right i'm trying to look in chat to see if
anybody had said uh uh bobby blackwolf says that's nice of them considering twitch just laid off
their accessibility manager i guess it's easier to give money to charity than actually do any
accessibility work
but true which did you catch my subtle segue to our next story logi yes i it was so subtle
so uh we got to hear from tommy talarico this week and you may be wondering what the hell does
that have to do with roblox well it's because apparently uh roblox corporation um lifted a
little bit of his sound effects uh or sound design from an old game called messiah back in
2000 and thought no one would notice but apparently someone did and so there was uh some stuff behind
the scenes and they finally settled to where uh the game the game is no longer not gonna have that
oof uh sound effect for free um so what's happening basically is tommy talarico is going to
allow them to have that sound effect back in the game if you are a creator of games on roblox you
can actually purchase the sound effect to use in your games for 100 um robux i think it's like
a dollar and then on top of that he's also going to be creating some new sound effects that you
could also use in your games as well ranging anywhere from like 10 bucks to 250 dollars
depending on the number of sounds that are included with it so it's available to developers
on there also he is uh working with the roblox corporation to create an official oof t-shirt
they're gonna sell them sure he's gonna get proceeds from uh but basically yeah the whole
thing's been settled without uh seems like a lawsuit um but yeah that was kind of interesting
that they've been well i wouldn't say it's interesting because if you've played roblox or
of browse through roblox you'll know that because a lot of the developer a lot of these games are
created by kids kids have no concept of copyright law or i mean this is literally just a bomb
waiting to go off as far as ip theft goes it's just ridiculous and so it's not surprising that
at the heart of the game more ip theft my my understanding of how that all happened was that
you know when they made roblox they kind of got like a uh one of those like a 1000 sound effects
licenseable for your thing or whatever and i'm i'm i don't know those exact details but it's one
of those like you know license a bunch of sound effects and the oof was included in there and oof
it shouldn't have been because it wasn't licensed from tommy or anything like that it was essentially
stolen so roblox thought that they had licensed it appropriately but it sounds like this middle
person uh is the one that's really to blame whoever had ripped it off for their collection
so interesting yeah so at least there is no harm no foul but they've worked on you know uh some
fair resolution for it uh no one specials on fire tonight uh pixel pakka says official oof t-shirt
lol to which no one special 77 chat replies it's an official t-shirt nice
yeah so you've been listening to orange lounge radio sorry i had to i had to do the roll credits
on the bad joke all right go ahead are we gonna see uh are we gonna see any uh roblox heading to
the amico or anything like that now that tommy's uh mixed that would be a gag that would be a gag
but i believe that the um the rule on amico is that everything has to be for amico and exclusive
to it i mean they could maybe dance around and have some type of uh official uh roblox
side game or version but um who knows anything's possible i guess yeah all right
one more story for you guys before we get to the round table let's talk about
plague inc this game has uh been talked about especially this year i can't imagine why but um
there's a new mode that they launched uh just in time where you try to stop a pandemic do you
think it's easy boys and girls well now you can try uh through plague inc so uh this new mode
called the cure mode you have to find a balance between contact tracing that scene research
helping to save the economy locking down as appropriate and so forth uh to try to bring
the end of a pandemic and if you figure it out call the white house um and let them know because
uh they might need some help but yeah so interesting is that it's the reverse of what
plague inc kind of was before is that you actually wanted to spread a virus to wipe out humanity
so this is the the more hopeful version of that to go for 2020 so i think that's kind of interesting
it's cute that the game's been turned on its head like that so have you ever played this game loki
i have to admit i haven't no i have i've heard a lot about it uh certainly because of what's
been going on this year so i imagine there'll be some streams and things like that so all right
um let's get to the listener roundtable we're going to invite your questions and comments uh
to our chat room over at twitch.tv slash vog network also um this is the part of the show
where we get into the mailbag now this week we didn't have any emails however because last week's
show got cut off early thanks to the internet we actually had some emails from last week we never
got to so i do want to read these two emails but i am going to warn you guys um it may be a little
dated because we're now two weeks from when they were sent um but let's get to our first email
tonight which is from i believe this is no one special although it's unsigned uh all right here
we go hi all i hope all is well with you this week since it's been a while since my last email
i thought i'd send one this week uh plus unless i think of something at the last second sending
this email negates the need for me to send one of my long-winded listener roundtable subjects
so while this isn't wholly email worthy i do have some good news to report so for brevity's sake i'll
tldr this despite it being incredibly late and i have giving up any hope of getting it i will
finally get that 1200 stimulus check in about a week i got a call from my ssdpe the other day
stating that she just received it on my behalf since stimulus checks went out to wherever people
who are on social security have their federal monthly checks sent and when her agency mails
out checks this week she'll forward the money to me now i'm imagining that there's a chance that
at least one of you are asking yourselves okay good for you what does this relate to gaming
after all olr is a show about gaming well to be fair it's a show about gaming and tangents
good point i'm getting to that as i've mentioned from time to time in the past one thing i've
always wanted was an honest to goodness arcade cabinet something like a classic game from the
80s or 90s be it any version of street fighter 2 one of the 2d mortal combat games cruisin usa
a neo geo mvs etc even with 1200 i still can't afford one of those unfortunately
they are closer to 2500 or 3000 at the least so that being said i'm going to bite the proverbial
bullet and buy the arcade one up version of the neo geo mvs from amazon linked to the amazon page
now before i go any further i don't recall arcade one up doing a neo geo no it's snk actually thank
you okay that's what i thought so snks actually themselves however it is it is probably happening
due to the success of arcade one up and i'm sure we have arcade one up to thank for this coming out
and it's very much in a similar vein to the arcade one up machines but i do just want to make that
clarity point is that arcade one up themselves is not the one doing it but you wouldn't necessarily
know by looking okay so um that all being said let me finish email maybe if i can swing it i'll
also order a few things from my pc on top of the neo geo mvs like new ram new controller and so
forth but that last part aside despite it not being perfect like not an actual arcade machine
that would accept quarters and tokens and have cartridge slots i'm still excited to have the next
best thing i do have a two-part question for you all have any of you at a minimum had an opportunity
to try the arcade one up version of the neo geo mvs um i'm gonna rephrase that to what we just
discussed and if so what are your thoughts on it pros and cons i haven't i didn't even know it was
out i thought it was coming out but he did link us to an amazon page where ah okay this item will
be released on november 24th so that's the answer none of us have played it yet because we can't it's
not out yet um well uh i've seen like video reviews from folks that have are familiar with
the mvs and um have played a lot of that through like a super gun or something like that and
talking about what it is in it sounds like it's pretty good as far as mimicking the mvs and um
the only complaints some people had were like maybe the controller might not be exactly what
you want but that's probably could be swapped out part-wise um some of the buttons and everything
um some of the graphics filters were kind of annoying like for example they had some where
if you wanted certain scan lines in there they only had it with like the graphics smoothing
option which is kind of irritating instead of like the pixel perfect option um so you may just
some of those issues might be a thing but otherwise it's a pretty good recreation of it
i think yeah and just you know i'm gonna have to base my assumption based off of actual arcade
one-up machines and what this is trying to emulate i will say number one it has a pretty impressive
lineup of games in it you know most of those arcade one-up machines only have five or six
games in them which is a problem for some people i'm not so bothered by it i get what they're
trying to do with that kind of like limited release but um the neo geo one does sound very
robust so there is that and um it's going to be a different you know kind of screen on it from
what you remember in the arcades back in the day um but i actually think that makes it more
manageable but i think the way you kind of phrased it where it's the next best thing i think is
probably going to be appropriate is like it's probably going to be enough for you to kind of
invoke those memories of playing it at an arcade you wouldn't want to deal with the quarter stuff
and all that stuff well i shouldn't say that i'm not to say who what type of collector people are
and so forth but let me rephrase that quarter stuff and token slot and all that that might be
more hassle than you think especially if you just want to get in there and play the games so you
know what there might actually be an upside to some of this but i i'd be curious to hear your
thoughts once you get it all sorted out and this comes in and by the way before anybody says
anything about spending a stimulus check on an arcade machine um people can spend the money
however they like and there's plenty of people that are spending the stimulus check on vacations
and things of that sort so how is this any different um and you know what i it's one of
those things where it's like i also totally recognize that like 2020 has been hard on people's
mental health across the board so like if this is something that a person can buy to make themselves
happy for a day again who am i to judge i ain't so i just wanted to get that out there because
i could see how some folks might be kind of asking some questions there and just remember
it's not your place to ask that question all right anyway the rest of the email thanks for taking
the time to read and answer this email this email is brought to you by the front door of the white
house which hopefully will hit drum part on the ass on his way out na na na na na na na hey hey
goodbye dances the cabbage patch you can tell this was written shortly after that um election
on tuesday yes mr smoosh i'm reading emails did you want to read the next email he's off
camera unfortunately but he's sitting here uh giving his opinion all right uh black kompat in
chat says retail therapy has been saving grace for me this year same like you know did i need
an xbox series x probably not am i happy i bought one yeah so there you go all right uh let's get to
one more email which is from yyr and again this is a dated email because of last week's issues
hello lr i wanted to weigh in oh by the way before i get into this too far yyr did i saw
this on discord i'm sorry i didn't see the stream but he did some type of charity stream today where
he was supposed to play max 300 41 times in a row to celebrate or was it 40 or 41 to celebrate
turning his age so i i thought that was impressive dude because i i don't even think i've ever been
one time yeah um even a nine-footer that's pretty hard that i probably could still do like let's
say orion seven eight siv mix right i still like i still remember how those notes go in my head
um but and and for some of you probably have no idea what we're talking about this is a ddr thing
okay um but uh the fact that he could do that 41 times that in itself is impressive i i hope it
went i hope the stream went very well i'm sorry i missed it um sunday's a very busy day oh sj100
matt says yyr's birthday is today well happy birthday all right well let's finish the birthday
boy's email okay uh i wanted to weigh in on the playstation 5 backwards compatibility issue we
were talking about on last week's show again we might be dealing with some dated things because
we've had some answered questions since then but let's move on we have a list a short one but a
list nonetheless of seemingly random games that we're told won't run on playstation 5 at all
we have a disclaimer on every playstation 4 game in the playstation store warning us that there
may be issues running it on playstation 5 and now we have ubisoft mentioning then unmentioning
issues with some of their ps4 games on ps5 personally for me this adds up to a bad omen i
get the sense that the playstation 5's backwards compatibility is going to come with asterisks and
kavats and that we're not going to get the full sense of what all these are until the consoles
are already in our hands i get the distinct impression that sony did not fully plan for this
as microsoft certainly appears to have done and that if someone is looking specifically to play
playstation 4 games they should probably buy a playstation 4 rather than bank on the theory that
playstation 5 would play them perfectly all of that said i hope to be proven wrong so now we
have some answers was yyr wrong i would say not completely because he did say there play them
perfectly and we have news it's not perfect but it's playable right so and i think those are some
of the nuances that might have caused some of that confusion uh that we got again when when
ubisoft to put out that announcement there so there's that's kind of my take on it now that
the consoles are out in people's hands is that it's not perfect and if you want to play perfect
if you want to play the game it was absolutely meant to be designed for especially if they
didn't do an updated release like no man's sky or something you want to play it on a playstation 4
and this is you know this is emulation versus the real thing right and there's always going to be
people with their strong opinions one way or the other so and fifth dream says that it wants to say
that is also on a vast minority of games most games play way better on playstation 5 and
especially when you're talking about first party games i'm sure because you know they went in and
and made those better or made sure they would work and they would work better anyway to conclude
birthday boys email uh thanks again for the show oh and by the way i wasn't kidding when i said to
expect a pixel poops announcement soon so please look forward to that have a great week erin or yyr
well i'm not what it's been a week where's my announcement all right now i'm excited to see
whatever he has in store that's awesome all right that's it for our emails um again looking at chat
to see if there's any questions i don't see any questions a lot of people impressed on the max 300
thing in chat for what it's worth uh loki do we have any last minute stories tonight um yeah there
was one quick thing so apparently some fans have ported over driver 2 to pc which is interesting
because it was originally a playstation exclusive um so now they have this open source uh they
basic basically pulled a mario 64 on it they reverse engineered the original code and then
made an actual proper port of it and they're releasing it just in time for the 20th anniversary
so it's called redriver 2 project and it's uh available on github github.com open driver 2
redriver 2 it's free by the way which i'm sure is going to get them in trouble so get it while you
can all right so um and also i got a text before the show from shane and maybe some of you in chat
have more of a grip of what's going on the situation um but apparently uh capcom has had
some information leak out um what was what the tech say a ton of capcom leaks just happened it
looks like by the way and that did trigger my memory about that last week we had a story i
don't remember if we got to it or not it might have been cut because of the internet issue
but there was a story about that customer data from capcom had leaked or or yeah apparently uh
this is something different so it says uh apparently a group a hacker group has stolen
a one terabyte worth of stuff uh but only have leaked 60 gigabytes of it and includes the devil
may cry 2 source code umbrella chronicles source code resident evil 4 vr ace attorney collection
for playstation 4 and switch is this the same group that did this to nintendo i don't know
that's my that's my curiosity yeah and that's what fifth dream is asking as well is uh are all
these leaks coming from the same leakers uh i'd be very curious about that because if i was another
gaming company right now i would be putting the the the law i mean i'm sure these i mean nintendo
you would think would be secure as it is in capcom so i don't know how they're getting in if they're
doing social engineering or what they're doing to get into this stuff but if i was a gaming company
i would be looking at my security policies real good right now because this is uh you know and
this again puts us in this weird ethical gray area where i don't think it's necessarily right
to be spreading all of this stuff that is hacked but it's all over social media it can't be avoided
it is what gamers are talking about so i just hope video game companies are are trying to take the
steps they needs that they don't suffer the same fate this is really rough i don't know what else
to say um fifth dream says what i understand some of these leaks happened years ago they're just
dribbling them out uh bob coffee says nintendo's if i recall correctly was leaked via a chinese
company that did the iq devices not nintendo proper well it's still you know what anytime
you have vendor agreements or whatever it is you got to make sure that stuff is on lockdown it's
it's any game company if you know what i don't know how many people we have out there still
listening that work in the game industry but i would be so curious if your company and i realize
y'all can't really tell me but you know you can tell me on the down low if you want um i would be
so curious if your company doesn't blast some sort of security information this week or if if
it hasn't already in the last couple weeks some sort of training everybody has to take on security
or changed measures or whatever just to make sure that this doesn't happen to the next company
because that's two big ones now and that's uh that's an oof for sure so all right anything else
we should talk about loki or is that it i think that's it i'm sure we'll hire more about that
next week yeah the capcom thing i it's it's we it's it's such an ethical gray area but i
if it catches wind and it's all over social media i feel like you know we have to talk about it
because that's the type of thing that people would be talking about at the dinner table um but yeah
it's just i think we have to take the approach of how do we prevent this from happening again if it
hasn't already uh from the comments of you know this could have happened to a ton of sites already
all right uh let's get to some final thoughts and wrap it up for the night um thank you guys for
tuning in uh to another episode of orange launch radio and being here especially uh at the launch
of another console generation and especially after last week's show did not go as intended
um so i'm glad tonight went a lot more smooth thank you thank you um so thank you guys for
tuning in and supporting us whether you were here live on sunday night um or whether you caught us
on the podcast feed a little later on really appreciate your support uh in that regard so um
if you enjoyed what you heard here at orange launch radio tell a friend or two about the show
help us spread the word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice but we
need more voices here to tell us bad jokes like no one special does uh and uh what your auto hosts
on um uh i almost said itunes your auto hosts on twitch go a real long way your reviews on itunes
are great but your auto hosts on twitch for vog network go a real long way super appreciate those
of you that do it i think bobby told me two weeks ago or last week that we had like 40 people that
were doing it so that is great i really want to thank everybody who goes out of their way to host
the feed here so thank you so much um that's a really great way to get the word out um otherwise
that's that's really all i got um have fun gaming be nice to each other enjoy your systems and stop
trying to exploit your new systems for clicks uh just play games that's what they're for let's get
official final thoughts um loki i'll go to you final thought i'm just gonna be working more on
my game you think you'll finish by the end of the year yeah i'm hopeful that i can there's been a
few things that have should have been easy that aren't easy so i'm just working on getting through
that and then my goal is to get once i have all of the gameplay loop done that's just all creating
levels and that'll make it much easier level content is much easier than having to develop
the game systems um quick request from chat and i apologize to the podcast listeners because this
isn't going to be great but she hulk 10 says let's see loki's shirt we can see the part that says
xbox but we can't really see what's underneath it there's some iconography underneath it so yeah
so there's different xbox properties in here so i saw this at target the other day so they've got
it's uh the years war logo there's a minecraft creeper master chief um helmet there's a steering
wheel which i'm assuming is forza orie and a treasure chest which i'm sure has to do with their
sea of thieves game
so it was just some like it was a it was on sale at target so i just picked it up
that and i also have one for a um uh maru chan ramen shirt so i got that as well love it all
right uh i don't really have a lot of extra final thoughts i think i just kind of got it out there
like um have fun enjoy games uh i know this is a really crappy time with covid putting people back
indoors and the holidays are going to be different from what you're used to but games are a way that
we can come together a little bit so um on a on a super cheesy note i'm glad you all come together
with us every sunday night and um spend time talking about games with us i mean that it's not
just a cheesy statement i really do so i think on that note we'll go ahead and roll the credits for
real thanks everybody have a great week and we'll see you in seven days to talk about more games
good night you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr
studios to join us for a live show tune into fog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific 9 p.m
eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the
staff of orange lounge radio or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you