[SPEAKER_10]: Tonight, February 13th, 2011, there will be no more hero games at Activision.
[SPEAKER_10]: A survey hints at details on Dance Central 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And could your PlayStation 3 games soon require a serial number registration?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: I am dropping stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a good way to start off the 401st episode of our show.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Into the next hundred.
[SPEAKER_04]: Think we'll make it to 500?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got nothing else to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got nothing better to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also joining us, say hello to the one and only Tech Master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, good to hear.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's the baby doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's doing okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoy reading the wife's blogs about the baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting because, you know, I don't have a child, but it seems like everybody around me, you know, not everybody, but many people around me are kind of starting to enter that, take that step.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of interesting to hear the stories.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you will see posts once a month.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it just reminds me, I'm getting old.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, have you thought about what the baby's first video game should be?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he's already played Grand Theft Auto, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait a minute, you let your baby play Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, he can't really hold the controller well, but he had it at the point where he had one hand on the left analog stick and the other hand on the trigger and he was driving around.
[SPEAKER_07]: So technically that is playing Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, he doesn't know what he's doing, but he had an Xbox 360 controller and he didn't kill anything, he just was driving around.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a story to tell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell him when he's like 13.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you know your first game was Grand Theft Auto?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because by then they'll be up to Grand Theft Auto 17 or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's also introduce the ever-present fourth guest on our show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have anybody else in the studio tonight, sadly, but we do have, of course, the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice and have been that way since 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the place to be if you want to join us in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do tape live every Sunday night at All Games Radio www.allgames.com right after the Bobby Blackwolf show 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern But if you want to join our chat room you can do that at chat.orangeloungeradio.com What's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: You took video?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my You actually have a little picture of Josh playing the 360 control That is adorable That is really adorable
[SPEAKER_11]: By the way, my secondary theme for tonight's show What's that?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's so cute What's that, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is posting random stuff in the chatroom Posting random stuff in the chatroom, just because?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I found a neat article in Cracked about Easter eggs hidden in albums And I think we need to start doing Easter eggs in our episodes Our episodes need Like, we have an epic burp and you run it through a spectrograph and it's a picture of a puppy
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, I'm like, this is why I didn't do this crap before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, now I'm doing all that crap on my level 85 character, so I'm like... And, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I also have Final Fantasy 3 on the DS, which is pretty cool so far.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm very happy with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: We were at Dimple and we had some leftover credit because we traded in like a ton of our old DVDs that we had either replaced or just were crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Local music chain, by the way, which also sells games used new.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we were like, well, let's just go ahead and use up our credit.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I picked a game and Dan picked a game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then we said, well, let's use our discount card.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it turned out we still had $5 left when we were done.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we thought we were using it all up.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we still have credit there.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I guess we're going to go back and get another game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still have no idea what that discount card's for.
[SPEAKER_07]: I probably have a ton of stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get like a random 50% off on your purchases or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Am I a bad person?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I don't really shop at music stores anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not since Tower Records went under.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was my chain was Tower Records.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to buy import CDs from Tower Records.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was before the interwebs or when interwebs was all dial-up, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: When Orange Lounge Radio had a 56K friendly stream, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a while ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's when I was shopping at Tower Records before they went under.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe Virgin Megastore once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Virgin was awesome for import CDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: But now I have to admit... Who bought an activator at Virgin?
[SPEAKER_04]: When I buy CDs, it's Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does that make me a bad person?
[SPEAKER_11]: When I buy CDs, I don't rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: I go on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I buy the mp3 downloads.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I want them that badly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, this might make me really bad, but the last CD I bought was the Tron soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought that at Target.
[SPEAKER_04]: CeeLo Green's album for $5.
[SPEAKER_11]: and they're all DRM free on top of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now iTunes is too and you can convert from their format but it really is just super convenient to get it all on Amazon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I was playing some Final Fantasy 3 while I was waiting around for stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I started Oregon Trail today, and I'm like... Oh, the Facebook one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played it for like five seconds, and I was like, this just... This is overcomplicating it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This game has died of dysentery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's the best way to put it.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, the thing that gets it is that buying the tickets... Now, I'll just go download an Apple MU and play it that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: The magic is gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: The magic is kind of gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have some friends that are into it on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you're into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, I have no right to judge anyone.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing that Knights of the Clique game for forever, although I haven't touched it in like a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I wasn't feeling Oregon Trail.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm three weeks clean on it, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you really?
[SPEAKER_04]: You should get like a sober sticker for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rewinding to MMOs a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, I don't want to dwell on WoW too much, but I will tell you one thing I've kind of been looking at.
[SPEAKER_04]: As a lot of Warcraft players and other MMO players have been looking at, there's this new game coming out called Rift.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you read at all about this game?
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it like based off of the tabletop rifts?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure because I don't know enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like the Palladium games?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know enough about that scene.
[SPEAKER_04]: But look at some of the YouTubes on Rift and tell me what you think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, while you're at it, look at videos because we were doing this the other night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at videos for Guild Wars 2 and tell me what you think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Guild Wars for a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guild Wars 2, much different than Guild Wars 1.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take a look and see if either of those might woo you from WoW for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it better not, because Dan doesn't want to buy any more games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, the good news is Rift has an open beta starting really, really soon.
[SPEAKER_05]: This does look pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take a look at those while we talk about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at some of the videos on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially some of the PvP looks really pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know you're not into PvP, but it has both.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've started doing PvP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I've done the battles.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to get you back on Horde House to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because our friend and listener got me PvP gear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on to Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't play a whole lot this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mainly just a few things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sword and Poker 2, still playing that in iOS.
[SPEAKER_07]: This last dungeon is taking forever, but it's fun still.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just unlocked more weapons I can buy, but they're really expensive, so I have to grind some more dungeons for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: um and then I played um Marvel vs Capcom 3 a little bit of that um yeah that too that's an awesome awesome awesome game um I'm not very good at those types of games but it is somewhat button masher friendly I wouldn't say I'm just like a button masher but like I don't have any like real strategy into it you know it's just like okay I know the basic moves and stuff like that and
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, feel it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, like, 50 hit combos for me or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Did you say you're just feeling it up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Feeling it out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was going to say, because there's some pretty, you know, boobtastic characters in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then, you know, Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's, you know, usual.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a must for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we play that at work.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, obviously, we can play more of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's being sued because of the name.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's a
[SPEAKER_04]: DeadPixelLive.com
[SPEAKER_04]: How did he get all these big name interviews when we weren't looking?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chat.orange.com for more comments here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ziba is saying, I am loving Rift and can't wait for Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So both those games are getting a lot of buzz.
[SPEAKER_06]: And of course, everybody's always going to ask, which one of these is going to be the WoW killer?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably neither.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I will tell you what the WoW killer will ultimately be.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can already tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will look at my crystal ball.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will tell you what game is the WoW killer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_11]: WoW 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: WoW is the WoW killer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait and see.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sounds very suicidal.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, no, because, well, who?
[SPEAKER_11]: How did the Roman Empire fall?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because of the Roman Empire.
[SPEAKER_04]: More to quote an old Loki quote, an old, old Loki quote, Ow!
[SPEAKER_04]: I just shot myself in the foot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why are you shooting me in the foot?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob, can I pet this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, is that Guild Wars 2 now you're looking at?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: That makes for great radio, by the way, when you're sitting there going, ooh, pretty.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should post some of those links in chat just so people can take a peek for themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you have to imagine it.
[SPEAKER_11]: This place makes Stormwind look like an easy-to-navigate one-lane street.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me talk about my gaming week and some of the games I play this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mostly the same type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been somewhat of a slow month in gaming, just like it has been movies.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's not been a lot of new stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, more WoW, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I did play one new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: One game kind of came out and it was kind of one of those blink and you might have missed it games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played You Don't Know Jack, the brand new game that just came out from THQ with Jellyvision, of course, who made the old You Don't Know Jack.
[SPEAKER_04]: So maybe it's not really a brand new game because it's more like, hey, remember the 90s?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because these games were huge in the 90s.
[SPEAKER_04]: You Don't Know Jack and You Don't Know Jack the Ride, which I want to say originally was a Sierra thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I could be wrong on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody might correct me on that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that could explain why the long hiatus.
[SPEAKER_04]: But regardless of how it happened, THQ has now put out a You Don't Know Jack game for the current generation of consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's PC, it's 360, PlayStation, it's everywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the 360 is the version I played and I was at a little party with some friends last night and we were playing the new You Don't Know Jack game and the good news is it is pretty much what I remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a funny, quick, polished trivia game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lots of jokes, just kind of like one after the other.
[SPEAKER_04]: That almost kind of dry sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to say British sense of humor, not that dry, but just really like non-stop pun after pun and there's these weird jokes
[SPEAKER_04]: Kitties Kitten
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: You can also download expansions.
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe three are planned right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: One is up already.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ten more episodes for five bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that is 50 cents an episode.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the value of this game, I would really ask you, how much value are you going to get in like a party atmosphere?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the good news is you can play this on Xbox Live, but I think this would be the absolute worst game
[SPEAKER_04]: Possible game you could play on Xbox Live with strangers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it would suck all the fun out of the game because you know you're going to have people out there with a finite number of episodes who already know the answers to all the questions and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think that part, it might be a little bit ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, playing with trusted friends, I think it could be a great Xbox Live game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, one of those, and of course when I say Xbox Live, obviously the PlayStation has this comparable thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: PC does not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which I find very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why the PC version is only $20.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Even more value there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, I mean, there's not a lot of people that would play that multiplayer on a PC.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't that be kind of hard to play that multiplayer on a PC?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really, it's where I play my WoW.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but I meant like, you know, with friends, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no real, you're not going to have like four controllers or something like that, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah, I get what you're saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it's a little tough there, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't own the PC version, so I don't know how they do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if you can have little buzzers or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do hear, though, on the PlayStation 3 version, you can use the actual game buzz controllers, and you don't know Jack, which is nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get a little more use out of those things.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think single player will only be funny for so long the good news is it is a funny game so you'll get your lols out of it but I think the game works best in a party atmosphere so I think the question would really be are you going to be able to bring this to a party and get use out of this if so it might be worth your money I think it's been mildly successful so far it sold okay but it's something I could figure that will probably drop in price relatively quickly
[SPEAKER_04]: Something to keep in the back of your mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way they did the episodes is a little weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you take your game from place to place, you're more likely to see repeats.
[SPEAKER_04]: So just be careful.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you really want to be smart, copy your game data to a memory card or a USB stick if you're going to take the game from place to place.
[SPEAKER_04]: That way the game remembers what episode you've already seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, you're really setting yourself up for repeats.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is pretty good about knowing which episodes you've already seen, especially if you're going to go on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you take it from one place to another, it's not going to know because it's a new Xbox, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's nothing to read from.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you're going to see repeats because you only have so many episodes in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I just kind of want to throw that out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a word of caution.
[SPEAKER_04]: The way they did that is a little weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you don't know Jack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very polished, very funny, constant giggles from the group we were playing with.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's a good value.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, 50 cents for a game is, you know, gosh, you go to Dave & Buster's and throw away money faster than that on those stupid crane games or skeeball or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think it's a decent value.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: maybe a few more questions for the buck or maybe a different way to randomize them or something maybe could be the feedback but I will save that for You Don't Know Jack 2 which I do hope happens at this point or whatever they're going to end up calling it so I definitely give the game a favorable review especially if you like these game show games this blows that seen it shit out of the water like seriously this is the definitive trivia party game
[SPEAKER_04]: The only possible contender maybe is Buzz on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if you have the Xbox, you don't really have that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this blows that Cena shit out of the water.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is much better.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, take a look.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, that was really it for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's get into some housekeeping tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was some, I don't want to say late-breaking news, but it just happened a little earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're competing against the Grammys tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, last week it was the Stupor Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight it's the Grammys.
[SPEAKER_04]: In two weeks it's what, the Oscars?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like, we just can't fucking win.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but no one cares about the Oscars.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everything is on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the good stuff's going to be on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to see Gaga hatch out of an egg, it'll be on YouTube later.
[SPEAKER_11]: I need to think of a good name to call the Grammys because I have the Super Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Grammys should be the Shamys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Kathy Griffin's The Shmemys or whatever she calls it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that's for the daytime Emmys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or the technical ones or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, besides, by the way, speaking of Kathy Griffin, just because I love that bitch, I got to give a shout out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear she's going to have a brand new show on Broadway?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's only going to be on for like a week in March, but it's called, ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Best name for a show ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Kathy Griffin wants a Tony.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this isn't the Kathy Griffin podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I digress.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's just really fucking funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will listen to her stand up while I play WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: I listen to a lot of random stuff while I play WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: I listen to podcasts while I play WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: I listen to WoW podcasts while I play WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very meta.
[SPEAKER_04]: The whole thing is very meta.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like when I was in Blade's Edge and we were on Blade's Edge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very meta.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was I going to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, the Grammys.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song won a Grammy.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Baba Yetu from Civilization IV, which is a really great song.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've never heard it, I'll have to fire up a clip here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't really prepared to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_04]: It won a Grammy, which is funny because the song is actually kind of old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's...
[SPEAKER_04]: It's been out for a little while because Civilization 4 was kind of what it was written for, but here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see, it didn't win for being in Civilization 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: The artist, Christopher Tin, put it in his recent CD that he released, and the CD, the song from the CD won, and I believe he actually won a Grammy for the whole CD as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: He won two Grammys tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here's a clip if you've never heard this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously, if you haven't played Civilization 4, A, you're missing one of the best PC games ever, and B, you haven't had a chance to just sit on the title screen and listen to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't this song just kind of make you feel like, oh yeah, I'm going to rule the world?
[SPEAKER_04]: This is going to be a military victory game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, this is offensive to Islam.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I'm sorry, that was a little big planet.
[SPEAKER_07]: My mistake.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: Grammys
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into some more video game news tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: The stuff that's not late-breaking, but still is going on in the world of gaming this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's going to start us off, as always.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although it was fixed, and I'm sure that the person that runs Kevin Butler's fake account for the fake person probably didn't understand what was going on here.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, the person that ran the Kevin Butler on Twitter accidentally reposted the key for... Or one of the keys to the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember the whole lawsuit going on because the keys got leaked out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, this is the key that turned out to be one used in the hack through the USB dongle, which I don't think anyone even really uses anymore, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Nonetheless, they retweeted, so let me guess, you sank my battleship, and then they retweeted the key.
[SPEAKER_04]: 4-6-D-C, oh, forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so, of course, you know, it was later removed off the Twitter account, but it is still funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of like, oh, hey, someone's not paying attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully no one got fired over it, but, you know, still funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you don't know what it is, which I'm sure whoever runs this account on behalf of the Kevin Butler character probably didn't know what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, if I didn't do this show, I wouldn't know what that is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, even doing this show, I would look at that and go, why is someone speaking to me in hex?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what is your problem?
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, and that doesn't even look, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That does not look anything like battleship numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, but if you're kind of that snarky character that Kevin Butler's supposed to be, it doesn't like that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huge Sony faux pas, or they'll get over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think the funnier thing about this is that all these blogs are reporting on it with a screenshot of the tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now the tweet has been seen by like 10 times as many people as would have seen it originally.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why it's really funny, but it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Irony, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Irony.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, before we get into the next story, I got derailed by something in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just think this is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I only have kind of heard of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, have you ever heard of this thing called GetGlue?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never... It's like a Foursquare.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine like Foursquare for just stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like a video game you're playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You could check in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how Foursquare works?
[SPEAKER_04]: You check in to like... And then you cheat while you're driving by?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm at Pinkberry and I'm checking in so I can be the mayor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if my friends are nearby, I'll get a text message.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now they have this thing called GetGlue where you can check into movies you're watching or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just got told that Orange Lounge Radio has a GetGlue page.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we have people that check in to listening to this on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just thought that was really cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I want to give a shout out to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're listening to this on the podcast or whatever, you should check in on GetGlue.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be a nice way to help spread the word of OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I noticed that some of the related ones happen to be like All Games or Video Game Outsiders, which is also on the network.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: And For Real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've never... Who's For Real?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that the band from the 90s that did I Like to Move It, Move It?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that who For Real is?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm getting off track.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's a little obscure, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is very obscure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it says they were on the... No, it's the one that did... It was a remix of something.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was on Max.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't remember what the hell it was now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm telling you, for real, did I like to move it, move it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is so stupid that we're having this conversation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Highs Off of You.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did that song, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Away from the 90s and into today.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about the Xperia Play.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xperia Play is the Sony PlayStation phone, for lack of a better term.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like a little PlayStation Go, but this time it actually has a phone in it, so there's a lot of purpose to be getting this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Xperia Play is, of course, the new smartphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is coming out in early spring.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will be on Verizon's network.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what they're saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: There was a Sony Ericsson MWC 2011 press conference where this Xperia Play got its launch window.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be coming out in March.
[SPEAKER_04]: The U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: will be one of the first destinations, and Verizon will be the first carrier for the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't say that it will be the only carrier for the phone, just that it will be the first.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's been a pretty good year for Verizon so far between the iPhone and this, so...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but carrier makes me think of a disease carrier.
[SPEAKER_04]: I imagine some of the other carriers will be getting this too.
[SPEAKER_04]: And for folks that are maybe like, I'm not feeling the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm more of a gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is going to be a pretty good choice for them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, by the way, just so you know, the Xperia Play, it's supposed to be preloaded with what they are saying is a legendary PlayStation 1 game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's also going to come with 50 different games from 20 publishers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not built in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to have to buy them.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I think the legendary game is supposed to be Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, they're not saying that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's just according to Kaz Harai.
[SPEAKER_04]: They haven't said exactly what the game is yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It could be, but that would be a Namco game.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of think it would come from Sony's first party itself.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be weird and say Twisted Metal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: That just seems like an easy game to put there.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to be Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it will be something from Sony in-house.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it's going to bring the third party into play.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be Irritating Stick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why when you said that I thought Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I do that all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, but Grand Theft Auto should be on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those two games couldn't be any more different.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gran Turismo would be a good choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be a very good choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: uh just so you know most of the games that will be coming out for the device they are ports of course of other games i noticed uh there's actually a little guitar hero logo in here which is really funny considering what we're going to talk about in a minute uh but uh yeah some of the other games that will be there assassin's creed dead space battlefield fifa a multiplayer fifa game in mobile what's that
[SPEAKER_04]: so, alright alright, well let's move on with some more news or actually wait, before we do, anyone gonna get one of these here in studio, anyone chat?
[SPEAKER_04]: gonna pick up the experience?
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a PSP I have a PSP, I have an iPhone and I'm locked into the iPhone contract, I can't go run out and get another phone I wouldn't care anyway, you know what, I keep getting flashbacks to the N-Gage and that was pretty bad
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this will be better than the N-Gage though, let's be real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be for real.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to play PlayStation 1 games on the go, just buy a PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, just buy a PSP 1000 and you can do it just as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except you don't have the dual sort of analog sticks, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: If I want to play PS1 games on the go, I'll just bring my PS1 with me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Amen.
[SPEAKER_11]: and get a mobile monitor, which I think I've still got one somewhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm a little bit disgusted though, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because about our next news story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Disgusted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, out with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'm sure many people know already, but the Hero franchise has gone BOOM!
[SPEAKER_11]: Activision is discontinuing development of Guitar Hero for 2011 and disbanding their business unit.
[SPEAKER_11]: and guess what else is included with that that's going to be DJ Hero as well they're not going to be releasing the new download content packs beyond what they already have and nothing new will be made however you can still download everything that's there now and basically they're saying that they've seen rapid declines in that genre but really I think that Rock Band does it better
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I mean, let's be honest though, is this really a surprise?
[SPEAKER_07]: No Uh, yes, it is a surprise because I would have thought they would have still tried to whore it out I mean, even if sales have dwindled a little bit, you know, why kill off the whole thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I know why they killed off the whole thing It's because investors tell them what to do
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, honestly, I'm kind of sitting here going, okay, big surprise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, you know, this was all over.
[SPEAKER_04]: This news was so big it was on CNN.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was all over Twitter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might have even been a trending topic for all I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But all these people were going, RIP Guitar Hero, dead and gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hardly knew ye.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's kind of like, um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Did anyone buy the last game in the series?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did anyone buy Warriors of Rock?
[SPEAKER_11]: I think we picked up the Green Day one for five bucks at Dimple.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not even Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, not Green Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was one of the... Van Halen, Metallica?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, one of the... It was a...
[SPEAKER_07]: Guitar Hero and let's be real five bucks for that Van Halen one is probably about all it's worth like it was really a terrible bad game it was an obvious milking of the franchise so bad that they gave it away free to inflate the numbers of the Guitar Hero 5 series so they could say hey look how many Guitar Hero units have sold for the franchise way more than Rock Band granted they had way more versions come out than Rock Band so
[SPEAKER_07]: It's still disappointing, I mean, because I don't think that they're done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they're done with this, but when they see an idea where they can make some money, they're going to go after it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I have a feeling that the next game they do is going to be similar to Dance Central, because I don't think they want to be out of the market, but I wouldn't be surprised if we see a dance hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's interesting is that I see some folks in chat, and of course, Black Wolf jumping in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I bought Warriors of Ra, I knew there'd be somebody, there'd be like one person that bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it didn't sell to zero copies, it sold some, but what I'm just saying is that this decline has been a little bit obvious for a while now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a lot of people out there that were the same ones touting R.I.P.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero were kind of rolling their eyes a little bit at the franchise and how it kind of has gone the past couple games.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's been nothing really that new in the series for a while now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I kind of hate to say it, but DJ Hero was going down a very similar path.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, the last game in the series wasn't terrible, but I didn't see where there was really a future in DJ Hero either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, unfortunately one of the things we weren't going to be talking about is how they were saying that their digital downloads were up 20%.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're lucky, DJ Hero was, for the first one, was much worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: It had five.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think five packs come out, if that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then DJ Hero 2 had about the same within a relatively short time frame, but I don't... You know, we were talking a little bit how they're basically going to...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, cease putting out download content for, you know, Guitar Hero and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But honestly, I don't think anyone would have noticed if they stopped because they weren't really doing much to begin with.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's kind of, kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, they really kind of let that slip through their hands.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, again, I just don't think the series was kind of going anywhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just was kind of on a one-track direction.
[SPEAKER_04]: And again, I really challenge a lot of these developers to innovate.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is how you're going to keep your games more interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, but see, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock Band, I mean, it's the last band standing, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: But unfortunately, they didn't really innovate enough, I guess, with Rock Band 3 with the keyboard and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: or they're not marketing it well enough, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not selling as well as the last one, period.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what I mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm just saying, you know, because you're saying they didn't innovate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me take a step back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they innovated, but they're not letting people know that so well.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't really see a lot of Rock Band 3 being marketed as now you can really learn to play an instrument.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can really learn to play keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't on the daytime talk shows like I kind of thought it would be and so on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not trying to say that Rock Band hasn't really innovated.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's done certainly more than Guitar Hero did, which is why it is now standing alone, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I don't think there'll be a Rock Band 4 this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would go so far as to say there's not going to be another rock band until there's another series of consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_11]: I honestly think it would be smart to support the current rock band and just put out more content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's definitely what they're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, there's...
[SPEAKER_07]: I honestly don't think there is a need to put out a new console game because their business model right now is just putting out tons of content for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So why do you need a new version?
[SPEAKER_11]: They're making money that way and on top of that it is fairly cost effective.
[SPEAKER_07]: because Activision's plan was kind of the opposite.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll force them to buy a new copy of the game or a new version of the game because we're not going to put out a lot of content for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the only way you're going to get new content is by spending the $60 to buy a brand new game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some interesting questions from chat here.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR Dollar Bill says, Guitar Hero started doing the DDR type scene where they made new songs but didn't advance the series much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kind of interesting though, DDR is still alive to tell the tale, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: DDR is still kickin'.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, DDR and Konami also promised that they're going to support DDR with tons of download content and they never fucking do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or for Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: Never had a ton of download content on a regular basis like they promised.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm thinking also DDR probably has a much lower budget than the Guitar Hero games and I don't think there's as high of an expectation there.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think in the end that's what's kept DDR going all these years.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the weight loss thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody thinks they're going to lose weight playing DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me bring up this other comment from our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ezam in our chat room at chat.orangelongeradio.com says, although I think a good question here is, can Konami take advantage of the void and try to get Guitar Freak's Drum Mania stateside?
[SPEAKER_04]: And my answer is a resounding giant no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to be bluntly honest with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want him to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think the games are as good as Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Might make you mad, but let's be real.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are not going to get those games here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Konami missed that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And two words, rock revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was their attempt to bring those games stateside and don't think it wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it was a...
[SPEAKER_04]: Hot Mess to say nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me put it this way, and I put it in my Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they want a second attempt at the guitar games and stuff like that, if you put out a decent release now, it might actually work because you're not going to have a lot of competition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, you're going to have rock bands competition, but you got to...
[SPEAKER_07]: We tell our customers that we have... There's tons of people trying to get into the video game or movie market and stuff like that and people that want to sell on eBay and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we tell them, you've got to have a niche because you're competing with people that have been established in the business for a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, same with the music game genre.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to have a niche.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, you're not going to be able to compete with the large library that Rock Band has.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're going to need to come up with either...
[SPEAKER_07]: Original songs, which granted, Konami is great at original songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami originals are just awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they have, for guitar games, they have a huge library of stuff that they can put in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of people in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: may not necessarily get it or be really enthusiastic about some of that stuff, but
[SPEAKER_07]: so what, just put it in the game as well and put some good licensed songs from the US in there and maybe don't fuck up the interface system with grey buttons or your stupid drum controller nobody wants to use just use the peripherals that are out there now, put out some good software and that's it and hell, call Guitar Freaks because you know what, you've got that franchise you have the rights to that, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, if Konami were to kill DDR, OLR and the rest of the computer would go on a rampage and go on a global-sized boycott.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of surprised that news hasn't already come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, not to be a pessimist, I know a lot of you still love your DDR, but I'm going to be just, let's not mince words here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not the same game I loved 10 years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that was terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it was created by an algorithm.
[SPEAKER_07]: There wasn't actually any original steps for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you couldn't make edits for those.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they wanted you to buy four fucking pads for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, that's not gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, back to the Activision news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say, I'm a tiny bit sad that means there's probably not gonna be that DJ Hero game on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I don't know if that's already in the can, so to speak, but I am assuming that's not happening at this point.
[SPEAKER_04]: and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would have been interesting to see that like in the portable market and the whole 3D thing, but oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably would have just been a cheap knockoff of the console games anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Loki, what else you got for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we're going to talk a little bit more about Activision and the fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, they're reducing their headcount by 500.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you can kind of guess where that's coming from.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're saying they're making significant investments elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our net headcount at the end of the year is probably not going to be materially different given that we're ramping up development teams around Blizzard's new MMO and around Call of Duty initiatives.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, because you have to understand this is why Guitar Hero and the whole Hero franchise went away.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's because I can sink, you know, if I'm Activision, I can sink, you know, say $50 million into, you know, a couple Guitar Hero games and maybe not make quite as much money back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I'll make back my investment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or I can sink $50 million into a couple Call of Duty games and they're going to sell like hotcakes.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's where they're going to put their money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and then this is the other thing that didn't really make any sense to me, but I guess, hey, you paid for the license, so why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Spider-Man!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's gonna be another Spider-Man game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, I don't know, the last Spider-Man game did so well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, so they have that coming in 2011.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, I guess, two TV licensed titles as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that they're going to see a new Family Guy game, because, God, the last Family Guy game was so wonderful, and a Wipeout game, which, to be honest, they did have a Wipeout game already, and it was not good.
[SPEAKER_07]: So... Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's totally awesome, just to keep that shit around, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I mean, there is that new Spider-Man movie that's coming out, what, next year or whatever, the one they're filming right now with the whole, the reboot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but this is just based on that, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, because this is just, it's going to be like Shattered Dimensions or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I would have thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of going back to this, I was actually reading, there was a letter to, well, I guess, a letter from the editor and the newest Game Informer that, this is obviously before the whole Guitar Hero stuff went down,
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Why the fuck are you trying to make a Bond game?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Bond franchise has kind of lost its appeal years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is a game that not necessarily this company would be good to make a title for.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe a good racing game instead.
[SPEAKER_04]: well I don't know about the because honestly I thought that first Daniel Craig Bond movie Casino Royale which a couple years ago was really good it was like it was a nice swift kick in the pants a lot of people were very skeptical about it it was really good but I think the biggest problem was that they were putting out a Bond game when Bond wasn't really in people's minds because Quantum of Solace didn't do as well and some would argue it probably wasn't as good of a movie either and this new Bond game Bloodstone or whatever it was called came out like two years after that like people were not thinking about James Bond
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: They knew it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so they just kind of set him up to fail and they got rid of him.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, there is a new Bond movie now coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: They finally confirmed they're going to do a new Bond movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully it'll be as good as Casino Royale was.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I wonder who's going to make the game tie in for that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's going to be Activision because they had the lights to the Bond franchise.
[SPEAKER_04]: But how did Goldeneye end up doing for them?
[SPEAKER_07]: That did okay, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just Goldeneye.
[SPEAKER_07]: All it is is Goldeneye re-skinned with Daniel Craig on it, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It probably sold more than the other one, sadly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It probably did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's not Bizarre's fault?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not Bizarre's fault.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bizarre's fault, or there was really no fault to them anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they could have made the game as great as possible, but when you put it out a week before fucking Call of Duty comes out, no one's going to pay attention to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to be like, fuck that, I'm getting Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_04]: The biggest problem, I think, with Blur is that it came out the exact same time as Split Second and Mod Nation Racers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And people just didn't want to buy all those racers.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Red Dead Redemption.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, Blur, I'm sure, was a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just tiny.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Activision, I don't think, cares.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's frustrating.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and by the way, I don't remember if this was mentioned before, but remember that Seven Studios, the one that put out that game Scratch?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, Activision bought them and then dissolved them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did Scratch even ever come out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope, it never came out because they bought the studio and then they fired them all.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Way to go, Activision.
[SPEAKER_04]: Way to get rid of your competition.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's something.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, geez.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and then one more thing I was going to mention, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: One other thing they said they weren't going to put out this year, a new Tony Hawk game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because the last two Tony Hawk games were terrible, so finally they learned a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: No new Tony Hawk game this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: All they need to do is go back to Pro Skater, and they'd be just fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I see you talking in our chat room, DarkSakura, to the listeners about James Bond.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, we were discussing, a couple of us had the same first Bond movie we saw in the theater.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was A View to a Kill.
[SPEAKER_04]: The 80s one, right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: With Duran Duran doing the intro and Grace Jones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Grace fucking Jones.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fierce, fierce human being.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like, vicious.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's next to the word fierce.
[SPEAKER_04]: She invented fierce.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no other.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you look in the dictionary, there's actually no words.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just automatically links you mentally to Wikipedia about her.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how Bizarre could have sold a million billion of the Bond game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just make it all about Grace Jones.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now I have to go on Wikipedia and look up Grace Jones.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how they sold a ton of games?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bond.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Getting a little silly now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, the Xbox Live House Party is coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might remember this is the whole little let's do the Summer of Arcade promotion at a different time in the year.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, seriously, they need to host this with Kid and Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to dig them out of wherever rehab center they're in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I apologize if I've taken someone's story later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think this is coming up tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there's been more and more furious rumors this week that Xbox is planning on launching a TV network within Xbox, which some time ago Conan was wooed to be a part of before they decided to stick with something a little more traditional.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would not be beyond all reason that Kid and Play could do some type of...
[SPEAKER_04]: House Party
[SPEAKER_07]: WolfGirl
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds like such crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: And apparently she was in Pee Wee's Playhouse Christmas Special.
[SPEAKER_11]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: And in the Beastmaster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, can I talk about the house party?
[SPEAKER_04]: I realize Grace Jones was not invited to the house party, but I still want to talk about some of the awesome games that are coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It all starts this week, February 16th.
[SPEAKER_04]: The first release comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hardcore Uprising comes out first.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a game that is kind of like Contra.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's really, really like Contra, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_04]: $15 for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bejeweled
[SPEAKER_04]: Blitz Blitz Blitz Blitz
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what else you got for us besides links to Grace Jones' Wikipedias?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, now I'm reading about Studio 54.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, according to EA, 7% of mobile gaming is done on the toilet.
[SPEAKER_11]: They did some research, and this is actually from EA Mobile.
[SPEAKER_11]: They basically said there were five different percentages of when people tend to play their games.
[SPEAKER_11]: And also went over some myths.
[SPEAKER_11]: So according to the research, 47% of the time is people playing at home.
[SPEAKER_11]: 12% of that time is during a commute, 14% while at work, 7% in the restroom, and 3% during school hours, and 1% at the airport.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, we have a clip of DarkSakura playing on her mobile phone here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sitting on the toilet.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sitting on the toilet.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's enough of that, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: There actually was a shirt that I almost got one time that says iPhone changed the way I pee.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought that was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: I admit I used to play my phone sometimes at work, but
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this one might have actually been a little more appropriate for mobile gaming Now flush
[SPEAKER_04]: Can I be real though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of surprised the number isn't higher.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that's people who admit to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Namco is having a sale right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: A variety of companies are having iPhone game sales right now where you can get a lot of pretty good iPhone games really cheap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the games I bought this week was Pac-Man Championship Edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's a pretty faithful translation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Controls could be a little better with actual tangible buttons, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'll tell you, I probably played most of that game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I play a lot of Solitaire on the toilet I will freely admit this, my toilet game of choice is Solitaire And reading my Facebook Loki, what's your favorite mobile game to play on the pooper?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't play games on the toilet Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Really, I don't What do you do, you just sit there and think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't need-
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, okay, there is one other game that actually I did play extensively in the bathroom and that was Angry Birds.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Dan walked by the bathroom and hearing the tweet noises.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's like, are you playing that game in there again?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, Angry Birds on the toilet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_11]: But hey, how about those other myths, by the way?
[SPEAKER_11]: The myth, the top mobile games are all casual.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they said that their biggest performers, there was Epyx, Infinity Blade, and Dead Space, which were at the top of the App Store.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that one size game fits all platforms, and not so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the Android ones are specifically having to be redone for working on Android.
[SPEAKER_11]: And brands don't matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he says, yeah, they do.
[SPEAKER_11]: The top iPhone games are all brands.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is as good as it gets.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he said, no, there's going to be better.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob told me to.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's not a lot coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will cut you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will put that sitting on the toilet on repeat and blast it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, sorry about that, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very rude of us.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tomorrow, we have Dragon Quest VI Realms of Revelation coming out on the Nintendo DS, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're looking for a game with anthropomorphic consoles, because they have Hyperdimension Neptunia, the special edition with an art book in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have chicks not really resembling consoles, but representing different consoles in that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Man, it's like the console wars for real.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brunswick Pro Bowling on the Xbox 360 with Kinect, and that's going to be coming out this week as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Marvel vs. Capcom 3 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely worth picking up that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone I know had it early because I have special connections in my new job.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Gears of War Triple Pack is coming out this week in case you haven't played any of those games and you want to catch up before the new one comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the way, how is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Marvel vs. Capcom 3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fucking awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all about Deadpool.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's just freaking sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and by the way, Shu McGrath and Jill Valentine, unlock content.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a key for the download content.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not download content.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's paid unlock content.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I don't think it's paid.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's just time delayed for people that don't have special editions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it may be paid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Other things.
[SPEAKER_07]: Amnesia on PC coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dance Paradise on Xbox 360 and also supporting Kinect.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear it's terrible though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep that in mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dungeons on PC Ys 1 and 2 Chronicles I'm sorry that's actually getting to next week but that will be coming out on PSP next week or the week after next that's it
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, going on to Japanese release dates and what's coming out in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Marvel vs. Capcom 3 is getting its release in Japan this week as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll be out on the Xbox 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also on the 360 this week, Two Worlds 2, the Japanese version, and a game called Catherine.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a game from Atlus that is coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Personas Team first game for the HD system.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's about...
[SPEAKER_04]: Vincent is a wishy-washy salaryman, a little too afraid to be tied down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facing the appeals of marriage from his longtime girlfriend Catherine, all he wanted to do was to escape.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one night he succeeded into the arms of the beautiful young Catherine.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's Catherine with a K and Catherine with a C. This sounds kind of weird, but it could be kind of awesome too.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is a strategy game, and there's like these guys with sheep heads.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is fucking weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: This looks like a scary game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like when you say Persona, I think, oh, it's going to be the Prinnies.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no, this is like a freaking weird game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's a creepy, erotic game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sort of.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like Night Trap all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, moving on to the PlayStation 3 and the releases coming out over there.
[SPEAKER_04]: On the PlayStation 3, of course, Catherine gets a release there as well, as well as Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ninja Gaiden Sigma 2 is getting a price reduction this week, if you haven't checked that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Two Worlds 2, also on the PlayStation 3 this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, lots of cross-platform love this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to the Nintendo Wii this week, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is nothing on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But next week, there's a Gundam game.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get to that next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know and on the Sony PSP if you're sad about Guitar Hero having gone under you might be a fan of this series DJ Max Portable 3 is a very big release for the music game fans this week on the PSP that is in regular and limited edition also Monochrome and My Mary May With Bee get price reductions this week that's really what it's called but DJ Max Portable 3 look at that
[SPEAKER_04]: All the great K-pop songs in a Beatmania-esque style interface, but on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_04]: Definitely a lot of cult fans.
[SPEAKER_04]: There will be a lot of people listening to this show that import that game, I am sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for Japanese release dates.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about overseas in the old country?
[SPEAKER_11]: A few things.
[SPEAKER_11]: We have on the 16th, Hardcore Uprising on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: And we also have on the 18th, Crash Time 4 for Xbox 360, Death Smiles, and then Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: We also have PopCap hits.
[SPEAKER_11]: Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Death Smiles is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I know what a lot of people will be playing this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Death Smiles.
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_11]: Marvel vs. Capcom 3 is totally worthy, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had a chance to check it out early too, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_11]: Worthy.
[SPEAKER_11]: But Tatsunoko vs. Capcom fighting scheme not as great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I wasn't too fond of that when I played Tatsunoko vs. Capcom.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very mash friendly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, sounds good for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love button mashing.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, just a couple more stories for you guys, and then we're going to get to the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we're not there just yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony is claiming that the Gran Turismo Academy, one little event contest that they have going on right now where people race and report their times, I guess, in Gran Turismo 5 on different tracks for different specific categories, with a chance to win a spot as a real race driver.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently they say round two was ruined by cheaters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it won't count, so they're moving everybody to round three.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's how they claim it was cheated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently the track has a nice little S turn in it, and so people were cutting corners in the track driving off-road.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, it's a design of the track.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't actually something that people used like a mod or something like that to cheat in.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were just cutting corners off-road.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cheating?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they're like, but in real racing, you would have gotten a penalty for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, maybe somebody that spent so long making their game... Well, then maybe the game should have penalized you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe if you had spent all that time, you know, perfecting your game, maybe you should have, I don't know, added a penalty for cutting the track like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I realize Gran Turismo is supposed to be, like, the real deal racing simulator and all that, but, like, games like Mario Kart and shit, and even things like Blur, you're kind of encouraged to do shit like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or Burnout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially Burnout.
[SPEAKER_04]: Off-roading is encouraged and rewarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: That game fuel.
[SPEAKER_04]: That entire fucking game was off-roading.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not even a glitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just a part of the track.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're cutting out the track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that seems a little silly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It seems a little silly to throw the whole thing out because of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I have to say about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think your competition's stupid.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although it's interesting because isn't the prize or whatever for winning the competition to race a real car?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I hope that they race on that track with the S-curve and drive the fucker off-road because that would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they don't want people that are going to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna do that anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I would do.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd drive that thing straight into a wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, expensive car.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crash.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might also get set on fire and I don't think you really want that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have a fire suit.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, round three, though, does start on Monday, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see how people cheat on that real soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on to some more stories for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're going to get into the classic game of the week, which of course is DarkSakura diving into the vault and finding a game that she thinks you guys should be playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead Space 2
[SPEAKER_04]: and unfortunately he's not able to walk forward with the mouse and you know this is kind of the bummer with a lot of games that have custom or don't have customizable controls is a lot of times they're customized really weird and people want to change them so
[SPEAKER_04]: Dead Space 2, We Hear You, Steve Papautas
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry if I said that wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: Said that there will be a PC version patch enabling full control remapping.
[SPEAKER_04]: It will be coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is some full remarks that were made.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Dead Space 2 team is aware of the issue that disabled players are having with Dead Space 2 PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, a number of folks on our team are so passionate about getting this fix done that they are currently working hard to allow players to remap key bindings to the mouse which should help disabled players enjoy the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm glad that they listened, especially with that reason being in place.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little silly it wasn't there the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, customizable controls is a very standard thing in this day and age.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, maybe this lesson will help other developers learn it, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a lot of games, though, that really need to have...
[SPEAKER_11]: I still... You remember how pissed off I got the very, very first time I played World of Warcraft and found I couldn't use my mouse?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or a controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because I'd been playing Final Fantasy XI on a controller and I'd been playing PSO on a controller.
[SPEAKER_11]: so they should just allow any kind of custom controller to work I think there's a mod for Warcraft where you can use a controller but it's not officially supported so you can't really count it I'm used to the damn keyboard now but I really think that games need to not limit people in how they can control that if you can map anything out on a keyboard then you should be able to map it out on a gamepad as well
[SPEAKER_04]: and I think it's all this this type of story is a very humbling thing I think too for the developers who have to kind of stop and go oh yeah not everybody is as fortunate as I am to have every you know the 10 fingers and 10 toes doing you know what they what it does you know what I mean so it's uh it's a little bit humbling and just a reminder customizable controls go a long way in helping more people play your game
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's move on to a segment we do here every week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a chance for DarkSakura to dive through the vault and find a video game that she says, Hey, you ungrateful kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, listen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop watching those crappy Grammys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get off my lawn.
[SPEAKER_04]: And play this classic game right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_11]: The game is Star Parodia, which I had the hardest time finding because a lot of places romanize it as Parodier, which makes sense because it's a parody of Star Soldier.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I've talked about this game before, but I haven't used it as a classic game.
[SPEAKER_11]: I checked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's take a look.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm gonna play a little bit of music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: And it only came out in Japan.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they were going to be bringing it out in North America as Phantasy Star Soldier, but they did not.
[SPEAKER_11]: It actually had a release through the Virtual Console in Europe on May 16th, 2008.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, of course, it was released in America on August 11th, 2008.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you guys can actually play this game now.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_11]: So it's a vertically scrolling shooter like the Star Soldier games and has the collecting power-ups to upgrade your weapons and different bosses and mini-bosses and horizontal shooting with your vehicle of choice.
[SPEAKER_11]: This one also has a high score time attack mode that were in Star Soldier.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now for the parody part.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really cutesy, has very cartoony type of graphics, and not very violent.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like when you kill an enemy, they don't die, they just wave white flags.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you can choose one of three different vehicles.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can choose the Paracelsus from Star Soldier, or a giant flying bomber man, or a PC engine that shoots cue cards and CD-ROMs at the enemies.
[SPEAKER_11]: This game is super adorable cute.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love this game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I remember when my friend, we were visiting my friend who lived in Berkeley at the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like right now they're fighting the origami monster.
[SPEAKER_04]: It looks like one of those tangrams.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: But a friend of ours, you know, was just breaking out the most bizarre of her PC Engine collection and saying, play this.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: So this is actually one I'm looking for a legit of.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's a fun little game.
[SPEAKER_11]: and... I mean, it's just... I love parody games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love games that are fun, you know, good, solid games that don't take themselves too seriously.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I love the Proteus series a lot more than this, obviously.
[SPEAKER_11]: But... this one's just really...
[SPEAKER_11]: And on top of that, I like that all the little guys that they talk to in the intro are little Bomberman guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they're outfitting a PC Engine, you know, with a big smiley face, with a copy of Super Star Soldier, so it'll fight.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a little sexy lady standing on the stage in the background there.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's like, ooh, don't shoot me.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think one of the enemies you fight in this is like a black Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_11]: and all kinds of stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really a fun little game.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I love the music in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: The music's great.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's the giant fish.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that's a fish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who plays a maraca, apparently.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it plays maracas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, it's totally worth it.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can get it on Virtual Console.
[SPEAKER_11]: I totally recommend it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's officially listed as Star Parodia.
[SPEAKER_11]: I learned it as Star Parodia, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's written as Star Parodia.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, there it is, your classic game of the week, Star Parodia, or whatever you want to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like Soldier, but, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it is available on Virtual Console?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it is, and America came out again on August 11th, 2008.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you have it, your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now it's part of the show where we're going to take a quick break.
[SPEAKER_04]: But don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to come right back.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got a lot more stories to talk about in Part B tonight, including a very interesting story about possible serial numbers coming to PlayStation 3 games tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: and your Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last chance to get those in you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Be sure to follow us on Twitter so you can interact with the show and send us your story suggestions.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday, the February 13th of 2011, or 2011, whatever it is you prefer.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're up against the Grammys tonight, but whatever, all the good stuff will be on YouTube later anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't stop some of our live people from kind of watching it with one eye and listening to this show with their ears or what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're still here, you know, kind of moving away at the gaming news from the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to get into the Twitter topics real soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: A chance for you guys to interact with us here live on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some rapid fire news, of course, in a moment as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe more talk about Marvel vs. Capcom 3.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Comic Insanity.
[SPEAKER_11]: And today we had a special guest on the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had PJ Perez, who is the publisher for Pop Goes the Icon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I also host this with Maren Marvel, as we all know her as Tiara, and Shadow, or Dan Shadow, or whichever name he's deciding to go by this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: We go live on Tuesday at InfamousNFAMOUS.net Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: The spinoff show that I do is called The Best Little Horde House in Azeroth, or Horde House for short, if you're a fan of World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll probably like this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's myself and Extifer being really lulzy about the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this week was some PvP-centric talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you are into PvP at all, you might want to check out this week's show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But of course, all the Warcraft news and everything going on in the world of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: on Horde House.
[SPEAKER_04]: Check it out on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not cool enough to have a website yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe someday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's get into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some quick, quick stuff that just didn't make the show otherwise.
[SPEAKER_04]: And definitely your last chance to get those Twitter topics in.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be getting those right after the quick fire news stories.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, Project M, a kind of a homebrew effort to make Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brawl play a little bit more like Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Melee, has released its first demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, what's kind of cool about this hack is it doesn't require that you have any sort of mods done to your system.
[SPEAKER_07]: All you need to do is dump it onto a SD card and pop it into your Wii, and away you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: so you can download that from Project M's website which is projectm.smashmods.com and I believe that you do need a card though that is less than 2 gigs in size in order to be able to have the thing work but yeah check it out it's really more for the hardcore Malibu player because there's a lot of tweaks and stuff in there that most average people probably wouldn't get so that is out there to check out
[SPEAKER_07]: In case you have a Netflix disc for your PlayStation Wii, well, unfortunately, it's not going to work after February 16th.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I guess, you know, they're going to send out an email to all the members saying that the disc will cease to function, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, of course, you can always download the streaming software via the Wii Shop channel because that's why they're getting rid of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is another option for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be sure to do that if you want to still stream stuff on your Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: The Battle of Little Slugger, Kano's Salt, and those are going to be released as remixed extended versions.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then the Beatus Blues, we're getting, I guess, a retro remix for that release.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be awesome because the music from Super Meat Boy is great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be probably some really hard stuff too, which will be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, his comment was, I wanted to have some stuff in there for people who delight in 100%ing expert Dragon Force.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that'll give you an idea of how hard it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they're expected sometime after February 15th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, let's get to some other news, and this kinda sorta has to do with that same thing, except it's not Super Meat Boy, it's Rock Band, and what is coming out this week on Rock Band, the good news is, despite all of the stuff that's going on with Guitar Hero, Rock Band is still kicking, with some expansions, and I like this, this week is the February Heartache Duets Pack, which I think is great, which includes Bonnie Tyler's Total Eclipse of the Heart.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's
[SPEAKER_04]: Lita Ford
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we do have Animotion with Obsession, which I think is cool Bob, B.O.B.
[SPEAKER_04]: with Hayley Williams with Airplanes Human League with Don't You Want Me Lady Antebellum with Need You Now Stevie Nicks with Stop Dragging My Heart Around Oh, now that's a good one By far the coolest No, this blows all the others out of the water You ready?
[SPEAKER_04]: Paradise by The Dashboard Light by Meatloaf
[SPEAKER_04]: Outstanding.
[SPEAKER_04]: Absolutely outstanding.
[SPEAKER_11]: But we just scared Shermie out with that list.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not quite.
[SPEAKER_04]: She is sitting in the doorway.
[SPEAKER_04]: This might be something even Shermie could enjoy.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's hitting the blogs this week about a three-year-old named Oliver Smith who was playing a game on the Nintendo Wii that his mom bought him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Victoria is the mom's name.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game is on the European version of the Wii.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Countdown, which is based off a television show that they have over in Britain.
[SPEAKER_04]: and basically you unscramble words.
[SPEAKER_04]: They show up in whatever format and then you unscramble them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the kid got a word, S-H-A-H-S-I-T-E-D, and you know what that unscrambled into?
[SPEAKER_04]: Shitheads.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this little three-year-old got exposed to that word, and of course, according to the angry mother, I couldn't believe my eyes as the word was slowly unveiled as an obscene insult.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oliver is a really bright kid, and we play this game to help him build up his word bank.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was already asking what the word meant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody let that one slip by in the dictionary.
[SPEAKER_11]: Whoops.
[SPEAKER_11]: But if you expose your children to it early, then it's not a special order and they won't be as inclined to say it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I don't even really want to report on it, but it's just kind of sad because of everything we have going on with Guitar Hero and all that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, Karaoke Revolution Glee Volume 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: 20 more songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us?
[SPEAKER_11]: A bunch of crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, not crap.
[SPEAKER_11]: Final Fantasy 1 and 2 is coming to PlayStation Network in Europe and it will be 7.99.
[SPEAKER_11]: And they're going to be the UMD versions that came out in 2008.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which, as far as I recall, weren't very great.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then there's going to be a new DDR game for iOS.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's going to be Dance Dance Revolution Freedom and it is free and has four songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I like that the tap to start is a thumbprint.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's actually cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know, it looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Maybe I'll give it a try.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it's free, why not?
[SPEAKER_11]: Shoot.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then it looks like Arcade Infinity is actually for real closing its doors.
[SPEAKER_11]: So they're going to be closing on February 26, 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: As opposed to fake closing their doors like we had a couple months ago.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, they're closing on February 26, 2011.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it's actually L.A.
[SPEAKER_11]: County denied their application for business license extension
[SPEAKER_11]: So, they have to close, the county wants them to close shop, pay for a new license, and wait for all of the hearings and city council votes in order for it to stay open, which could take up to eight months.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do they have such, what's their problem with this arcade?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, it's like they hate them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, they're saying it's not the money, it's just how long AI would have had to remain closed.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, it's going away.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate you LA.
[SPEAKER_11]: Officially.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's just, it's, you know, we kind of talked about this when the news came up the first time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just kind of sad to hear about these arcades closing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know, but I'm sure there'll be no shortage of little arcades where ticket spitting machines come out and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move into the Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_04]: Every week you guys send us your tweets at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_04]: We like to read some of our favorites here on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So getting into some of the tweets sent to us tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a few.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh, there's tons of tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And getting into the first tweet here from Eternal Rapture says, Listening live for the first time tonight because I live in the UK.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm staying up till 5 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's way past your bedtime.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope it's a three-day weekend or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft tweets us and says, Since Bobby Yetu won the Grammy it was nominated for, I think it's only fair to have it on OLR's I Love This Song this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you think so?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I'm all for having actual content on the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be amazing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sending us a tweet saying, the only relevant Grammy news, I'm sorry, is that it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, no, it is a tweet to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only relevant Grammy news is Christopher Tinn winning one for Baba Yetu from Civ 4, which is very relevant.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: That is extremely relevant.
[SPEAKER_04]: Glad to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jake Jake LL sends us, sorry, that's a spam tweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get an NFL game for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blue Swim sends us a tweet here saying, Loki, have you seen the new Earth Defense Force insect Armageddon trailer, Pesticide Gun?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I haven't seen it yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, how about that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Blue Swim sends us a link to that little video right here so we can take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me pause this and turn this up.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what sucks about that game?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it's been delayed.
[SPEAKER_07]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The fact that it's delayed to June.
[SPEAKER_04]: You mad?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, not mad but disappointed.
[SPEAKER_04]: and a couple from Tigerclaw here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess a Plants vs. Zombies board game is actually happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: A board game?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a little strange, but kind of not surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: A lot of this stuff usually crosses over into other worlds.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, there's a Plants vs. Zombies board game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was spotted at Toy Fair 2011.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be a 2-4 player game with 80 zombie guards, cards, excuse me, 40 plant cards and different game boards on which you place these plants and battle the various zombies.
[SPEAKER_11]: I got to play that on an iPad the other day.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wanted an iPad after that.
[SPEAKER_04]: The iPad works a little better, those versions, than the other ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, also a tweet from Tigerclaw telling us that the World of Starcraft mod, remember this?
[SPEAKER_04]: This was somebody taking Starcraft 2 and making a custom mod in it that was World of Starcraft, and Blizzard did not take too kindly to this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We talked about this on Horde House a little bit this week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It is now called Starcraft Universe.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it has a name that I guess is a little less threatening to Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now Sony gets pissed off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yeah, it has its name changed and there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And lastly, SSJ100Matt says his tweet tonight saying, Resident hockey fan with some hockey game news.
[SPEAKER_04]: NHL 2K11 is available now for the iPad for $5.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're into hockey, check that out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it's not Blades of Steel though.
[SPEAKER_04]: That will always be the best hockey game as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a couple last-minute tweets.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll read these.
[SPEAKER_04]: SilverSonic tweets us on Twitter and saying, I just linked this in the chat room, but did you hear the story of the 11-year-old boy in the UK that spent 1 million pounds on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: He links us the story here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess the 11-year-old kid racked up a 1,000-pound debt on the debit card through the Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: he bought accessories and new games on the consoles after it saved details of a previously registered card it's hard to get those cards off there yeah it is
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, why is she kind of letting the kid run rampant with this?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's this little picture where her and the kid are kind of posing together, looking all, I don't know, I don't want to say happy, but they look kind of frumpy, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what's interesting is that I guess she showed the thing to the kid, and she says, when I showed him, he burst into tears.
[SPEAKER_04]: He unplugged the Xbox and said he didn't want it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't punished him because he feels bad enough and I know he won't do it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm working two jobs and I'm a single mother.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't pay this back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Be responsible.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why did you put the card in there in the first place?
[SPEAKER_07]: They have parental things that they can enable to where you can disable live purchases.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't pay attention on how to set controls on your consoles, then you can only blame yourself for when someone spends money on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't pretend, oh, I didn't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it for tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Twitter.com slash OLR if you want to follow us on Twitter and send us some tweets for next week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no patience for those type of people.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of ironic, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone's suing Sony this time, so Sony's suing other people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, LG has sent a lawsuit to Sony regarding their system, the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: They claim that certain electronic devices having a Blu-ray disc player and components there violates four of its patents.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that includes, I guess, a lot of devices like Bravia TVs.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the only piece of hardware, I guess, they were singling out was the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they actually have a specific model, which is the 160 gigabyte system.
[SPEAKER_07]: The complaint with the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: International Trade Commission has the power to block imports of products that violate U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: patents.
[SPEAKER_07]: In short, LG is looking to have the ITC keep the PS3s off American shores.
[SPEAKER_07]: They said they've also filed a civil suit against Sony in federal court in California making similar claims and seeking cash compensation for unauthorized use of its inventions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, moving on with this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This rumor just never stops.
[SPEAKER_04]: This rumor is always around, and it's, when is Apple getting into gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: When is Apple getting into gaming?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of like, well, they're already in gaming if you consider the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_04]: But okay, how about the consoles?
[SPEAKER_04]: When are they going to get back into consoles?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I guess you could say the Pippin, but I think Apple would rather not talk about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But yeah, one of the rumors that keeps coming up is the Apple TV because, you know, they've sold this device for very cheap and it's kind of way to get Apple connected to your television.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now the rumors are coming up again that perhaps Apple TV games are more real than you think.
[SPEAKER_07]: But how, let me put it this way, the Apple TV, is it even powerful enough to run games on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I know it's, I think it's Intel Atom CPU, but, I mean, is that comparable to like an iPod or something, or an iPhone?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, can they run, I mean, would they even be able to have the horsepower to do that?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you'd be talking top of the line stuff here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think you'd be playing exactly Gears of War on one of these things.
[SPEAKER_04]: But maybe either some type of device between your iPhone and this, like maybe it can talk to the iPhone and kind of like what your PSP is supposed to do with the PS3 where you beam images from one source to the other.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be cool now if you could stream games from say your iPod or iPhone or something like that and then play them on the Apple TV with a controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: A physical controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although at the same time just like a physical controller for my iPod would be awfully nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Could I use my remote control as a tangible controller, perhaps?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, wait, I didn't even tell you where this rumor comes from because you're going to laugh at this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is why this is a rumor all over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's beta code out there for the new iOS 4.3 because, you know, they regularly do updates to iOS and so forth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, 4.3 apparently in the code references ATV games and people think that means Apple TV because ATV.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the code I guess also talks about controllers of some sort, leaderboards, scheduling games and of course, a storefront.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, this news isn't, like, shocking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think this is kind of one of those matter-of-time types of things, but it's interesting to see what sort of things they have planned.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there would be a new Apple TV that would help facilitate this, and we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: The price point's awfully nice of the Apple TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if they're trying to get people to bring it in as, like, a game console.
[SPEAKER_02]: True, true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell, if they even drop the price, like, say, another $20, $79.99, that would be pretty, you know, appealing to people that aren't necessarily...
[SPEAKER_07]: into gaming and the other thing which would be kind of cool and I'm not too sure on the whole I don't know too much about the Apple TV other than the fact that you can stream shit from your PC your Apple or iTunes or whatever to it and stuff can you run apps on there already on the Apple TV can like I say browse Google or something you know do Facebook and stuff like that you can do on like the iPods and the iPhones and stuff can you do that stuff already on Apple TV
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I think you can do movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well you can do movies, but you can't run apps.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't do Facebook or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that would be interesting if they did that because then they would be trying to compete with Google TV and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you throw gaming in there, that could be interesting seeing as it's way cheaper than Google TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be smart for them to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It gets people to bring that shit into their house for the gaming, and then they can sell them on, hey, look, you can buy TV shows, or you can buy this.
[SPEAKER_04]: This could be a real stretch here, but maybe this is part of what the whole iPad 2 thing has to do with.
[SPEAKER_04]: because we haven't heard a lot out of iPad 2 besides that it's supposed to have this front-facing camera and might have the nice retina display.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: We haven't really heard anything but a bunch of rumors.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there will be that inevitable press conference at some point.
[SPEAKER_04]: So could this maybe tie into that somehow?
[SPEAKER_07]: They were saying even that the 3.4  or was it 4.3?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The new
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us in the meantime?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it looks like there has been an alleged Dance Central 2 survey that might be looking at a feature list.
[SPEAKER_11]: So basically, Kotaku says that it has an email survey from Microsoft Game Studios that has a list of those features, that it's in pre-production.
[SPEAKER_11]: and that it would have the ability to create custom dances and play as backup dancers or singers and then you can replay entire sequences and get specific feedback on your dancing and then they're also having a fitness mode and an online offline multiplayer contest and that you will have a social aspect to it so
[SPEAKER_04]: God, does this mean that you can put a video of yourself, like, dancing through, captured via the Kinect, I don't know, like, somehow automatically?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds kind of scary to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, they want that whole community thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: And after all, they've been, you know, doing the first party Kinect games and take pictures of you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I'm surprised you can't share those pictures, you know, with like Facebook and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least I'm unaware that you can easily.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I would think that they would want to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And wasn't there some sort of feature that was supposed to be coming where we can do screenshots from games and stuff like that and like share them on Facebook and that kind of crap?
[SPEAKER_07]: Cause wasn't there like when they were talking about the whole Facebook integration and stuff And it's like, hey look, I just, you know, blah blah blah and Tiger Woods And here's a screenshot of me hitting a hole in one or some crap
[SPEAKER_04]: SingStar has that.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Def Jam Rapstar has that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come on, Konami.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got components for a good game in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Def Jam Rapstar is one of the better music games that's been put out recently.
[SPEAKER_04]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the potential.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're just like, I don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is kind of disappointing, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Crysis 2 has been leaked online, including multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not the final version of the game, but it's a near-final build of the game, including multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also, apparently, I guess that there's...
[SPEAKER_07]: Some other things including that it doesn't have the DRM on it, that there's a way to bypass it and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I believe there's some stuff that's placeholder in it, like some of the sound effects, some of the assets are missing, but it is quite playable and is floating around out there for those unscrupulous types that may want to download that and check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: or you could support the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or you can do them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, all the dev tools are included with it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which means that came from the inside.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's a development copy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, it came from the inside.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's got to be frustrating, though, for the company as a whole.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a way to screw over your coworkers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, a month before it comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're going to have to be doing some damage control on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: yeah um it that I think the the same thing happened with the last crisis game as well that it leaked out before it came out I remember I remember that it did and I just didn't care though because that was a time when I actually was building computer for crisis um and so I actually got crisis with my graphics card that came with my computer so it wasn't such a big deal for me but um
[SPEAKER_07]: That's gotta suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it would have sucked even more if it was on consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that would have been terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: But let's see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just going to read.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were talking about comments, though, of what's not exactly working in it and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's, yeah, assets missing.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's temporary sounds and stuff for certain things, and it's buggy, which is not surprising.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You think this could be damaging for the entire series in the future?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, could this jeopardize more than just Crysis 2?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: well no but I think that they definitely need to make sure that they what they should have done
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Now we know who the goat killed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Same with this.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a development copy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It got leaked from the inside, so you gotta find out who leaked it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm just imagining what the temporary sounds are like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like you shoot someone and he goes, I don't think it's anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think if it's anything, it's probably stuff from the original Crisis game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I was a developer, I'd put in funny sounds as my placeholders.
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of want to check out the game though, honestly, because I liked the first one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just couldn't finish it because it was so goddamn buggy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I'm picking up the next one on console though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Xbox 360 all the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, one more story for you guys before we get into some of the other segments here about the... This is kind of along the same lines because this could be an effect we might see in the future for this whole piracy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Companies are doing what they want to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is about PlayStation 3 games possibly getting serial numbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is some sources that were speaking with the site PS3 Sense, which is Dutch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sony is going to implement a serial code security system for future PS3 game releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: This will be very similar to what you already know on PC titles.
[SPEAKER_04]: You get a long code that comes in the box.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to enter that in in order to play the game or install the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that code can be used on up to five consoles.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, of course, folks are saying, well, you're just basically slowing down the inevitable.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are going to find ways to hack around those serial number requirements anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then you just piss off those folks that buy this stuff legitimately.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you've just killed the used market as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope they don't do that because it's just dumb.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's interesting is that Kotaku actually called Sony on this for comments, and Sony told him, we are looking at a few options, not ready to confirm our next steps yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So yes, they are looking at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: They didn't flat out deny it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: and you know what the problem with that is?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not even going to necessarily stop piracy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to stop people buying your console is what it's going to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to stop people, especially people like the hardcore gamers out there that have multiple consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just not going to buy this game on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will buy it on the Xbox 360 or whatever other consoles are out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's exactly what's going to happen because I think Sony would be surprised how fast word is going to travel like that and if
[SPEAKER_04]: And Piracy on their games is not a huge... I mean, let's put it this way.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Xbox 360 has had Piracy on it for a very long time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't see them going to very drastic measures like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whereas PS3 piracy is just kind of getting around.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of cumbersome because Blu-ray rips aren't exactly the smallest things to download.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're talking some games being 20 to 50 gigs in size.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not convenient for a lot of people to just download and pirate.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, people could do it, and there are people out there that will do it, but it's a lot of...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hoops that jump through, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to go this route and kind of punish everybody that owns a PS3, it's a really dumb idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if they think it's necessary, then great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go that route.
[SPEAKER_07]: But don't be surprised if there's a huge backlash over it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm looking at our chatroom at chat.orangeloundtrader.com to try and see some of the comments here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gamer Girl in our chatroom says, dude, that doesn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're trying to put serial numbers on humans now, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that might be a little bit too sci-fi for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Frisbee says, more of a reason for me not to buy a PlayStation 3 and its products.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dartetsuya says, why is it the Earth's measures only seem to harm the legit users?
[SPEAKER_04]: and RedTheHaze says, rumors from no-name site, something plausible from a no-name site.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you never know.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, there's been things we've reported on in the past that, you know, they call us a no-name site, so, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I know we're not on the A list of internet gaming websites.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're more like on the F list, which is fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: If their console gets completely hacked open anyways...
[SPEAKER_07]: Jailbreaking a console is okay Jailbreaking a console is okay
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, let's just say that they do implement some sort of serial code or whatever that can be tracked.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, right now people have found ways to get past even the firmware checks because the newest firmware that's out there obviously breaks all the hacks that are out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, people have found ways around that even, and they're still able to connect to the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if they can find a way around that, they can probably find a way around the authentication thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then it doesn't even matter and on top of all that how the hell are you going to work that authentication thing in to people that don't have access to online if your console is not connected to the internet then you can't play your damn game that you bought so how's that going to work
[SPEAKER_11]: I can say this for a business looking into something is not the same thing as implementing it and I think that they're smart to look at their options but if they do implement it then that's when it gets stupid they do kind of owe it to these third parties that you know some of them having a lot of problems you know we just reported on that crisis story or whatever they do kind of owe it to them to keep their system safe so I don't know
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_04]: And every week you guys send us emails and DarkSakura likes to dive into the email bag and read some of her favorite emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: So DarkSakura, why don't you get to it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, today's emails... Oh, we actually just got one more while I decided to check, so I'm going to read it to you.
[SPEAKER_11]: God, we got a lot of emails today, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Which I guess is good in contrast to how it's been before.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, OLR, this is Red the Haze, long-time listener since 2007.
[SPEAKER_11]: If this email makes you in time for your February 13th show, as to I'm typing this last minute...
[SPEAKER_11]: I called for the first time last week on your 400th show to congratulate you and I spoke about the Super Bowl and I would like to apologize to you guys about that.
[SPEAKER_11]: OLR is one of my favorite podcasts and I felt bad in talking about something not game related or even food related so I came up with a last minute gaming question.
[SPEAKER_11]: My question is this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm about to join the Air Force soon when I finish basic training and go to tech school.
[SPEAKER_11]: I won't be able to game on the consoles for a while and only be allowed to have a laptop or PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you guys recommend a gaming laptop, a pre-built PC, and some PC gaming controllers?
[SPEAKER_11]: Since the Wired360 controller's D-pad is crap for some emulator action, I would say right away that probably the best gaming-specific laptops out there are the Alienwares.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're gonna pay some money for them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And seriously, I have an Asus Republic of Gamers laptop or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It works great for games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the one I bought is pretty low-end, but I can run Grand Theft Auto in it, which is a very, I guess...
[SPEAKER_07]: it could use some work as far as enhancing the game spec wise it can run Crysis fine chugs on Grand Theft Auto but you know you can just don't spend a lot of money because those aces not the aces but the Alienware ones can be like over a thousand dollars my PC is this what do I have again
[SPEAKER_11]: I have an HP Quad Core that I picked up a couple years ago for $800 with a monitor and all.
[SPEAKER_11]: And all I had to do was put in a new graphics card and power supply.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I play everything I want to play and I do all my graphics work and it's just fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I mean, you guys have seen what games look like on my computer.
[SPEAKER_11]: They run really well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, also, he was saying he's playing on running emulators, right?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't need anything super high-end.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you're running emulators, remember that, especially when it comes down to maim and stuff, the main things you're going to want to focus on are the speed of your CPU and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, most emulators will run on a freaking netbook.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm talking about MAME here.
[SPEAKER_07]: MAME, you're going to really need to focus on one thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter if it's dual core, quad core, because most of the MAME builds don't support the multi-threading and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you're really going to have to focus on the actual core speed of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you want something that's high twos to threes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think they have fours out there, but...
[SPEAKER_11]: Dan's had MAME running just fine on his quad core.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just so you know, I want to jump in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, but I'm saying, you know, a lot of stuff that's fine, but like if you're trying to run really high-end MAME stuff like, you know, Gauntlet Legends or something like that, I mean, that's going to require a 4 gigahertz processor.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me jump in here because RedTheHaze is actually in chat right now in our chat room and says, Money isn't a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm willing to spend 1K+.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's probably your answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, I would say kind of two things here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a Toshiba that I bought on sale for like $400 during a 4th of July sale at Fry's like two years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it runs wow, cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't play max graphics settings, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: I can get away with playing a few PC games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can play StarCraft 2 on it on low settings too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I can kind of get away with some of the newer stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just I won't get that pristine gaming experience.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that was only $400.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep in mind with my lower end, it was under spec for Star Trek Online, but I played Star Trek Online just fine.
[SPEAKER_11]: It looked shitty, but it played.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's all I cared about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love this comment from Salacious Pop in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: And maybe the best feedback is actually going to come from our chatroom on this because I haven't bought a laptop in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this is pretty much how I did it when I bought it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is what Salacious Pop says in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_04]: To be honest, just look at what's on clearance at Best Buy that has a name brand ATI or Radeon card and then Google benchmarks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think that's the smart thing to do is don't go in there and impulse buy something or don't buy something just because it's on sale.
[SPEAKER_04]: Google the things, get reviews on them, see what they're capable of, and try to make the best informed decision you can.
[SPEAKER_04]: But if you want me to recommend you something right off the cusp, oh my gosh, technology changes so fast, it's really hard for me to say something.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Toshiba I bought two years ago, they probably don't even make anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's probably an even better one that's 400 bucks now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that laptop Loki has.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty nice, the Asus.
[SPEAKER_11]: My little dinky netbook.
[SPEAKER_11]: I run SNES ROMs on it all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I run them in Linux.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, of course, it's running more efficiently than it would have been in Windows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sadly, I'm not going to be able to name that definitive laptop for you, but I think you've got tons of options.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just do your best to make an informed decision when you go shopping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't impulse buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do not impulse buy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you guys for all your hard work and passion for gaming.
[SPEAKER_11]: I wish you all the best.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: All hearts.
[SPEAKER_11]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: Forgive any grammatical mistakes as to I've been up for the last 20 hours finishing up a special Valentine's video for my GF and forgot that you guys are on right now as I'm typing this letter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Much love, RedTheHaze.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or hey, if you want to spend a lot of money on a computer or something, do your own case mod.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just build a fucking...
[SPEAKER_07]: you know regular computer inside of like a you know a nice you know durable like suitcase type thing you can totally have a cut out Air Force logo and show your you know a really nice case mod for see that's the thing high end laptops are so fucking expensive and if you're like you know they're saying like there's some there $3,000 for $3,000 you can build a nice PC and a nice monitor if you spend just a little bit of time you know putting together even a very crude you know case mod for it
[SPEAKER_07]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is from RubbaBuh.
[SPEAKER_11]: When you were doing the listless, I'm thinking horror genre games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Lonsdart Deathmatch.
[SPEAKER_11]: The graphics would look like those airplane safety cards.
[SPEAKER_11]: Davros Speak and Spell.
[SPEAKER_11]: Spell Exterminate.
[SPEAKER_11]: Teddy Ruxpin Soul Stealer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, I'm Teddy Ruxpin and you have to sleep sometime.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those Teddy Ruxpin dolls were pretty scary back in the day, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: They were freaky.
[SPEAKER_11]: TDU 2
[SPEAKER_07]: Do cops know how to drive off-road this time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that was hilarious in the last one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, there's cops chasing after me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to drive off-road.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, you can't get me.
[SPEAKER_11]: The other news is that GameStop is giving out codes for TDU2 Casino to the first purchasers of the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only problem is the day it was released, none of the casino codes worked.
[SPEAKER_11]: I discovered that the codes weren't activated until February 9th at the earliest it was really great being able to find that on the Atari support forums but they never put it in on the news feeds on their site or in the in-game news feed
[SPEAKER_11]: That's poopy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, email from CMD, whoever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey guys, a couple of days ago my mother purchased on pre-order for me the Nintendo 3DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: It is selling for $350 Australian, I guess that's AUD Australian, which includes the 3DS, one game, and an accessories pack.
[SPEAKER_11]: So March 31st I am going to be super happy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good for you, send us one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Jamie wants one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey guys, Molten Brown here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm writing to congratulate you on your 400th episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: Keep up the awesome work.
[SPEAKER_11]: My weekends are never the same without you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not really writing in with game-related questions or news, but just some comments.
[SPEAKER_11]: One, to Loki, over a comment you said a couple of episodes ago about a court's decision to allow the suit against J-Hat.
[SPEAKER_11]: The idea that a court has jurisdiction against a person whose online activities has a presence in their state is not a new or random thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: If I remember civil procedure correctly, depending on what the website is doing, directly advertising and soliciting customers, I think it's a message board site where the owners and other parties can communicate with each other or being a neutral site that just allows users to look up information will influence whether the court feels they have jurisdiction over a party.
[SPEAKER_11]: The more the site seems to directly advertise and solicit customers, the more likely it is that the court will find they do have jurisdiction over the party who owns slash uses the website because the party has purposefully availed themselves to the privilege of doing business in the particular state.
[SPEAKER_11]: This means that the party voluntarily subjected themselves to the jurisdictions of courts in that state.
[SPEAKER_11]: A court can see J-Hat's website as soliciting customers because it was advertising a service, the ability to jailbreak your PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't say it's a service because all he was doing is sharing information.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not really, you know, hey, I'll jailbreak your PS3 for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think it's a matter of perception, but it does have a point.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's however the court decides to see it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I can understand if they were bringing him to California because his website's hosted in California, but that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was all because he communicated on Twitter, which pretty much everybody on the planet does nowadays.
[SPEAKER_07]: and he had a PayPal account, which he had a donation thing on his webpage.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was their criteria for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really, it was because, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a lot of lawyers on retainer in California, so that...
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever, it's still going through and I remember there's some extra stuff going on with the case right now where now he's surrendered his hard drive and stuff to the courts for Sony to go through as well as with his lawyer present of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think the translation is, ha ha!
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody's like, oh no, I hope he deleted his hard drive stuff and I hope all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: He didn't think he did anything wrong and he's out to prove that and so he has nothing to hide.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number two, at Rob, your fake fight with Ranma during 400th episode made me think of this song.
[SPEAKER_11]: YouTube link here.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listening to the first few seconds will explain why.
[SPEAKER_11]: The video isn't that impressive, but it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't like that bitch.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't see her.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that's pretty much me and Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone can say the word bitch over and over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_11]: 3.
[SPEAKER_11]: On my nickname.
[SPEAKER_11]: Since Rob makes fun of my nickname from time to time, I felt I had to explain it.
[SPEAKER_11]: When I was trying to figure out a nickname for America's Army, I created Molten Brown in homage to my eyes, which kind of look mahogany on the edges, the closest color I could think of, but as you get closer to the people, the color lightens up significantly.
[SPEAKER_11]: I always thought...
[SPEAKER_11]: My eyes had a molten feel to them like there was a flame behind my eyes that caused the color to lighten.
[SPEAKER_11]: Additionally, when I'm angry or happy, my eye color seems to lighten up as if the fire is being turned up a notch because of how I am feeling.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I thought Molten Brown made sense as a nickname.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's poetic.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, that's all from me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, don't I feel like crap for going straight to the poop reference.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pun intended.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a nice story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now I feel like Molten Brown myself.
[SPEAKER_11]: This message is brought to you by snow.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only substance I can think of that's beautiful but consistently makes me want to punch someone in the face.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a good way to sum it up.
[SPEAKER_11]: This one is from Catastrophic Moggy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, OLR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure this week you'll all be abuzz about the news of the deaths of Guitar Hero and DJ Hero, so I thought I'd pass on a bit of news that's got me excited.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was more than a bit miffed when I heard that the 3DS was region locked.
[SPEAKER_11]: I often import DS games because they are cheaper and usually release long before they are in Europe.
[SPEAKER_11]: That is, if they remember to release them here at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: I know it might sound silly, but I also prefer the cases that are used in the US.
[SPEAKER_11]: Much better than the ugly, bulky, semi-clear cases we get here.
[SPEAKER_11]: I actually like the European cases, honestly, but I see your point.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, what I am getting at is that I was seriously thinking about whether I'll bother getting a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I only got a 360 a couple months ago and still have tons of games I want to try.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I read that Cave Story is being released on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that threw a spanner in the works.
[SPEAKER_11]: and the concept art looks really impressive.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you guys around Catastrophic Magi.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to look at this now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want to see what the art looks like.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Jamie wants this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to link it in the chat room because it's pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: I tried Cave Story but I thought it was kind of meh.
[SPEAKER_11]: But dude, this is pretty.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go, everyone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Take a look in there.
[SPEAKER_11]: and now for our next email and by the way, thank you CatastrophicMuggy for sharing that link it's pretty anyway, next email up hey OLR, seeing as the mailbag has been somewhat skimpy on average for a while now I thought that I'd send an email this week covering a few topics
[SPEAKER_11]: First off, there is a free video available on PSN, iTunes, and the Xbox Live Zoom Marketplace which is the pilot of Mr. Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's easy to find on PSN and iTunes but it takes a little hunting to find it via Xbox Live Zoom.
[SPEAKER_11]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_11]: On a semi-related note, I found out a cool little deal that I'm sure that DarkSakura would make use of since she's a Marvel fan.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_11]: Assuming that there's Target stores out west and sales are nationwide, not just reasonable, they have Planet Hulk on Blu-ray for dirt cheap.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least at my favorite Target, the shelf tag listed as $10 however it rang up as $7.50.
[SPEAKER_11]: Movies, especially Blu-rays, don't get much cheaper than that new or used.
[SPEAKER_11]: After seeing it, I was awestruck over how gorgeous the animation was and how good the voice acting was.
[SPEAKER_11]: All in all, it's a good buy.
[SPEAKER_11]: As a side note, if you were able to do so, try picking up the animated Dante's Inferno movie released in tandem with the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was equally as good as Planet Hulk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, if you're a fan of certain voice actors, I should mention that both Mark Hamill and Steve Blum had roles in Dante's Inferno.
[SPEAKER_11]: See, I would be interested in seeing Dante's Inferno, but I am not a Hulk fan at all because Marvel has just gone overboard with Hulk.
[SPEAKER_11]: and every single freaking issue that Hulk should have nothing to do with.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hulk was in Spider-Girl.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do Hulk and Spider-Girl have in common?
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's not an argument for this podcast.
[SPEAKER_11]: So probably no Hulk for me.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I did like the Ultimate Avengers ones.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those are cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: As for the last topic, I assume that you have already covered the story about Activision giving Guitar Hero the axe as well as shredding Tony Hawk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Puns fully intended.
[SPEAKER_11]: In my honest opinion, it's about time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Activision really ran these two franchises into the ground and frankly they haven't learned that quality is greater than quantity.
[SPEAKER_11]: Where they went wrong with Guitar Hero, at least, is the fact that they inundated the market with poorly supported via download content titles every year like clockwork.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, if they had followed EA's slash Harmonix lead and used the Rock Band business model, they would have fared better and the bottom wouldn't have fallen out of the music game market.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bet that within two to three years' time, the Call of Duty series will likely suffer the same fate.
[SPEAKER_11]: It isn't too far of a stretch to predict that happening.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for taking the time to read this email.
[SPEAKER_11]: Errors and all, it's appreciated.
[SPEAKER_11]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: Although I haven't fully put it together in time for this week's show, hopefully by next week if possible, I'd like to initiate a little contest open to USPS3 owners.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry everyone else, you wouldn't be able to make use of the prize even if you won due to how PSN is set up.
[SPEAKER_11]: It'll be one winner who will get some videos from the USPSN video store.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyone who has a PS3 and is in the US may enter.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just need to come up with a wordy trivia question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's shiny.
[SPEAKER_11]: And last one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Happy 401.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is it wrong that I play Angry Birds on the toilet at work?
[SPEAKER_11]: This is from Mike.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's you and everyone else.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much for the emails.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com is the place to send your emails to have them read next week here on Z Program.
[SPEAKER_11]: And maybe I'll still have my, you know, disease voice.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a few more news stories for you guys, and then we're going to get to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but before we get to those, we have to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the part of the show where we get angsty, as we've done for the last 400 weeks.
[SPEAKER_11]: My F you goes towards people not understanding the difference between making a comment about an article and then spamming your Facebook with a bajillion comments arguing a political point that you really don't care to discuss.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, forget it.
[SPEAKER_11]: If it happens again, I'm going to do what I did this time and delete it.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the form of me.
[SPEAKER_11]: My wall, me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your wall, you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Respect my authority.
[SPEAKER_04]: Facebook is serious business.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why I'm back on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I never left LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know why people are... I didn't leave LiveJournal, but I ignored it for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I realize there's a lot of creepy shit on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I get the LOL, the Harry Potter stuff, but that's not what everybody's into.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: I know I was mad at something earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to Drama, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good fallback option, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you to Dance360 for breaking.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um... Dance in the back going, yeah!
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to that little audio boo-boo I just had there going on there.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to not being perfect.
[SPEAKER_04]: And F you to the fact I don't have tacos right now because tacos suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, can I add one little tiny one?
[SPEAKER_11]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you're going to help me.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: F you to my Ventrilo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I can help fix that for you though.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, actually, I don't have a lot to be mad about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Things are fine right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to the fact that I'm separated on Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not like separated in that context, maybe separated by distance.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's just a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, you know, the meaning's still there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh come on, Rob.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody got decapitated, so you're okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, let's get back into a couple more gaming news stories and then we're going to get to your calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should be fun tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now they're doing something very similar to the Contra thing where they have a project that's a collaboration between a bunch of different members.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have one that's actually being done between 12 of the community members.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called Hansel and Gretel Bot.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a seven-level LittleBigPlanet 2 adventure that has cutscenes and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they say that the level design is on par with the single-player campaign that's with LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: So definitely worth checking out, and it will be out hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they actually covered it on the PlayStation blog as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to really be picky choosy on what video games I buy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe I'll rent it or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyhow, one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we're going to get to the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do make sure if you're going to give us a call on Skype, you do call Echo 123 first to test your setup.
[SPEAKER_04]: And remember the other rule of radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're going to call a radio show, mute your radio once you get through.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, one more story for you guys, though, and it has to do with dogs and kitties.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendogs plus cats is one of the launch titles for the 3DS, and the breeds have been revealed.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, of course, there are going to be several different versions of the game, duh.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of them is Toy Poodle and Friends, which comes with a Toy Poodle, a Pembroke Welsh Corgi, Mini Schnauzer, Boxer, Bull Terrier, Labrador Retriever, Shih Tzu, Jack Russell, and Pomeranian.
[SPEAKER_04]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not a dog person.
[SPEAKER_04]: French Bulldog and Friends comes with French Bulldog, Shetland Sheepdog, Cavalier King Charles Spaniel, Chihuahua, Dalmatian, Yorkshire Terrier, German Shepherd, Husky, and Basset Hound.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Shiba Inu and Friends, which will be Golden Retriever and Friends for those of us here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: and Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shiba Inu, Golden Retriever, Beagle, Mini Pinscher, Dachshund, Maltese, Great Dane, Pugs, and Cocker Spaniels.
[SPEAKER_11]: And your Great Dane will die in two years.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't really see what the cats are yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if the cats are the same in every game or what the deal is.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd get which everyone has a Mal in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they were worshipped.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I'd want a Fat Shermie too.
[SPEAKER_04]: More information is available on the Japanese site, Nintendo.co.jp.
[SPEAKER_04]: More information is available there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will probably get the one with the Welsh Corgi in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though it's a freaking poodle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_11]: I want one with a big, big fat shirmy in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want this game, but I feel compelled to buy this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't want this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't either, and I feel compelled to buy it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be one of those games that I play for like a day, and then I get so sick of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, me too.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just want Fat Shermie the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my new dream game, everybody, is Fat Shermie.
[SPEAKER_04]: What would happen in Fat Shermie the game?
[SPEAKER_11]: You get to poke her and have her make really weird faces at you and then you'd have to clean up her litter box.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then you'd also have to figure out ways to keep her from shitting on the kitchen floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'd be very careful not to talk about the tester.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's not in the room so we can talk about it all we want.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_04]: Calls already coming in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, X-Link, how you doing, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, doing good.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up, man?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'd be better if I know I wasn't getting gypped off or you don't know Jack for the PC.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's kind of funny because the creators are Pokemon and PC people, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: How so?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I guess apparently on one of the forums, one of the guys took a screenshot of the Twitter account for You Don't Know Jack, and one of the guys replied by, because they were asking if they were willing to pay more money, if they could get more than two players local, and he goes, are more PC players too fat to fit more than two at a keyboard?
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, wow.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was like, really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little bit funny.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't know if they legitimately did it on purpose or they kind of did it as kind of like a test run to see how many people buy it and maybe put it down the road as possibly a DLC or a patch or something or what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I hope they really seriously do just one or two because it doesn't feel like the full experience without like four players that I'm used to playing beforehand.
[SPEAKER_00]: but you know before speaking of beforehand though we didn't have back in the 90s all this Xbox Live stuff and all that fun stuff like if you didn't have other people to play with in the same room it just yeah but at the same time too though if I have four people here at the house and I want to play with four people like my next door neighbors for example then I can't do that I can only play with one person at a time like if I were to play somewhere else and it's not like me and my girlfriend versus my two neighbors instead it will be either me and my girlfriend my girlfriend versus one of my neighbors or
[SPEAKER_00]: or me versus my girl.
[SPEAKER_00]: You know what I'm saying though?
[SPEAKER_00]: Two people will be left out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are getting the shorter end of the stick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, it is $10 cheaper for what it's worth.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but still, I'd rather pay if it was the extra $10 for the two.
[SPEAKER_00]: Still, I would definitely pay that because it still feels a little left out.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the same time too, I hope they do something about that because at the same time too, a lot of people are complaining about it.
[SPEAKER_00]: and I'm sure a lot more people were too and if it was like one of people like me for example who bought on day one and didn't know this I might have been a little hesitant and be like well screw this I'll wait till Steam has on sale then buy it.
[SPEAKER_00]: But at the same time too though it's a great game and definitely worth 20 bucks and it has Steam achievements for the PC and it's definitely worth to buy.
[SPEAKER_00]: Also Swords and Poker 1 and 2 are back on the iTunes store
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a shit ton of fun, I guess I could say personally, playing those two games.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I always bounce back and forth between the first and second one.
[SPEAKER_00]: And it's a lot of fun, so if you're into card games, definitely buy those.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is such an awesome game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, now that it's on the App Store, you need to buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, they came back?
[SPEAKER_07]: They came back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sword and Poker 2 and Sword and Poker 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, go buy it on the App Store.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will take over your life.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a pretty big endorsement.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll have to look into that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Both of them are about $5-$6.
[SPEAKER_00]: I know the second one is like $3 and I think the first one is $2.
[SPEAKER_00]: So yeah, you're looking at like $5-$6 worth of money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably like at least 50 hours into the second game already.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I'm like a few hours into the second one but I'm still trying to finish up the first one and the first one is just as bad as the second.
[SPEAKER_00]: But it's a lot of fun though, it's very challenging.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let me take it back to You Don't Know Jack for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: As somebody who played it like a long time ago, these tech issues aside, were you really happy to see this come back?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is this a worthy upgrade?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes and yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has all the pretty much old features, like a few new things added as well, but anybody who's a trivia fan, definitely buy it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's worth the money, regardless of what system.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think it will be the first of several revival games?
[SPEAKER_00]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I hope so in a good way, not in a bad way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because they did a pretty decent job, like I said before.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just really wish that there were four players that could do something like that down the road or maybe add another one with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then, yes, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the fact that it has DLC and stuff that's going to be attached to it would make it even worse.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because now instead of buying, like, you don't know Jack Sports, now it's like, oh, you can get the Sports DLC for it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, definitely.
[SPEAKER_00]: And also, I bought NBA Jam for the iTouch and iPad, and it's wonderful.
[SPEAKER_00]: Really?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would think on the iOS, though, those games would kind of blow.
[SPEAKER_00]: No, it's a little smaller, but for me, I like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the same way as NBA Jam, and it has a lot of unlockable stuff.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing it for quite a while, so...
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, buddy, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls, but enjoy the You Don't Know Jack, even though you didn't get it on Xbox 360, so I can't play with you, but I guess life goes on.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hopefully make it one day PC.
[SPEAKER_04]: You always have WoW to play.
[SPEAKER_00]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_00]: Although... How do you do in Civ V, by the way?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was playing it for a while, and then I went back to WoW.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you interested in Rift at all?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any interest in Rift?
[SPEAKER_00]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got to let you go so we can get more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You too.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Again, if you want to give us a call, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go take another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was just calling in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Bring back all these memories of like old games I used to play, like
[SPEAKER_13]: Street Fighter, Metal Gear, Mortal Kombat, King of Fighters, Final Fantasy, Darkstalkers, Double Dragon, Metroid, Ninja Gaiden, Shinobi, Tekken, Virtua Fighter, Spyro,
[SPEAKER_04]: You should turn down your speakers, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I want to see how long you can keep going.
[SPEAKER_04]: What other old classic games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, what's the point?
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thank you very much to the caller from area code 612-670... Maybe I'll give the rest out later.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, this is D.R.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dollar Bill.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, just quickly.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't think I'd get through this quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, I was trying to remember if you didn't know Jack, the original PC version.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think there was four players even on the original version.
[SPEAKER_09]: There wasn't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it was three on the original version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, so I couldn't say his thing about it should have been four players, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: If it was based on the same concept, I'm trying to picture four people holding the keyboard together.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just seems kind of crowded, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: At one keyboard, yeah, that might be a little bit comfy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I mean, the online multiplayer, I agree with.
[SPEAKER_09]: They should do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But on a local machine, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It just didn't seem right.
[SPEAKER_04]: but you used to do three on one keyboard and I seem to remember the buzzer keys were like Q space bar and like right bracket or something they were kind of like spread out so you could sit kind of in an interesting arrangement and do it four might be getting a little comfy but you could like give a person the mouse and they could like click it I don't know ooh that would be a good one okay
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, that one, and there was something else, and I... Oh, yeah, just really quick, because I heard at the beginning of the show, you guys were talking about DDR and Guitar Hero, how, like, they both seem to be following one point of the continuously kind of the same game, but very little evolution between the two.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, you know, DDR just slowly didn't really evolve much, just maybe some different step charts and maybe a couple different modes eventually, but it's still alive a lot longer than Guitar Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: One theory that we had is that the games are simply lower budget.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because keep in mind, Konami, they do license songs now, but they don't license quite as many.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like 10 songs maybe in a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they use their in-house team for the rest of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think the expectations just aren't quite as high.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think they still sell quite a few through the whole weight loss thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like it's not Wii Fit, but certainly... I was even listening to a morning show here locally where somebody brought up, and they were saying it jokingly,
[SPEAKER_04]: It was some chick who got a Wii for Valentine's Day and she was saying to the host that she was going to play lots of Wii Fit and the host was going, you're not going to play any Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to play it for three days and then you're going to be over it and then you'll say, oh, I'm going to play Dance Dance Revolution.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll play that two times too.
[SPEAKER_04]: So the name is still out there is my point.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's still getting name checked in some places but I just think overall those games are lower budget and so they have lower expectations and I think that's why those games still go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And unfortunately
[SPEAKER_07]: It shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's also still very Japan-centric.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Konami closed their offices here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_04]: They might have the one in L.A., I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the one in L.A.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they don't have the one in Hawaii.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't have the one in North Bay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, I'm sorry, NorCal in the Bay.
[SPEAKER_04]: They don't have those anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So most of that, I imagine, is coming out of Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: And those games are probably still selling in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whereas Guitar Hero, what, did they have one in Japan?
[SPEAKER_04]: And that was it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't think it ever got released in Japan I didn't think it would Guitar Hero?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think there was like one I think one of them did get a localized Japanese release but I don't think it was huge I could be wrong, don't quote me on that or call me an idiot if I'm wrong but I want to say one time I do remember reading about it Okay, that's cool Anything else on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anything else on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, that's alright, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just didn't have much to say except, hi guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well at least you aren't high as hell like the last caller.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You too, bye guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Last Minute Stories for our listeners tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I was going to see here.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're talking a little bit more about the Xperia Play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, it's going to have battery life enough for five plus hours of gameplay, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's got a 5.1 megapixel camera, 400 megabytes of onboard memory, as well as you can expand it via SD memory cards.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you to Orange Wright in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very knowledgeable dude when it comes to the music games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Hero 3 and Aerosmith were released in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same as the other releases, no localization.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for the clarification.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this time, Rob, I'm not going to attack you tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have some interesting topics I want to discuss.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll make them brief as possible.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: But first, I would like to give my prediction for episode 500.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Number one, you and Salacious Pop get married live on the air.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that, but okay, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Predictions, predictions.
[SPEAKER_03]: And right after that we find out DarkSakura is pregnant and she gives birth live on the air.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, not happening.
[SPEAKER_03]: And after all is said and done, Loki is still oblivious to the entire world as he still plays Grand Theft Auto IV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, in two years they're going to have Grand Theft Auto 5, so I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we're going to be playing Saints Row 3 later on this year, so I'm very excited about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least a quick break on Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hey, gotta be honest though, the Grand Theft Auto games we play are not quite the Grand Theft Auto games that other people play.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's a little different type of an animal that we're playing lots of high explosives and people flying through the air and and bus foo there is bus foo in this game it's it's a sight that behold seriously we'll be making new videos once it's all done too I can't wait to see those
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, any other lovely predictions?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a ways to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all for the predictions, but as I've been listening for the last couple of podcasts, I've been trying to catch up.
[SPEAKER_03]: My quick take on Sony's Neo Geo Pocket.
[SPEAKER_03]: It says it's going to be 3G and all this enabled.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can see it now.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to market the portable console at about
[SPEAKER_03]: $400.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what they're going to do, they're probably going to partnership with either AT&T or T-Mobile where you go in and you get the console for $99.99 with a two-year contract with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, lock them in with a contract.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what they're trying to do with the phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, hey, it kind of worked for the taco.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why not for the NGP?
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, if anyone is serious about gaming with 3G on the NGP or even anything like the iPod or iPad, whatever, don't fucking sign up for this shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think you just get the cheapest data plan possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: But seriously though, if I want to game my laptop, and I got through a week of just using it for surfing the web, but I have MiFi.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't use it anymore because it's $45 a month for just data, whereas I can just tether it to my phone and I get the same shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, they don't want you to do that, and that's done through a hack, but hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a relatively easy hack, so it can be done by pretty much anybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, I know, my phone is the same way, I can do that with mine, but now that, you know, Version Mobile and everybody else, they're capping how much bandwidth you can spend when doing all of this, and guarantee, if everyone's gonna be on these 3G networks gaming, it'll be a funny thing that, as they're gaming, they hit their cap, and you see their network logo saying, sorry, you have used up all your bandwidth, push this button to add more time, or
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no way you'll run through... Unless you're gaming 24-7 over 3G, and a lot of people have Wi-Fi in their houses, there is not going to be a time that you're into a cap problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just not fast enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be rare to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why they have those caps in place, because those people are using way more data.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've tried streaming stuff on my phone, and it shows me the kind of data it's using, but unless you don't have Wi-Fi in your house, you're just on this 3G and that's it, then maybe it would take some really heavy use.
[SPEAKER_07]: But for most people where they're near Wi-Fi, like I have Wi-Fi at work, I have Wi-Fi at home, there's Wi-Fi here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I just have, I can bounce on all those with my phone, with my iPod, and there's very rare times that are in between that I actually need to use the 3G for anything, or, you know, my cable goes out or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's very rare, so I don't think that's really going to be an issue, but, you know, who knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well Ranma, I'm going to let you go to get some more calls Alright, cool, that's cool Alright, take care buddy You got it, bye Alright, we got more calls coming in Why not, let's get to it Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, hi Am I on?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes Oh, okay Yeah, I got a little Confession to make actually I have a really bad crack problem And I don't know I feel that
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know, playing video games sometimes helps, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, what caused you to start smoking crack in the first place?
[SPEAKER_14]: It was probably the Nintendo coming out with Mario Sports Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's more of a recent thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, Sports Mix hasn't really come out yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's been out for a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, one week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've been addicted to crack for a week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh Uh-huh
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I mean, well, I mean, I'm just kind of curious why you and your buddies want to like troll this online radio show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, like, we don't think we're like all that or nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We do our show for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've kind of worked our asses off for the past nine years to provide the show for free to people on the internet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm just wondering what made it worthy of trolling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, was it something we said?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you guys just like really fucking bored or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think a small penis is involved.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's let the man have his say.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't need to troll him back.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just be real with me, dude.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, actually, we're pretty big fans, actually.
[SPEAKER_14]: We've been looking at it a long time, and we just thought, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've been really big fans, so for that you want to call in and talk about your crack problem and spam our picture feed and spam the Twitter account and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how you show your appreciation for us working our ass off for free for so many years?
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, if maybe I said something to make the interwebs angry, then cool, let us know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did we say to bring the wrath of whatever 4chan-y site you guys are with?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the deal?
[SPEAKER_04]: well yeah just be real dude don't you don't have to like ask your friends for an answer or whatever like I applaud you for not hanging up the phone like a chicken shit when I called you out but like just be real with me what's up what is this all about are you don't you have something you want to promote or plug is there a website behind this whole thing
[SPEAKER_14]: No, to be perfectly honest, this is boredom.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is boredom?
[SPEAKER_14]: Dude!
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, for the record, this is the only time we've actually done this.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've never...
[SPEAKER_14]: We love video games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, if you're bored, go play a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just, I just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get it, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I just kind of feel like you're wasting your time.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, but, I mean.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, okay, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And thanks for the hits.
[SPEAKER_04]: I appreciate it because, you know, E3 is all about who gets the most hits on their website right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you guys have really helped with that tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that'll help.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: But in all seriousness, dude, you guys really are cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do like what you guys are doing.
[SPEAKER_14]: We really do listen, and I'm being sincere about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, you have a funny way of showing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I'm just saying, you got a funny way of showing it, pal, but I... You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I realize it's the internet, and that's the type of stuff we subject ourselves to doing a public show, but I'm just saying...
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard a lot worse in my lifetime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, growing up as a gay guy for as many years as I've done and so forth, I've been subjected to a lot worse in my lifetime.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, but... Anyhow, you have a lovely day.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for trolling.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, you too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_11]: At least he's not posting on the internet that I need to get back in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Given that I'm not the one that cooks.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still want to know, like...
[SPEAKER_04]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, just tell me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Baba Booey?
[SPEAKER_04]: You got his number.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the deal?
[SPEAKER_04]: I do, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: If I give it... I'm not saying give it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm saying track it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's New York.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't... And it's one of those, like, I don't...
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Was it something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it because you're a bitch, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're a bitch?
[SPEAKER_04]: So they got to troll the show because you're a bitch?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck them.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can be as much of a bitch as I want.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even care.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's giving it more attention than it deserves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we get answers.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, who wants to follow that call?
[SPEAKER_04]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or use me on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The folks in chat seems to enjoy that last call.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, let's talk a little bit more about Activision and what they're focusing their efforts towards now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since they're not doing the Guitar Hero franchise, they are continuing on with their toy licensing franchise.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know how they did the games with the Zuzu Pets and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now with Squinkies!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Squinkies, based off of some sort of toy that's like those 25 cent machines where there's a little crappy toy that comes in the bubble.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're making a game based off that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, they're making a game called Skylanders Spyro's Adventure, which has...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what the
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what they did.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yes, there's Activision pooping on your franchises.
[SPEAKER_07]: Putting out kids games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if it's highly marketable, then they're going to pimp it out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go to some more calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawn Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, my buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: How are you tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nah, doing pretty good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just trying to wait for the next day or so when I have to take the girl out for Valentine's Day.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just lamenting over the death of the inevitable guitar hero.
[SPEAKER_01]: We kind of knew that was coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you sad?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you one of those people that was on Twitter going, RIP Guitar Hero, pouring a 40 in your honor?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, not at all.
[SPEAKER_01]: As a matter of fact, I knew this was going to happen ever since Guitar Hero 3 came out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, no, more like World Tour.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's when they started to have the whole Me Too attitude of, let's just milk the proverbial golden cap dry until we can pummel harmonics, which...
[SPEAKER_01]: and Turn never worked out.
[SPEAKER_01]: See, this is the thing with Activision.
[SPEAKER_01]: In a nutshell, they take good franchises and they just run them and just send them straight to hell.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like what they're going to do with Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, when you have five Guitar Hero games out in a single year, that's almost like one per quarter.
[SPEAKER_01]: That goes to show that you just don't give a shit about the franchise.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Konami, on the other hand, they at least make efforts to innovate and just please the hardcore fanbase while picking up the casuals along the way.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least they're having some sort of consistency.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know about now, but during their time with the whole DDR series, even with Bomani in general, they just kept it a little bit more consistent and not as bland.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, I mean, it's... The way I see it is that Harmonix now is tasked with just, like, trying not to, you know, make the same mistakes as Activision.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously, they're well aware of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But more importantly, they have to innovate.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because that's what made them survive that day.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that's what will keep them going, you know, keep them going forward.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think is the reason why, I mean I know you, you have been calling into this show for years, which I totally appreciate, don't get me wrong, especially in light of the last couple calls we've had.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have called in about DDR and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think about this whole, why does DDR seem to persevere when I'm not so sure DDR really innovates in the way that some other games do?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you still add, you still have the, I guess the way I see it is that Konami still recognizes that the hardcore players are still the ones that are going to be picking up DDR a lot more than, let's say, the casuals, by a slight edge.
[SPEAKER_01]: So you have to please, you know, they're trying to please both demographics.
[SPEAKER_01]: So they have a multi-pronged approach to their series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: whereas Activision just treats it like shovelware.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just try to get all the licenses, not really innovate in terms of new gameplay features.
[SPEAKER_01]: What I heard was the most appalling innovation that they had was just the ability to change the guitar skin.
[SPEAKER_01]: Unlike, let's say, Harmonix, which actually allowed you, in the third installment, play with a lot more instruments, like a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_01]: and the ability to play them in pro mode, which says a lot about them, that they're really thinking long term with that whole franchise, whereas Activision just cares about how much money can we make with Guitar Hero in each quarter.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's all about the bottom line Bills, bills, bills
[SPEAKER_01]: Herald heralded that whole video game you know the whole genre into into near disaster or the video game crash I'm pretty sure you know I have a gut feeling that Activision will be the ones that's gonna herald everything to mediocrity like in two years I bet you in two years they're gonna have like a
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to let you go, buddy, so we can go and wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: But thank you, as always, for your insight, because I know you're passionate about the music games.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't say it wasn't entertaining.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get to the last last minute stories from Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't think I have much left here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It hasn't been a very exciting Newsweek, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_04]: Outside of the more and more and more stuff getting shut down over at Activision, there's not a lot else to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I think I pretty much covered most of everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's pretty much it, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts as we get down to the end of the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know that face that's really scrunchy that people do for trolls on the internet?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: I kept imagining that call, just that mouth moving back and forward while that guy was talking, and it made me giggle a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually saw a really funny gif of that with the whole, you mad, you mad, you mad, like rotating around it, and it's just funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: The internet, it's fun to be a part of.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Loki, what's your final thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: People need to stop talking like they type on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's... Lol, Loki!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's seriously the worst... IKR?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the worst trend whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just... Remember how people used to get pissed off at other people with the Ebonics and shit like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just getting worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: ZOMG!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like, okay, yeah, we understand you mistyped on a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha ha, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't need to talk like that because you sound like an idiot.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will say one thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: We found OMG Yogurt and they were pretty good.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up with all these yogurt explosion chains recently?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and I hate Kotaku's new layout.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should say Gawker's new layout.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, sometimes you don't need to improve something because it's fine the way it was.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, now go troll that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a reason to go troll.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, trolling our website is like stalking Kathy Griffith or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like, seriously, who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, no one cares.
[SPEAKER_07]: And honestly, we don't get a lot of page hits, so no one's really going to notice that you're trolling.
[SPEAKER_04]: whatever the more we talk about it the more they're going to be like we should do it again my final thought I want to do more traveling and I'm thinking a trip to Seattle would need to be in the near future possibly around Labor Day possibly you're telling me a different time because other traveling in March I'm thinking about a particular expo that goes on in Seattle every year anyhow we'll have to talk about that offline
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anyhow, that's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys, as always, for listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's obviously another crazy day here at the ranch, but you know, in all seriousness, you know what we ask?
[SPEAKER_04]: We are an independent show.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do look at our website.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have no advertising.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't make money off this.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, we pay to do this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: All we ask, this is all we've ever asked, tell friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leave us a nice review on iTunes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Join our Facebook page.
[SPEAKER_04]: check in on GetGlue or whatever so people see that you're listening to the show and they go hmm I wonder what this is all about and just help us spread the word about Orange Launch Radio because you know we do try to be that show where every gamer has a voice independent and don't get paid for it so we're not paid to say anything or one way or another so there you go if you did get paid that'd be nice I will pay you in bacon it's alright I want Pinkberry I'll pay you in Pinkberry someday
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, that's it, we're done We're out of here, have a wonderful night everybody We'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio Goodbye
[SPEAKER_10]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week