Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and LocoCade
Tonight, August 16th, 2009
Is there a wee cushion on the horizon?
Will the Playstation 3 soon see you laughing?
And could you soon be able to take a trip to Silent Hill for real?
Orange Lounge Radio
Well hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
We are that podcast where every gamer has a voice
Dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle
With you for the next few hours, my name is Rob Roberts
And joining me as always, say hello to the one and only
Happiest bunny on the farm, as I used to call her every day on this week
DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Wait, how did that get started anyway?
I don't even remember
Oh, because I had my happy bunny stuff for a while
You used to be obsessed with happy bunny if I remember right
And now I think happy bunny is kind of stupid
Oh really? Well, happy bunny kind of jumped the shark a little bit
Now you see happy bunny everywhere on everything
Happy bunny was cool when no one knew about it
Exactly
And also say hello to the one and only tech master, Loki
Hello
How are you doing, Loki?
Fine
Not the happiest bunny on the farm, Loki
No, I'm not a bunny on a farm
You're very quiet tonight, Loki, what is going on?
Nothing, I'm trying to remember a password
And I think I got it
And I got it
Oh, I'm trying to see what you're trying to log into
Alright
Imani Sowz is what I'm logging into
Not the download torrents, but to read their forms
I see
What's so important on their forms?
Nothing, I want to see if some guy returned my PM
And he didn't
He's a bastard
I thought they said read their porn, so
If you are corresponding with Loki, you should write him back, ass
No, it's alright
I was second in line for a system 573 board, but I didn't
I probably don't need it now, so it's alright
You are very quiet tonight, and I can't figure out why
Let's try turning up your mic a little bit
The beauty of live radio, boys and girls
Oh, I thought you meant like I wasn't saying a lot, not that I was quiet
No, like you were actually quiet on the mic, now you were too loud
I think we're good now
Alright
So there we go
The joy of live radio as we tape live here on Sunday nights at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com, live after The Bobby Black Wolf Show
I have an announcement
You have an announcement, yes
Rob had chicken for dinner
I did, it was delicious
He didn't get me any
Grilled chicken
I had chicken and a biscuit
It still smells like chicken in this room, and it's driving me nuts
Look, I was hungry, I literally had nothing to eat today
I'm gonna make my husband bring me some food
You should do that, that's why you got married, right?
Yeah, so that it'd be my man servant
I too had chicken for dinner
Did you?
Yes
What kind of chicken did you have?
I had chicken covered with Ritz cracker bits
Have you been, since we're turning into Orange Launch Foodio
We'll get into our gaming week in just a moment
But since we're turning into Orange Launch Foodio
Have you been to that new restaurant?
And I think, you know, we're an international show
So I'm sure this place exists, other places
But it's new to Sacramento
Have you been to Wingstop?
No
It's pretty interesting
I refuse to eat there
Why is that?
Because it's attached to Pizza Hut
No, that's Wing...
No, Wing Street
That's a different one
No, Wingstop is a new one that they have here
Where they just, you know, they serve wings, obviously
In all these different flavors
And I don't think I've ever had, like, food worse for you
Probably that food at Wingstop
Hooters wings are worse for you
Are they?
But Hooters wings are good
No they're not
I think Hooters wings are good
Everything at Hooters sucks
Even the women suck
Everything at Hooters is awful
What is wrong with this picture?
I'm gonna keep the dirty comment down
I love Hooters more than anyone else in this room
Their food, I have given their food, like, three different chances
And, like, not only is their food bad, but their service is worse
It's just, it's absolutely crap
Their hostels taste like too much vinegar
For example, I went in one time and I decided
Okay, I'm gonna get a burger and what the hell
Let's get, order the wings because everyone's raving about the wings and stuff
Order the burger, the burger took an hour for me to get at my table
The wings, mind you, which is their staple food that they serve there
Took two hours to get to me
Now Loki's too loud
And they tasted like shit, okay
Get him angry, then he'll be louder
And not only that, okay, so I tried normal, like, their normal hot wings or whatever
They tasted like shit
I tried them, like, a different flavor
It's a different flavor of shit
It's just, it's, it's awful
There is nothing good at that place
All their food sucks and if you go for the ambiance, you're stupid
You can get better food at a strip club
Are you kidding?
I just, the last time I went to Hooters was Victoria and I
We were like, where should we go eat?
Let's go to Hooters!
And we went, we had fun, we were laughing the whole time
Our waitress had big boobies and we were, you know, making fun of her
But in a positive way, like, you know
Seriously, okay, strip club food is not very good
It was better than Hooters
And you know what?
At a strip club, I'm not gonna just have to imagine naked boobies
I can see them firsthand
So, you know, I'm sorry, it's just not worth my time
Here's my, here's my question about Hooters
Do you remember that E3?
It was probably 2004, 2005
When we were staying at the ghetto, ghetto ghetto ghetto
Motel 6 on Hollywood Boulevard
Like, I don't know what inspired us to stay there
I ought to be young and in our 20s again
But to be staying at that ghetto Motel 6
And we had to walk up Hollywood Boulevard
Through a concert that Jimmy Kimmel Live was doing or something
To get to Hooters, because we were like
Hadn't you never been there at that point?
I've never been there
That's right, and I was like, Loki!
You're like a manly man and you've never been to Hooters
I'm like, don't tell me you're gonna make a gay man take you to Hooters
So eventually a gay man did have to take him to Hooters
So we went to Hooters
And, you know, it was, it was our first experience
Well, his first experience at Hooters
And I guess it wasn't favorable
Well, just also getting there took us like 30 minutes
When it was just like a block up the street
We could see it, but it took a half an hour to get there
So, anyhow
But it wasn't crowded, because everybody was out in the street watching the concert
And then once the concert was over, oh damn, did that place fill up fast
It's crazy
Alright, anyhow, sorry, we'll stop talking about Hooters
And talk about our gaming week!
Dark Soccer, how was your gaming week?
What types of games have you been playing this week?
It was actually busy, believe it or not
I've really been getting into Blue Dragon
Which, yeah, it took me long enough, but shut up
And I really like it for its classic RPG-ocity
You know, it's been pretty fun for me
And I also played through Raiden Fighters Aces
And nearly beat the game, except that I was in a lot of pain when I was playing it
Well, I was, it was really more that I was just gonna play for a little bit of it
And then, you know, put it aside
But I actually played all the way through
And then I kept getting to the last stage
And because my hand hurt so bad, I couldn't hit the fire button fast enough
So I kept also not counteracting the fire that was coming at me
And kept dying
And it turns out that when you have to continue, it starts you off from the beginning of the stage
And I just said, you know what, fuck a bunch of this
And, you know, I'm not gonna do it
So I put it down and then promptly went to go put my hand in a big thing of ice water
Because it really, really hurt
And then I also played a lot of the Namco Museum package that we picked up
And, you know, just some Galaga and some Pac-Man
Wait, is this the 360 compilation?
Okay, so this is like the Galaga Resurrection and some of the arcade titles they've put out over the past couple years
They kind of butchered the Galaga one
I like, I had more fun going back and playing Galaga 98, uh, Galaga 88
So, you know, Dan and I were actually talking about, you know, this is more fun on TurboGrafx
So, um, it's not a bad collection, it's a really good collection
And I love Namco, yay Namco, kiss kiss
But, eh
And then, um, we were gonna play some Symphony of the Night and as it turned out that Dan hasn't authorized our Xbox yet
So I can't play it
Even though we have it on his account, I can't play it
And I was like, ugh, ugh, ugh
So, um, so then I started playing a lot of Blue Dragon
And I love, love, love, love, love Blue Dragon
And I just got back to their village
If anyone who's played the game knows where that is
What part of the game I'm at
Now that game took a lot of shit for being kind of generic, for being kind of, like, not that impressive
Some people have said for considering who all's behind it
You know what? They can bite me
Okay then
Because the thing that I like about it is that it has the classic RPG feel
It has a good solid story
And yeah, maybe it's not, ooh, innovative
Maybe it doesn't have the stigma of being Final Fantasy
But I bet if you slapped a Final Fantasy name on it and changed the characters, I bet you'd love it
Seriously
But I mean, it has the charm of, uh
I've noticed this typically about games that Toriyama designs
That they tend to have that charm that comes with his art style
And I loved that
That was fantastic for me
And Uematsu's music, I mean, oh my god, Uematsu
It made me happy
See, I get that, but I'm way more about Lost Odyssey than I was Blue Dragon
I didn't think Blue Dragon was as terrible as a lot of folks made it out to be
But I just thought it was, eh, it's aight
It's aight
Did you just say it's aight?
Yeah
Stop
It's classic, it's new and classic at the same time
You know what I mean?
It's a new story, it's something to play through, but something that you can pick up that will automatically be familiar to you
So for me, it's been filling my must-play Super Nintendo with a more comfortable controller
Alright
And of course I've been playing Sims 3
I started another family because the game decided to fart on one of mine
Well, technically what happened is that, um
Someone turned off my computer while I was in the middle of a game
And didn't save said game
So it was either the Spouse or Windows Updates
Which I thought I had turned those off too
So, whatever
And um, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, I've also been playing on Gaia
I like the booty grab
Uh, going to the chatroom at chat.orangelandtrady.com for questions and comments
Ray Iyanami asked Dark Sakura, hold it
Which game on RFA, which Raiden fighters, and was it on one credit?
Um, actually no because like I said, my hand hurt a lot
So I played the first one
Um
And
You know, I was really just gonna sit down and see what it was like
Cause I hadn't played the Aces ones
So I played through and
Yeah, I was
I really don't have the fine control that I used to
Because I've, you know, like I said
My hand has been, um, sticking with a suture in it
And my tendons are healing themselves
So I haven't really been able to play
Like I might have, you know
A few years ago
So, uh, no I didn't do it on one credit
But hopefully in a couple months that'll be all better, right?
Yeah, well when it's all better I'm gonna be going back to R-Type
Alright
Loki, how about you and your gaming week?
I played DDR, that was it
That's all I played is DDR
Or, not DDR, what the hell am I talking about? I didn't play any DDR
I'm a DDR freak, so you know
Really? This is actually kind of noteworthy
I'm like, you actually started exercising
What is this?
Eventually I will, but no
I'm a green DDR freak, so
No, I've been playing Grand Theft Auto all the week
All week long, and we have
Been recording our, like, multiplayer game
Because Grand Theft Auto and DDR have so much in common
Okay, it's a three letter acronym
I was looking to say, and I was staring at DDR freak
That's why I made the slip, okay?
So, whatever
With all due respect to the many friends I made on there
Including you guys
Since when was DDR freak relevant again?
It's not, I'm looking at
I'm trying to, okay
Because I have my pads that I've built
You remember when I built them? Hell, it was that long ago
I've used them since
No, I haven't used them since then
So, I have them sitting in my garage
And I'm just seeing if it's going to be more
Agentageous to actually
Purchase some
Already pre-done arcade style pads
For DDR
Or should I just fix it?
Because right now I have to ground
The pads because the static electricity being built up
By the Lexan
Arrows
It causes the
Thing I have it attached to
To interpret the keys
To short out
Because it just builds up static electricity
And then, like, shocks it
Which is not good
Because it'll stop working after about two minutes
And then have to reboot the whole computer
So
I need to figure out how to ground them
And one time I read how to do that
And I can't remember now, so
I'm just going to buy new ones
Because it's easier that way
Frisbee in our chat room says
Grand Theft Arrow
No, but Grand Theft Auto
We've been playing quite a bit, of course
I have like
Five hours of footage now
Of us playing Grand Theft Auto
Even a little bit of me playing
Earth Defense Force
Because we decided to switch off to Earth Defense Force
Because our other co-worker decided
He wanted to go play Magic the Gathering with somebody
So we were like, ah, fuck that
But yeah, Grand Theft Auto
It'll be awesome, I just have to
Edit it down now to
Something funny
And set the music
Good, because the Orange Launch Radio channel needs more content
It's in HD, so it'll be awesome
Yeah, because that new capture thing I have
Is awesome, it works so well
So it'll make things a lot easier
For capturing video to put on the site
And
Good, we need to do some mystery science
Theatering to video games
That's what we need to do
There's actually some old school talk going on in the chat room right now
Yeah
What's it called?
Block Box
So we brought up Tetranet
You remember Tetranet?
I remember Tetranet, I used to play that stuff all the time
Sorry to interrupt
And I'm getting an arcade cabinet
Really?
Is it an actual game, or what is it?
It's an arcade cabinet
Just the cabinet?
For what?
What do you plan to put on it?
Maim, DDR
It's a candy cabinet
Do you know what a candy cabinet is?
I haven't the slightest idea what that is
You know those cabinets that line Arcade Infinity?
The really small ones?
Oh, yeah, like the ones you sit down and play?
Yes, that's a candy cabinet
Oh, those are pretty cool
There's a deal going on
There's the Neo Geo forums
I found it looking for something else
Because at one time
I wanted to buy a DDR machine
But then I had to scale down
my wishes
Because a DDR machine would cost me at least $2500
Probably more than that
And that's just not affordable
So a candy cab
I'm looking at a
new Astro City machine
Which is a Sega made one
And um
It's supposed to run somewhere around $450
I think
And they're basically doing a big bulk shipment
And they have some extras available
They're being shipped to San Francisco
So um
Hopefully, I'm trying to get the guy to
send me a personal message again
So I can actually put down the deposit for it
Because they're supposed to be coming
Between now and September, so
That'd be awesome
Because then I'm gonna put a
To become like a
Little, short, stubby
DDR machine
Are you sure it's actually DDR and not Grand Theft Auto?
It can be both
Actually, we were thinking about
Getting one of those for all of our Neo Geo
Well, you should act on this
I mean, 400 bucks
And they're shipping them already
Actually, they're already on a boat
They're already on a boat on the way here
Yes, they're on a motherfucking boat
So they're already on their way over
It's just, um
You know, he's trying to sell 30 of them
Otherwise, he's gonna keep them
And sell them for higher
I should ask the spouse, just
He could pay for it out of pinball money
We're having a hard time hearing you, DarkSakura
Make sure that mic's really good
Thank you, much better
And then I'm having a milkshake
And my stomach feels like it's gonna explode
Because I have lots of milkshake in me
Well, there you go
Let's see my gaming week
Wednesday
We all got a patch on Xbox Live, right?
And everybody, you know, had to update
To this new patch that
You know, added all this new stuff in Netflix
And blah, blah, blah
Kind of changed some things with the achievements and so on
So I'm gonna download that and I'm messing with the achievements and stuff for a little bit
Thought I'd look at Netflix
And I like the fact that you can add the movies
From the Netflix channel now
You can kind of browse through what new movies are out and things
I thought that was pretty awesome
Then I turn it off and I'm off doing other things for a while
And then I'm bored
So I put a tweet up on Twitter that says
Hi, I'm bored, who wants to play Rock Band?
So a couple of the OLR listeners are like, me, me, me
So they invite me into a game
We're playing some Rock Band, da, da, da, da, da
I have to step away for a little bit because I gotta do some other errands real quick
And I got other things I gotta do
But then I go back after about 20 minutes
Turn on the Xbox 360 again and then
It starts doing all
That's actually the sound it makes
It just starts throwing up everywhere
Making all these, like, jaggeds on the screen
And looks very ugly
And it'll happen in the middle of a game
It'll happen when I'm trying to boot up and so forth
So, of course, what do I instantly blame?
The patch that went out on Wednesday
I'm like, oh my god, my system got borked by the patch
I'm becoming a statistic
I'm like, this happened before, right?
And we have a ton of people that got their Xboxes screwed up because of the patch
Well, turns out
There's a handful of people on Twitter
Who claim that happened, but
I made this whole YouTube and I posted it to the
Orange Ons Radio channel and most people are telling me
Just have lucky timing
And your system's about to red ring
Well, I can fucking tell that
It's obviously about to red ring
It's broken already
I mean, it's not getting past a certain point, red ring or not
So, congratulations me, my Xbox is broke
And, once you know it
I'm just outside the three year warranty thing
That means I get to open it up
I'm like three years and six months after it
You wanna open it up?
We'll see, we can fix it
I've had a few
Oh, goodie
Hey, 50% is better than zero percent
Sounds like my trauma center record, look
I don't know, I'm kind of all about fixing it
But at the same time, I'm like
And there's a story later on about price cuts
And I'm like, maybe I'll just wait and get the elite system
Because I kinda want the new stuff
But, hold on a minute
Why am I allowing myself to think this way?
Why do I even need to be worrying about repairs and so on in the first place?
What the hell kind of system
Fries itself after three years?
Really?
Video game systems
Most of them have been pretty stable
Most people have old school Nintendos that still work
Granted, you have to blow on the cartridge and so on
But, not bad for like 25 years old
Eh?
You're preaching to the choir, okay?
I have five systems that have died, okay?
My Dreamcast is 10 years old and still works
We've been celebrating the Genesis
On Bobby Black Wolf's show tonight
He was talking a lot about that
That just celebrated his 20th anniversary
Those still work
That are older than most of our listeners ages combined
In the back room of my house
That, guess what?
Still work!
Except for the Atari 7800, but it still has an hour supply
So, let's not talk about that
It's just stupid
Like, and I just
You know, it's just kind of funny
The response I was getting was a lot of people was like, yep
You're Red Ringing 2
Oh yeah, oh yeah, I've been there
And, you know, I couldn't help but think
I'm so grateful that everybody's letting me know
I'm not alone
On the other hand, I'm thinking
What the hell kind of gaming society have we become
That this is even borderline acceptable
That we've just chalked this up to
Eh, it happens
Oh yeah, oh yeah
Those Xbox 360s
Totally unreliable
I guess I'll have to get another one
I'm just thinking to myself
Where did we go wrong?
Where did we allow this to be acceptable?
Why is Microsoft doing as well as they are?
To bring in a more sociological aspect to it
Sorry, this is the way the world is
Because your initial systems were broken
I was sort of doing something
Um
It's the fact that people would rather be complacent
Than put any effort into changing a situation
In general
And so, enough people just let it go
And they can get away with it
But, you know, enough people complain about something
And something might eventually happen
You know
If they think that they can get away with it this long
They're just gonna keep getting away with it
Until enough people hold them accountable
That's all there is to that
Well, all I have to say is that
It just sucks
Like, the whole thing just sucks
And Microsoft sucks
And, you know, you suck for not making more of a stink about it
Not you specifically
But you as gamers in general
And I suck for not realizing this before
And everything sucks
And the fact that I'm gonna have to buy a new 360
Sucks too
Or I guess I could get this one fixed
I'm having offers for fixing
And apparently Loki has an awesome 50% fixed record
And the other one was just unfixable
I tried everything, okay
It was just too far gone
Oh, who knows
And actdeft is apologizing to me in chat
But you don't need to apologize, it's not your fault
Stop apologizing
People who apologize for things that aren't their fault
Sucks
Well, that's actually the big thing
That I think
Is the problem with the industry
As it is now
With almost anything actually
Is that
Too many people are just
More willing to
Oh, I don't wanna conflict
I don't wanna put the effort into it
I don't wanna do this about it
Oh, well that's just how it is
That's how things are gonna be
You know
Everyone get off your asses
And complain if you've got something wrong
This is the thing
Here's what I want, I'm gonna put a challenge
Out there
This would make me happy
I will spend the $300 on a new elite
Or whatever I have to do when the price drop comes down
I will do all this stuff
And continue to just let Microsoft
Rate me in the butt as they're doing right now
I will continue to allow this
If my challenge goes responded to
By the media and the gaming industry
I know there's some of you insider folk that listen
And don't wanna admit it
I know there's some of you that work for gaming companies and so forth
That listen and probably don't wanna admit it to your employer
But look, this is the one thing I want
That will make me happy
Because in 3 or 4 years Microsoft is gonna come out
And tout their new console
Their Xbox 720
Or whatever you wanna call it
Or hell, there's talk that there might be a slim down
This is what I want
This is what I want every media outlet
This is what I want every gamer
To ask Microsoft
About their new system
Will it last more than 3 years?
Yeah
Does this system red ring
Those are the questions I want Microsoft
To be asked to their face
And have to answer
Why should I trust you
That your system is not another pile of poop
I do it
Okay, so this hasn't been done yet
I think that what we should do also
Is, and this is actually something
As a community
Have you ever heard of a site called
Starbucked.com?
No, but does this have to do with Battlestar Galactica?
No, it's about a person who had
Such a horrible customer service experience
With Starbucks
That he created a consumer advocacy site
So that people could voice their concerns regarding
Problems they've had with Starbucks
And his problem is actually something
That could have been fixed
If one person had gotten off their ass and helped him properly
So, um
I think that I should make a site
And don't nobody make it for me
Unless you want to make me an admin of it
Is a red ringed, you know
Oh, there's got to be a site like that already
I looked, there wasn't
Really?
You know, to make a big, you know
Hi, this is a picture of our red ringed system
This is what was done about it
And keep a running tally
Of all of these
And start, you know, sending
Up and go, hey look
Here's where you guys have screwed up
Here's our tally this week, here's our tally this week
Here, just search Twitter, seriously
Search Twitter, R-R-O-D, watch
I even, I was at work
On Friday and I mentioned, we had some
Down time because our systems were down
And I mentioned, oh yeah, my Xbox
And people I never suspected even played
Video games, like outside of like
Madden and stuff were saying, oh you got the
Red rings, huh? Yeah, I got that too
And like everybody in class was piping up
Yeah, the red rings, oh I know the red rings
Well you know what, then why not, let's
Let's, um, if I pulled up
Everything on Twitter that had
Red ring of death, printed it out
In black and white because I don't want to save my color cartridges
And emailed the stack
Not emailed, but mailed the stack
Of papers to
Microsoft and go, look
I don't think they do anything
Because people are still buying 360's
But what's it do? So it doesn't boot up now?
Or is it just not play your games?
It does a blalalala thing after
It's been on like two minutes
Sometimes during the boot, sometimes while I'm in the middle of the game
Doesn't matter
To be honest, I haven't really tried it since that one night
So
That's where I'm at
To be perfectly honest though
I mean, I think we're on
What, our third
360, but keep in mind
We have an advantage
I just want the history of gaming to put
A black mark on, excuse me
A red mark on Xbox
A red ring around the Xbox
A red ring on the Xbox 360
For this travesty
And the fact that they're covering it up very well
I mean, has there been any console
In history
That has the hardware issues that the 360 has?
The reason why
They, I think are being able
To keep their head afloat regarding everything
Is the fact that they've been so quick to replace
Systems too
Like, I know, honestly Rob
I think you should still give a call, give a try
You know, say hey
I bought this, you know, before
All this was going on
You guys owe me
You know, see what happens
You know, if they want to keep your business as a customer
They're gonna bend over backwards
Bobby says the PS2, Bobby actually says a lot in chat
Let me read some of the comments from chat
Bobby says they know
Sorry, Microsoft knows
They know, they won't admit it, but they know
And
Yeah, he says his original
Xbox still works, so does mine
Mine does too
And he goes on to say the difference between the PS2 and the 360
Is that there were no blogs when the PS2s
Were failing in mass, and you know, that's
Certainly a legitimate viewpoint
I don't know, see here's the thing though
I don't know anyone that had a PS2 that failed
Outside of people I've met on the internet
Like, when I was gaming
I didn't know anybody that had a failed PS2
Mine didn't fail, I know like 50 people that have
360s fail
My Japanese PS2, guess what?
It still works!
Yeah, my Japanese PS2 still works too
I mean, first release model
We got ours way back when
We had this like
Cause I wanted Tekken that bad
So we got our
We have a Japanese PS3
There was I think a PS2, sorry
If I'm right, it was a demo system
Back from when Game Masters
Was still open
And that was years ago
And I'm on my fifth PS2 and you met me in person
I guess that's true
But you know what I mean, like, you know
My Japanese PS2 still works perfectly
And those are the ones that were
Definitely having problems back in the day
My PS2 that I have now
Works perfectly
I'm just annoyed
What else did we get in chat?
I do have a stack of PS1s by the way
I want to get onto other stuff in my gaming week
Cause I did more than just bitch about my
Bork to Xbox 360, but let's see, what else was there
I think I posted a chat from Wiki
In response to the November 2006 update
Error that bricked his console
A California man filed a class action lawsuit against
Microsoft in Washington federal court in early December
2006, the lawsuit seeks
5 million in damages and the free repair of any
Console rendered unusable by the update
This will be the second such lawsuit filed against
Microsoft, the first having been filed in 2005
Shortly after the... etc
Unfortunately not enough
People had their consoles borked by this update
And people are, you know, telling me up and down
That it wasn't the update
All I know is that, you know
It sure is convenient timing for this to happen
Have you tried bringing it without the hard drive?
I haven't, should I try that?
Yes
Ok, I'll try that, see what happens
Because it could be something corrupted on the hard drive
Do you have Rock Band 2 installed to your hard drive?
I do, but the thing will crap out before
Even playing Rock Band 2
But you have it installed to your hard drive
Cause it just reads your disc for a second
And then it runs it off the hard drive
Ok, I'll try that
That would certainly be better, but we'll see
Alright, anyhow
Other stuff I played my gaming week
Cause I have much more in my gaming week than just
Abort 360 that I still, by the way
My resolution right now is I'm not doing anything
Till this rumored price drop will get to later in the show
Maybe I'll get it repaired
I don't know, right now I'm leaning
Right now I'm leaning towards just getting a new
Get a new one and make sure it's a new elite, not an older elite
That people have been sitting on forever
Or, yeah, that's what I'll try and do
But anyhow
What I wanted to get into elsewhere in my gaming week
Because this is something that deserves
Positive talk and not negative talk
Is Ion Online I played a little more of
They had their next closed beta
I guess the final one, it's the second closed beta
I've participated in
And I got to play the game a lot more than
Two weeks ago, the first time I played the beta for Ion Online
I still feel like I've only really
Scratched the surface of the game
And I was having a lot of problems with
Graphics stuff
The game doesn't work too hot with
Vista, but I found if I ran in full screen windowed mode
I was able to get a much better frame rate
So, you know, just you have to really
Tinker with those settings and at least they've made it very
Customizable in the graphics and so on
The game is a very good looking game
It's a very smooth game
It's kind of fun, it's wow-ish
It definitely, you can feel the
Wow inspiration there, but one thing I liked
That WoW doesn't have is the
Whole chained combat
Meaning that there are moves that you can do
That only open up after you do
A first move, like maybe you do a
Special little thing with your mace, then you can make
A lightning bolt fall down or whatever
It's branching combos
Ragnarok Online has that
Yeah, Monk class, you have your combos
Well that's every class in this game has something like that
But I mean, I'm saying that Ragnarok Online certainly
Thought of, you know, implementing stuff like that
Well sure, I'm sure a lot of what
Can be thought of has been thought of in MMOs
Who knows, there could be more though
I only got my character to level 8
Which is like scratching the surface of the game
I didn't even get into any PVP or instances or what have you
So can I fairly review this game?
No, but off the closed beta
Can I say I'm interested?
The game was fun enough
Where I would feel like I could buy the game
And I won't be getting ripped off
Yes, I think it's worth checking out
So that's what I plan to do in September
And then hopefully I'll be able to spend some more time with it
And tell you my final thoughts on it
So there you go
And I've been playing a priest
So, there it is
I wanna play
Anyhow
Hold on, I'm reading comments from chat here
About, yes
To publicly acknowledge it
Because it keeps going back and forth in chat
I am aware that CC Gaming
Repairs 360s
And would also take the 360 for scrap
I just haven't decided what I want to do yet
You know, because I'd have to ship it
Which is gonna be money, but
You know, I don't know
I want some time to think and try these
Other solutions too before I just
Commit to one particular solution
Certainly that's something I'm heavily considering
But we'll see
Alright
That's it for our gaming weeks
Let's get into
What's this present? Ooh, present
Some of my more obscure Bimani stuff
You burned me a DVD mini
Yeah, I remember you used to use CD
Minis all the time, now it's DVD Minis
Well that's because it was, they were
Cheap by the spindle and
You know, the pre-shift fit on them
Perfectly, all my stuff was just fine
But the next one I'm gonna burn you is an actual DVD
Alright, uh
Let's get into some housekeeping tonight
Of which we don't have a lot, but we will continue to plug our
Twitter at OLR and then of course we're on
Facebook as the OLR me
We have a MySpace supposedly too
Is anyone on MySpace anymore? No, we had some friend requests
There the other day, so I guess we do
And yeah, LiveJournal
Orange launch MySpace is so 2005
It really is, okay
Let's get into some gaming news then and we'll
Start with Loki
Yes, there is a couple of rumors
Regarding some Wii software
One of which is of course
Wii Fit, there is a rumored price point
For it, which of course
Not too surprising, they have the
Bundle at the
$99.99 price point
Which is, you know
Or I should say $99.99 price point
I think that's a little higher, that's kinda weird
But anyways, it's pretty close to what the
Normal Wii Fit bundle is
Then of course the rumor is the standalone
Game is gonna be $29.99 as well
No word exactly on
When those are gonna be officially announced
But I don't know
That sounds about right to me
You know, $29.99 for a game that's
Not too different than the original
Sounds fair, I guess
Maybe
The other weird thing though
That they have
And this is also coming from
A marketing survey, apparently
They have a slide
That shows
What appears to be some
Sort of new peripheral that's gonna be
With a game that's
Like a bicycling game and the peripheral
Itself actually looks like one of those
Oh
Gosh
I forget the kind of bike
The exercise bike?
Stationary?
Recumbent bike
I think, something like that
It's really interesting because
It almost looks like a Wii Fit type of
Game
You can definitely see Miis in the pictures
And stuff like that, but I don't think it's
Necessarily something from
Nintendo themselves
Because
Some of the other characters don't necessarily look like
Miis, but they have different things like
Road races, you can walk
Your dog in the game, you can do
Almost like a prop copter type thing
You can
Rotate one of the things
Spin a rotisserie barbecue
Downhill
Racing, you name it
And of course the usual
Calorie tracking and that kind of
Stuff, but I mean it looks kind of cool
And definitely something I could see on
The Wii, so
No word on what that is, I'm guessing it's probably a third
Party putting that out, probably someone like Ubisoft
Or EA or something
Well it wouldn't surprise me too if one of these
Bicycling things got picked up because it seems
Like at E3, remember when there was a
Kenshi Hall and everything? We would see something
Like this demoed, like a
Bicycling exercise game
There's some companies exploring this, have been
For a long time
I wouldn't be surprised if it even was Nintendo doing it or something
Just maybe that one screenshot
Is kind of misleading because the one character
Doesn't look like a Mii, but
Everything doesn't have to look like a Mii in the games
But who knows
The other thing is, it sort of looks like an island
Setting, and I know that they've talked about
Putting the other games on that stupid island
That they created for Wii Fit
In Wii Sports Resort
Wii Fit's on an island?
Well they have like, the jogging
Is on an island
So I don't know if it's the same island
But it's very similar
Skinny Island, what would the name of that island be?
It's WooHoo Island or something
WooHoo Island? I think that's what they called it
WooHoo, I'm not fat anymore, yay
Or Sex Island, as Sims would call it
WooHoo Island
WooHoo! Whoopee
I don't know
It's neat
I would be more excited about the pedal thing than I would be
The Wii Fit balance board, because at least the pedal thing
You know, it seems like exercise
Whereas the balance board, you're just kind of
Standing there, leaning back and forth
You know, back and forth
I don't know
Again, our good friend Bobby is just piping up with all sorts of trivia tonight
Saying Miyamoto wants that to become
One of the new characters that is indeed
WooHoo Island
Is the name of where all this takes place
Well I don't want to see any other games with the island
You know, running around doing stuff
You know, Mario at WooHoo Island
You know, killing Koopas
Oh wait for it, it'll happen
There's a new Smash Brothers game with WooHoo Island
As a playable character
That'll be a stage, it'll be a stage
No, it'll be a character
The island will be a character
He said it himself, the island's a character
Spoiler right there
I mean, how do you face off against a whole island?
You can't
X-Men did it
Giants has X-Men number one
Uh huh
Oh my gosh
Told you I'm a geek
Um, so uh
I don't know, what do you guys think of this?
Is this bicycle peripheral something that would interest you guys?
Or no?
It'd be interesting to see it, but
Once again, I'd probably use it about as much as I do Wii Fit
Wii Fit though, it fills the space
Underneath my TV stand
That's it
You should lend it to me
It's all about price to me
I actually use Wii Fit once in a while
I haven't lately, I've been slacking off
And I need to stop doing that
It's summer, it's too hot in the summer
The price would be $89.99
Including the peripheral, it's about the price of a Wii Fit
For the bike and the game?
That's not terrible
If the game was fun and the bike thing actually worked
Cause she's actually sitting on the couch
Or something, right?
And the bike is kinda there
If that is actually sturdy
Then that might be cool
I don't know though
We'll have to see
I like exercise bikes and stuff
You know what, I can go to my gym
And play my Gameboy on a bike
But that's also how much a month?
I don't pay a whole lot for my gym
I'm out of contract
I see
Alright, moving on to some other news
Talking about something on the DS
As opposed to the Nintendo Wii
Dragon Quest IX of course
Was a huge game over in Japan when it came out
As all Dragon Quest games are
And so of course the question is
When is it going to come out over here?
Well apparently there was a Q&A session
This week with investors
And the president of Squeenix
Yoishi Wada said that they are
Considering releasing Dragon Quest IX
Overseas
And still deciding which regions are actually
Going to get it
And they don't plan to release it until after April
Of 2010
They're assholes is basically what it is
I'm serious, it's just like
Eh, why do we feel like it?
You'll be lucky and be pleased when you get it
It's just like
You know, they see the fans of the series
Over here just as like
Beggars on the street that they
May casually throw down their
Money so that they can bask in the glory
Of Dragon Quest
They can go fuck themselves because I don't give a shit
About their fucking game
Dragon Quest is a horrible series in my opinion
Oh, now come on, now you're just being petty
Because Dragon Quest VIII was awesome
No it wasn't
And Dragon Quest VIII
Sold about half a million copies here in North America
That isn't any
Small number, I mean is it a blockbuster?
No
Is it pretty decent? Yeah
So why not?
And look, I'm going to say something that I know is going to piss
Some people off but I kind of don't care because I'm just
Keeping it real, okay
This is the case when I support piracy
Honestly
When these foreign companies are too stubborn
To release the games over here
I say you know what
Then if you can understand Japanese
Copy the Japanese one and get it
Why do you have to worry about that? Because they have people that will
Translate it and then they'll add a patch
To the ROM and boom it's in English
And I know I'm going to take some flack for that comment
But I kind of don't care because I was doing that with
DDR years ago when they
Refused to release that over here and you know
When they finally released it over here I bought
Every single one even when they were crap
For quite a while
And Konami thanks you for that by releasing even
Crappier games
The lesson we learned there that doesn't matter
But I just
This kind of news that like they just
I'm all about like
I understand resources and that there's
Other games they want to do
And maybe they want to do some things that are outside the box
And so forth but I don't know
This thing kind of just reeks of
And we just don't feel
Like it right now
Type thing
And some folks in chat GameGuru says
Mother 3 in Act F speaks up
With the Mother 3 fan translation
Yeah
I'm all for that too
You know
I'm just
I don't understand why they just won't
I can't imagine it takes that
Long to translate a game especially when
You have fans that translate it
For you
I mean that's got to be the ultimate kick in the pants
When you have these fan companies
Beating you to it
People that are paid 40 hours
A week to do this
I don't know
Keep in mind though that when
They do it themselves
Not only do they have to pay
Translator, they have to
Pay writer
They have to take the time to change
Anything in game
Graphically that has
They need to
Translate from one language to another
They have to pay
Someone to localize it
To make the jokes come across
I played through a
Fan done copy of Final Fantasy 5
And there were just a few things in there
That I got because I had
Studied some Japanese for a while
That I don't know that other people
Might have gotten because the joke
Is
It was actually a pun
So
There are things that are lost in translation
That you do have to
Go through
Reorganizing for the cultural element
To make it something that would be
Understood by your audience
So there is actually a good deal of cost
That comes in with
The translation process
When you are paying for it
For the fans
For them, it's a labor of love
It's something that they enjoy doing
But when the company brings it out, they have to pay
Somebody to do this
And even if someone says, oh I'll do it for free
I'm sorry that doesn't work, you still have to pay them
Because there are labor laws
And then there is marketing
There is
Production cost
In the actual physical copies of the game
There's
You know, shipment
You have to deal with a lot of the money
That they would make back on Dragon Quest 9?
But when they also
And again, I'm doing this straight from a business
Perspective, they have to look at previous sales
And look at what their overhead was
Versus how much they actually made
The last few games that they have localized over here
At least on the 360 and stuff, haven't done that great
I mean, Star Ocean, Last Hope wasn't all that great
The Last Remnant
Was not that great at all
The game itself wasn't that great
And then the one before that, which I don't remember
The name off the top of my head
But that didn't do that well either
It's just, I don't know
Was that Infinite on Discovery?
Yes, Infinite on Discovery
But there's just a lot of weird stuff that they're doing
Like, Chrono Trigger did alright
Shit, dude, it's just a ROM
That they're basically running off an emulator
I mean, that's basically all they did
You can't tell me that they programmed the engine
From scratch and rebuilt the game
I'm sorry, I don't buy that at all
And I could totally see them going the route of like
You know, the Final Fantasy 4 after years stuff
Where they just take the ROM and kind of edit it
And add some new stuff to it
And boom, new game, let's resell it
And even the stuff that they've done online
Like Final Fantasy 4 and whatnot
I mean, My Life as a King is kind of eh
When they had download content
That probably should have been included in the game to begin with
And My Life as a Dark Lord was kind of eh
It was alright, I guess
And their tactical
I don't remember the other Final Fantasy tactical game
That they had
The Tower Defense one
Is kind of just
This is alright, but they haven't really been having
That many good hits lately
And other than Final Fantasy 4 and 3 and stuff like that
On DS
When they actually remade them
And that was kind of cool
Because there's effort put into it
And it's Final Fantasy
But I don't know, maybe they're just worried
That it's not going to do as well
And why pay the money to have it, you know, translated
But it's a major release for them
I don't see why they wouldn't do it
They're probably going to do it
And it'll just take some time
Because, you know, as history has shown
Square is really slow
When it comes to finishing their games
I'm looking at some comments in chat
Gripper01
Says
Plus with fan translations they are not censored
Like the early Final Fantasy translations
Hmm
Apparently
GameGuru is saying
Atlas even offered to publish Mother 3 for Nintendo
And Nintendo of Japan denied it
And I guess this whole back and forth
Is that because of all the parity
In the games
Nintendo of America is afraid of getting sued
So they want to make some changes
And Nintendo of Japan won't let them
It's just weird, that whole mess
So why don't they release it in, well
Do they, have they released it like on
Virtual console or something like that?
Mother 3 is a DS game, so no
It's a Game Boy Advance game
But they could still do it
I don't know, I mean it's basically Super Nintendo
I don't, they
In theory I think it could be done
Actually I need to find the translated ROM
Because I am going to play the translated ROM
People
I'm saying this now
Because I don't care
But yeah, actually something that brings the other thing
Going back to what I was saying
Is you also have to deal with distribution
And with dealing with the companies
That you're going to be releasing the game through
Money, it all comes down to money
I guess
Alright, well let's move on
With some more news while I steam over
Not having Dragon Quest 9, I guess
It's not that bad, because this is a DS game
And I don't have the attention span for DS games
So whatever
Well, how about something else that you'd have
To have a bit of an attention span if you plan on
Finishing it at all
Mega Man 9
There's new download content, and guess what it does
It makes the game harder
Why?
You have Super Hero Mode
Which costs a dollar
A whole dollar
A whole dollar, it's 80 Microsoft points
And
It basically
Just keeps, it increases the number of
Enemies that you're going to see on screen
At any given time in the game
So yeah, it's for all you
People who want the next big challenge
It's basically for people who like asshole Mario
Or who have like those
Leftover points that you just can't seem
To get rid of, because everything is
Everything is in multiples
Of 100, except rock band songs
See, that would be kind of cool
If they did that for like Super Mario Brothers
Like re-release Mario Brothers
With a level editor or something like that
And then have it where you could share levels online
Of course that would be innovative and use online
So Nintendo would never buy that
A perfect example of something you could do
Simple, you don't have to actually program
Really a whole ton to it
Release it
People would love it
And you'd get a lot of money back
You'd put a lot of effort in
Because Nintendo certainly doesn't do that
Yeah, but then they'd get sued for copying
Little Big Planet
Yeah, I'm in the camp that's like
Isn't Mega Man 9 hard enough?
I guess there's definitely the hardcore fans
I haven't played it yet, I bought it a long time ago
But I still haven't played it
I only was able to beat like 3 or 4 of the robots
Before I was like, okay I'm spent
I'm done
You know what I'd like to see?
I'd actually like to see a new
That would make me happy
How about some Mega Man 9 easy mode content?
I'd pay a dollar for that
Actually I had an idea of something that I would like to see
And that's called like
Like Uber Man
Where it's Mega Man and you have to fight through
All of the 1 through 9 robots
And then do the Uber Wily stage
I think that's every Mega Man fan's dream game
Just Mega Man orgy
Where it's like all 81 master robots
Or however many they've had over the series
Not even counting X
I'm not even going to throw the X series into it
Because that could be like the sequel when this game does well
But Mega Man orgy would just be a game
Where it's like all 81 robots
Going at it at once
And then do it Metroid style
Which is a very interesting orgy
Considering one of those robots is a woman
And the other 80 are men
Just do it all Metroid style
And make the dungeons like Mega Man Legends
Tie that in there
Oh that would be hot
But it has to remain 2D
It has to remain 2D
I was thinking of a game that just had all 81 stages in it
And playable at once
But I like your idea of a
Metroidvania style Mega Man game
With all the robots
That's pretty cool
And if you totally used the escape velocity thing
Then you would be able to
Go back to your last save point
You know, location
Do weird warps like that
And then Samus would come out and kick Mega Man's ass
So you totally took my game
But that actually is
Ok we're putting that under Dream Games
And 4 player co-op because that would be awesome
Just for fun
That's under Dream Games now for Orange Knowledge Radio
It's an official Dream Game
What Mega Man orgy?
Yeah Mega Man orgy
I like what ActDeft calls it in chat
Mega 10 RGY
So the 0 is an o in orgy
I like that
Ok
You are now marketing director of this game
Congratulations on your promotion
You now get a non-existent job
So add that to the wiki
That's going on the list
And at the end
There's a big butt
What?
Are you high?
It's an easter egg
You know like when you can hold the buttons down
And the stars turn into chickens
Why would you just put a big butt
At the end of the game?
Are you like high?
Because it's on our list
Are you 5 years old?
Way to take a perfectly awesome game
And just literally shit on it
Because it's on our list
It would have a caption
Kiss our ass Capcom
No you don't do that
That's wrong
Oh come on you should look at our other games on our list
Exactly
This is why it doesn't need to be on the list
Because that list is just ridiculous stuff
This is ridiculous it's never gonna happen
Well it's just because it's never gonna happen
It's just I don't have
I'm sure there's people out there that have done custom Mega Man games
And it wouldn't be that difficult
The chat room would like to point out that what you're describing
Could be Guts Man's ass
It could be
Easter egg in the game you know
Guts Man with a certain number of life left
And you get a butt
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong with me for finding this funny?
How old am I? Like five?
Seriously?
It doesn't matter it's all for fun
Fun does not require an age
Alright but fun requires a new story real quick
Here before this story or before this show
Literally goes down the crapper
Speaking of your butt
Nintendo has patented a brand new
Inflatable cushion that you would use
For a horseback riding game
Why?
Just that's the most retarded thing
I have ever heard
It looks absolutely awful
It basically their picture that they have
First off looks like this like grown man
Dressed up like a little kid
Which is creepy enough if you ask me
And then the actual cushion itself
Is literally just like an inner tube
That they have strapped the Wii remote to
And you rock back and forth
I think that's supposed to be a kid
I understand it's supposed to be a kid
But it looks like a man child
So what is this for?
For a finally arcade perfect port
Of Final Furlong or what is this?
It's for I don't know
Sitting on your butt
It's for those racing games that they have
Where you sit on the Wii balance board
But if you have hemorrhoids you can't do it
So then you can sit on the cushion
Is this where your butt gets a little tickle
If you do well on the game?
This is stupid I mean seriously
You know what this reminds me of?
Do you remember that episode of South Park
With the bicycle that was powered
Like it was something like when everything
Was going green or whatever
And they would sit down on the thing
That was just basically a giant dildo
And then they had to blow on this thing
To make it go that looked like they were
Sucking cock
That's what this Wii inflatable cushion
Reminds me of like I'm gonna have that
In my living room
Let me describe how this works first off
Thank you wild wacky action bike
Thank you
As if it wasn't completely obvious
It's an inflatable air cushion
Or other type of seat
With pockets for the Wii remote
It's for simulating horseback riding
Or riding of other animals real or imagined
Or even vehicles
For example
You can indicate the gait of a horse
By gently
By gently moving forward and backward
On the cushion
To go slow
Or fast forward and backward
Rocking motions to gallop
So basically this game
Will adjust your speed based on
How fast you hump the cushion
Awesome
That seems completely useless
And not only that
But I mean really is this practical
I mean seriously
We had a problem with the Wii balance board
Only holding 300 pounds
People got pissed off
Because I'm a fatty
And I want to do Wii Fit
But I can't play it
What about riding the horse
I pop the cushion
You don't even have to be fat
To pop the cushion
Or let's say you're getting too into this game
And you're rocking back and forth
Or even you have special piercings
I can just see
This is the whole rocking back and forth
The whole thing deflates
While you're playing it
Like how sad
Is this for real
It's for real
Is this Nintendo making the patent
Or whatever this is
You know what this thing kind of looks like to me
You know those
Okay
You know at the gym they have the inflatable
Balls and they have the ones that are half
Size
Which makes me think of those with another rocking
You know thing put on it
This one also looks really um
It looks like a wacky action bike
It's not necessary
I mean seriously how many games
Are you going to play where you're riding
A horse
It's absolutely not necessary
And why the hell would they patent this
Well keep in mind though
It's a good idea to
They could patent something and not actually bring it out
But it keeps someone else from doing it
GameGuru in chat says we find out
Why it's called WooHoo Island
Great
So we're going to get WooHoo biking and WooHoo horse riding
With this thing
It's just strange
I mean why can't you
Although if this is legit
If this is a real thing that Nintendo is planning
You know you can't wait for that
Press conference when Reggie Fils-Aime
Comes out of one of these
Like
It's next year's E3 press conference
When you're just like oh my god Nintendo is seriously
Just fucking lost it this time
Like just the last two years of press conferences
Were bad but now when Reggie Fils-Aime
Comes rolling out on one of these things
You're just going to be like oh my god
This is just difficult to watch
I would love to go there and just walk out
Walk out right at that
Well that's it I'm done
I'm done
I give up
This is absolutely stupid
Can somebody please do that at E3
Somebody who's special enough to get
Invited in Nintendo's conference
Somebody who doesn't mind
Getting blacklisted a little bit
That's it I'm done
This is so stupid I'm out of here
See ya
I am done D-U-N
Done
And get up and walk out
There is no practical use for this whatsoever
It's a giant device that holds a remote
That shakes it back and forth
How difficult would it be to take this
Same horse riding game and just
Shake the remote slow to go slow
Shake it faster to go faster
Oh my god look at that I didn't have to buy
Any more peripherals
Can you imagine the size of the box
This game is going to come in if it's just this
Giant device
Well you probably have to inflate it yourself
It probably comes in a small box and
You
You have to inflate it yourself
You know what the whole talk about
The cushion thing just sort of made my brain
Shut off so I decided to look at Teriyaki Doritos
Instead
Will you stop being so random
First you want our Mega Man game to have
A butt then you say I don't
Care about inflatable Nintendo cushion
This could be the biggest joke of the year
I want Teriyaki Doritos
Really
I really want Teriyaki Doritos right now
This is going to be one of those
Shows where it's like
I'm sorry the whole concept of this
Cushion thing literally made
My brain shut off
For like a minute
And then by the time
I came back to consciousness I was looking
At Teriyaki Doritos
You know the best part about this is
I bet you the Wii remote is not sensitive enough
To sense these little rocking motions
That would be the
Punchline to the whole thing
Let's see some comments
Frisbee says
My name is Reggie I'm about kicking ass
Taking names and fucking a pillow
Boy oh boy
Gripper01 in chat says
Is this something we need to be teaching our kids
Hold on shush
Gripper01 says I'm still waiting for Excitebots to be released
In the UK Nintendo hates Europe
Well hey at least you'll have this peripheral
Possibly
So is this going to break certain girls' hymens
I mean are they going to become women
Just from playing this game
That's what I want to know
Because this game sounds
Oh my god
Just chalk that up to the list of Wii injuries
Broken lamp
Shattered television screen
Broken hymen
Just add that to the list
Oh my god Loki why did you go there
Because that's horseback riding
Hello
It was on topic
Hymen Breaker Wii 2009
Ok I think we can
Pretty much just you know
Sum it up this is a horrible idea
You know what
Is it Nintendo horrible
You know what here's the thing
It's kind of interesting
In all honesty all jokes
Aside like
To see somebody putting you know
A respectable reputable game company
Behind an inflatable pillow
That will move
You really have to wonder
Like where are they going with this
It could be interesting
I see potential modifications involving the res vibrator
I just you know
It is hard for me to be serious about this Rob
I think if anything this is a sign of hope
Because it gives me hope
That at any conference that
You know they hold from now on
I'm hoping that I see this
What's her name
That new one
What's her name Piper
Is that her name
I want her to come out on one of these
No
She autographed an Xbox supposedly
That's doing horrible things for my imagination right now
Alright
Let's move on please
To another story
And we're going to talk about
Hey other Nintendo Wii news but this one
Is actually a lot more serious I'm sorry to say
32 gigabyte SD cards
Will soon be usable in Wiis
Actually I think they already take the 32 gigabyte
Or sorry gigabyte
Yeah gigabyte cards right
They take them now but here's the thing is that
Apparently
Right now if you want
To use download content
You basically you can store it on the card but you have to
Copy it over basically to the actual
Wii console every time you want to use it
But not for much longer
Apparently pretty soon
You will be able to play your download content
Directly off of the SD cards
Which will finally justify
Nintendo's
Choice to not put a hard drive in these things
Because as you can change out the cards and so on
That's kind of cool
But apparently
There's a new IGN report
Saying that all the tricks used for both
Guitar Hero and Rock Band in the past
Leaving internal memory open is gone
Instead straight up booting off the SD card
Is available and that means easier downloads
Larger expansions and quicker
Loads when bringing in song data from the
SD card into Guitar Hero
Nintendo 5 and apparently that's the first game
And no support from Nintendo
So they just figured this out on themselves
On their own
Interesting
So
I'm curious to see if any other developers are going to use this
Other than companies that are just trying to mirror
What they're doing on the 360 and the PS3
It does piss me off though that they haven't
You know done any download content
Other than I guess Animal Crossing
But Animal Crossing you don't really actually
Buy the download content I don't think
It's kind of something that comes in the mail
Just like you get used to
It's probably already in the game anyways
I'm kind of pissed off that they aren't
Actually doing any expansions
And stuff for these new games that they're putting out
And even still like
Let's support the MP3 stuff
Before on the SD cards and then
Now with the newer games
Sorry we're not going to do that anymore
You're taking a step backwards come on
Well
I'm glad to hear that they're putting in that functionality
That really should have been there from the get go
But hey better late than never right?
So
You know ironically enough though I haven't bought really
A lot of virtual console games in a long
Long time
There's some stuff coming up later in the show
That I find interesting but
As far as you know virtual console stuff
There really hasn't been a lot lately I've been interested in
Except the Final Fantasy IV
WiiWare games
What about the WiiWare game that's
I haven't heard of this what's that?
Next quest that used to be called
Ikiran something or whatever
It's like Kid Icarus basically
Oh neat no I hadn't heard of this
They changed it because apparently
Ikiran quest or whatever it was called
Is too close to Kid Icarus and Nintendo got pissed
Interesting
When's this coming out is it already out?
No I hadn't heard of this game
I don't know that last WiiWare game I downloaded
Was so terrible that BitBoy or whatever it was called
I think I'm turned off to WiiWare games for a little while
I mean that's how awful this game was
So awful
Anyhow more gaming stories
And then release dates coming up soon
And of course the classic game of the week before we end part 8 at night
Well how about some more Wii stuff
Wii?
Wii sing actually
That is going to have a four
Player karaoke mode
As in four mics
Four people singing at one time
It says
That there's actually not
A full track list out yet
But they are working with EMI
Warner Universal and a few independent
But there are thirty
Songs available already
Pokerface, Locomotion
Delilah
There's also
Viva La Vida
You know some stuff from
That album
And then
But the big thing Rob that should make you happy
Is if there's Abba
Yes
You get four part harmony
Awesome
Yeah but I'm kind of done on the karaoke games
I mean is there really room in the marketplace right now
For yet another karaoke game
Well I would play this one though because
It wouldn't be me singing by myself
I guess it's cool that
You know cause the Wii doesn't really have
A lot of karaoke games that I know of
I think there's some overseas
Like they have a karaoke channel right
And then the Konami's karaoke revolution
Is coming out, there are new ones out on Wii
They have American Idol's on Wii
Oh do they? Well that's the same thing
Konami just lost their American Idol license
Or whatever, their new series of karaoke
Games don't have that branding on it
So I consider that the same series
Is that the only series available on Wii right now?
There's Disney Sing It
That's the other series that's available
That's got a narrow
Audience, that's not something I can
Break out at a party
Yeah
Um
Rock band
Yeah I guess you saw that
I don't know it just seems to me that the karaoke marketplace
Is kind of oversaturated right now
I mean is there really room for all these games to be doing well
From what I understand, and I could be completely wrong
But my understanding was that Lips
The Xbox 360 one was not doing that well
Lips is ugh
Which is too bad cause it's by the guys who did
Elite Beat Agents
Yet they're still doing another one though
Are they really?
I remember that
I was under the impression that Sing Star
Was actually doing better than Lips
But maybe that's just because Europe
Sing Star is the karaoke game in Europe
You know
I like Sing Star
I don't know, they have a lot of versions coming out
You actually got me to play that
Sing Star's fun, I like Sing Star
Which is weird, I wouldn't consider myself
Like oh I'm a rabid Sing Star fan
But yet I have Sing Star volume 1, volume 2
And ABBA all on PS3 and I want Sing Star Queen
I would get that
We should do another Sing Star Party
I think it'd be fun, Sing Star Party
Ok, I'll bring people
We'll have to make that happen, maybe later
I'll bring someone who's listening right now
Since I'm not going to PAX, I'm thinking Sing Star Party
This might have to happen
Let's have our own PAX
Call it O-O-O-O-O-O-O
Tampax
No, you need to
Call it Tampax
Well what time is, or when's
We got BlizzCon this year
It's right before PAX, right?
This next weekend is BlizzCon
Well, you could just become part of
The second annual QQCon
Ah, QQCon, I like this idea
That's right, I remember QQCon last year
But this year I'm not sad
That I'm not going to BlizzCon
Because I'm over WoW now
And WoW got spoiled anyways, we're going to get to it a little bit later
You know what, it just occurred to me
We could actually rent
Like
Like an office room or something
And have just
Systems set up and just do O-L-R-Con
First year O-L-R-Con
Just some little office
That's how they start
I guess that's true
Airport Hilton
No, we used to do
Actually, we used to have
Ground Zero Con in Mobile
And they held it at college
In the student center
I like Frisbee's idea, PAX in the back yard
PAX yard
Nice
We haven't had it, remember we used to do
The old Baymani parties way back when
That should be the same thing, just be
Gamer nerd syndrome party
NerdCon at my house, dude, I've got pinball
I wonder how much it would cost
Her in a small space just for the day
Oh, look into this
You should, you've got time off because of your hand right now
You need to find us a place to have a con
Quick poll of chat
Who would come to O-L-R-Con?
Y or N
You would check out for O-L-R-Con
And your response must be either a Y or an N
Spelled out W-H-Y
Or E-N
Like I said in random today
Alright
We might have to make that happen
Anyhow, let's get to some release dates
While we ponder the idea of an O-L-R-Con
We can host it at an Olive Garden
They can cater
Catered by Olive Garden
You know what, fuck that
I cook better than Olive Garden
I will cook
What about doing one of those really
No offense to
SacAnime, but remember how they used to have
SacAnime at Sunrise Mall
You know, the really ghetto mall that we have around here
Wouldn't it be funny to do O-L-R-Con
At Sunrise Mall
At the mall?
With the one room that they have that's
They had movies playing at
A closed down
McDonald's
I remember that
That was the strangest
AnimeCon I'd ever seen in my life
Was the one that was at the mall
Where the closed stores served as screening rooms
And then you'd just see random people in costumes
Throughout the mall
Meanwhile there's people trying to go to Macy's
You know, it's just so strange
It's the most awkward thing I've ever seen
In my life
Alright, anyhow
Anyways, this week
Not a whole lot coming out
There are some pretty good games, but it's still
Kind of that slow part of the summer
This week on DS Core
Game from Graffiti
It's a first person shooter
It's been delayed forever
But finally making its way out
Still Life 2 on PC
Coming out this week as well
My friends on
DS
Because
Apparently if you play this game you have no friends
So you need
Your friends on the DS
War Leaders, Clash of Nations
On PC this week
Sudoku Ball Detective
Yes, it's a
Game that you solve detective
Mysteries by playing games of
Sudoku
Awesome
My Makeup
A game for girls
Delta Force Extreme 2
They have that coming out
As well as Plants vs. Zombies
The packaged version
Is making its way out this week as well
Wolfenstein
On PC, Xbox 360, and PS3
Coming out this week
Spectrobes Origins
Pretty good
Roleplaying game
From Disney Interactive
Making its way out to the Wii this week
My Dress Up also goes with
The My Makeup thing
Also for girls
ATV Quad Kings from Zoo
Games
That's the most generic ATV off-road racing
Game I've ever seen
Joint Operations
Combined Arms
Coming out on PC this week
And that is it
Let me move on to
Japan in Japanese
Release dates
About the My Makeup thing
Could also be for the occasional
Cross-dresser
I guess
Don't say something is just for girls
Because some boys might be into that
My character in Ion looks like a drag queen
Your character in Ion has a fan
She has a fan, how amazing is that
I do have to mention this because I think it is
On Steam, but it's an awesome name
For a game
Pizza Morgana, Monsters and Manipulations
In the Magical Forest
Pizza Morgana
It's an adventure game
That's kind of a gothic
Hot topic looking type thing
Interesting
Games coming out in Japan, not a lot
There is nothing new on the
Playstation 3 or the Xbox 360
There is a new game coming out on the 20th
On Playstation 2, it's called Melty Blood
Actress Again
Yes, that is really the name of it
Melty Blood Actress Again
It's a fighting game
Bringing a whole new level to the 2D fighting world
Three different fighting styles
A larger moveset and new characters
I guess this is continuing
In the Melty Blood series
Is that an anime or something?
Or is this just a video game series I've never heard of
L2 Love Cross Loop
Is also a game coming out of Japan on the
Playstation 2 this week
On the Nintendo DS
Live Battle Card
Is the only new release this week
It's a very slow release week over in Japan
There is on the Sony PSP
Heart no Kunen no Alice
Comes out, as well as
Ukame Kakushi comes out from
Konami this week
I'm trying to see what kind of game this is
But it doesn't look like any of their series
It just looks like
It's O-O-K-A-M-I
Is what it is
So I'm not sure what series
I think that's a new one
Great God something says Dark Sakura
It's a big sight
Exactly
For something like that actually that would be something
I'd have to see the kanji for because I should know
Both of those kanji, aha
Well there you go that's really all there is in
Japan this week
For our
For our buddies in the UK actually
We've got a number of releases
If you've been able to ignore Madden
That game
Has touched my life because Dan
Had to go for a minute opening
On the 19th we have Shadow Complex
On Xbox 360
Did you make a yay?
No I said how do you share me?
The cat's hanging around
She's about to be dinner in a moment
On the 20th Tales of Monkey Island
The Siege of Spinner City
And the 21st DJ Star
And Raven Squad
Supercar Challenge and then Wolfenstein
Oh it's a Dworkenstein
Anyway
That's it
Alright well there's a new patent
Submitted by Sony
Apparently it's a device
Or
A program to
Interpret whether you
Or different emotions that you are feeling
While playing I guess the PS3
One example
That they show is laughter
Which apparently they have this
Really weird looking guy laughing at a
Video of somebody
Kicking themselves in the ass with a machine
That they're powering with their own
Hands
Will it sense boredom?
Yes
Well apparently
They make that joke too
Actually they're saying that
Not necessarily sure what it would do
But it would be able to sense laughter
As well as other emotions
Sadness, excitement, anger, joy, interest
And boredom
They say perhaps if the game detects boredom
They have enemies on screen, if it detects anger
The difficulty can go down and finally
If it detects sadness
And they're punchline to the joke
It will tell you just to stop playing
Lair
I'm wondering though if it's gonna
Detect me laughing when they make an announcement
About like some new PS3 system or something
Like that that's gonna be more expensive than the
Previous one just like the PSP Go
Because that would be hilarious
So yeah you think I'm gonna buy that?
Nope
You know um this peripheral
Should go with the Nintendo one
Like they needed to combine their forces so that
It can sense me giggling when I'm riding
The inflatable
Wii sack or whatever it's called
The Wii sack
I like that
That'll be the name
Alright then it's called the Wii sack until we get a
Real name for it
That seems kind of a
Dumb technology because like
All I had to do was act angry
Or something like
Grrr I'm angry
You know and the game gets easier
I don't know
What if it doesn't tell you
That this is in the game
Like it's just something that is kind of there
People will find out
They have ways of finding out
It's probably something that they're not really gonna use
But they wanna you know
In case PS3
Wants to do a Milo you know
Something like that
They can detect laughter and all what not
Something so they have the technology
Before Microsoft does maybe?
Yeah something so they can say hey we patented
That we sue you now
Hmm
Well I don't know
It could be
Interesting but I really would have to see
The application of how this is used
Like I'm into this a lot
More than I am the Wii sack
But this is
You know it could be hokey
It could be kind of neat you know I like the idea
Of a game you know because you all know those
People that get so angry when they're playing the games
Not that there's anyone in this room like that Loki
That they're throwing controllers on the ground
I never throw controllers
I never throw controllers because controllers
Are expensive and there's no reason to get pissed off
But you get angry you do get very angry
When playing games no come on
I've heard you do that
Well okay if I was playing Grand Theft Auto
Or something like that and the game
Glitches out on me or something like that
Like uh
You know I fire six sniper rounds
The game retarded
I fire six sniper rounds into the back of someone's
Head and then they're like oh hey someone's
Shooting at me and they turn around and fire a pistol
And kill me and they're like come on
My favorite is when Loki will go
And then the game's all like I don't know what I'm doing
What the fuck
Exactly because it's retarded
My favorite is when Loki impersonates
The game
I do that to people too
It's fun all around
Alright something that is
Gonna be impersonated all over again
Blizzard for
WoW's fifth anniversary
Onyxia is making a return
Y'all Onyxia was a level
60 raid of course in old school
Warcraft where 40 of you would
Fight the dragon Onyxia once
And now it's kind of a bit of a joke like people
Will go run the Onyxia thing because you can totally
Solo Onyxia now or at least
Duo it
Very easy and kind of take her
Down and do that whole quest where you get the
Onyxia's head in the middle of Orgrimmar
Or whatever it is that you're at
So they're gonna go back
For the fifth anniversary and basically
Redo Onyxia's lair and the Onyxia
Boss as a 10 man
And heroic 25 man as all
The raids in WoW are now long gone
Are the days of the 40 man dungeons
Apparently there's gonna be loot
And the cool thing about the loot if you're a WoW player
Is that she's gonna drop
The same stuff she did before
But it's all been
Scaled to level 80 gear
So meaning that like the
Stats that was on the
Gear before was for 60 they're scaling it up to
80 so it's like you can have tier 2
Gear that's just as cool as some of the gear they
Have now that's pretty cool
Also there's gonna be a
310% speed flying mount
Modeled after Onyxia that's gonna be
A rare drop so that'll be something
A lot of folks are after
Hopefully it's not glitched out like the dragon was at one time
During Final Fantasy 11
Where you couldn't kill the dragon
Remember that?
Oh yeah I heard about that
That was after we were playing but yeah I remember hearing about that
No no it was while we were playing
But it was hilarious
Also some WoW news this week
Of course Blizzcon's coming up this next weekend
And some details have apparently
Been leaked about what they are gonna be talking about
At Blizzcon. Cataclysm is supposedly
The name of the new WoW expansion
I don't even know if the name's been confirmed yet
It's a registered trademark from them now
Alright well anyway
So despite the name possibly getting out
Apparently some of the information about the game
Has leaked out too
You will be able to go to 85
In this new expansion
Which is different because usually
WoW has been doing the 10 level increments
Burning Crusade lets you go to 10
Or sorry lets you go to 70
Which was 10 up from 60
Wrath of the Lich King lets you go up to 80
And now you can go up to 85
In Cataclysm
Also the other interesting thing about Cataclysm
It's not really a new world
They're not launching a new world
There's no Outlands or Northrend type thing
No what this is gonna be is improvements
To the old world
Which is kind of interesting because
I don't know how they're gonna be able to do that
Yeah isn't that something everybody benefits from
Because that's a big thing that WoW does now
Is the whole phasing element
So maybe you can only get phased if you have the Cataclysm expansion
Otherwise you're stuck in the old WoW
I don't know
I don't know what they're doing with this
Also some new races are rumored for the game
Worgen will be the new Alliance class
And Goblins will be the new Horde class
And the other interesting thing
Is that some new job
Race combinations are opening up
For instance now you can be a Tauren Paladin
Or Troll Druid
That's a big one because Druids you had to be
Tauren or Night Elf to be
But apparently now Trolls can be Druids too
And assumably Worgens
Since nothing else on the Alliance side opened up for Druids
So interesting
You'll be able to fly in some parts of old world now too
Which was a thing that was being requested
I don't know though
For me honestly as somebody who recently left
WoW this isn't really
Cool enough sounding for me to want to go back
I have to be honest
The improvements sound neat and sound needed
But I'm not seeing anything where I'm like
Oh damn
Well I'm sure that's not all the details about it
True
They usually put a little more effort into their expansions
I would think a new heroic job class would be in there too
Like Death Knight
Like I was hoping for the next heroic class would be cool
I'm sure there's
I don't know
It'd be interesting
It could all be speculation too
It could be like one of those you know
Culmination of all the rumors that are on there
The new name of the expansion
Because of the registered trademark
The rumor of the new classes
Based on the Halloween masks
That appeared or whatever
And some other crap
You know I'm
I don't know
We'll find out next week I guess
I mean seriously
We'll find out in a week
But all of it sounds plausible
I mean nothing that's being announced sounds unplausible
But I think the new race job combinations
That's going to be very interesting
Alright let's get into a segment here we like to do on
Orange Lawns Radio called the classic video game
Of the week
It's a moment where we take a minute to reflect back on
Games history and
Dark Sakura likes to take a trip to the vault
And find a game that she thinks you know what you guys
Ought to be playing this game this week
So Dark Sakura
What is the classic video game
Of the week?
I'm going for another series this time Rob
How dare you?
Sorry we can't get the music volume down
There we go
Raiden you say?
Alright let's cue up some music from Raiden here
Well
Basically yeah this one goes through the whole PlayStation screen
Launch up thing sorry
But basically for anyone who doesn't know
Raiden is
A scrolling shooter
It's put out by Seibu Kairatsu
And it was
In the arcades
And I think we got it by Fabtech
Over here in the states
Also supposed to be
Kind of hard to emulate because of
The way that they changed the game boards
For them
But it came out
On PlayStation as the
Raiden project
Well at least Raiden 1 and 2 did
And then we got
It came out on Amiga, Atari Jaguar
The TurboGrafx
It came out on the duo
As Super Raiden
Atari Lynx, Super Nintendo
Came out for PC, Genesis
And there's actually a mobile phone version too
Seibu Kairatsu did
All of the ones that came out
Until 98 and then
Moss Limited did the games
That came out since 2005
And the games since 2005 also came out
On the Taito Type X boards
Which were supposed to be
They were pretty hard to duplicate the emulation for
So anyway
The world was taken over by aliens
And the world says screw you aliens
And fights back, that's the story
So you also had
You could play one player
Or have two players and play together
You also had a variety of different weapons
You know
That you would get through different power ups
My favorite being the little electric
Thingy weapon which
In fact it's on the screen right now in the example
Showing where you would fire this
Continuous stream of energy that would
Lock on to
Certain enemies and then wrap around them
And you know
Pull towards them, it's kind of like how
You know those electric globe
Things where you put your hand on it
And all the energy goes to where your hand is
That's my favorite weapon in the game
And the games that came out in the series were
Raiden, Raiden 2, Raiden DX
Raiden 3, and Raiden 4. Raiden DX
Of those is probably my favorite
There were also spin off games
That were
I'm sure
Actually we talked about them
Recently
When I was going over my
Gaming week
It was Viper Phase 1
Raiden Fighters, Raiden Fighters 2, and Raiden Fighters Jet
So
Big, big, big, big, big
Big, big, big series of games
And
It's actually probably one of
My favorite shooters to this date
It's also
It can get pretty hard
Because you get a lot of
Bullets and a lot of enemies on the screen
And they're big and
It's just a lot of fun
Definitely a lot of fun
Plus the music is great
I'll turn it up here a little bit
I think the clip that I gave you
Is actually from Raiden Project
I have a story about Raiden Project
What's that?
I remember being completely
Intoxicated on Everclear
And beating this game
Nice
That was the same night that I ended up having so much
Everclear how close I needed
I was 19
No, I take that back, I was 20
You say that proudly
Yeah, I was 20
Alright, well there you have it folks
Your classic game of the week
Raiden, the whole dang series
Because Dark Soccer said the series
So that's what you get
Alright, well thank you very much Dark Soccer
We'll look forward to see what you pick for us next week
But in the meantime we're going to take a quick break
We're going to do some Twitter and so forth
But we have plenty more show to come
When we come back from a break
Twitter topics
Something new we're trying tonight
We've been trying to incorporate Twitter into the show for a long time now
So we're going to do some Twitter topics when we come back
Rapid fire news and some more discussions
Including Silent Hill
A chance for you to go visit
Like real Silent Hill
Not really, but as close as it's going to get
We're going to talk about that
And it sounds kind of cool
So stay tuned
And welcome back everybody
To more of Orange Lounge Radio
Here on this lovely Sunday evening
August the 16th of 2009
Where we are taping live
Our what, 334th
Episode of Orange Lounge Radio
Slightly more than half evil
Yes, it just keeps on going
And no signs of quitting anytime soon
We're coming back this segment
We're going to get into some Twitter topics here shortly
And if you wanted to submit a topic
You could do that earlier
By joining our Twitter
You can't send it now, it's too late
Because we already have picked what we want to talk about tonight
But if you want to do that for future weeks
You can send those to us at OLR on Twitter
And if you're not following us on Twitter yet
Why not? You should be there
I wanted to mention one game
I didn't mention it during my gaming week
Because it wasn't really my gaming week
And not a game I've been playing
Non-stop
Just been obsessed with it
I think he's racked up like 15-16 hours
Just this week alone
It's an iPhone game, believe it or not
And the iPhone game is called
Zenonia is the name of the game
Z-E-N-O-N-I-A
And it's a game I probably need to look at and check out
I guess there's a free demo available out there
But if you want to play more than a certain amount of time
You have to pay money for it
But I guess it's like a
The best way I can describe it from what I saw
Is a style game
Kind of like the role playing game
But more of the action style
Like Secret of Mana is
With the multiple quests going on at once
Like WoW has
And I guess you can be good or evil in the game
John was trying to tell me a little bit about the game
I thought it was interesting enough to give a mention here on the show
Because iPhones have some pretty interesting games on it
Some of the games I didn't even mention
That I played this week were on the iPhone
There's a new Space Invaders game on the iPhone
That I checked out that's kind of interesting
Because you can use your own music collection in some of the stages
And there's also Civilization Revolution got a release on the iPhone this week
Which is a pretty neat port I got to say
I didn't play it a whole lot
So I don't want to give it a full review
But I was fairly impressed with the port of the game I must say
I played Peggle
Did you play Peggle? Good times on the iPhone
It's not bad on the iPhone
It's the only version of it I have
Good stuff
Alright let's get into some Twitter topics
Tell us some things you want us to talk about tonight
Deathwishing says
Starcraft 2 petition has over 100k signatures
For LAN support
Discuss that
Remember we were talking about
Was this the one where we said people need to get over it?
I don't think it was this actually though
I think it was something else
I would think because LAN is a big part of Starcraft
I know how they have tournaments
It's really huge over in Asia
And the regions over there
But it's just
I don't know why they would
I think the reason why they want to take out
LAN because
One, piracy
Because they want all their online play
Or all the multiplayer to go through
I want to say BattleNet
Yeah BattleNet
But
I always thought it was for statistical purposes
They want to
Log every game that's played by folks
And keep track of statistics and so forth
But yeah piracy is a nice little bonus
Basically piracy is what it is
I mean it makes sense because
You're making these people buy
Three different versions of the same damn game
Because you're just saying
Oh well
The campaigns are separate
When any other RTS
Game out there
Command and Conquer
How even the original Starcraft had all the campaigns
Right there from the get go
It's kind of a little bit
I don't know milking it a bit
So yeah I can see how
Some people might be a little pissed off by that
And you know what
And I'm just going to say this now because
We're going to be reporting on it later on I'm sure
They're going to crack this
It's going to happen
People want to play this in LAN
And you know what's going to happen
Is they're just going to tunnel it just like they do with the PSP
And the Wii or the Gamecube and all that stuff
You know warp pipe was mentioned earlier
But they're just going to find a way to tunnel this
With some third party software
Why don't we just give them
The benefit of the doubt right now that
It'll be secure for about a week and then
It'll be broken again
Actdeftinchat says online petitions
Never work for a few exceptions
And you know that's kind of true too
If you want to, if you really want to make a statement
Guys, put your money where your mouth is
Don't buy the game when it comes out
Because if there's 100,000 people
That dent in their first week sales
Of the game, that'll be heard loud and clear
But this online petition
That can be swept under the rug
At the end of the day, do you still buy the game?
If yes, then
They had no reason to put it back in
You need to send physical mail instead of like
You know, just a petition
You send a letter
Because 100,000 letters
Look a lot better than 100,000 emails
And definitely a lot better than 100,000 signatures
Or do both
Do all three
Surtur, I might be saying that wrong
Or Surtur, Surtur, S-U-R-T-U-R
On Twitter says please discuss the PS3 slim
I'd like to get a PS3 but they're too expensive
I assume the slim will be cheaper or there'll be a price cut
What is this slim that you're talking about
There's no slim, they denied it
Denied, denied, denied
You know what's interesting though
Surtur, if I'm saying your name right
Just because, you know, we've made that assumption before
That just because they are remaking the system
Means it's going to be cheaper
Not true, look at the PSP
See they're going to be cheaper, I guarantee it's not gonna be cheaper
It's not gonna be cheaper
This is their MO
They basically take the console or whatever
They drop the price of the old system
Which is something that we're starting to see a little bit
And then
They basically release the new system at the same price the old system was
I would hope that they would drop the price of the system
Because I think it would be something that is in their best interest
Because their sales are hurting
And they're definitely not getting better anytime soon
And yeah, the slim PS3 might be appealing to some people, because hey, it's new, it looks different, it's nicer looking, we're assuming.
And whatnot, maybe some backwards compatibility is added in. I think that's kind of wishful thinking there, but we'll have to see.
They're going to announce it next week, I'm sure, at Gamescom. It's going to happen. I mean, that's the rumors right now, and they're definitely prepping for it.
And between the birds and you guys, I guess, it's definitely happening. I mean, it's just a matter of time whenever they decide to announce it.
Gripper01 in chat says, the PS2 Slim was more expensive than the Fat. Was it? I think I remember a comment earlier, though, he's overseas, so maybe it could be different from region to region.
I don't think it was more expensive. I think it was probably the same price, if not cheaper. But hey, that seems to be the trend nowadays. Let's release a new system with less features for more money.
And Frisbee says, this tiny enemy crab... I like that. Funny.
It's a matter of time. It's just a waiting game until they announce it, and no one's going to be surprised by it. If I were Sony right now, I'd be probably pissed off, because they can't fucking keep a secret for anything.
They really... I mean, even though it kind of hurts our business a bit with the moles and everything, they really need to root out those moles if they want to keep some secrets.
What you need to do, not that I endorse this in any manner, what you need to do is you tell one person something different, and you see what gets reported, and then you know who your mole is.
Dr. Noir says, free tracks for Guitar Hero World Tour, and then gives us a link to an article that talks about new Guitar Hero World Tour tracks that are coming out. Apparently there's an Activision track pack that came out.
Apparently it is... folks that work for Activision, they're bands, so you get these bands Awaken, H is Orange, and 100 Reasons, and these songs that... hey, they're free!
It's very hard to complain about free things, but I would probably... I don't own Guitar Hero World Tour. I would probably get to Guitar Hero 5, though.
Free tracks are good, I mean...
It's hard to complain about free tracks, but honestly, very rarely would I probably play them. I mean, I look at the Rock Band tracks, very few of those do I play.
But at the same time, there's one or two that I do enjoy, and considering they were free, you know, and I had to sift through 20 to find one or two that I like, it's still free, you know, so it's very hard to complain about free things.
You can download it, and guess what, if you don't like it, you can always delete it later.
Yes you can.
And it's free.
So when do those come out? Those are coming out this week? Yeah, today, or they just came out this past week.
So check that out in the Guitar Hero World Tour store right now.
If you want to send us a topic to talk about on Twitter, we'll open up Twitter topics next week, just a little bit before the show, but probably if we already are covering your topic somewhere else in the show, sadly you probably didn't make it tonight, but always try again next week.
Let's do some rapid fire news quickly. We don't want to talk about this news a long time, but we want to get it across anyway. So Loki, how about some rapid fire news?
So this is a total shock, but apparently Activision is offering Guitar Hero 5, and then if you buy Guitar Hero 5, you get Guitar Hero Van Halen free.
Totally new news to me, but yeah, so that is the offer. It's all through the month of September, and basically you purchase your game. There's apparently codes in the back of the manual.
I think that's the way it was with World Tour as well, and there's some other stuff that goes along with that.
But using those codes, you enter them in online to prove that you've purchased the game, and then you can get your free copy of Guitar Hero Van Halen. Not only will you get it free, you will get it weeks early, because it takes six weeks to ship to you, and the game doesn't come out until December 22nd.
Which I gotta imagine their sales on that game are going to be crap, unless they're going to count the free copies of the sale.
I am totally surprised and shocked by this news.
I am shocked. It's like a hypothetical situation come true. It's just so weird.
There you go.
Some other interesting stuff. Also rumors, of course, that the Elite is going to be getting a price cut at the end of this month, and apparently this is coming from a leak of a Myers catalog.
Good, because I know someone who needs a new 360.
It's a catalog that's going to be hitting stands on August 30th. It shows that the Elite model has a new price of $299.
And of course, that kind of goes along with the whole rumor that the Pro system is going away, because on the new arcades, the box art only shows the arcade and Elite systems.
No Pro system to be found at all, so the rumor is that that SKU is going away and is being replaced by the Elite system for $299.
Makes sense to me. Probably will happen. Might even get announced next week, so wouldn't be a big surprise.
And then, last but not least, there is another rumor that white and pink DSIs are coming to America.
And apparently these were found in a Toys R Us database, listing both color schemes.
I don't know, that sounds totally false to me. I don't believe that that's ever going to happen, especially not in September.
Okay, fine. Some rapid fire news I've got for you guys.
Hey DDR fans, there's finally a point to those USB slots in the DDRX machines.
That's right, Konami this week opened up the new DDR Edit website. It's DDREdit.KonamiOnline.com.
You can actually go in there and open up a little editor and make your own steps to various songs in the game, except not all of them.
I actually went in there and played with it a little bit. It looks like there's only about seven or eight songs you can edit, at least right now.
Maybe they're doing it in waves or what have you, but you use this little, it's all a web tool.
It's not something you download. It's all online in Flash or whatever, and it runs horribly, at least on my computer it did.
It was all out of sync and everything.
I miss the days of edit mode and doing hell edits.
I miss that too. We would actually get the Japanese games that you could edit the songs and take them into the arcade because it all matched up.
Yeah.
Fun times.
Or we'd edit hack them to add freeze arrows to songs that didn't have freeze arrows.
That's right, I remember that.
Yeah, fun times.
Fun times.
I remember you giving away the boxes of movies.
That's right, it was make edit, get porn.
Yes.
Good times.
Epic times.
Whatever happened to that kid that won? Dave, remember him? Whatever happened to him?
He became a man that day.
Did he?
Well, I got the box full of anime and stuff that one time, which eventually went back to, which went to Dimple.
Funny.
Hey, live at QuakeCon 2009 has been spotted some new games on Xbox Live Arcade.
Doom 2 has been spotted out there on the show floor apparently.
And Quake Live, both for Xbox 360's arcade, were both apparently out there on a floor, on the floor.
I guess, let me actually clarify, I guess only Doom 2 was out there actually playable on the floor,
but somebody actually had like a shirt that said Quake Arena Arcade or what have you, and they've got some pictures and so forth.
Lies! They're all lies!
I don't believe it, one second.
I don't know, I just had to be the counterpoint to that.
There's somebody, there's like a picture of somebody playing Doom 2 on Xbox with an Xbox controller.
It's photoshopped, it's a lie.
Shut up.
Lastly from me tonight, there's a brand new game coming out for an old system, and the old system, the Atari Lynx.
What? I have one of those.
There's a new game called Zaku coming out for the Atari Lynx.
Yes, it is named after one of OLR's infamous callers is getting his own game on the Atari Lynx.
I'm getting this.
It's the same people that brought you, do you remember Baker Prince that came out on the Genesis in 2006?
Kind of.
The Legend of Wukong also.
Now those are actually like localized games from Taiwan that I guess just came out or whatever,
but this is something I guess that was built on the development kit for the Atari Lynx on an Amiga, of all things,
and is actually coming out and supposedly has pretty kick butt graphics for a Lynx, that is.
It's too other than not bringing it out in other systems because, I don't know, I don't have a Lynx simulator.
I have a Lynx, but I just don't...
Are they actually doing a cartridge for it?
That's what the plan is, it looks like.
I think I might have to pick this up.
They did one for Baker Prince, I know, and they charged a lot of money for it.
This looks like a lot of fun.
Those carts were expensive.
Well here's an idea of what it's all about.
It's a horizontal shooter and it is a hero who dons her rocket shoes and power gloves
and sets off on a journey to retrieve stolen development tools being used to flood the market with bad games.
There you go.
I'm actually signing it for the mailing list right now.
Sounds like a cause that you can believe in.
Well DarkSakura, don't sign up for the mailing list just yet because you have to give us some rapid fire news.
Do I? Well crap, okay.
Well here's some news.
I really like corn chips. No, for real.
The actual news, there is an addition to the PAL PSN updates.
They're getting Marvel vs. Capcom 2, which will be 11.99 euro, 14.99 pound.
It has a free trial.
And also are getting Call of Juarez Bound in Blood demo and more content for Red Faction Guerrilla.
Also, Rock Band Unplugged is getting some Iron Maiden songs.
The Trooper and Number of the Beast for 99 pounds of pop.
So that's pretty good.
And also there's stuff for NHL 10 and Little Big Planet, blah blah blah.
Oh, and one last thing.
For that one, Fat Princess is getting a connectivity patch.
Moving forward, Tecmo is getting a few games on the Virtual Console.
Ninja Gaiden and Rygar are to be coming out.
Also, I think they were talking about, Tecmo Bowl already did come out.
I really like Ninja Gaiden, but also Solomon's Key is being added to that too.
I like the old school arcade Rygar. That was an awesome game.
Also, this makes me a very very very infinity happy girl, is Loom.
There's news about Loom.
Telltale is talking about considering doing another Loom game.
Which I will be all over happy happy happy if that actually happens.
It was actually said that the game itself was about two and a half hours long.
And that they're trying to do two and a half hour long games and Loom fits quite well with that little strategy.
I like Loom. I have Loom. I should actually start playing it.
Loom is cool. I'd be down with a Loom remake.
There's definitely a lot of nostalgia behind that.
Alright, let's get back into some discussion topics tonight.
Yes, apparently there's a new deal.
This is coming from the Raven software designer Manveer Har, who has tweeted that apparently he's going to offer to reimburse you for your copy of Wolfenstein.
If you purchase Wolfenstein, obviously. Keep your receipt.
If, and this is the big ifs, if they beat out Madden 10 in this month in NPD sales.
Ha!
So the offer only applies to sales in August. The NPD figures will be used to calculate the totals.
You have to follow the guy on Twitter.
And in case you really wanted to do that, his name is Manveer Har is his Twitter name.
And limit one copy per person.
Let me go ahead and restate that again.
Ha!
I mean, no disrespect, but come on. Madden 10 is like, you know, it's not the type of game we usually talk about here on this show.
But I can clearly recognize the impact that that game has on, you know,
I have co-workers who came into work dead tired on Friday.
Like, I have students in my class who came in dead tired on Friday.
And I'm like, what's going on? What gives?
And they're like, oh, Madden came out yesterday.
And I'm like, I should know that.
Like, I do a video game show on the internet.
I don't like to tell my students that because I don't want their teacher, you know, them to download and hear their teacher saying fuck on the internet.
But, you know, I just, I'm thinking in the back of my mind like, oh, duh, you should kind of know that.
But Madden 10 is a huge game.
That's the point I'm trying to make. It's a landmark event game.
Well, your husband probably had to work like till 3 a.m. that day, huh?
I am so confident this will never happen that will this apply to the Tingle thing as well?
What? You just extended the Tingle bet?
No, no, no, no, no. It's a different bet.
It's a different bet altogether.
Hold on, hold on. Hit record, everybody. Hit record. Here we go.
Not only will he give you free copies of Wolfenstein, I will dress up like Tingle playing Madden. Or Wolfenstein, I guess, that would be appropriate.
But it's never gonna happen. Never.
Tingle with the gun, speaking German.
So, if, I just want to clarify the terms of the bet, just in case, because you never know what might happen.
So if Wolfenstein, the new Wolfenstein, should outsell Madden in the first month of release, you'll dress up as Tingle here on the show.
If this gentleman has to reimburse all his customers, you too will dress up like Tingle here on the show.
Alright, but not, you will not set fire and Bobby Black will fire a judgement on it.
No, that's just, that's a judgement, because...
But instead, you will play Wolfenstein.
Yes, and this isn't like we're adding the numbers of Wolfenstein to the millionth. No, that is not gonna happen.
Completely different bet, and you all wanted, you all wanted something to come back.
You all wanted something where Loki would be willing to dress up as Tingle again, so here it is.
It's not gonna happen. I only make bets that I'm confident in that I'm gonna win, so...
I mean, come on. Really? Something's gonna outsell Madden?
I know, from selling Madden, that that's not gonna fucking happen, so...
But hey, let's hope for the wishful thinking there.
Hey, and the guys behind Wolfenstein thank you, because you just upped their sales by, you know, how many people listen to the show?
Two.
Oh yeah, two. There you go.
I mean, anyone with the same mind knows that there's no way, it's just like him, he knows there's no way that's gonna happen, but hey, it makes him look nice.
So there you go, you're just nice. You're offering the Tingle thing again.
One of these days, man, you know, some day this show is gonna have to end. Some day.
And I hope before it's over we get you in a Tingle costume one way or another.
Nope, never gonna happen. Had to lose a bet, and unfortunately, uh...
My judgement's not selling.
Alright, anyhow, we're being made anymore.
Let's move on to something else. Hey, maybe Loki could dress up as this. This is a little more manly. He could dress up as Pyramid Head or something out of Silent Hill.
Uh, hey, Silent Hill, actually we'll have a lot of people dressing up in the name of Silent Hill.
Apparently there's going to be an actual Silent Hill haunted house, or as they're calling it, a haunted attraction coming to South California, Southern California.
Orange County, to be specific. The OC is going to be getting this Silent Hill haunted house.
And, uh, yeah, I'm guessing that it's actually going to be like a haunted house that you walk through.
Apparently they did like a Saw one last year that was really scary based off the movie Saw, which, you know, you already know how we feel about that.
But Silent Hill's cool. So, you know, they'll have probably people dressed up like the nurses, and they'll probably have a giant Pyramid Head.
Like, you could get raped by Pyramid Head IRL. That would be awesome. Sadly, this haunted house or whatever probably isn't going to be that awesome, but whatever.
It might still be worth a look, especially if you're in the area. Hey, if you're in Southern California, you should probably go check this out.
Although it does sound like it's going to be a little bit pricey. I think I was looking at the website, and it was something like 20-something bucks. I don't remember. It was kind of expensive.
That's about normal for, like, a haunted house. Like, the last haunted house we went to, which was... I'm going to bring up the site. It might make music, guys, because I think it makes music. Sorry, guys.
Oh, by the way, it's also the slowest loading site. Oh, that was weird. Ooh, it makes Silent Hill music. Ooh. Yeah, there's two mazes, and the other one's called Fear.
This looks scary, Jamie. Are you sure you want to go? Not to Silent Hill. Single admission, $13.
God, we are doing this. So, anyway, sorry. Sorry for the Silent Hill music, but it gives you a little ambience there.
That would be fun, actually, to go down there and go to the haunted house and go to Disneyland. I think we might have to make that happen.
I had a Saw attraction one time. That was pretty cool. Yeah, that was a year ago, right? Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm not into Saw. You already know how I feel about Saw. Torture porn. Silent Hill, cool. Saw, torture porn.
Saw is too hard to figure out what's going on nowadays. It's like trying to figure out what's going on in Crank 2.
It's a twist. And... Tigerclaw says if you guys go, you will need to record it on video. They won't let you.
They probably won't let us in there with a video camera. Plus, I don't need... Hat cam!
I don't need me screaming like a girl out there on YouTube, because Jamie will be able to testify to this after.
Maybe she already can. I don't know. But I will scream like a girl in this attraction the minute I see something that is scary.
You want to know how I won't be scared? How you can tell if I won't be scared? Huh. Because I won't be saying anything.
You've been in scary situations with me, and you know what I do. I shut up. And I'm really quiet.
I will scream obscenities, even if there are children around. My voice will get even higher than it's ever gotten on the radio.
Yes, it will. Yeah, you've seen me on rides. Yes.
You should just put a mic or turn on your phone to record just the audio, because that would be hilarious.
We're getting requests from chatters wanting us to pick them up on the way to the haunted house.
We should just tell people when we're going, and then we'll have like, we'll all go in together.
It'll be a big, because I know like, Jimmy, who used to do the show, what the hell was the show he did with John?
STFU. That was the show they did. The one that's based off that sports show.
He lives in OC. Like, they live in that area, so I know he would come.
We should get a whole bunch of us to go, and I'll meet up, and then you can all hear me scream like a girl in person, laugh, ha ha ha.
And then we could at least film before and after. And then I'll be like, white as a ghost, and so forth.
Ospher in chat says, Rob, reciprocate that high voice, please.
I'm not going to do that here on the radio. I can't. Like, I legitimately cannot do the screaming like a little girl obscenities.
I'm going to do my imitation of scared Rob.
Oh, God.
Okay, let me take a breath. Get in character. Oh, my God.
When have I ever said, oh, my God, y'all.
You do that when you're teasing.
Oh, my God.
You do that when you tease people.
Fine.
Oh, my God. That's Rob, by the way.
He's pretty close, a little higher. Needs more swearing. Needs more swearing.
Well, I, you know, wasn't going to, but that's Rob. And, yeah, it is high enough to break glass.
You know who else lives in L.A. that we should challenge to come to this with us?
Uh-oh.
Is our friends from All Games Interactive.
Oh.
Yeah, that's what we need to do. We need to get Lawrence. We need to get Scott.
We need to get Jessica and all of them to come with us.
And we should have, like, a scare off or something.
Becky says she'll come with us.
I'm, oh, this needs to happen now. This needs to happen.
Is anybody from All Games Interactive listening? Let's throw down. Let's have a scare off.
I don't know how a scare off works.
You should have to hold a glass of water. And if you spill the glass of water.
I want to know why Oscar's thanking me.
I like this idea. I really like this idea.
Have to hold something that shows, or, like, hook something up to our body. The Wii Vitality Sensor.
Too bad it won't be out in time.
God damn it. Just when I found a use for the Wii Vitality Sensor to see who gets more scared here, me or Jessica, right?
The damn thing isn't going to be out in time.
Too bad they don't have...
I want to do it very drunk, Rob.
Do they have, like, a portable heart rate monitor or something like that?
Yeah. They make those.
Do they?
Or, actually, the iPhone has an app that's a heart rate monitor where you just tap in time with your heartbeat.
No, that wouldn't work.
Yeah.
I'm afraid...
Actual heart rate monitor is, like, 69 bucks a piece.
I'm afraid that I will be trying to contain my scary...
Like, I'll be trying to fight it because I'm very competitive.
Like, I am a very competitive person. I'll admit it.
That, like, if I'm going against somebody from All Games Interactive in a scare-off or whatever,
that I will somehow, like, between being actually scared and trying to, like, hold it in, like, I'm not going to scream, I'm not going to scream,
that I will shit my pants in the middle of the haunted house.
You know, it should do.
And I don't want that to happen.
That's anonymous.
You should have judges go with you.
Have three judges go one time with you and one time with her, and then rate the scare detection factor.
I don't know why I'm picking on Jessica.
I feel for some reason she's the easiest target of who's most likely to get scared from the All Games Interactive crew.
But for all I know, Mary Young is the target, or Scott, for I don't know.
Okay, so who would you pick, then, to do in a least likely to be scared?
I need an All Games Interactive expert to tell me who is most likely to get scared at Silent Hill,
because I have an experience that I can challenge to a scare-off.
Jessica's no longer a part of All Games.
Well, she was, though, right?
Well, who, then, would you think would be best off for a least likely to be scared?
A what? And then a scare-off with you?
I don't know if it would be me that would be least likely to be scared.
Okay, the Tower of Terror scared the shit out of me.
But then again, I've also been in an elevator when it's fallen.
The chat is suggesting Derek H. Does he even live in LA? I don't think he does.
Isn't he, like, in the Midwest or something? I don't know. I could be wrong.
All right, anyhow.
Look, I'm going to stop picking on our friends at All Games Interactive and just, you know,
we're just going to go to this and have fun.
And if they want to come, hey, great.
But I'm down for going to this Silent Hill haunted house.
I love Silent Hill. It would be fun. Super fun.
And Silent Hill loves you for dinner.
Let's move on with some more stories.
And then your phone call is coming up later this hour.
Well, this is a definite bit of not really a surprise, but it's sort of happy and not happy at the same time.
Sega doesn't have any plans to do anything to commemorate the Dreamcast launch,
because Dreamcast launch happened 9-9-99, so they're not doing anything 9-9-09.
But they said unofficially that there should be some celebrations and some parties,
things to mark, you know, such a momentous day in gaming.
But that they don't really have any plans to celebrate the U.S. launch.
However, there is some talk about putting up some of the potential digital downloads of Dreamcast games.
It's just the limiting factor being how large they are right now.
Unfortunately, I think a lot of people aren't going to realize that they're going to have a 10th anniversary.
To me, the Dreamcast right now is going to be like the Cabela's game during the Halo 3 launch.
Whereas the Dreamcast's anniversary is going to be the Cabela's game to the Beatles' catalog being re-released on the 9th.
So a lot of people are going to think, Beatles? No Dreamcast.
You know what? We need to do something on Wednesday.
We need to come over here and play Dreamcast.
Because of the anniversary that day?
And record it.
You know, it's a lot of Sega anniversaries this week. It's not just the Dreamcast, but the Genesis.
I mean, Bobby talked a lot about this on his show tonight, so go download that if you want to check it out.
But the 20th anniversary of Genesis was this week too.
And then, of course, Dreamcast is coming up very soon.
So it's just lots and lots of stuff.
I remember sitting in that line outside the damn mall and getting so bored that we went over and bought books at Barnes & Noble and came back and got in line.
The launch of the Dreamcast was during the period where, believe it or not, I wasn't playing a lot of video games.
Like, the years I was living in Chico, kind of away at college, I kind of fell out of video gaming.
My love of gaming for a while. So I kind of missed the launch of the Dreamcast.
But in retrospect, I was able to, you know, kind of catch up on it and see just, like, how awesome of a system it was.
This was back in the day when Dan and I were like, we're going to wait for the US system. We're going to wait. We're going to less import it.
So we already were playing our Dreamcast for a while.
We even did the Sonic Adventure rental where you could rent a Dreamcast and a special release of Sonic Adventure.
Nice. I'm kind of surprised, though, that Sega's not even at the bare minimum, like, releasing Crazy Taxi on Xbox Live Arcade or something.
You know, like, you know how Sega loves to re-release their old nostalgia stuff.
You know, give us a little something some Dreamcast love.
I mean, I guess, though, okay, now granted, before somebody in chat mentions it, which I'm sure they will, they do have the poll going on right now for the Genesis game that's going to be released on Xbox Live Arcade.
Did you guys hear about this? They're, like, doing a poll at, what is it, genesispoll.com or something like that to see what game should be the next one they release on Xbox Live Arcade.
And I think right now Earthworm Jim is winning by a landslide, which is too bad, because, like, Wonder Boy and ToeJam and Earl and Revenge of Shinobi are all in that.
Revenge of Shinobi are all in that poll as well.
It'd be nice if it actually load.
Did the whole thing not load?
No.
That's weird. You should see a poll in the middle there with the options of the game that would come out next.
That's weird that it's not showing up for you. Show it up for me at home.
Maybe the poll's over? I don't know.
Maybe.
Weird.
But Earthworm Jim was kicking all the other game's ass. That's the one that's going to win.
Yeah.
So.
Earthworm Jim was actually a really good game.
And I'm sure that they're probably all slated to come out. It's just, which one do we want to release first?
Exactly. I'm sure they're all being worked on right now.
Which is kind of cool, because, you know, it's nice to know we'll get all those games eventually, even though I'm not the biggest fan of the Genesis remakes on Xbox Live Arcade.
Although, oddly enough, I do love the Mega Collection, because I think the Mega Collection's a really, really good value.
But I think the ones by themselves don't bring that much to the table outside of achievements and, you know, just being a rehashed version of the old game.
But, heck, same thing as Virtual Console, I guess.
If we want to put it that way.
Alright, so too bad that we won't see more Dreamcast 11 on September 9th of 2009, but I guess it was just ahead of its time.
I don't know what else to chalk it up to.
Let's move on with some more news.
Alright. Well, we talked a little bit before about Guitar Hero 5 and the free game.
Well, now you can do some song imports into it as well.
Kind of a feature that, you know, Rock Band 2 started off with.
But now it's nice, at least, Guitar Hero 5 will allow you to import your tracks from Guitar Hero World Tour.
And, apparently, Guitar Hero Smash Hits as well.
I guess the newer games now are coming with a code in the manual that basically has...
It's like a code in the back of the manual that's individual to each game that you can basically plug in to get, you know, your, I guess, authorization to download them.
For costs, of course, just like Rock Band was five bucks.
No pricing, though, has been announced yet for it.
But the options, though, for PS3 and Xbox 360, you can download the whole lump of songs, or you can pick and choose which ones you want.
And, apparently, most of the tracks will be available, including, I guess, 152 of the 158 tracks that are available right now for download content for Guitar Hero World Tour will be compatible with Guitar Hero 5.
The other cool thing, though, is, apparently, Band Hero also will be backwards compatible with these other games as well.
So, that's kind of cool. No word, though, on if you can import the Band Hero songs into Guitar Hero 5 or vice versa.
Isn't, literally, Band Hero just a different skinned version of Guitar Hero 5, though?
Yes.
Like, literally?
Literally, it is.
Just different skinned version with different songs?
And it's different track lists. It's more geared towards kids, supposedly, but it's just basically...
In other words, I like it more.
It's another excuse to put out, you know, another version of the game.
It's another thing that they can go, hey, look, you know, Guitar Hero's out selling Rock Band, like, ten times over.
Yeah, because you're releasing ten times more games, stupid!
I don't know. It's just, it's getting ridiculous now.
Thankfully, I think a lot of people are seeing that, and they've figured out, hey, you know what? I don't want to buy all these games.
And, you know, before I used to pick up some of the Guitar Hero games, even though I didn't really play them.
Not anymore. I'm not really touching them, because I do realize that they're just all stuff that could be available for, you know...
They're download content. They only have a few tracks to come out each month.
Rock Band has a few tracks to come out each week.
And it's a real bummer. It's a real bummer that my Xbox died when it did.
Because I had just downloaded Janus Joplin, Piece of My Heart, which I was so looking forward to playing.
And the Gorillaz Pack, too. And never got to play them, because of my Xbox dying.
But anyhow, you know what, though? Loki, I actually think I'm going to pick up Guitar Hero 5.
Because the song list looks pretty awesome.
And I skipped World Tour, though. I didn't buy World Tour, ever.
I probably will get Guitar Hero World 5. At least the game by itself.
I probably won't get the whole... I don't need the drums and all that bullshit.
And you know what you can do? Pro tip here?
Just go rent World Tour and get the code from the back, and hopefully no one else has thought of that.
Hopefully. Hopefully.
Eh, it's a big deal. I'm sure the game will come down in price, big time, used at some point.
Well, then again, I won't be able to get the code, huh?
Well, no. If it's used, you may still will, too.
Because the codes really don't mean anything right now. They aren't used for anything.
So if you do happen to find it used, you can still use it.
You know, there's still probably kind of price to use.
And I don't know if I... I don't think there were any songs in World Tour I wanted that badly.
And then the other thing, too...
Rock Band 2 right now is $99 for the bundle. Which is not bad, I mean, if you haven't picked up.
Okay, that's a funny thing right here.
There's the Beatles Rock Band bundle that they have right now.
We found out that the title's going to be heavily allocated, which means they're only going to release limited quantities to distributors.
And, you know, retail stores are probably going to get them.
Because they're going to be really hard to find, basically.
It's actually cheaper to buy Rock Band 2, the bundle, and then buy Beatles Rock Band the game only.
You'll literally save almost $100 and you'll get two games instead of one.
I mean, if it's that important that your instruments look like the Beatles' instruments...
I mean, we're talking a plastic guitar here...
If it's really... is it $100 important?
I mean, seriously, if you really want to spend the extra $100, you can buy another guitar that looks...
You know, one of the two separate guitars that they have available as well.
But, I mean, seriously, if you're just holding out for that bundle, just buy Rock Band 2 and then get the other game.
But aren't they going to phase out the Rock Band 2 bundles eventually?
Probably not, because not everyone's going to want Beatles Rock Band.
I'm sure Rock Band 2 will be around for a while until Rock Band 3.
Probably Rock Band 3 will be coming out probably next year.
So they'll probably keep Rock Band 2 around until 3 comes out.
I wonder what 3 will do that really ups the ante.
Probably offer the same stuff that they did in Beatles Rock Band, like the 3-part harmonies.
Maybe some sort of... I don't really know.
I'm hoping, though, it at least does the whole thing where your Rock Band 1 and Rock Band 2 library can be exported,
and you're just going to have this gigantic jukebox of songs available.
Definitely. I wouldn't see why they wouldn't.
The only thing that they may have is obviously the older songs won't support the 3-part harmonies, but who cares?
You don't need to have that.
And they could always maybe patch it in.
Yeah, I doubt they'll do it, but they could.
They could.
Probably the songs they release going forward will all have that.
And who knows, if they know that that's coming, maybe some of the songs that come out over the next year are going to secretly have it in there.
I would think, but maybe not. I don't know.
Maybe?
Did you talk about Roadie Battle?
No, not yet.
What's kind of neat, though, with the Wii version, they're actually doing something called Roadie Battle, which, surprisingly enough, is actually something innovative.
What it's going to be is it's a mode that you use with your DS.
Basically, you need two DSs to do this, I guess, if you're playing with two humans using the DS.
And then the other two people will play a versus battle on Guitar Hero and on the Wii.
And so during that time, you have little mini-games that you play on the DS.
Like, for example, you're sabotaging the other player, so you unscrew the amp.
So you actually make the little motions like you're screwing in something, and basically that will screw up the other person.
Or they'll have one where you have to reset the soundboard.
And so they have little marks where the sliders need to be, and you have to slide your stylus to move the sliders.
I think that's kind of cool.
And I think that would be kind of cool as a standalone multiplayer game or something like that on the Wii for Guitar Hero 5.
Just say you want to play a little mini-game or something like that. Different. That would be kind of neat.
I guess any new future is kind of cool, I guess, if nothing else.
If you don't have two people, you know, you don't have two DSs or something like that, you can actually play against a computer.
But it's neat.
All right. Very cool.
Hey, a lot of things that, or I should say, a lot of complaints have been made about the Xbox 360's friends list and the fact that it's limited to basically 100 friends.
Well, and people are wondering, why doesn't Xbox just up the friends list?
And, you know, honestly, guys, it's not as easy as just flipping a switch, you know.
Probably this is, you know, takes a lot of work on the server ends and so forth.
You know, if things were built a certain way, then they're kind of stuck that way.
But apparently, a lot of this dates back to Halo 2.
Apparently, original Xbox games were coded to be limited to 100 friends, and that limit was brought into the current generation.
And this has to do with a report from G4, I guess, talked to a high level Microsoft source.
The real reason why they cannot up the friends list is because more people are still playing Halo 2.
So if you want the friends list to be upped, Halo 2 has to go away, I guess.
Or they're going to have to make some major fixes to Halo 2. I don't know if they can really do that.
So it's probably going to take a long time for that limit to go away.
But really, I mean, I've found myself struggling with the 100 friend limit.
But at the same time, I just kind of will remove people I've never talked to since the day they add me or never have played a game with or what have you.
And that seems to work okay.
I just remove people after they've been offline for like 30 days.
Yeah, then you kind of figure they're not coming back.
And if they do, it's no big deal.
Or, you know, obviously if it's my friends or something like that that I know in real life, you know, I won't take them off there.
But, you know, for the most part, I will take people that are not on there for 30 days.
And the thought is maybe some folks will get off of Halo 2 once Halo 3 ODST comes out in September.
But you know what? I don't know. I think there's always going to be some people playing Halo 2.
When they pull the plug on Halo 2 someday, there are going to be some pissed off gamers.
But the question is, you know, how many are they willing to risk pissing off to do it?
Or why can't they just like, I don't know, limit your friends list to show just the first 100 in Halo 2 and then just have it later, you know, more later or something like that.
Just limit it to the first 100.
Alright. Well, let's get into the mailbag.
Every week we invite your emails at mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com.
And the lovely DarkSakura opens up the email bag and dives in and picks a few of her favorite emails to read here on the program.
So, who's emailed us this week? mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com. DarkSakura.
We have one from Mark who says, I'm a new fan of your show and I added your video game talk show to my podcast to my Yahoo RSS feed so I can hear you all the time.
Now, what are all your PlayStation 3 PSN names?
I don't have one because I don't play on it.
Wouldn't that buy me a game of your favorite PS3 games?
What? No, your PSN name.
Oh, PSN name? Um, Green Sky but IE instead of Y.
Loki, OLR, caps. I can't remember if there's a space though in between Loki and OLR.
Mine's all one word, all lowercase.
Mine's, I think on the PlayStation Network, he caps spaces. So, maybe you can.
I think, I don't remember. It's in the forums. Go look in the forums.
Next email. Oh, it's by the same person.
Well, I'm not going to read one by the same person twice.
Well, I don't know.
Read it at the end.
Well, I'm actually closing it right now.
This one comes from Redertainment.
Hi, I'm a resident of Utah and frequent the Best Buy store where the pilot program that was discussed last week is taking place.
I didn't ask the manager about it under the guise of doing a story for a gaming site.
What I learned is that they are taking the trade in values from the Gamestop website.
Also, not all the games are subject to this program, just ones that are out of print and are hard to sell.
I couldn't get any other details as I am not an employee.
Also, Super Mormon Brothers, really? Come on, you can come up with better.
For instance, Grand Theft Auto, LDS and City, Sim Missionary, DDR Mormon, Tabernacle Choir Mix, and Are You Smarter Than a Member of the Quorum of the Seventy?
That's all I have.
Staycare? Redertainment.
This message brought to you by the Utah State Legislature where racism, classism, and homophobia are not just encouraged, it's rewarded.
That is so funny that we actually did have a listener in that town that we were talking about last week's show. That's great.
This is from Robert M.
Interesting you mentioned Johnny Cash in Guitar Hero 5.
I love the original Tony Hawk Pro Skater games, Lisa 1 and 2, especially the soundtracks of those games.
It seems to lose focus creatively and musically with Underground and Underground 2.
The later of which containing such random artists as Frank Sinatra, The Doors, and, yes, Cash.
I can accept such an eclectic variety of artists in a music slash rhythm game more readily than in a skating game, though.
I'm not sure how I feel about the character model in 5 yet, excuse me, nor have I made up my mind about Hendrix being in World Tour.
We just had commentary from Shermy.
To play freaking morons advocate, I get the feeling that Mr. Kotick meant to say that he felt retail costs, I think we discussed this,
may need to increase as project budgets marketing increase. Of course, if that's what you mean, say that.
In an ideal world, which this isn't, Bobby wouldn't trip over a scorpion and fall into an alligator pit and be replaced with Gary Kitchens and or David Crane after a merger with their company Skyworks Technologies.
Moving forward. Yes, I'm reading at rapid speed.
This is from Jeff.
Hi Jeff.
Hey guys, I'm a new listener, love your show. I wanted to know if all of your episodes can be downloaded off iTunes or only a certain amount.
Also, my condolences to Loki and his wife for their loss. I also wanted to know if any of you are looking forward to Uncharted 2 or Ratchet and Clank.
Uncharted 2, in my opinion, is going to be a big seller for the PS3.
The PS3 is coming into its own finally. Big name titles coming their way for the system. Thanks guys and keep up the great podcast.
I've heard good things about Uncharted 2. I haven't checked it out myself. I need to get the demo for it, which I will probably do now that I'm Xbox-less for a little while until I figure out what I'm going to do to replace that.
What was the first part of that? Something about iTunes. Oh, only the last 10 episodes are available on iTunes.
OLR PSP.com, you can get the last 20. It's the one site where it goes back a little further, but unfortunately we don't really offer any further back than that. I do know some OLR listeners have scrounged up old episodes.
Just because of server load and space, every show is 90 megabytes. It's a huge amount of bandwidth, so we can't offer every show. We have a bunch of listeners who have old shows and there's this OLR archive.
I tried to go to it today, though, and I got a bunch of spam, so I don't know if the link is no longer good, but apparently they dug up the old, old episodes. Episode 1 even, I think. I don't know if folks in the chat room can confirm it tonight.
Did you find all the old stuff? I think that's the old ones. Did you put it? I haven't burned them yet.
Somebody said season 1 is on the OLR archive now, but you have to remember, just remember, if you're going to go back and download episode 1, episode 2, it was a totally different show 7 years ago.
We grew. It was less mature. Totally different. Just warning you. And I had a migraine the whole first episode, just warning everyone. And then I think that was, wasn't that when I went to go sleep in the Harry Potter room?
That was later, I think. That was later, yeah. I slept in a little bed under the stairs. Jason and Raichan found the old episodes. They had them somehow. I must have burned them off for Raichan when I sent her the ferret years ago. I bet I did. How funny.
So, moving forward now. And actually, this is one of those weeks where I've actually had to pick different emails because we've got so many. So, if your emails aren't getting read, I'm sorry. It's just we really do have to move through here.
Shook here, or is it Shookay? I don't know. Lately, I've been thinking about getting Final Fantasy X on PS2 for my 13th birthday on October 17th. The thing is, my old man, who's just about as heartless as a grizzled non-vet, won't let me get what he calls quote pussy jab stuff. End quote. Ew.
That's not racist at all. No, not at all. Could you give me some advice as to coercing him into letting me get it? It'd be much appreciated. Tell him it's localized for American audiences.
That's about it. Or do what I used to do in sneak. Buy it yourself. It's Final Fantasy X for the PS2? Yeah. Dude, that's like 20 bucks now. You can do it. Sell back some old games to GameStop and just buy the game yourself.
And, dude, Final Fantasy X had Blitzball. That's pretty hardcore. And thank you for being a lot more open-minded than your father. No insult's intended towards your father, but he sounds bigoted.
He sounds like an asshole and complete ill-will meant towards your father. Sorry. Ill-will meant. I mean, I don't like to insult people's parents. Yeah, I know.
Because even though our parents may be, you know, my dad is fairly racist and thick-headed, but I still love my dad. Well, when my mom and dad say stupid shit, I call them on it.
But that's just the way we are in our family, you know? They call me on stuff, I call them on stuff. So, what can you do? Is Shermie smelling the microphone? I'm trying to get her to say something. No.
Oh, you almost strangled poor Shermie. Poor Shermie. Go sit on Dan's desk. She likes people, she just is nervous, okay?
Yeah, tell your dad, you know, to get with the times. Ooh, this one's for me from Cheeseburger.
Jamie, what's a good starter pinball machine for under $1,000? Oh, and post more videos on YouTube, they're great. Just for the record, T-H-E-R-E is for location. T-H-E-Y apostrophe R-E is what you intended.
Good pinball tables under $1,000. Good look on eBay and Craigslist, seriously. You're gonna pick up a beater, just so that you know, typically for that low.
But you can, it's a good way to get started, you know. If you pick up a beater machine that needs a little bit of work, and start putting the work into it yourself, you can trade it later on for other tables for things that you want better.
Yeah, those are really, also, there's a, Dan's not here for me to get the name of it from him, but there's a Sacramento Pinball Group actually puts up a purchase stuff every so often, and that's a group that my husband's a part of.
But eBay and Craigslist, really, you just need to make sure that you look for, you know, everything works, or, you know, if there's a problem with it, don't make sure there's no, like, board problems.
You know, something that you're gonna have to instantly get into soldering up a board together, you know. Playfield, you know, if you see cabinet damage, playfield damage, at least make sure that it's in good working condition before you get it.
Cabinet damage and playfield damage can be repaired. And if they can't, let you just buy a new one later on.
So, last email?
Okay.
From Geekboi2424, Hey guys, with the summer of Arcade coming to an end, and Rob's obsession with Super Metroid, I wanted to know if you're interested in Shadow Complex. What makes it look good to you, or makes it look bad? Thanks for the opinions, and I love the show. Logan, aka Geekboi2424.
I have to be honest, I don't know much about the game, and especially because my Xbox 360 fried this week, I don't think I'll be getting this anytime soon, but I love the idea of a game influenced by Super Metroid, and I'm all about that.
You know, I'll check it out, at least the demo, just based on that alone. Just the fact that it's that whole exploration and power-ups, and I just love that kind of design. You know I love my Super Metroid, and I just love the design of that game. I loved Castlevania, too.
The Symphony of the Night, of course. So, I'm all about at least checking it out, if nothing else.
Alright.
Sounds good to me.
Get your mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com if you wish to send us more emails to read in the future. In the meantime, it's time to get into our FUs of the week. Thankfully, there wasn't a lot of stupidity out there on the internet last week, at least we didn't find any, so we don't really have anything to dedicate this week's FUs to. Oh, except for the fact that my Xbox 360 fried itself.
My FU goes to how much my hand hurts and the freaking suture that was left in it. The end.
Lucky. FU goes to all the drinks that I just had because I feel really full, and also to the guy that's on the Neo Geo forums that's selling all the candy cabinets that won't get back to me. I know a lot of people are antsy because they're waiting here back for them, and I want to put back my deposit to guarantee my cabinet. That's it.
I don't know. I don't really have a lot of FUs. FUs to the fact that I nap too much. That's my FU this week. FU to napping. Although, actually napping is awesome. I shouldn't say FU to it because it's really cool, actually. I just do it too much. That's the problem.
I like naps.
Naps are cool. Unless you nap all the time like me. Alright, just a couple more stories, and then we're going to open up our Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio. But we have a few more stories before we get to that. So, Loki.
Are you a girl and a gamer who wishes that there were more girl gamer perspectives for you? Yes, yes I am. Well, you're in luck because now there's the Gamers Girl, which is a brand new blog that you can find at thegamersgirl.blogspot.com, and it's a website geared towards women who are dating gamers.
And they have interesting little articles. One of them that they're highlighting, of course, is the Gamer Widow. Basically, a woman that has lost their boyfriend to gaming.
They offer tips for gamers to keep their significant other from resenting or interrupting their game time needlessly. Like, for example, setting aside a half an hour right when you get home from work to lavish affection on your partner before you switch on the 360.
And I gotta tell you, from my own experience, that does work. So, you might want to follow that advice. But yes, it's neat, I guess. I also found out from a spam ad that popped up on Go Nintendo the other day that there's actually a gamer and geek dating site.
Geek to geek? I've seen sites like that before. I don't think that was the particular one I'd seen before. It's like GK to GK? Yeah, there's some of those out there.
Well, there's some for everybody, I guess. Yep. Alright, hey, one more story for you guys, then we're gonna go to the Skype line, and this story has to do with something that women and men and everybody can bond over.
Pokemons! Let me show you them. There are some new Pokemans games coming out this spring. The Heart Gold version and the Soul Silver version.
And what these are, these are remakes of Pokemon Gold and Silver, and they'll now be on the DS. So, yeah, that's pretty much all you need to know, right? They're coming out Spring 2010.
Let's see, what is the little quote here? Announcing these much anticipated game launches at the Pokemon World Championships allows us to give the news directly to the legions of fans who represent the true heart and soul of Pokemon.
We want to thank these loyal fans by revealing the details to them first, but of course now we all know. That quote, by the way, from JC Smith, the Pokemon Company International's Director of Marketing.
So, there you go, remakes coming for the DS. As far as what features and so forth on them, don't know yet, but there's a trailer out there, and it looks like it does have Wi-Fi battling going on on it, so that's kind of cool, I guess.
I actually had, um, was it Gold and Silver I had? No, the last one I think I had was Ruby. I think it was the last one I had. It was an advanced game.
But I'm kind of, I'm kind of not into Pokemon anymore. You don't want to show people your Pokemans? Not anymore. I'm not as into them as I used to be.
I think I remember you playing that, or maybe it was Shane playing that on the Game Boy Advance thing for the GameCube.
I was playing Ruby on that one for a while. I think I had Ruby and he had Sapphire and we were doing the training thing for a little bit.
I was playing Pearl for a while when I would go to the gym and play Pokemans.
I don't know, Pokemon's just so repetitive to me. That's my problem with it. It just got too repetitive.
You know what, nothing will ever top Pokemon Snap in terms of coolness.
Awesome. I love Pokemon Snap. I still play that on Virtual Console once in a great while, but it happens.
Hey, how about that Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR. Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio. We're going to go ahead and open it up and take your calls.
While we wait for your calls, how about some last minute stories? Do we have any last minute stories tonight, Loki?
Yes, RedBox is test marketing video game rentals in their kiosk for $2 a night. They're testing this right now in their Reno, Nevada market.
Okay, we got a call. Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
Hey, it's Ranma. What's going on, everyone?
You always seem to get through, Ranma. What's on your mind, buddy?
Not too much. Once again, I take another one for the team. I went out, I dropped $5 on Rock Revolution.
I heard about this insane price drop for Rock Revolution, that it was coming way down in price, so you actually picked this up, huh?
Yes, actually it was retailing for $16.99 at most places. It's a place right across from my job price match GameStop for me, which was pretty cool.
Nice. So, uh, well?
If I paid more than $5.99, I mean $4.99, I would have thrown it across the room.
Well, since you only paid $5, doesn't that make it eligible to be thrown across the room?
The fact that it has twisted scissors, we're not going to take it. It slides because of that. Any song, any game that has that song works for me.
Wait, isn't that a cover?
Yeah, aren't they all bad covers?
I don't care. It's still awesome.
So, I mean, but how's the game itself? I mean, how's the interface? How does it run? I mean, are we just picking on Rock Revolution because it's, you know, the bastard child of music games, or what's the reason to really hate this game?
Because it's nothing more than, like, Guitar Freak's Drum Mania hyped up on some really bad coke and steroids.
How so?
Okay, first off, when playing with the drums, I keep forgetting that there is an actual cymbal for the foot pedal instead of the lines. I keep forgetting about that.
Overall, the game plays where three songs, your song goes, the album goes gold. If you complete five songs, the album goes platinum.
And there are options, one of the objectives is, where you play one of the songs, it goes up in three levels of difficulty as you're playing, but it tells you on the screen what level you're at.
And another one is where you practice a certain part of the song, and you have to play it back fully memorized.
That is kind of weird.
Well, after two albums, you get the pick of an arena, no, they give you an arena, you pick three songs and you play it right through, which is not so bad.
Wow, but having to play them from memory, that's kind of dumb.
I know it is, but it's only for like, not the whole song, it's maybe like 30 seconds of the song. It goes through with you twice, and then it goes over again from memory.
I guess that's not terrible.
That's not so bad.
I don't know, I actually am thinking of trying to find this game and pick it up. I mean, it's only $5. I mean, whatever, I've spent more than that on crappy Xbox Live arcade games.
I think that describes most of us.
AJ Mixon Chat says, if you're going to buy Rock Revolution for $5 just for the Bomani Pack, stop. Do not.
Believe it or not, much as I enjoy playing drums, I am more really curious about going on eBay and getting the drum kit, because I Best Buy has an outlet store on eBay, and the auction starts at like $30.
Unfortunately, it comes with the game, so knowing me, I buy the drum kit and just give the game away to somebody.
Can't you still get the drums for Rock Revolution somewhere? And keep in mind, they're not compatible with anything. Aren't the drums in Rock Revolution not compatible with any of the other games?
Pretty much, yeah.
I do, active have me worried saying that, oh, the Rock Band drums don't work with the game.
You know what, look on Harmonix, we talked about this last week, Harmonix's website has a compatibility chart that includes Rock Band, and it will tell you right there, so take a look.
Works for me.
So, anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
Um, no, not all fan.
Alright. Have a good one, Raman, thanks for calling.
No problem. Later.
GameGuru says, Rock Revolution is like a train wreck, you can't look away. That comment, of course, with all our other chat comments at chat.orangelandsradio.com.
Rock Revolution, the Yaris of music games.
Aw, that was sad. I almost feel kind of bad for it.
No, I don't. I don't feel bad, because they had their opportunity, for like years they had their opportunity, but they decided, you know what, we're just going to license the rights to our guitar peripherals or whatever, we're going to license those for the guitar hero arcade game.
And they only embarrassed themselves at E3 a few years ago, didn't they?
Yes.
Alright, let's go to the phones. Hi, you're on Orange Lands Radio, who's this?
This is DS Master 25.
Hi, DS Master 25, what's on your mind?
Uh, not much, just you guys talking Rock Revolution, um, I've actually, I've had the ROM for like, probably about two days now.
You're not supposed to tell people we have ROMs.
This is translated, and it's really crappy on DS, other than it has one part of the game that is missing from the console versions.
What's that?
The singing.
That's right, the console versions don't even have the singing, because they're covers, huh, so they can't really match up.
But yeah, you, uh, you, now I can't think of a lot of DS games where you do that, you actually sing in the microphone, right?
Yeah, it has the pitch bars, you know how Karaoke Revolution works, right?
Yeah.
Basically, it's that interface, so it's a little bit iffy, unless you have the DS headset, then you're fine, so don't use the mic on the DS.
I see.
Well, here's my question about it, and this is the will it blend question of gaming, because you know, you can always ask, but will it blend?
Here's my question, but is it fun?
Uh, this thing, part in drumming, was about as fun as it got. The bass, I saw it first, because I had the Guitar Hero peripheral for the DS.
So I figured, oh, they might have something, you know, along the lines of Guitar Freaks, when you're getting this sort of spiel, so I plugged it in expecting, you know, like the down, the upward note chart going on, but that wasn't the case, it was just like strum up, strum down, strum up, strum down.
Same thing for the bass, but with the four strings. It's stupid.
So, basically, to sum it up, it's about as fun as dark grey notes on a black background.
Have you heard, though, Konami's not giving up?
Pretty much.
Guitar Freaks has a new version coming out in Japan, and apparently now they've finally caught on to the five fret thing, they're going to go up to five frets.
I do not like that idea. What the, ugh.
You know what's funny? Do you remember this? Do you remember this years ago? Years and years ago, do you remember when Red Octane, before Guitar Hero came out, their business was making money off of peripherals for Konami games.
They actually released a controller, like, seven, six, five, I don't remember, five, six years ago, before Guitar Hero was out, they released a controller for Guitar Freaks with five buttons on it.
And everybody always asked, why the hell are there five buttons on this controller? Oh, there must be a new Guitar Freaks game coming out with five buttons, and then it turns out, well, it was a precursor to them putting out Guitar Hero.
Probably the fact, probably Konami's not revitalizing their series kind of probably drove Red Octane to do it themselves, and ended up being very successful with it.
Yeah, but I could not, see, but I was a Guitar Freaks player before I played Guitar Hero, and my uncle kept telling me, like, start going up on medium, use that fourth and fifth button.
I'm like, I can't, I'm too used to the three button pressing system that was on Guitar Freaks, I'm so used to the Japanese guitar game.
It takes time, you just practice and it takes time. Four isn't as hard to do, because you can do four without really moving your hand, it's five that gets tricky because you have to learn how to move your hand back and forth.
That's when it gets really hard, but four, most Guitar Freaks players can do four pretty easy because it's still one hand, you just have to get your pinky, you have to do pinky exercises every day, and you'll get better.
See, and actually get this, my school, for fundraisers for the music program, they've been having Guitar Hero tournaments all these years, and actually they finally had a rock band last year.
Now it's just a matter of time before they, because with DJ Hero coming out, do you think, I think you guys might have heard this before, but it still makes me think, because I've been working on this whole mod with Disney rock songs on Guitar Freaks, kind of like how people have been modding Guitar Hero tracks for a while.
I've been doing it with Guitar Freaks, but now it's all Disney stuff because they haven't done a Disney Guitar Freaks for Drummania, so basically, why haven't they done Disney with anything else other than DDR and Poppin?
Don't give them ideas, because Disney has their own studio, Disney has their own gaming studio, and for whatever reason, well because DDR is Konami's thing, Disney can't really rip it off for themselves, but Konami, as you can see, does not have the locks on guitar games, so if Disney wants to do their own guitar game, they will. That's probably the reason behind it.
But here's one thing I kind of figure, around the lines, no one helped operate the Jonas Brothers that are just speaking Disney. I was actually at a Demi concert, and there was this supposed preview coming up with the Jonas Brothers talking Guitar Hero, and possibly an expansion pack for them.
I could see that happening, and well, you look at the way that Gabe stopped, instead of teenage boys, you're going to be seeing tween girls in one line.
As Kevin Smith says, in six years, those girls will be 18.
Alright, DS Master, we're going to let you go, but thanks so much for the call, alright?
Alright, just one last question.
Do you think, especially with DJ Hero and Scratch coming out, do you ever think there's ever going to be a revitalization for Beatmania, period?
Sadly, the closest you're going to get is these knockoff games coming out. Not the DJ Hero, but the other one, the Scratch Ultimate DJ.
Scratch is as close to Beatmania as you're going to get, and it is pretty damn close to Beatmania.
Konami just doesn't care about Bomani anymore, and a lot of that has to do with the closure of their Northern California office. Sorry to say.
Which sucks.
It does suck, but there's not a lot we can do.
Alright, DS Master, thanks so much for the call. Take care, buddy.
Peace out, and keep the shows rocking.
We'll try.
1877 Game OLR username on Skype, OrangeLoungeRadio, if you want to give us a call, try to get through here on the line.
We'll probably take maybe one more call, and then we'll probably be done here.
DarkTit2, you want to remind us that 2DX17 is coming out.
Oh, right there.
Jesus Christ, I didn't even say hello.
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Let me guess, this Legend of Zaku.
Of course, how would you have guessed?
Did you, because you cut me off, did you know that they are releasing an Atari Lynx game named after you?
Really?
Yes.
Oh wow.
I'm not kidding, there's an Atari Lynx game coming out called Zaku. Check it out.
Better not be, better not rip off a Gundam or anything like that.
Well, the only thing I'm going to warn you is that Zaku is a chick, so somehow something got misinterpreted, so you'll have to go take it up with them.
Whatever, anyways, something just came up to my attention recently.
I don't know if you noticed, but apparently Sega is pulling the plug on the ChromaHounds 360 servers.
In other words, the $50 that we pay for Xbox Live every year isn't really helping us, isn't really keeping the servers on for an unlimited amount of time.
In other words, we're paying $50 and yet our servers are more likely not going to, they don't look like they're going to be safe.
Because if Sega could pull the plug on that, what's going to stop other companies from doing the same thing?
Is this really news, though? Because I thought, at least on the original Xbox, that servers were being shut down for the old sports games.
Am I correct or am I wrong on that?
No, they were.
So this has happened before, it's just I think this is the first time we've heard of this happening on the Xbox 360.
And the fact that it's a non-sports title that, you know, ages, you know, the ages gets old and replaced with a new sports title, you know, that both kind of plays into it, too.
I mean, it sucks, but it's also kind of not the first time.
But I mean, I understand your point, you know, what are we paying $50 for if it's not for the maintenance of these servers?
I mean, I don't get it that we're paying that much money and we're getting, you know, the fact of the matter is this, just getting shafted for, I don't know, I guess it's because it has the, you know, the potential to set precedent.
And Sega could do it that anyone else has the potential to just say, oh, we'll pull the plug on the server, even though you're paying $50 a year.
I can understand them pulling the plug on the server if literally no one is using it.
I mean, even if it's just a handful of people, I mean, are there listeners?
I mean, honestly, I want an honest poll of the listeners.
Is anyone still playing ChromeHounds online at least once a week?
I mean, I don't know, you know, and again, I understand what you're saying about precedent and all that stuff.
But I can also understand that if they need to close down this server to make room for a new game that, you know, there is a finite amount of space out there and an amount of bandwidth that maybe they just need to get rid of.
Does it suck, especially considering we're paying for it? Yeah.
I mean, the fact of the matter is that we're pretty much paying $50 for dedicated servers, and then all of a sudden we find out that aside from the sports games, which are seasonal, I bet, you know, which are obviously seasonal, and it's expected that they close out a few servers for an outdated Madden game, for example.
But for something like ChromeHounds, which is completely non-sports, just to have the servers close and we're still paying for it, it's just, I don't know, it's just mind-boggling.
Deathwishing in chat says he plays. I find matches every night. Yeah, I think he's called in about ChromeHounds before, so that kind of doesn't surprise me. I don't think I see anyone else, though.
Hmm. Well, you know, I don't know if there's an easy answer to this. I mean, unfortunately, I think it's one of those things where they'll just take a chance on pissing off a few people to make room for some new game they've got coming out.
It's Sega Sky. I doubt they would even have the ability to follow up on ChromeHounds unless, of course, they were financially inclined to do so.
It's a recurring theme, though, tonight, though, is that we keep getting screwed on all these things, yet we just kind of seem to take it. The Xbox Red ringings, the servers getting shut down.
At least for PSN, I kind of expect the servers will go down because they're free, so they're only up for a limited amount of time.
Except for popular games, but we expected that in the older PS2 days when a server is free, but not for something that we pay for.
Hmm. I don't know if there's an easy answer, Zaku. We have to speak with our wallets. The Starcraft thing. That was the other thing I was going to mention.
Alright, Zaku, do you have anything else for listeners today before we go and wrap it up?
Alright, I don't know. Is it just me that I've noticed that Quake Live, apparently John Carmack actually said over the weekend in QuakeCon, is that that free online version of Quake, Quake Live, can't really sustain itself on ads.
I'm not surprised.
Which brings me to the point, is there even chance or any room for a viable business model for a game that just relies heavily on ad revenues?
Because I think if Quake Live proves one thing, is that even in a tight economy, this one was hemorrhaging money.
Hence the need for them to actually start releasing premium content. Or actually, no, I take that back. It's like a premium subscription where you actually create your own servers.
I think in order to answer that question, you have to ask yourself, how often do you click on ads?
Well, it's not that you click on the ads. It's that the ads are actually strewn all over the actual maps in the game.
I see.
So it's not necessarily clicking the ads. It's just the fact that, I guess, if it's something nostalgic like Quake, and the fact of the matter is that it wasn't even enough even on ads to break even, then I don't know if it might be viable for future business models with that same type.
I don't know.
I don't think there is enough money to be made there, because I don't think people really act on that stuff. I don't know. I think the business model is going to have to be incorporating some paid content into it for the hardcore section of it.
I mean, EA managed to get some sort of assurance in the fact that with Battlefield Heroes, at least that paid content is for the most part optional.
I remember reading before tonight's show about this and that Quake Live, they're actually going to do a paid thing where you will be able to set up your own private rooms and so forth.
Right. I mean, with Battlefield Heroes, it's kind of like the other side of the coin where EA is not forcing you to buy certain content in order to play the game.
It's just mostly aesthetics and just to level up your character a lot quicker. So you can pretty much sustain without having to resort to buying DLC.
So I don't know if that's a viable model that could supplement ad revenues as well.
Well, one way to find out. We'll see.
Alright, Zaku, we've got to let you go, but thanks so much, buddy. Okay?
Alright, have a good one.
You too.
And he needs to check out that Atari Lynx game thing going on. We have a conference call coming in.
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio. Who's this?
Hey, what's up? It's the Rob D.
Hi.
I'll let everyone else introduce themselves, I guess.
And who do you want, sir?
And it's Shadowclaw.
So we have a conference call coming in. We usually don't take these very often, but my curiosity has peaked tonight. So what do we owe the conference call tonight?
Honestly, most of it is because I wanted to call in and we were talking on Skype at the time, so we just decided to, instead of actually editing the conference call, to just call in.
Awesome. Well, hello everybody. What's on your mind, Rob?
Well, I thought I'd talk about my interesting experience at the Chicago Comic Con last week.
Please.
So I went there. They wanted to get some anime and manga programming in, so I figured, you know, I'd submit a panel. I actually wanted to do a panel about localizing American comics in Japan, which you can talk about a lot there, like the Spider-Man manga, the Spider-Man live-action show, and stuff like that.
And, yeah, it turns out they didn't actually advertise any of the anime and manga panels anywhere at the convention, so I ended up getting one person to come in on Sunday.
Wow. Oh, I think I read about this in your journal. This is that same convention. Like, horrible signage and stuff, right?
Yeah. Well, you've been there. It's the same place that ASEN was at, so imagine if everything was at the convention center where you registered and they didn't have any signs pointing toward the hotel at all.
Like, who would go there?
Wow. Okay. Did the convention actually have a lot of people?
Yeah. I don't know exactly how many. In 2006, they got, I think, 60,000 people. I have no idea how many they got this year. I'm sure it's been down a lot since then. I mean, the convention itself was pretty much just a garage sale full of bootlegs and old comics.
Was it in the program or anything?
There was a two-page spread in the program with no schedule and no panels in there.
Wow.
No descriptions in there.
Someone really made you the bastard child of the convention.
Pretty much.
I'm sorry to hear that. Yeah. I mean, for those who haven't been to that little area in Chicago, you have to, I mean, that walkway is no short trip either to get from one to the other, so if you don't know where to go, I mean, during ASEN, you can figure it out because there's tons of people traveling through there all the time.
But, yeah, if it's not being trafficked, people don't know where to go.
And just to make this gaming related, they had a ton of gaming bootlegs there, too. Like, people were selling full sets of ROMs on the floor. They had a main cabinet going with a couple tournaments throughout the day.
That's pretty bold.
There was a gaming section. Actually, it was kind of funny. They had a Street Fighter IV tournament, or they were supposed to, and they wanted people to pay $20 to enter, and of course, no one did, so they didn't end up having it.
Huh.
It was an interesting convention. I can't say I'd want to go back, and if I didn't get a free badge, I don't think I would have gone.
But at least, you know, now you know, and at least it wasn't, like, that wasn't the focus. I mean, you know, for, I guess, maybe a comic book convention, they probably did all right, but that's unfortunate, though.
Mm-hmm.
Kind of a waste of time.
Can I complain about King of Fighters XII a little bit, or do you want to end the Skype?
Of course you can. I wanted to give the other guys a chance to say something, too, if they wanted to say anything.
It's fine. You can go on.
All right. King of Fighters then.
We're busy playing World of Warcraft, actually.
Nice.
We're installing Windows 7, which is going fun.
Much better than Vista.
Shadow's Light got me hooked on World of Warcraft. It's the default.
I'm telling you, Ion Online's pretty cool. If you're a Warcraft fan, I got to say, Ion Online, I'm liking that.
Dude, I keep hearing so many good things about Ion Online. I'm going to give it a try, like, in a couple of days.
It's worth a look. Dark Soccer?
I was actually wondering if his impressions of King of Fighters XII were the same as mine.
I think it's got a great foundation. I like the fighting in it, and I like the graphics, but unfortunately, SNK didn't really...
I guess they didn't have enough time to animate everything, because too many characters are missing. Half the moves are missing.
It's kind of like making a foundation for a skyscraper and putting up a lemonade stand.
Well, did you notice what they did, though, with the characters themselves is that they're sprite-wrapped 3D.
It was very interesting, but it also causes some really weird... just things that don't look right graphically with the characters themselves.
And on top of that, there's, like, no story.
Yeah, I love the animation in the game, though. I mean, it's got the best animation of any game I've seen since Street Fighter III, really.
But the advantage, though, for them doing it in that manner is that if they want to change anything visually about the character, they can map it over the 3D model without changing movesets.
I'm just hoping we actually get those movesets back, for the most part. I mean, I'm a Clark Steel player, and he's got two moves, literally.
Is it just me, or is he over-roided?
Oh, yes. It's going to be impossible for me to cosplay as Clark from now on, certainly in that style, unless I decide to go shopping with Hulk Hogan or Barry Bonds sometime soon.
I also didn't like that they did Athena in the cutesy anime style.
I don't mind that so much. Actually, that one's warmed up to me. The change... I'm a little bit iffy on Kenzo so far.
Yeah. Well, I like, though, that it seems that... I like his outfit in that, though. It seems like they're doing more towards the Psycho-Soldier outfit.
What's up with no Mai? That's a thing. Isn't that weird?
I don't...
Well, the other thing that gets me is that there's no interaction between the characters. Like, for example, if you had Leona versus Heidern in the old game, she'd come out and salute him because he raised her in the storyline.
And, you know, you'd have the Mai and Andy thing about her taunting him over wanting a baby or something.
Uh-oh. Are we losing you guys? Hello?
Oh, hello. Sorry.
Hi.
Sorry. I think my Skype hiccup's a little bit there.
That's alright.
But, I don't know. People didn't really play as Mai that much to begin with. I mean, they were watching her bounce, for the most part.
I liked Mai.
Mai is actually a staple of my team because I'm really good with her.
Fair enough.
Alright, well guys, we're gonna let you go so we can wrap up, but thanks for the call and have fun with all your respective games. Windows 7 and WoW and whatever you're playing these days, Rob.
Right now I'm playing a lot of Bladesblue, actually. That's what I've been playing all night and training.
Have fun with that. Hope your Xbox 360 doesn't fry.
You'll be getting your TurboGrafx as soon as we get a paycheck in.
Yay! I look forward to it.
Alright. Take care, guys. Have a good one, everybody.
You too, guys.
Later.
See ya.
Later, everybody.
That's funny. We don't get conference calls very often, but...
That was fun.
One of these days I just want every single person listening to all make a mass Skype conference call and then call us. It'll be complete chaos.
We can do SkypeCon all on Twitter.
I'm on the radio! I'm on the radio!
Alright, let's start to wrap up, guys, tonight, because it's already after 9 o'clock and we want to get out of here before it's too late.
But more last minute stories. Loki, I don't know if you have anything else.
I have nothing else.
Really? Wow. It was kind of a slow news week this week. Compared to other weeks, it was a little slow this week.
And nothing else I wanted to talk about. Let me put it that way.
There was other things to talk about, but there's nothing I wanted.
But nothing that big. Alright. Fine. Be that way.
I'm fighting spyware and it's just pissing me off.
Oh, how annoying.
Well, it's stuff I got to do at safe mode and I don't feel like doing it right now, so...
Ugh.
It's just searching for crap and then I get a wrong page and then it locks your system up because it wants to download spyware and it's a pain in the ass.
You know what's funny, since everybody's talking about this Skype thing.
I remember for a while, I don't know what ever happened with it, but they were talking about doing another show on All Games after us.
Like a late night show or what have you.
And I think what would be cool is somebody should just host a Skype thing.
Like an OLR post show that's just a massive orgy of people on Skype after the show.
I think that would be kind of fun.
And people can talk about the inside jokes from the show and tonight.
That would be fun.
So, alright. That's it. We're going to wrap up. Go around and give everybody's final thought.
DarkSakura, if you have no last minute stories tonight, then why don't you give us your final thought?
My final thought is my dinner was really good but I still want meat.
Tasty, tasty death.
My final thought is I want yogurt.
Ooh, robins.
But all the yogurt places close Sunday.
But Baskin-Robbins is open.
We'd have to like not do Afterbirth.
No, they close at 10.
We'd have to hurry through Afterbirth.
Let's do Afterbirth anyway. I don't care.
I'm thinking of the grocery store.
It's totally selfish of me but I'm thinking of...
Because the arcade cabinet is technically my birthday gift because the wife is letting me have it.
And that's a gift alone.
But I am going to open up the unofficial Loki's Greedy Bastard birthday gift fund for arcade cabinet use.
So links will be in the form.
I will donate and then I can feel guilt-free when I don't get you anything else.
That's fine. You don't have to get me anything at all anyways.
That's what everyone says.
Alright, let's go ahead and close up guys and call it a night.
Thank you guys as always for downloading and listening to our program. We really appreciate it.
If you want to help us out, just help us spread the word.
Tell somebody you know about the show.
Help build our community by joining the Twitter.
If you can't be here to listen live, we're trying to think of ways to get you guys to interact anyway.
Through Mailbag, through Twitter, Facebook and so on.
We want to hear from you.
Keep spreading the love you guys but use protection.
We'll see you next week with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
We'll be back to do it all again in 7 days.
Bye guys. Have a good week.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com.
Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific Time.
The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com.
But we're probably right anyway.
See you next week.