[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, August 23, 2009, a new pay-as-you-go business model is announced for a popular 360 game, one gaming device will soon allow you to read comic books, and was a recently closed studio working on the next Final Fantasy game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are that talk show dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_09]: We like to think of ourselves as the place where every gamer has a voice because we let you call in, we let you chat with us at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: We let you tweet us too.
[SPEAKER_09]: We try to keep up with the times and the new technologies and it all happens live at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time, 9 o'clock Eastern Time.
[SPEAKER_09]: and our friends at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: A big shout out to them for letting us steal their bandwidth on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll be with you here over the next three hours.
[SPEAKER_09]: With me as always, say hello to the one and only Jamie Summers, Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crunchy.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Crunchy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell the listeners about what you are eating right now because I find it very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I really wanted cereal, but I really wanted peanut butter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then I was like, I've got some really tasty bread from Trader Joe's.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what I did is I took my sprouted wheat bread from Trader Joe's and put a bunch of creamy Jif and have put... Why not Skippy?
[SPEAKER_09]: Annette Funicello is crying somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Foodio, live, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_09]: I swear we ought to have a spin-off.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is full of fiber and protein, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's low-glycemic, so the world can bite me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I swear we ought to have a spin-off show about, like, food or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't, it just seems like a natural progression for a show.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, say hello, as always.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to ignore him any longer, because he's an important part of our show.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell would we do without him?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tech Master Loki!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, those are all lies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, mostly.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: How are you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I feel somber, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was working out front planting plants.
[SPEAKER_09]: How is it being a homeowner now, a couple months in, having to do all this housework?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tiring.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, it's funny, though, because there was this plant that was growing out front next to our neighbor's fence, and we weren't really sure if it was our neighbor's plant or ours, but technically it's on our side of the property, so it's ours.
[SPEAKER_10]: But apparently you can pull it apart the way that it kind of grows.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can actually pull it apart.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we took this one giant plant and made like 16 smaller plants out of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: and they're all going to grow and expand bigger and take over the entire yard.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like Animal Crossing for real.
[SPEAKER_10]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, that's what I did there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm surprised you, Loki, with your handiwork.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't get one of those things I've seen on late night television which is those rolls of flowers that you see that you can get at Home Depot where you just unravel.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like a carpet or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: You throw it down and it's all seeds so you water it and then you just get the hometown buffet of flowers in your front yard.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you can do that with just seeds.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you don't need to spend money on... And I don't know if you've ever tried rolling anything down.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't roll it straight.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would just be awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, last night we got... We were actually doing stuff to the house.
[SPEAKER_10]: We bought a rug last night, which Kat decided to start tearing up because it's the only carpet in the house and now she can scratch it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then we bought curtains for the front room to shield the outside world from our porn watching.
[SPEAKER_10]: That, and it's really sunny.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, we put those up and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't need all the flowers up there.
[SPEAKER_09]: When are you inviting me over to see all these changes at the house?
[SPEAKER_09]: Once we're done, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just giving you a hard time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Come over anytime you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'd be better, though, once I get the cabinet in and stuff, but... You need a housewarming party.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what you need to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just, it's never clean.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: You've had a lot of busy stuff going on lately, but at some point, you should have a housewarming party.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's almost like... I don't know when the statute of limitations on that stuff is, because...
[SPEAKER_10]: We moved in, what, two months ago?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know when you've gone beyond the point of homewarming parties.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think there's a point where it's like, okay, you forego.
[SPEAKER_09]: You mean you would give up housewarming presents and not have a housewarming party?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, I would not be foregoing housewarming presents.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, well, let's introduce our chat room as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: As always, where would we be without the listeners?
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat.OrangeLoungeRadio.com Let's give the chat room a name tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's call it Rufus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why are we calling the chat room... Chat room, your name is Rufus.
[SPEAKER_09]: Barnaby.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why are we calling the chat room Rufus or Barnaby or Barnabas?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which, by the way, I am all about this Tim Burton Dark Shadows movie with Johnny Depp as Barnabas.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hello, can I get here any faster?
[SPEAKER_09]: Penelope Penelope
[SPEAKER_09]: And then people are going to tune in at 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_09]: People that tune in late who weren't here when the show started on time, they're going to be like, who the fuck's Penelope?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why they should have been here, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just going to get strange.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a feeling we're just going to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to take more Vicodin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's go to Penelope and read some of the comments that we have tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alpha Cananogram says about Loki's house, Sky just wants to watch the porn.
[SPEAKER_09]: on the big screen TV, possibly.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not that impressive, really.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are weird things, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last time we had Jim and Annie and Christopher over, we actually watched the parody to Friends.
[SPEAKER_10]: When you watch those parody porns, there's nothing sexy about that at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're trying to make the characters look like the characters in the show, and they do a horrible job at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, it's more weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like watching a very slow-mo car wreck or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you thought about just watching just a straight-up porn that doesn't try to be any type of funny thing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Good luck finding one, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, they're all kind of funny and weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like old people.
[SPEAKER_09]: One of my favorite chatroom nicknames, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: In Penelope right now wants to know... Ew, I just said that that person's in Penelope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wants to know, are there naked pics of Penelope?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, look, you're... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't want to... I like that Alpha Cananogram referred to Penelope Pitstop because that's old school, yo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was from an old cartoon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to school people.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it wasn't on Nickelodeon, I probably never saw it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Would that be from Wacky Races?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was Wacky Races.
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds like a character from Wacky Races.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any moment, somebody's going to yell it out in chat anyway, so we'll get there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amaze Satsuma asks, We went from Rufus to a girl's name.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did Chad have a sex change?
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, DarkSakura thinks so.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was indeed Wacky Races.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that was just a guess because I wouldn't remember such a horrible cartoon.
[SPEAKER_10]: You watch a lot of cartoons.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I don't watch horrible cartoons like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Penelope Pitstop.
[SPEAKER_10]: It sounds like a racing character.
[SPEAKER_08]: Her car was called the Compact Pussycat.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a compact pussy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have three people all just piping up, starting with X-Link, who beat everybody else to it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wacky Racers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or Wacky Races.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which goes back to video games!
[SPEAKER_09]: We have this odd delay, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live, and it's not like we're on a delay because people are afraid we're going to say fuck or something, but just the nature of the encoding and the fact that it takes a minute to go to all-game server, then you download it because you're buffering everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's just, by nature, this 20-second delay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So sometimes the last question is in the chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't see the answers for 20 seconds, so...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, I was actually playing some Blue Dragon and some Ragnarok Online, which I got back into, and stuff on Gaia, but, uh... Addict.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not playing anything now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you're playing MMOs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Somebody on this show has to keep the Addict tradition going.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had to stop because I had the rest of that suture removed from my hand on Friday.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ha ha, you can't bitch slap me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a left hand, Robb.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I got two feet.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you are not protected.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm actually reading up on Janet Waldo who did Penelope Pitstop's voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: She was Judy Jetson.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fascinating.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm assuming she's done if she's talking about the Jetsons.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently not as exciting as Wacky Races.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually tried to play a few different things this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I...
[SPEAKER_10]: I went and actually played some indie games and of course people were recommending that I play I made a game with zombies in it and yeah, it was funny and it was actually pretty fun so I enjoyed that also
[SPEAKER_10]: For whatever reason, because now that they have the rankings in there, where people can actually rate different games and stuff, you can actually see what the top-rated indie games and stuff are.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I decided to play the top-rated indie game, which is Minor Dig Deep.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't know why, but I'm addicted to that game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's...
[SPEAKER_10]: Almost pointless.
[SPEAKER_10]: The game, you basically, you're a miner, and you go into a hole, and you actually dig into the walls, almost like Dig Dug, but there's no, like, you know, dinosaurs right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to point out, though, not the kind of 17-year-old miner, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're talking about a pickaxe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, like a pickaxe, you know, miner.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, maybe under 17.
[SPEAKER_09]: Miner 2049er, if you're old school like me.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: And you do this forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: This seriously sounds like a game I used to play like 15 years ago on old school PC.
[SPEAKER_09]: The 256 color shareware.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you do this forever, and I don't know why, but I can't stop playing this game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually, you know... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I could have been playing like Earth Defense Force, which I did play a little bit of this week, but...
[SPEAKER_10]: I kept going back to play this game, and I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it sounds like it's crowned as the top-rated game right now, as rightfully deserved.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, I don't really know what the point is, but I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_09]: As your Ed's in chat wants to know what game you're talking about one more time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Minor Dig Deep.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's an indie game.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a top-rated indie game, at least when you downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who knows, because those lists can change on a daily basis, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, because I think there was some concern that just like people spam Dig, some of these indie developers might try to spam Xbox to try and get their titles to the top.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does it seem like it's working?
[SPEAKER_10]: If they are, it's hard to notice because there's so many people voting on stuff that...
[SPEAKER_10]: Really, I don't see how that can be.
[SPEAKER_10]: And actually, it's not a matter of like you can place a vote for a title.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you can vote like a five, but like say later on something really pissed you off about it, you can change it to a zero or one or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can change it whenever you want.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's basically just, you know, tallies whatever people are thinking of it at that time.
[SPEAKER_09]: When I went in there, because unfortunately, if you listened to last week's show, you know I'm Xbox-less right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But when I was playing with that new patch last week, one of the first things I did is I went in there and I rated Snake 360 to support our buddy who was on the show a couple months ago when that game first rolled out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I went and I was like, oh, I'm going to rate this a 5 and see kind of how it takes place.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it didn't seem like my vote, because you can see the number of people that have voted.
[SPEAKER_09]: It didn't seem like my vote
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I did find it very interesting that the game rating worked very similar to the Netflix rating.
[SPEAKER_09]: How since you don't really have a mouse and pointer to click how many stars, you have to kind of cycle through all the way to five or back to one to rate it by hitting the A button so many times.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't know, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played Earth Defense Force earlier this week as well, and that's rated a solid 4 now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which it rightly deserves, because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: It just broke 80 hours this week in the game, and I don't know why, because it's just really hard and frustrating.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'm actually...
[SPEAKER_10]: working my way through it some more i finally got uh one of the higher up weapons and i'm missing i'm still missing some of the other weapons though but in order to farm them the one level you have to play it only drops like one or two weapons a level and you know since it's random at what you know weapons it picks to me it could be one of the any 200 weapons that are in that game and i'm missing like two i mean you can see how it could take forever to get what you need but um
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm about 80% done with the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm getting almost to the point where...
[SPEAKER_10]: I need to really get some good people to help out with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have a friend who's actually playing that at work as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so he's been helping me on breaks and stuff like that when we're not playing Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then, of course, I played Grand Theft Auto this week and didn't really change anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although I went over to my sister's house because she has a modded 360 as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got her that for her birthday.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so I've been giving her every now and then copies of...
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you really give the gift of piracy for someone's birthday?
[SPEAKER_10]: She's poor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Before that, she had a modded PS2 with games dumped to the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yes, I've been giving the gift of piracy to her because she can't afford actual games.
[SPEAKER_10]: She does rent, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: She rents legitimate games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I shouldn't be supporting such blatant piracy, but it's out there, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: To be fair, she does have a legit copy of Grand Theft Auto 4.
[SPEAKER_10]: So she does have it, legitimately.
[SPEAKER_10]: So the fact that I'm burning off a new copy of it that happens to be modified, it's still kind of in that gray area.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's not like she doesn't own a legit copy of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was showing her because she didn't actually try any of the weapons that I modified or anything because she doesn't have the phone yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: She's been too busy trying to punch people with the super punch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although, for whatever reason, the nuke shotgun that I built in there, because normally I play Lost and Damned, and so some things don't work quite right how they're supposed to, but since she only has Grand Theft Auto 4...
[SPEAKER_10]: That nuke shotgun works like a nuke.
[SPEAKER_10]: No matter where I shot it, somehow the shockwave hit me and killed me every time.
[SPEAKER_09]: You really do need to YouTube some of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have two hours of footage.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to go through it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looking forward to seeing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more question I want to ask you.
[SPEAKER_09]: As I mentioned before, my Xbox 360 is broke right now so I can't really look at this myself.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if you've bothered to check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe a chatter knows.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is the top rated Xbox 360 game right now?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if that's something you can look up on Xbox.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you see ratings on Xbox.com now?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure maybe a chatter will look that up for us.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I try to go on Xbox.com while we're recording the show, it won't like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It uses up a lot of memory.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of curious.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's like Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to think of the games that were high rated when I took a peek.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything was so new at that point.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Grand Theft Auto is pretty high up there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like a 4.5.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think there's anything that's a solid five, so it's going to be really hard to distinguish since, you know, it's sections of a star being shaded there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like, is that a half, third?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Halo 3 says, sex with the elderly is their chat nickname.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that the game tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody's going to name themselves something really foul that I have to read?
[SPEAKER_09]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if that's just a lie.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if they just shouted out an Xbox 360 game because they knew I'd read it and just believe them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I'm a sucker.
[SPEAKER_09]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously I've been QQing about my broken Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm calmed down a lot this week than I was last week because it was still fresh in my mind last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a little more mellow this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I have my plan of action for what I plan to do about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will not be buying a new Elite.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll tell you that much.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is one thing I did decide.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I'll talk a little more about this later on because...
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't play the new expansion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was just playing old school Wipeout HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess, well, how old school is Wipeout HD?
[SPEAKER_09]: But you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_09]: The original version of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, damn, I love me some F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Wipeout HD really is kind of the closest thing we have to that on another console.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I really like that mode that's called, I think, Zone Mode when you're racing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes the track all this solid color...
[SPEAKER_09]: as you're racing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has this very techno look to it, obviously, as Wipeout HD does.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then as you race, the track changes colors as you accumulate so many points.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm having fun with Wipeout HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't really played a lot of it online, but it has been...
[SPEAKER_09]: Satiating my thirst for gameplay this week with a lack of an Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously the PlayStation 3 is a perfectly fine gaming system.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there's some certain things on it I can't play on 360 that I'm kind of catching up on right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Wipeout HD is one of them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still looking for a cheap copy of Valkyria Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_09]: But from what I understand, because I remember we reported on the show a while back that Valkyria Chronicles dipped to 1999.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently it went back up.
[SPEAKER_09]: because it has been I don't know if the price dip made it more successful or it's a cult thing now or what the deal is but I know that's on my hit list of games I want to play until I get my 360 situation resolved and then of course whenever Final Fantasy 13 comes out I will be buying that on PS3 and I was watching Blu-rays too I finally caught up on a few of those I think you should hang out with me and play Dreamcast Dreamcast?
[SPEAKER_10]: On September 9th I will It'll be fun
[SPEAKER_10]: I forgot to mention that I also have a System 573 board coming my way tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now for those that don't know what a System 573 board is, what is that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Bomani hardware.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually, well this one in particular is a Dance Maniacs second mix J-Append.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so literally if I were to hook it up to a monitor and build controls and stuff like that, I could play Dance Maniacs as an actual arcade game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you can convert the machine into a DDR machine if I really wanted to.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it costs like an extra $100 to do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have the actual cartridges and security stuff to do it if I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if I will though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I can just run StepMe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm reading some comments from Penelope at chat.orangeloungeradio.com TigerClaw says, Zone was a mode first introduced in Wipeout Pure on the PSP I did not know that, I missed the PSP version SG100Matt says, the top indie rated game is I Made a Game with Zombies with 4.5 stars and 5,081 votes Yeah, it's been getting, well that was like number 3 It's been getting bigger because, you know, everyone loves it Everyone loves Zombies It's a dollar
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a good dollar spent.
[SPEAKER_10]: Definitely recommend you try it.
[SPEAKER_10]: People are calling it this year's Still Alive, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: It has a really weird, catchy song about the game that's horribly sung, but it just talks about the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does it seem like this whole rebranding of the... I don't even remember what it was called before.
[SPEAKER_09]: To indie games.
[SPEAKER_09]: What the hell was it called?
[SPEAKER_09]: Community games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you think the rebranding of community games to indie games has been successful?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it sure sounds like more people are following what's going on now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think, though, what's making it better is that they've dropped the minimum price.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because before, the minimum price used to be 200 Microsoft points, which is $250 now.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I mean, it's a lot easier just to buy stuff for 80 points.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it goes really fast.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is unfortunate that the games don't have achievements.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand why, because obviously someone would make that game, you know, press A, get 200 gamerscore.
[SPEAKER_09]: But even if they would do achievements with a zero gamerscore, or just, you know, because there are plenty of achievements out there in the retail games that are just zero gamerscore.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just unlocking it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or maybe like a separate...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what the hell they want to call it, but something maybe separate.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be kind of cool, because no one would let me compete against friends.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because on those games, you can't really do the leaderboards and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would never do points, because someone could just go, okay, you started the game, 1,000 points.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: But just something that kind of encourages a little bit of competition.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just kind of brainstorming here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ways they could make it even bigger.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they will later, but just not right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as other games I've been playing this week, not really a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was playing Guild Wars for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not a lot, but it's one of those MMOs I have that I'm not really paying for because I already bought the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Guild Wars' model is that once you buy the game, you can play online for free pretty much forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of cool that you can just go back and revisit whenever you want.
[SPEAKER_09]: I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of Guild Wars, and I don't think it's in tonight's show role, I also watched that trailer for Guild Wars 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looks pretty sweet, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_09]: So definitely keeping an eye on Guild Wars.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's get into some more gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: After some housekeeping, we do, of course, always want to plug some of the ways you can follow us and join the community that we sometimes call the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you want to join our Twitter, www.twitter.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, you can join us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just search for the OL Army.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're on LiveJournal as well and Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_09]: Follow us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get involved with the community.
[SPEAKER_09]: We try to read your comments and so forth on every show all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, some other comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: INGN0 asks, No Wolfenstein?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, not this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not really the type of game that I've been eagerly anticipating.
[SPEAKER_09]: I played the old Wolfenstein 3D and that was about it for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wolfenstein?
[SPEAKER_09]: Any interest, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I...
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't finished, you know, uh, Bionic Commando, um, and a half a dozen, more than half a dozen, a few dozen games that I've bought already, so, you know, I'm just kind of taking a break from buying full price, you know, Xbox Live Arcade games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, don't get me wrong, if they ever came out with a Bionic Commando sequel that would be on Xbox Live Arcade done the same fashion as, say, you know, Rearmed, then yes, I would probably buy that in a heartbeat, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shadow Complex, or whatever the game is that we're talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please, don't hear me wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not bashing Shadow Complex.
[SPEAKER_09]: Again, if my Xbox 360 hadn't have fried last week, I would have gladly checked it out this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, shit happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so Loki, get us started with some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so Microsoft had a little bit of a keynote during Gamescom this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, they didn't really discuss a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really, the only thing they discussed was...
[SPEAKER_10]: So, of course, I'm totally shocked that they announced a new Fable game, but Fable 3 will be coming out next year, and they didn't really go into great detail what exactly you're going to be doing, but apparently you will be, I guess, assuming that they're going to be playing as the son or daughter of your Fable 2 hero, and you're going to be starting a revolution to become the new ruler of Albion, and of course, based on, you know,
[SPEAKER_10]: What you do as a ruler can have obviously positive or negative effects on the world around you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just like Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm sorry, but if it's just like Fable 2, then it's going to be all hype.
[SPEAKER_10]: No content.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, not no content, but not as much content as promised.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of liked Fable 2, but... It was alright, but it just wasn't like, oh my god, the best game ever, as he was pitching it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Peter Molyneux kind of has a reputation for really, really hyping things beyond what they really end up being.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hence, you know, why...
[SPEAKER_09]: We all approach this project Milo with a hint of skepticism, at least I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I did like Fable 2 quite a bit, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's one of my favorite Xbox 360 games of last year.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's my question about Fable 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you're going to be playing the child of a character in Fable 2, does that mean all these decisions you made in Fable 2 ultimately are going to impact in Fable 3?
[SPEAKER_09]: That didn't really happen in Fable 2 with Fable 1.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm not really sure if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're just saying that...
[SPEAKER_10]: The storylines, basically, that your hero is going to be... It's their children, since the game starts off in Fable 2, where you pick a sex, and that's basically it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I guess they said the game's going to take place 50 years after the first one, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: um which will be used to influence the world basically a judgment system was people will come to you and say okay this uh this poor child you know stole bread from this person do you want to let them go or kill them you know and you can just you know obviously pick the right or wrong whatever you you know feel is right or wrong but you can't come up with creative punishments you can't say you know make them bake bread for the entire town or anything like that yeah it's like you can um you know
[SPEAKER_10]: Judge her immediately, like the person that stole food, or you can investigate the situation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or you can set her on fire.
[SPEAKER_07]: I vote for fire.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the AI wasn't that... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: That means if you're evil, you could grab them and throw them into the burning building.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it's saying you can also shake someone's hand or refuse to.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can also embrace somebody, snog them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Baby shake?
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope you can throw them off cliffs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or even better, jump off a cliff while holding on to them and then drag them with you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Throw your dog at them.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's basically the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's, you know, becoming the king and... It will be the best game ever, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: And somehow they'll probably work in Milo in there or some crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fable 3, My Life as a King.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, that is, you know, basically Fable 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, it's neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, the other thing that they talked about, because goddamn if Fable 3 wasn't enough, they talked about Fable 2 Episodic.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people were thinking, oh my god, there's more content coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, Fable 2 Episodic is a pay-to-play version of Fable 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: And basically, Fable 2 had different chapter points, I guess, in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: and so the first chapter is free and then of course once you're done with that you can choose to buy the next chapter or buy the rest of the game and I guess there's five episodes in total and it's supposed to be released on September 29th and they didn't say how expensive the game will be I'm guessing around the same price as Fable 2
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a test.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm actually a little more welcoming of this idea than you might think.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's a good idea because Fable 2 didn't have a demo and this would be a good way to check out a game say for example it's more of an extended demo because you get to play through the first part of the game for free and then if you like it then you can go ahead and purchase it later or if you're just on the fence about it you can buy the next chapter and see if you still like it or something like that so it's not just dumping all the money
[SPEAKER_08]: But they are getting more money, though, out of you by charging in an episodic manner as opposed to buying the whole game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, granted, we don't know how many points each part is going to cost yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would assume so because, I mean, that's typically when you buy, for example, an individual size of something or when you buy the six pack, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a fair comparison.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was kind of thinking of it as a pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you buy Fable 2, you get the pizza, but now you can get a slice of pizza.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pizza sounds good.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pizza does sound very good, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's get pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: We might have to during break.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wait a minute, you didn't bring food tonight, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went sushi.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had a TNT roll, which is... And it all comes back to food.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not my fault.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it was like... Maguro...
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to say there's Spicy Yahi and Yellowfin and some other stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it was good and hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Spicy Mayonnaise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Comments from chat, because of course this seems to be lighting up our chat room a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Bobby's on the same page we are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Blackwolf in chat says, I like the episodic model because that way if I don't continue the game, I'm not paying for the whole game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm only paying for the part of the game that I finished.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unfolded Raptor follows up with, but that's like watching 15 minutes of a movie then paying for another 15 minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: BlackWolf says, well, you know, if I want to walk out of the movie after the first 15 minutes, I didn't pay for the entire two-hour movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what's interesting is that you do see actually a lot of movie companies putting out like the first eight minutes of a movie on the internet for you to watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Amazon does that with TV episodes that you can download.
[SPEAKER_09]: And books!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'll give you samples of the books.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's a good idea, but I'm thinking that they should offer an incentive that if you decide after the first episode that you want to buy the whole game, that they give you an option to pay the difference.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to do that, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're just basically...
[SPEAKER_10]: The first episode is free.
[SPEAKER_10]: So after the first episode, after each chapter, you have the option to purchase the rest of the game or just purchase the next chapter.
[SPEAKER_09]: This really could be.
[SPEAKER_09]: We could be looking at the future of how we're going to pay for a lot of our games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially if this is successful.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how successful it will be because it's not a new game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think a lot of people that were interested in this game already got it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's certainly by tempting folks with a free chapter, a way to entice folks to check it out maybe and get a few more extra sales.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't see how that's going to be bad news for Microsoft or Lionhead.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the pot of the video game world.
But...
[SPEAKER_09]: Just one hit, man.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the interesting thing is, I mean, think about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: PSP Go, despite the crap we've given it on this show for not being that much better than the PSP, and especially price-wise, is going to be completely free of media.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be digital downloads only.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nintendo DS, or the DSi I should say specifically is a large part is going to be digital download only.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the biggest components and biggest games you see now on 360, PlayStation Network, Nintendo WiiWare are all download games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wouldn't be surprised at all if one of the major players Nintendo, Sony, or Microsoft in the next console and I think if anybody it's going to be Sony says
[SPEAKER_09]: No media, no discs, no Blu-ray, or this will play Blu-rays, but the games do not come out on Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_09]: It will be 100% digital distribution.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it will fail.
[SPEAKER_09]: You think?
[SPEAKER_10]: It will fail.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if it's like this, though?
[SPEAKER_10]: It will still fail.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know why it's going to fail?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's because people like owning stuff, and people like the option.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't have a problem with adding other ways you can purchase content.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you decide that, you know what, I don't feel like buying the game, I can buy either the episode, I can buy the full digital download, which is available on their service as well, or I can go purchase the retail game out there and do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I'm not given that option, then that's kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then what happens later on with, say, your console dies.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know a lot of times with the PlayStation 3 and stuff, I'm sure you can go re-download all that stuff later because it's just tied to your account.
[SPEAKER_10]: But still, though, it's not...
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't loan out your games.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't sell used.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's really... There's a lot more factors in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And people like the collector crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, hello, Modern Warfare 2 with some fucking night vision goggles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Can't digitally download night vision goggles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at my vault.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe I'm apples to oranges here a little bit, but then tell me why iTunes and iPods are so successful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because people that purchase Apple products are suckers for that kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you cannot deny iTunes is successful.
[SPEAKER_10]: But seriously, what phone out there, okay, what phone...
[SPEAKER_10]: has cartridges or disks that plug into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No phone does.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that kind of content is expected on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's why it's not a big deal.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, if Apple were to come out with, say, a console and decides that, okay, it's only going to be through their app store, then people might not be so apt to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They may go, eh, you know what, I'm just going to stick with a console that I can actually purchase physical stuff for.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: A lot of negativity in the chat room on this idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: Penelope.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: In Penelope, there's a lot of  and not necessarily the Fable 2 thing I'm talking about, the what if the next generation of gaming was all digital.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have  Actdeft says it will fail.
[SPEAKER_09]: Codeman says, I hate downloading games.
[SPEAKER_09]: My internet connection is so slow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Frisbee says, I like having a disc to hold or cart.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I like this comment from Sex with the Elderly says, I can't wait till people start stealing PSPs and all their content with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then having no media will suck ass.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll get into this later.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why the PSP goes sucks because we have to bring it up on every show.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um,
[SPEAKER_10]: They're really dumb.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be fair, I'm only picking on Sony because if the PSP Go is any indication, this is what they're thinking.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I don't think it's a good idea anyways with Microsoft either.
[SPEAKER_10]: I probably wouldn't buy a console from Microsoft if it didn't have physical media.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think that they're going to be more apt to having physical media because there's a lot more exposure out there, whereas it's just their service.
[SPEAKER_10]: What if someone doesn't have broadband or internet?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you're going to still lose some sales, and that's not a smart thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, what you should do is open up as many different avenues for people to purchase content.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like this, with Fable 2, I think is a good idea because now you have three different options.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can purchase the full game, you can purchase it by episode, or you can purchase the retail copy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or, hell, you can purchase the used retail copy out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, there's a lot of options for you, and options are never a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Game Informer
[SPEAKER_09]: ran a report, and in the latest issue of Game Informer, they actually did a survey where they surveyed 5,000 console owners, and according to these 5,000 console owners, the Xbox 360's current failure rate because of the E74 error, 54.2%.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, to be fair, they also surveyed for the PlayStation 3's and their yellow light issues, 10.3% on those, and the Wii's, 6.8%.
[SPEAKER_09]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: I can admit that I think those that go so far as to subscribe to a magazine or so forth probably use their Xbox 360s on a pretty regular basis, maybe a little bit heavier than some people who don't subscribe to magazines do.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so I think just by nature, the more you use your console, the more you're going to open it up to failure.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just true of any piece of hardware.
[SPEAKER_09]: The more you use it, the more it's likely to fail someday.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it's true in general statement, but it shouldn't be failing at the rates that they're talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll get to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's inevitable that the more you use something, the more likely it is to break.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's just a fact.
[SPEAKER_09]: But do I think this number is that far off?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say the real number is probably somewhere around a third.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I still look at this and go...
[SPEAKER_09]: Most companies that would have that type of failure rate on some type of thing they put out, like a television, a CD player, a car, would recall it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They would be forced to recall it.
[SPEAKER_10]: They can't.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'd be bad PR.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is good PR?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it's good PR for them because notice, even though it may have a 54% failure rate...
[SPEAKER_10]: People, they're still the second largest console share in the United States.
[SPEAKER_10]: People don't care, because people will go out and buy a new console once their console breaks, if it's out of warranty.
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll go buy a new one, because you know why?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because the games are good.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have a good library of games, and people don't give a crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, see, it goes back to the system is only good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And actually, that's probably the point as to because I know there's been people that have been asking, well, if you're so mad about it, why are you going to buy another one?
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's kind of like, well, dude, because I've invested all this money in the games, not just the physical games and the online games, that selling them back, I'm sorry, that's a waste of my money.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would think though that the failure rate is probably around that 54%.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've had, what, I have had maybe a total of eight consoles, and I think five of them died at one point.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody has their own ideas, and everybody has their own interpretations of these results.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I think we can all agree, it ain't 54.2%.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's obviously a skewed statistic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which way it's skewed, that's open to interpretation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Microsoft responded to it this week by the way and here was their response and this was in a statement to TG Daily Microsoft stands behind the Xbox 360 as a superior entertainment console with one of the best warranties in the industry
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Translation?
[SPEAKER_10]: and yes, that people do enjoy their console.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, they failed to address that their first line of systems that came out in the first few revisions sucks so bad that more than half of them have failed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And in fact, I would be surprised if not all of them failing at some point.
[SPEAKER_10]: The newer systems though, the newer revisions, the newer motherboards and stuff that they're putting out, less likely to fail, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And probably, you know,
[SPEAKER_10]: Up to par with, I'd say, the other consoles, you know, around that 10% range.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, a lot of people did buy it at launch, or at least relatively close to launch, and all their consoles are going to fail at some point or another, and it's just a matter of time.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like a ticking time bomb.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you're continually making them better, but you fucked up in the beginning, and that's a big problem, and you needed to recall all of them and get them all back and give them the new revisions.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be the proper thing to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wasn't going to quite say that much, but... You know, I... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a tricky issue.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, in the age of the internet, in gaming, we haven't really seen something like this before.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can't tell me that the PS3 and the Wii failure rates are anything close to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Close to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because they rushed to get it to market.
[SPEAKER_10]: And yes, it benefited them in the fact that their install base is a lot bigger.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, their hardware is kind of shoddy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do find it fascinating they dance around the statistic in their response they never deny it notice that in the response they don't deny it at all I think they expected it
[SPEAKER_09]: but that being but here's the thing what they say at the end of their statement as much as that's blowing smoke up my ass it's true I mean with the fact that they do have a choke hold on a lot of the big games out there on the market right now that can only be played on Xbox 360 and that they do have they are doing a lot of things right in that regard outside of just the system itself is kind of hard to deny yeah well here's my thing and that's why you know I'm essentially I guess some of you might say taking it a little bit
[SPEAKER_10]: But at the same time, I think if you're a consumer out there, and you're now worried about, you haven't bought a 360 yet, and you're worried that, okay, if I buy a 360 it's going to fail, I think that worry right now, it shouldn't be a worry, because now the systems have gotten to the point, though, where they aren't failing like they were doing before.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think it is safe to buy it now, because of all the hard revisions they've done.
[SPEAKER_10]: What they really should have done is all those revisions before the console was released, but, you know, hey...
[SPEAKER_10]: They made a huge mistake, and now they're in the process of trying to pick up the pieces and fixing the problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, will people forget about this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Will people remember this for the next console launch?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, you better damn believe it, and there will be a lot of people probably waiting and seeing if there's going to be issues with their next console.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, if you're curious what I decided to do with my Xbox 360, I am... He's going to set it on fire and throw it off a cliff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I might.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I decided I'm going to... Although that would be kind of fun, actually.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm going to give it a try.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to let Loki try to fix it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because he knows how to fix them, apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm going to let him try.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a 50% success rate.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'll take my chance.
[SPEAKER_09]: This way, if...
[SPEAKER_09]: This way I don't have to ship it off and pay those costs or anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Loki will do it for free.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll pay for parts or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, if it doesn't work, then I know Bobby has a friend that will buy for parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I will send it to the junkyard to be scrapped at the pick and pull, basically, of Xbox 360s.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will do that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Unless they don't want it because Loki ruins it, then I will set it on fire and throw it off.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll try not to ruin it too much.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, try it, please, because I do want to send it off to the virtual pick and pull if that happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I will, if I have to, because Loki can't fix it, not that I don't have faith in Loki, but if Loki can't fix it, then I am not going to buy an Xbox 360 Elite.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not going to wait for the price drop because I decided that was a stupid idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why would I, in turn, give Microsoft more money for their high-end console
[SPEAKER_09]: because the first one failed.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was dumb.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was an e-jerk reaction of mine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I take it back.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would instead buy the lowest, cheapest end Xbox 360 I can buy that's not used.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because if I go for the $199 Xbox arcade, I don't need a hard drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't need the fancy black color or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: The HDMI is on the arcades now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then at least I'll have HDMI moving forward.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's my plan.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Bobby is saying that his friend will want it even ruined.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, Loki, have fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you fix it, great.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't, off to the pick and pull.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hoping that we're on the positive end of my 50%.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll update your win-loss ratio here on our Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: The one that did work, that was successful, still works today.
[SPEAKER_10]: It still works.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: I keep waiting for it to fail again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will donate my 360 to science.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, question.
[SPEAKER_07]: When you did your repairs, was your film...
[SPEAKER_07]: Was your failure rate closer to the beginning or closer to the end?
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the end.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first one worked flawlessly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Second one, not so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's okay, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: You can still be in business, because your failure rate is close to Microsoft's failure rate, and they're still kicking.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Off to Loki's repair shop.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I blame their console for my failure anyways.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, Luke, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just going to get more...
[SPEAKER_09]: angsty comments if I continue on this whole tirade with the 360 and so forth it is a tricky line here I do feel a sense of
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn it, shit, fuck.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, with the whole Xbox 360 red ringing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But at the same time, I do understand shit happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it just makes me... I don't know if angry is the right word.
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes me irritated.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you try doing it without the... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes me irritated that so many people are having the same problem and yet Microsoft just says, well, but we're still cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're still the best.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you try it without the hard drive?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: This week I decided I've been having, in my personal life, I've been having the most shitty week you could possibly imagine.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm faking it really well on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's the thing, is that I just decided I'm not going to make my week worse by even trying that 360 this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, no problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll take care of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, how about other stuff, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about some World of Warcraft stuff?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: They've raised the cap to 85 for levels, but now they're going back and revamping old zones and changing them completely.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since the big cataclysm thing, some areas are destroyed, and then some of the places like Desolace and the Barrens are becoming green.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're redesigning cities so that you can fly.
[SPEAKER_08]: and, um, actually in Undercity too, um, they are actually, uh, having more interaction with the terrain, you can have flooding happen, so, also seven new zones, um, uh, like, um, Oldham, Mount, I guess that's Hyjal, and the Sunken City, which is an undersea zone, so you get underwater mounts and blah blah blah blah blah blah blah,
[SPEAKER_08]: Twilight Highlands, and Deep Home.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sounds very dwarfy in name.
[SPEAKER_09]: So all the rumors we heard about last week were essentially true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and new profession, archaeology.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, so you can be Indiana Jones, but a goblin.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: That actually would be enough to have me try it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Archaeology edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because I'd really like to see how something like that would enhance your character.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a while since I've played, but honestly, though, I'm sticking with RO.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if this is enough to get me back to WoW.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess I have to see it when the expansion comes out.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, never say never.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said I would never go back to Final Fantasy XI, and I did for a month, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know, I do think it's interesting because they've been talking about revamping old Azeroth for a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now they're going to do it and make you pay for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there is some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a little bit more as far as the racial abilities for the new races.
[SPEAKER_08]: For Worgen, you can switch between human and Worgen form instantaneously at will.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have Dark Flight, which increases movement speed by 70% for 10 seconds with a 3-minute cooldown.
[SPEAKER_08]: Viciousness, you have Flayer, and then Goblins are basically like the Ferengi of the Horde.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're the businessmen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good comparison.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can... There's actually a... You kind of look like Quark, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: A skill called... I wonder if you can give them Umox.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we're... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if they can make me a Warp Core Breach.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do they have the lobes for business?
[SPEAKER_08]: God, so nerdy.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Best Deals Anywhere is one of their skills.
[SPEAKER_08]: Better Living Through Chemistry, which increases alchemy skill by 15 points.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I like Time is Money.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it increases attack and casting speed by 1%.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Archaeology skill gives you the ability to excavate hidden items in ruins.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can do research notes that let you unlock new abilities for the Path of the Titans character progression.
[SPEAKER_08]: So... Go flip that whip.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: I think, personally, as a WoW player, I think goblins are annoying.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would never want to play as one.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was disappointed to hear that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, for other stuff going on with that, with the new dungeons, they actually have the level lists up for the five-man dungeons.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I don't want to say five-man.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to say five-character dungeons.
[SPEAKER_08]: That works for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or a party of five.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or sentai ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: Grim Battle is $85 Skywall is $80-$82 Abyssal Maw is $80-$83 Deep Home is $80-$83 Uldum is $83-$84 and an $85
[SPEAKER_08]: Blackrock Caverns for level 85, and then they do five-person versions of two of the older dungeons.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Deadmines has a level 85 version, and Shadowfang Keep.
[SPEAKER_09]: And for those that don't know, those are some beloved old-school instances from original WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then for four new raids, two of them have been revealed.
[SPEAKER_08]: One is the Firelands and one of them is called Nefarian's Throne Room, which features Blackwing Lairs and Boss Nefarian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hence the name!
[SPEAKER_08]: Har har!
[SPEAKER_09]: I do think it's interesting, this whole heroic Deadmines thing, because if you play original Deadmines at the level you're supposed to be playing Deadmines at, it takes forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's going to be interesting to see if they scale it back so Deadmines does not take as long to get through, or if it's still going to be like an epic four-hour run.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they're also putting in, with the 3.3 patch, there's a panel that's cross-server LFG for five-man dungeons, so you can get more people together to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's needed, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also new race combinations available now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have Human Hunter, Orc Mage, Night Elf Mage, Blood Elf Warrior, Dwarf Shaman, Dwarf Mage, Undead Hunter, Tarn Paladin, Tarn Priest, Gnome Priest, and Troll Druid.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a stat overhaul.
[SPEAKER_08]: The stats are being simplified.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you have your spell power, MP5, armor penetration, all that's gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really just a whole bunch of them.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's actually all up on the WoW page.
[SPEAKER_08]: For other class changes, just look on the panel on your thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's all there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Flying mounts are available.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Azeroth.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can fly around all you want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank heavens.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have your guild progression.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually have a numerical method now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You have raided battlegrounds, new PvP changes, a bunch of other crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a bunch of other stuff that I personally don't care about.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it sounds like it's going to be a pretty good expansion, a good swift kick in the pants to the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, that's one thing Blizzard likes to do.
[SPEAKER_09]: They really like to change that game up.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, that game is nothing like it used to be.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, see, I think that that's, honestly, the whole point that I see with that is this is how, you know, going through their head, well, people get tired of the same old, same old, same old, same old.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, people are going to leave when they get bored with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not give them no excuse to get bored?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not make something new?
[SPEAKER_08]: However, the thing that bored me was the way the game plays in general, and the fact that there's a bunch of idiots playing it, so...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's still not enough to read.
[SPEAKER_09]: You probably have to find the right click to play with.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would like to check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I might consider looking at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I certainly haven't installed World of Warcraft on this computer, and I still have my account.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might be worth it for me to check out, but certainly not until I'm healed up enough to be able to play a game that requires a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Star Trek Star Trek Star Trek
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to make the Olarian.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've already started picking races that I want to make the Olarians from.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you go on with your bad self.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to be orange.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, let's move on to more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new Slim system is 30% smaller, or actually 33% smaller, 36% lighter, and uses 34% less power.
[SPEAKER_10]: It comes with a 120GB hard drive, and of course at the new price of $299.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that is actually going to be released supposedly in the first week of September.
[SPEAKER_10]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, according to GameStop, it's actually supposed to be coming out next week, or as early as next week, but, you know, basically we'll be replacing the new, well, the 80 gig system and the 160 gig system that they had out already.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which just goes to prove that whenever you try to put out a cease and desist, you're only validating the material.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on top of all this, they dropped the 80GB system to $299 as well, and they also dropped the $160 to $399, which begs the question, why the hell did you do that?
[SPEAKER_10]: At least in that order.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, they totally don't get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why would you drop the price of those two systems?
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand to clear them out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_10]: That makes perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then you announce the new system at the same time.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now I have these new slim 120GB systems in my store with 80GB systems that are the same price.
[SPEAKER_10]: Duh!
[SPEAKER_10]: Am I going to buy the new system that has a larger hard drive for the same price?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I think I will.
[SPEAKER_10]: And at the same time, would you really spend an extra $100 for an extra 40GB on your hard drive?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's also been a discovery.
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently when they were registering the Slim, I guess with the FCC and all this...
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess filing for another SKU that's going to be with a 250GB hard drive.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's probably coming later on.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, great!
[SPEAKER_10]: Now we know that there's a larger hard drive system coming out later on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why the hell are we going to, you know, if you're really not in a hurry to buy a system, you'll probably want to wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this other one might be more money too.
[SPEAKER_10]: It probably will be.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus, I still don't really know, what do I put on this hard drive?
[SPEAKER_10]: All those games installs because most of the games that are released now on Blu-ray do require an install because their drive is slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the other thing too, in case you're wondering, the system did get rid of the alternative operating system install as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you're thinking about installing Linux on this slim system, you are dead wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: That won't be happening.
[SPEAKER_06]: They'll find a way.
[SPEAKER_10]: So way to go, Sony, removing features from your system as well now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We know they're going to find a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Linux community is stubborn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus, how many people really honestly are getting the PlayStation 3 to install Linux on it?
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not like the fat ones are hard to find.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's only offering them a challenge now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously, people may have been okay with not doing it because it's readily available now, but
[SPEAKER_10]: The thing is, why would you remove that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I understand that you don't need to necessarily do that, but really, did that cost anything to them?
[SPEAKER_10]: No?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, the other funny thing, too, is it takes two seconds longer to boot up each time, for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Strange.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: or not the mouse but you know what I mean when you have the thing in place you can kind of see in the background some of the stuff except now you can interact with that background if that makes sense at all.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, a status indicator is coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: This will be located in the top right corner of your PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'll show your user icon that you have, however many friends that you have that are online, and also, most importantly, a little mail indicator if you have any new messages.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, we'll have a little scrolling tick bar with the latest news from PSN, which I think they already kind of have.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that'll just be adapted into this new status indicator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, apparently, now when you hit the PS button, no longer will the battery life indicator sit right on top of the clock.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what's kind of cool, though, is those new dynamic themes that they have.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you seen those?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're animated themes now that you can have in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, like, they have a little big planet one where the Sackboy's running on, you know, a planet.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I guess you also now have premium avatars, they're saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know what that means
[SPEAKER_09]: The Friends list is getting also reformatted.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shortcuts to the PlayStation Store, because naturally they want to make it easier for you to buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And apparently a big change coming to trophies.
[SPEAKER_09]: With 3.0 firmware, game developers will now be able to modify how trophies are displayed for add-on content.
[SPEAKER_09]: So apparently you still have the list combined when you're looking at the PlayStation Network or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I guess the developers have the freedom to...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: SSJ100 Matt in our chatroom, chat.orange-radio.com asks an interesting question about PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why is it that with each new in-creation of the PS3, it keeps losing features?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's lost backwards compatibility, flash card reader, fewer USB slots, and now the inability to install an OS onto it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it just me, or shouldn't a console evolve with each new SKU?
[SPEAKER_09]: From the looks of it, it's devolving so much that we will lose controller support in two years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, that part was sarcastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're dropping stuff out of the system to cut the cost of the system because that's the only way they can drop it to $2.99 without losing $500 or whatever on each system.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I thought backwards compatibility was all software-based now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought so too.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's not the whole PS2 in your PS3 like it was at the beginning.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought so too, but for whatever reason, maybe licensing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't imagine it would be licensing though because Linux is free.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you don't even have to...
[SPEAKER_10]: You're buying, or you're not really buying, you're downloading Linux anyways off the internet and installing it to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not like it's already there or something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we got one more story from Jamie, then we're gonna get into some release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a pony.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's my story.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you and me are big comic book nerds.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this is news that makes me particularly happy as long as they get good comics.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a digital comic reader that's going to be on the PSP in December.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually are working with Marvel to have...
[SPEAKER_08]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I like actually buying comics.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I love going to the store.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I read a bunch of digital comics anyway, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, actually, now that I think about it, I don't really use our PSP that much, but if I did, I would be interested in it, because I actually have downloaded a number of comics on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_08]: I read the first three graphic novels of Bone on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_08]: on my iPhone and I downloaded the Star Trek movie countdown, the tie-in that was supposed to be the prequel to the events in the movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I thought that was very convenient.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was definitely cheaper than going and paying three bucks for the issue.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then again, I've gone right out and I'm reading the Nero book
[SPEAKER_08]: And Marvel, I know, would have to be behind it because they have been pushing the whole digital comic thing pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft in our chatroom says I hope it's subscription based SSJ100Matt says What does DC Comics have to say about this?
[SPEAKER_09]: They did make the DC Universe game PS3 exclusive and now they're supporting its competition
[SPEAKER_08]: DC and Marvel have teamed up before for a number of things I think that DC would have to hop in on this and it would be good for all the businesses and you know what I would actually like to see is see some of the indie comic companies be included in this you know maybe even a web comic reader
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, they are going to have... It's not just Marvel, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's why I said Archie and Image are involved as well, but I didn't mention anything on DC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wouldn't see why DC couldn't jump in on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're more than welcome, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just haven't done it yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, let's move on to some release dates before the comics get here and we lose DarkSakura because she'll be too busy reading them.
[SPEAKER_10]: RavenSquad Hidden Dagger Xbox 360
[SPEAKER_10]: Curse Mountain Sudoku Ball Detective Harvest Moon Frantic Farming Puzzle Day Harvest Moon
[SPEAKER_10]: Batman Arkham Asylum, making its way out on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fallout 3, Broken Seal and Point Lookout, available on PC and on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dissidia, Final Fantasy, making its way out on the PSP, which will be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Real Fishing Angler's Dream on the Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is going to be an excellent title for the DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Click, Diss and Make Up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, I'm being sarcastic there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's probably going to really suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: Same with this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wizards of Waverly Place, based on the Disney, I don't know, teen comedy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Emergency Room, Real Life Rescues on the DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: Harvest Moon, Magical Melody being ported to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Monokimiya 2 Fall of Alchemy getting its limited edition on PlayStation 2 and that would be it alright let's move into some Japanese release dates and after a couple of slow weeks we finally have a pretty busy week over in Japan look at the Xbox 360 Dream Club comes out on the Xbox 360 and I'm sorry I have to read the description of this game it certainly does not sound like something we will be getting over here but it looks all kinds of awesome do you have a pure heart?
[SPEAKER_09]: welcome in
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: the ladies are not just companions they are performers as well watch them sing and dance the better you know them the more songs they will perform be sure to get to the club during the special event nights instead of the usual maid outfits the ladies will welcome you and get up such as yukatas and bikinis have a lovely clubbing experience get your VIP card today that game again is Dream Club from D3 and it sounds pretty fucking amazing and I want to play it you know if it's D3 we may get that over here
[SPEAKER_10]: Because D3, they're likely to put out crazy shit like that over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially since the women in this game, based on the screenshots, have giant boobies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, another game with chicks with giant boobies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also on the Xbox 360 this week, Memories Off 6, Next Relation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, Next Relation.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, hopefully she's not related if Memories are off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Moving on to other consoles.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the PlayStation 3, Grand Theft Auto 4 gets a price reduction in Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, Fear 2 also making its way out to Japan this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was also on the Xbox 360, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gendai Daisenryaku
[SPEAKER_09]: Ishoku Sokuhatsu
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, it looks kind of like an RTS type of strategy.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks like a strategy, command and conquer-ish type of game on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: Memories Off 6 is getting a PlayStation 2 port.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tomb Raider Anniversary and Legend to get price reductions if you never caught those on the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: On the Nintendo DS, Super Robo Gakuen comes out this week on the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gakuen is high school...
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's Robot High School?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that what this is?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, is it G-A-K-U-E-N?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that would be High School.
[SPEAKER_09]: So yeah, it looks like Robot High School is the game here.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm trying to look at screenshots, but can't.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it looks like a little type of a strategy type game coming out this week on the DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: And lastly, looking at the PSP real quick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you can...
[SPEAKER_09]: import in Japan the English language version of Final Fantasy Dissida if you want because obviously that's a big game we're getting out here this week I do want to point out though Soul Calibur Broken Destiny is out in Japan this week that is the new Soul Calibur game on PSP so I bet we do have some hardcore Soul Calibur fans that will want to import that probably not you can wait another week and then get that actually fine that's going to do it for PSP releases and Japanese releases
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, for our UK releases, on the 26th, we have Invincible Tiger, The Legend of Hantao, and Watchmen The End is Nigh Part 2 on Xbox 360, both of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 27th, for PS3, is Invincible Tiger, The Legend of Hantao.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the 28th, we have Allied Ace Pilots on DS, Batman Arkham Asylum, Xbox 360 and PS3, King of Fighters 12...
[SPEAKER_08]: Meh, Might and Magic, Clash of Heroes on DS, Soul Calibur Broken, Destiny on PSP, Supercar Challenge, and World Cup of Pool.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: World Cup of Pool?
[SPEAKER_09]: Pool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me make sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: It makes it sound like it's a cup full of pool, but chlorine-flavored water, but I'm assuming it's... I'm assuming it's like a swimming game or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Cup of poo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_09]: Two Girls World Cup?
[SPEAKER_04]: La la la la la.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, I don't know how to follow that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we'll talk about the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sony, one of the things they announced while they were talking about secret console revisions and stuff like that is that they're
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: And they will apparently be less costly to develop for and cost less to gamers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, no real prices have been announced yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: They plan on having 15 at launch and 50 by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_10]: And some of the titles that they did mention were coming out include Tetris, Field Runners, Heroes of Sparta, and Mini-Gore.
[SPEAKER_10]: And once again...
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: That might make it a little bit worth it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if they hadn't, you would have bitched about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I would have bitched about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We all would have bitched about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it doesn't sound like there's no hardware feature.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's no reason these games can't be on the original PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: So why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to sell them to the original PSP owners.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which begs the question, why would I buy the PSP Go?
[SPEAKER_10]: Why would anybody buy the PSP Go other than the fact that it's...
[SPEAKER_10]: It has a sliding screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that really worth more money?
[SPEAKER_09]: I will buy a PSP Go when the price drops.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it won't take long.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet you anything it will not take long.
[SPEAKER_09]: It may be 2010, but it won't take long.
[SPEAKER_09]: When the price of the PSP Go matches the price of the PSP, which has to happen eventually, I will buy one.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what they're going to do?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to get rid of the original PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then they're going to make you buy that of course it's not going to happen anytime soon because you've got like bundles now for Dissidia, you've got a bundle for Gran Turismo coming out in September you've got a bundle with Assassin's Creed coming out in November
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no reason that you can't find a PSP 3000.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alpha Catanagram in chat says, I would buy a PSP Go when the price drop occurs and use it as a belt buckle.
[SPEAKER_09]: That actually sounds kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you ever seen those belt buckles with the scrolling text on them?
[SPEAKER_09]: And it gets everybody to look at your crotch?
[SPEAKER_08]: You can order those at ThinkGeek.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've seen those before.
[SPEAKER_08]: The LED belt buckles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine having a PSP Go showing a little movie on your crotch.
[SPEAKER_09]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which is actually footage of your crotch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: You nasty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which would be fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, did they ever say what's going to happen with my UMDs?
[SPEAKER_09]: How I'm going to put my UMDs on my Go?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but I read a funny article by GameStop.
[SPEAKER_10]: They were saying that they expect them to be traded in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not that there's going to be an official program.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just that people are going to be so enamored with PSP Go that they're just going to throw all their UMDs out and rebuy the content again because they love Sony so much.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure there are some fanboys that will, but I just don't see it being an epidemic.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm sure that people would do that, because obviously Sony's not giving them a way to... My thing is, at the same time, if you do own an original PSP system, and they may just say, fuck you, you own an original PSP system, why the hell do we need a method for you to
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, dump your UMDs on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just buy new games!
[SPEAKER_10]: Or, I don't know, just don't buy a new system because you have a PSP system already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why would you buy another system, you idiot?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just my opinion there.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just still not seeing the reasons to jump ship.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Go, though, I think would be good for people who don't already own... Even then, it's not the right price.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say if you don't own a PSP, buy a PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't need the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing that super that it gets you unless you really need a quiet system or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there are ways you can run stuff off your memory card even now.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, no, legit ways, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, you can still purchase all those games online if you do want to do digital downloads.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just buy your own memory card.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you want to bet that half of the games in this mini thing are...
[SPEAKER_09]: Virtual Console Rehashes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Old games sold out again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Galaga on my PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: They already have PlayStation Network games that are independent titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're like PlayStation Network games like Super Stardust and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: How's that any different?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, the file sizes are smaller and they're going to be cheaper.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whoop-dee-shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, just make them cheaper and make the file sizes smaller.
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't need to necessarily make it a whole new category of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess if you want to draw more attention to the PSP or something, you can do that, which is what they did.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Making something cheaper and cheaper to develop for doesn't really warrant them putting another bullet point in their system, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: M.T.V.
[SPEAKER_09]: Games and Harmonix
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Beatles Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's still rock band.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just a singing version of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you don't have the instruments.
[SPEAKER_09]: You just have the singing parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: To be fair, you know, again, it's about options.
[SPEAKER_09]: It goes back to what we were talking about earlier in the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just another way to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: There are some people that don't really want all those plastic instruments.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then I could see this really being aimed at the Beatles fans who are...
[SPEAKER_09]: wanting to have the game, but they don't want all this plastic instrument crap in their house.
[SPEAKER_03]: Those people are communists.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might be a small audience, but it's an audience.
[SPEAKER_09]: And certainly they want to sell this game to as many people as possible.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or perhaps you already own all the instruments and everything and you just want some extra microphones so you can do your three-part harmonies.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually a certainly plausible outcome as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: No SingStar Beatles, but you know, hey, Rock Band Beatles, it's not like it looks that bad or anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks pretty awesome, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really looking forward to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if they are planning on releasing this, they sure as hell haven't told anyone yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, this might also only be in Britain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind, all this news is coming out of Europe, so it may not be something that's actually planned here, but it might be just planned over there.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: It actually originally came out in Japan on the PC-8801 in 1986, and then the Mega CD version came out, which of course for the Sega CD over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: They actually made a ton of improvements over the PC-88 version.
[SPEAKER_08]: Instead of just having the static background, the background for each level is full motion video with a polygon overlay for all the ships and asteroids and everything coming at you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's a really, really good game.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was an FM7 version that was also released.
[SPEAKER_08]: and it came out in the US for PC but that was put up by Sierra Online at any rate it was actually a competitor with Star Fox for the day except Star Fox was all fully rendered on the cartridge and like I said this had a
[SPEAKER_08]: A full motion video background, and it still is a traditional kind of shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly though, it had better, graphically it was better, but it didn't have that innovative feel to it that Star Fox did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, so, yeah, terrorists take over the Earth, and, uh, we get these, uh, cool little ships that get to, you know, shoot people in the end.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, it did have a sequel, which was, um, Sylphid the Lost Planet, um, which was a PS2 game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then Project Sylphid was actually a spiritual successor, um, not really a game in the series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, a little bit of trivia about Sylphid too, um, is that, um, there was, uh, a monster in Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_08]: that's called Sylphid.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, um, in, uh, Mahiro-matic, there's actually a jetpack that Mahiro uses called the Sylphid.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then in BlazBlue, um, Sylphid is the name of Rachel Alucard's tribe.
[SPEAKER_08]: This game also has one of the best intros ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really one that you have to watch and listen to.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the other thing that I really dig about this one, as opposed to the original version of it, is as you're flying through the level, you get radio feedback from the rest of the fleet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like in Star Fox.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's not quite the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: In Star Fox, if you go back earlier in that file, we'll play a little bit of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little different.
[SPEAKER_08]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think those have really good music, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I heard it yelling... There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and see, in Star Fox, the way it was, is that it was your squadron, your formation of ships, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You had your partners.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this, it's you're getting... Like, have you ever... Alright, I know this is kind of old school, but have you ever listened to just CB channels?
[SPEAKER_09]: Back in the day, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: and orders went out or feedback went out or some sort of announcement it may not be necessarily directed to you but you're still going to hear it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do people still use CD?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, trackers do.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you see though in that sense then it actually adds a sense of realism to the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for the record, in terms of if you're traveling with people, like in your separate vehicles, having a CB is actually very good for areas that you'll lose cell reception.
[SPEAKER_09]: Plus cell cost minutes, anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not always.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at any rate, I think it's a fantastic game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silphied.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I didn't say Slipeed.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, people used to do that all the time too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Your classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not the newer one that came out on 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the old school one on Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the sequel though is PS2.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I played that one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I have it somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: And for the record, they were talking about Policenauts earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: I came very close to using Policenauts as the classic game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, we're going to get into a story about police knots later, but I'll leave that for later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I didn't mean to.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a Twitter thing, so it's going to come up later.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking of Twitter, we'll get into Twitter topics right after a little bit of a break.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are going to take a break, though, here in studio to cover more.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, we take the break, though, to get energized, to pee, to maybe order pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Becky's bringing me tacos.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, lucky.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was going to offer to you on the air, guys, do you want me to make you guys pizza?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's actually okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I probably shouldn't because I had a big old crepe earlier today.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have organic mushroom and black olive pizzas.
[SPEAKER_09]: That does sound kind of good.
[SPEAKER_08]: I also have plain cheese pizzas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want any unless you're going to have some.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, if I make pizza, I can just have it for lunch tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: My man, by the way, is not here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I am going to be going stir-crazy so people will be seeing me in IRC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be back with more of Orange Lounge Radio right after this.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have plenty more to talk about in Part B tonight, including our rapid-fire news and talk about a new interesting achievement on Xbox 360 for killing 1,000 children in a game and a possible revamp of DSiWare and a Final Fantasy game you will probably never, ever see.
[SPEAKER_09]: We will talk about all of that in Part B after a quick break, so stay tuned here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anonymous things.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want my address out there on the internet.
[SPEAKER_09]: But yeah, so it cost me a little more money since I do that, but you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still have an OLR Wii, but I haven't done anything with that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we need like an OLRPS3.com or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll work on it someday.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, if you're interested in helping us build websites and develop, you want to... We pay great, nothing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But pat on the back and job well done.
[SPEAKER_10]: Eventually.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: 7 bucks, $7.50
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: You've seen me do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was some type of Namco 25th anniversary thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it was Pac-Man, Ms.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pac-Man, and Galaga were all on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They wanted 195,000 tickets for that thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's like $3,000 in real money.
[SPEAKER_10]: Trust me, they're not really that expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dang.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probably a few hundred bucks and that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could build one cheaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it did look pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was kind of curious to get one, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: T.O.A.G.A.C.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe a little broken, but it'll still get you to the stream.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you can listen to us on the iPhone on the All Games app.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can listen to us on the PSP on the OLR app.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're covered.
[SPEAKER_09]: One way or another.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twitter topics tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: Every night we invite you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need a theme song for Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll have to think about that for next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like Conan O'Brien has a little theme song for his Twitter segment.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You should do...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rizzlem.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was thinking something.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll think of something for next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the meantime, don't call me during the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why are my parents calling me during the show?
[SPEAKER_09]: You should use the beep.
[SPEAKER_09]: You should use that beep.
[SPEAKER_09]: What beep?
[SPEAKER_09]: That beep beep should be the theme for Twitter topics?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Big Black Cock We haven't had that in a while
[SPEAKER_09]: Ray Ayanami wants us to talk about Raystorm HD and not just because his name is in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But apparently there is a new game coming out called Raystorm HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a remake, possibly, of an old school Taito game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently they...
[SPEAKER_09]: It appeared on PartnerNet.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where they saw it.
[SPEAKER_09]: PartnerNet is Xbox's little testing grounds for Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, somebody did.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there it is, RayStorm HD.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't remember the first one very well.
[SPEAKER_09]: I almost feel like I should bring it up on YouTube and look at a clip of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does anyone know the game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Jamie, do you know RayStorm?
[SPEAKER_08]: If it has to do with, what was it, Ray Crisis?
[SPEAKER_08]: Then I think so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on, I'm bringing up some of the gameplay here in studio so I can check this out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, this is like a fun show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun series.
[SPEAKER_09]: So if you schmuck fans, alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, the graphics look nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like major targeting.
[SPEAKER_09]: This was an arcade game originally, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember, but I've got all kinds of versions of that series.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is that a vertical game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that looks like a vertical game.
[SPEAKER_09]: The graphics are kind of rad for something this old school.
[SPEAKER_09]: I imagine it has to be an arcade game.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: and they're calling it a 24 hour gaming marathon to fund pediatric cancer research and treatment and I guess this is taking place on October 17th of this year and they're trying to get all these sites to come together to raise money for this extra life charity and it's to raise money for pediatric cancer which sounds like a great cause honestly it's going to be 8am on October 17th and they have all these groups participating I guess Sarcastic Gamer
[SPEAKER_09]: I've not listened to that show, but I've seen their thing on iTunes as part of this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Destructoid is apparently on board as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Limit Break Radio, I guess they'll probably be doing a Final Fantasy XI marathon, wants to know if we can come on board as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to commit to something if I can't give it 100%.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think it's a great cause.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I think if we don't do it ourselves, we'll have to support somebody else doing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Gaming marathon, October 17th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Could we do it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_09]: 24 hours worth of games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obscure fucking vault games would be the theme of our marathon.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think anybody else could do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that would be good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And to keep the continuation going, we'll have different systems hooked up so that while one system's going, we can switch games to a new one and just pass the controller over so that we don't have a lull in playing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe like a new game every hour or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Works for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want to figure it out because I don't know if we could do that here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic Adventure Marathon.
[SPEAKER_09]: It might be too small of a space here.
[SPEAKER_09]: We might have to do it at the... Do it in the front room.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if we can get all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: The weather should be better.
[SPEAKER_09]: We could always go back to the garage.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: If we do it on the big TV, though, we can actually put up a cam footage without a refresh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because you've seen me take pictures off of my TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, would you be willing to do it too?
[SPEAKER_09]: Could we do this for 24 hours?
[SPEAKER_10]: We could do it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have HD capture stuff now.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I could capture... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: We could stream it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll have to figure something out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to commit until we're 100% sure we can give it our all, but we are interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we've been talking about doing a gaming marathon for a long time, so it would be fun to get in on something like this with some other podcasts and things like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: And certainly the cause is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we want to help.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still, though, wanted, you know, along those same lines, wanted to do a classic game segment every week, too, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we should do nothing but classic games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, we should just do obscure fucking classic games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm not talking about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm talking about, you know, us having a classic gaming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, like on YouTube or something?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: Might be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you guys have some ideas, get in touch with us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at Orangelandrader.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd be curious what you guys think would be fun for the marathon.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: So thanks for the heads up on that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll have to read a little more on that website about who we contact for more information.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if you're out there listening, please get in touch with us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Mailbag at Orangelandrader.com because I think that could be fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tweet from Actdeft to our Twitter OLR wants us to mention the Policenauts English localization.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently there is a fan translation of Policenauts that was finished.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now this game of course was out on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was also on the Sega Saturn and get this, the 3DO.
[SPEAKER_09]: And what makes this game notable is that it was a Hideo Kojima game.
Hold on.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: point and click game but it never came out in English but the fans got together and translated it and it's a patch that you can apply to your ROM I'm supposing of Policenauts I don't know what version it is that they patched I'm assuming it's got to be the PS1 that's probably the easiest one but there you go so if you want to check out Policenauts you can do that now
[SPEAKER_10]: in a completely non-legit way.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I mean, if you actually own the import game, and you make a copy of it, dump your own copy of it with whatever program's out there, and you patch it with this, you probably know that most people aren't going to do this, or that are downloading this are probably getting it illegally, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: The game is 13 years old, and I say, if they cared that much about it, they would have translated it to English 13 years ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Obviously, they don't care at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nope, they don't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura is digging it out of the vault right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Actdeft says in chat right now that I think it's the PS1 version.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: A couple more quick Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_09]: Technicolor with the three wants to know what are our thoughts on the Halo 3 ODST tour truck thing going around the country right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if they have one of those at the State Fair.
[SPEAKER_09]: They had Rock Band 2 there last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: um play Halo 3 there there's a good impression of what Halo ODST is going to be like I mean really they haven't changed too much I mean yeah you're playing you know the Shock Trooper but and it's not the scale's been kind of dropped down a little bit but I don't know it's not like it's like night and day gameplay I think hmm
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, some more Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_09]: TigerClaw305 says, Blizzard is planning a pseudo-land support for StarCraft 2 and possibly Diablo 3 and links this to a story talking about, there was a quote in here I wanted to read, where the interviewer, and this is from ShackNews.com, asked the developer if they were possibly working on a solution that would be like a pseudo-land connection where the game will check in with Battle.net to authenticate and then it'll go back to acting like a land.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they replied, something like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maintaining a connection with Battle.net, I don't know if it's once or periodically, but then also having a peer-to-peer connection between players to facilitate a very low-ping, high-bandwidth connection.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are the things that they're working on.
[SPEAKER_09]: So a bit of an olive branch to the community, maybe?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would think this type of thing was probably always planned, but they're going to want the regular pings to Battle.net to make sure the game is legit.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, because if they only pinged it once, somebody would figure out a way to patch that.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're going to figure out a way to patch it anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the lanners are going to have to give the concession that they're going to have to attach to Battle.net to give this game, but they'll at least not have to play through Battle.net.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that would suck.
[SPEAKER_09]: If Battle.net goes down, your whole game is fucked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Right?
[SPEAKER_09]: So hopefully there'll be some type of concession there.
[SPEAKER_09]: SB Hale tweets us and says, $300 PS3, definitely not an under-the-radar story, but for those of us Xbox 360 and Wii owners, do you feel there's a need to own all three consoles?
[SPEAKER_09]: Besides the fact that the PS3 is a Blu-ray player, of course, I've yet to find a good reason why I shouldn't pick one up at that price.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you know the golden rule of gaming here at Orange Lounge Radio is that a system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The interesting thing about the PlayStation though as a console is that you also have that added Blu-ray in.
[SPEAKER_09]: So you do  I mean whether you say besides that or not, you have to factor that in a little bit to your decision.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think the question is really going to be does what the PlayStation 3 offer
[SPEAKER_09]: As far as exclusive games and things you can't get on your Xbox 360, is that what you want?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want games like LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want MAG?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you want Final Fantasy XIV and some of these games that are PlayStation 3 exclusive?
[SPEAKER_09]: Is that worth the $300 to you?
[SPEAKER_09]: If so, then yeah, you gotta get one.
[SPEAKER_09]: If not right now, then you can stand to wait a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: But also don't discount the other features of the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: The fact that it is a pretty good media device as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: That it does have home, if that's something that interests you.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the whole fact that you can have the online movie store, which has some different offerings than the Xbox 360 does.
[SPEAKER_09]: The HD movies and all that are important to you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think you have to consider all of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But in the end, if you're getting everything that you possibly need out of gaming on your 360, then no, you don't need a PS3.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if there's something that the PS3 offers you that you need, and I will say it's a hell of a lot quieter, then go for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, by the way, if you don't have an HDTV though, there's no point in getting Blu-ray.
[SPEAKER_09]: There really isn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I'm assuming you probably are an HDTV owner.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Zbunchat wants to point out Final Fantasy XIV is going to be on the PC too.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, and that may be where most people want to play it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura found her copy of Policenauts on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_09]: There it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wish we had webcam in this studio but we don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's definitely all in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to put that on the website?
[SPEAKER_09]: The Pix Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, there we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more, and sorry if we didn't get to all the tweets tonight, but Matt Ostrovsky says, Interesting story about a company that is close to making the first PS3 mod chip.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh, could a mod chip be coming soon to the PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you heard about this, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, but that would be a pain in the ass to burn stuff onto Blu-ray and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blu-ray discs are really expensive and that's like almost 50 gigs of data.
[SPEAKER_10]: Direct Boot of PS3 Original Import and Backup Games
[SPEAKER_09]: Direct boot of PS2, originally imported back of games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm assuming that means only if your console plays PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Does multi-region Blu-rays, multi-region DVDs.
[SPEAKER_09]: No configuration disk needed.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a transparent stealth operation, they call it.
[SPEAKER_09]: No USB interface.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's up to date.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only 12 wires to solder.
[SPEAKER_09]: Solder?
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, solder.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tempting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, but still you have to solder, and what if they fix it with a patch?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're going to be screwed because that thing's hardwired to your system.
[SPEAKER_10]: My Wii is soldered, and it has a soldered-in mod chip.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not worried about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that thing has an on-off switch, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I don't use it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's always on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, they have it just in case, and it's only really had to have been updated once, and really I don't need the on-off switch on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just an optional thing you can install on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, worst case scenario, if for whatever reason this decided, you know, they broke it or something, or they, you know, disabled the chip, you can always clip those wires that you soldered.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, it's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, there's a whole thing on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look at the tweets to OLR, Ask SSJ100Mac, because he posted it there.
[SPEAKER_09]: How much is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I said how much is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't see on that site, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, if you want to tweet us a story that's... We like stuff that's under the radar, because obviously you knew this week we were going to talk about WoW Cataclysm.
[SPEAKER_09]: You knew we were going to talk about the PS3 Slim.
[SPEAKER_09]: But usually the stuff that might fall off the radar, we definitely want you to bring to our attention on Twitter or any topics you want us to discuss.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep an eye out Sundays, a couple hours before we go live.
[SPEAKER_09]: I usually put a shout-out on there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, let's get into some rapid-fire news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, you're going to need to stop reading the tweets.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, the first picture's up.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, the Policenauts game?
[SPEAKER_09]: And that's what, on OrangeLoungeRadio.com in our picture gallery, right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been waiting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm ready to go.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, Loki, rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rapid, rapid.
[SPEAKER_10]: You may remember that Sega had a survey asking what should be the next game that they publish on Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network, and we were, well...
[SPEAKER_10]: Earthworm Jim won that.
[SPEAKER_10]: However, they had to pull Earthworm Jim because, unfortunately, Interplay, at the same time, also announced that they're making a new Earthworm Jim game for PlayStation Network, WiiWare, and Xbox Live Arcade, as well as mobile platforms.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, new Earthworm Jim coming, but there's still another Xbox Live Arcade Genesis pull, so you'll have to see who wins that, I think, currently, right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: ToeJam & Earl is winning that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, there is a rumor that looks like Canada will be getting a new Elite Bundle.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be coming with Halo 3, and on top of that, they're also going to be throwing in a wireless network adapter, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And all that can be had for $349.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I think that's Canadian dollars.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_10]: Apparently, it is available.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually going to be... It's available right now at The Source, which I guess is a Circuit City affiliate out of Canada.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they have the online offer.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually for $3.29.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Guitar Hero 5 will be incompatible with World Tour.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, the download content for World Tour, I guess, of the 158 songs that are on World Tour and Smash Hits, you'll only be able to download 152 of those back to your console, I guess, when you're importing songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, I mean, that makes sense, because Rock Band, there was like five tracks you couldn't download, or three or five tracks that you couldn't download because of licensing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, by the way, the chat wants us to mention that ToeJam & Earl was the new winner of the poll once the Earthworm Jim remake was mentioned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Diablo 3, Witch Doctor, Wizard, Monk
[SPEAKER_09]: but Monk by the way was originally in the Hellfire expansion in the original Diablo where Barbarian, Bard, Rogue, Sorcerer and Warrior showed up so I assume there's going to be at least a couple more classes that show up in Diablo 3 although not too many because you know they got to do the expansions later on right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, the Wii and the DS are getting new Tetris games next year.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's right, it's a partnership between Majesco and Tetris Online.
[SPEAKER_09]: They'll be coming out on the Wii and the DS in the spring of 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: No idea what the Tetris game is going to be like, but you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tetris DS was pretty badass.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if we necessarily need another one.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Eye of Judgment is making its way to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was announced at Gamescom this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: You will get basically a version of Eye of Judgment, but of course there is no eye.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's why there's no bet.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's still a lot of questions as to whether this will use the same cards or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: We just know the game is coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Loki says it will not count towards the bet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why not, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: The reason why it won't count towards the bet is because it's not as ridiculous as the Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Eye of Judgment is an actual physical card game that you had to play using the PlayStation 9 camera.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, it was the camera in the game portion of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not so sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even if I did add the Eye of Judgment to the bed or whatever, it still wouldn't meet a million units.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not going to do that because it's just stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: We need to move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to find a new cause and a new outfit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, DarkSakura, do you have some rapid fire news for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: I do indeed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, Midway Europe is now Trade West Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were purchased.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's actually gone through.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's being fully rebranded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, LittleBigPlanet is getting a re-release with 18 new levels and 7 download content packs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty cool, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I remember when Tradewest, by the way, did Double Dragon back in the day.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were a big 8-bit developer.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if it's the same company, but I just remember that name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the LittleBigPlanet packs are going to be the Metal Gear Solid level pack featuring the Paintinator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Metal Gear Solid costumes, monster costumes, monster packs, history costumes, history pack, and animal costumes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Probs to a Media Molecule
[SPEAKER_08]: well and since we've had some discussion about Hideo Kojima he actually has said that he finds Metal Gear Solid series very puzzling too which is why he keeps detailed timelines for all of the characters in the game he says and I quote this is especially tricky when you create the future first and then go back in time to create something new there are a lot of small aspects where sometimes it doesn't match completely sounds like
[SPEAKER_08]: Marvel Comics, or Star Trek.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, but they fixed all that with the movie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not the newer canon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, one other thing I wanted to mention, though, was the whole...
[SPEAKER_09]: LittleBigPlanet stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forgot what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The water level is coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's something I wanted to say about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's real water now, so you can actually make real water levels and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: One more comment from chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amazatsuma on the whole Tingle bet says, We will move on once we see Loki dresses Tingle.
[SPEAKER_09]: Am I right, Penelope?
[SPEAKER_07]: I renamed them back to OL Army.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, they were balls for a little while.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had your opportunity.
[SPEAKER_10]: I can't help it if you can't come through with your end of the bargain.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just like...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I make bets that I know I'm going to win for example, there was somebody one of my customers was betting me on the top grossing game this year and he said that he bet that Wii Sports Resort was going to be the top grossing game not only was he cocky about it but he said that it would beat out anything the number 2 one by 2 million units and he also said so my guess of course was Modern Warfare 2 because you're a fucking idiot if you think Wii Sports Resort is going to sell that many units
[SPEAKER_10]: And he's like, fine, I'll give you Modern Warfare 2 on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm like, you are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: But okay, I'll take that bet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I will win that bet as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is the bet?
[SPEAKER_10]: We haven't figured it out yet what the actual prize of the bet will be, but he's so confident that he's going to win that he'll probably do something stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I just have to wait for him to act on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well, there's apparently an achievement that was discovered for the new game Fairytale Fights, where you get some points for killing 1,000 children.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to go over well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, I think they should keep it.
[SPEAKER_10]: because that'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's kind of one of those things that's lulzy for now, you know, in their little development, but probably won't actually get out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boy, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, shoot, your pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you imagine if it really did?
[SPEAKER_09]: Your pizza's burnt.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura burned my pizza.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was smelling it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It smelled nice and toasty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, it does smell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it really, like, crispy?
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of want to see it, but we're trying to do a radio show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you do a monologue, Loki, while I go look at the burnt pizza?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to do a monologue.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they're investigating a burnt pizza as if you haven't seen a burnt pizza before.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just black and crispier!
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yes, going back to the bet, there is no way that I'm going to add Eye of Judgment PSP to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even though I am confident if I did, that it wouldn't matter.
[SPEAKER_10]: But see, that's the problem though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Once we add Eye of Judgment PSP, then where does it stop?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to have to keep adding games until you eventually win.
[SPEAKER_10]: And who really wants to play that way?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not a bet.
[SPEAKER_10]: You should have won the first bet in the first place.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why is everybody so curious about the burnt pizza?
[SPEAKER_10]: They're weird.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyways, um... Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm making her upload a picture of it to the pictures blog at orangemonstrator.com so you can see the fail.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm getting yelled at from the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Technically, it's aluminum alloy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought it was aluminum.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you're so British.
[SPEAKER_09]: God, I wish our microphone would pick up the yelling from the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just literally heard screaming, I'm not British!
[SPEAKER_10]: And Deathwishing says in chatroom, there's an achievement on Dirt 2 called Two Girls, One Cup.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's actually Two Cups, One Girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's about winning two cups in the game with one female driver.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let me move on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm getting into another story that doesn't involve burnt food or what have you now that the whole house smells like crispy.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm eyeing the taco on a silver platter that I want to devour.
[SPEAKER_09]: Independent Xbox Live game has been banned.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because of visual sexual assault reminders.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a game called And Yet I Love You.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't even hear what she's saying.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, she's not on the radio, so we're just ignoring her.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't have a mic, I can't hear you!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's bad radio etiquette.
[SPEAKER_09]: Terrible radio etiquette.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, it was on the Japanese marketplace.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was pulled because it was too erotic.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was an independent developer, Naoki Sagawa.
[SPEAKER_09]: I wonder if that's related to the DDR Naoki.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, probably not.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is no sex in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is not an adult game.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, apparently there were visual reminders of sexual assault because in one scene, the girl's hands are restrained.
[SPEAKER_09]: In one scene, a girl is being pushed down and her panties are visible.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: And there it was.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was kicked away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now what's interesting is that I'm reading this story on Kotaku here and they make a very good point.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they say, by the way, while this is acceptable, you have Dead or Alive where you punch and kick females and you can see their panties pretty well.
[SPEAKER_09]: You need to take a picture of the taco on a silver platter and put that on the blog too because that's pretty amazing what Becky did there.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura needs a moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura needs freaking food real bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I feel bad about the pizza, although, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your pizza's bacon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Sony has to make some explanations.
[SPEAKER_08]: They got some explaining to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: When they removed the backwards compatibility from the Slim, they needed to say what exactly was going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they say, and this is a quote from John Kohler, who's SCEA's Director of Marketing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now that we're at a point where we're three years into the life cycle of the PS3, there are so many PS3 disc-based games that are available that we think, and notice this from our research, that most consumers that are purchasing the PS3 cite PS3 games as a primary reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: So basically they're saying, oh, people don't care about PS2 anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: Chat?
[SPEAKER_09]: People in studio?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they right?
[SPEAKER_09]: Do people not care about PS2 anymore?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or as Ray Iannami in chat says, and I love this, backwards compatibility is so last gen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Referencing an old OLR reference.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: What do you think, Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are they right?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they're not right.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just they're basically saying, why the hell would we give you a feature for free when you can buy our PlayStation 2 system for $100?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or soon to be Playstation 2 downloadable titles I bet you that is what you're going to see in the next year Then they're going to start releasing the Playstation 2 as downloadable titles Just to fuck us all But we can't add backwards compatibility Butch, we can sure as hell emulate these titles perfectly We know software emulation is out there We know it's possible They just don't want to give it to us Yep Lame
[SPEAKER_09]: and yes I do kind of want backwards compatibility I mean yes I realize the games are old but I still have them and who doesn't sit there once in a while and go you know I kind of want to play Magic Pen Gel and draw a giant penis you know it's sometimes we get these desires to play the old PS2 games or Final Fantasy 12 I never did beat yes I have a PlayStation 2 that I could go back and hook up if I really wanted to but that's valuable shelf space
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I am sending updated pictures of my tacos by the way I love how we have the food blog going on I posted a link in chat but it's on orangelaundry.com and you'll be able to see all these pictures if you're listening on the podcast but you probably don't care
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's a little silly of them to rid us of the backwards compatibility, especially when software emulation, at least of some titles, has been done.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a little bit frustrating, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, yeah, true, I can hook up the PS2 if I really want to play them that bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just saying I would be more apt to still buying PlayStation 2 games if they would play... I haven't bought a PS2 game since Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was the last one I ever bought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well...
[SPEAKER_10]: They'll be happy to sell them to you as a digital download later on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, with the announcement of the PlayStation Network minis, of course, Nintendo is looking to revamp its DSiWare service to kind of combat it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what they're planning on doing, although the pricing won't change on the actual downloads, they'll basically stick to the $2, $5, $9 price models.
[SPEAKER_10]: They will have a lower barrier to entry for publishers.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, they're going to have some size limits as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Including, for example, a $5 game must be under 200MB.
[SPEAKER_10]: Otherwise, Nintendo will charge a higher royalty.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which, that doesn't seem like much of an advantage, but okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just think they need some better games on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know from seeing a lot of reviews I've been reading, you know, for different things, I always see reviews for clocks and calculators.
[SPEAKER_10]: And honestly, I don't need more fucking clocks and calculators.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't need a clock or calculator on my DSi.
[SPEAKER_09]: The DSi has a clock.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I know the regular DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a DSi, but at least the regular DS has a clock.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's themed clocks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Silly.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't need more clocks or calculators.
[SPEAKER_09]: What does Nintendo need on DSiWare in order for people to pay attention?
[SPEAKER_09]: Virtual console.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: That would... People would be eating that crap up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess, but I would just be frustrated because you know they're not going to let me just carry over the virtual console games I already have.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd have to re-buy them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I don't think I'd be... Homie, don't play that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, but I don't think I'm going to be... Your chair broke.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did the chair just break live on air?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: That can't be good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, it just popped off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, popped off.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it broke.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, shoddy chair.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, dear.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tonight's show is...
[SPEAKER_10]: Footstool?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, it's not the footstool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poor Loki, we need to get... I almost bought an inflatable chair with my Dave and Buster's tickets.
[SPEAKER_09]: No!
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a hot pink inflatable chair with a pair of lips on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now I'm thinking we need one for the studio for Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to pick up a folding chair next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you know, in the old studio at my house... So they want a picture of Bork Chair.
[SPEAKER_09]: No.
[SPEAKER_09]: The couch is now gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: The ex came and took your couch away.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm glad our studio's here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Random show is very random.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Grin, remember them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Grin turned into Frown because they had to close last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that was because... Yes, Grin frowned because they got closed.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we shouldn't laugh, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's not nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: But apparently, they were the ones behind the Bionic Commando game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And we didn't end up reporting this on our show last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it was just kind of a busy show, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: But they actually closed.
[SPEAKER_09]: They were the ones that were behind Bionic Commando, which was...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_09]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: Regulate!
[SPEAKER_09]: Do not anger, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you act like a fucking child in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna treat you like a freaking child.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do not taunt, HappyFunBall.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is not a democracy.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is a cheerocracy.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, this is a freaking fashion... Becky got the reference.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you hear the lull in the background?
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a DarkSakurosity.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, speaking of DarkSakurosity...
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear Rob, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear Jamie, fuck you back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Love, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh baby, oh baby.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey guys!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_08]: This summer has exhausted me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you spent?
[SPEAKER_08]: Between the summer of Arcade PSN and the two Monkey Island games that have been released, I am worn out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Need a cigarette?
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kidding, no smoke.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just got into the Champions Online beta and let me tell you, they're doing it all wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's some real good qualities in that game, but it will take a lot to fix things if they want to attract people to the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then again, with an offer that includes a spot in the Star Trek beta, I don't think they need to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I feel I need to ask a question now.
[SPEAKER_08]: What three games are you looking forward to next month, if any?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm waiting on Marvel Ultimate Alliance, Scribblenauts, and Beatles Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_08]: Keep what you're doing, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Peace!
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's from Dan Jetto.
[SPEAKER_04]: I held the microphone away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Dan Shadow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, I'm totally waiting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I totally, totally want Marvel Ultimate Alliance 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Except it's a freaking stupid Civil War crap, and I hate the Civil War crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, Scribbledots, I'm also looking forward to, um... You make Abraham Lincoln cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the Marvel Civil War crap that they did that I got so sick of.
[SPEAKER_08]: They could at least do, like, the Skrull War or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Secret Invasion.
[SPEAKER_09]: To answer the question for me, Ion, I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beatles Rock Band is a good example of something else I'm looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_09]: That'll be very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: And...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything's kind of a blur for Christmas and a lot of the stuff I was interested in got pushed back to 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are definitely the two at the top of my list.
[SPEAKER_09]: It depends on if I get my 360 fix soon or not.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_09]: Games you're looking forward to?
[SPEAKER_09]: Any planned purchases?
[SPEAKER_09]: DJ Hero.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, that would be number three for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I definitely have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good call.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought that was October for some reason, not September.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is October.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's almost September, so we can count it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: Close enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: September, I don't really have anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: He'll take that answer and he'll like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: September, I don't really have anything I'm looking for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Scribblenauts, I guess, would be kind of cool, but I probably won't be buying that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I may be buying that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Amkara222 in chat says Final Fantasy XIV.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think that'll be out next month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Keep talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still eating.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'd be lucky if the beta would come out next month, but I somehow sadly doubt it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, we're going to get to the next email as soon as DarkSakura finishes chewing.
[SPEAKER_09]: But a mailbag at Orange Entree.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am so stealing a chip.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I just want you, I'm going to dare you to stop me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, is the pizza still cooking?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, OLR Crew, what do you think of Bethesda's Wet?
[SPEAKER_08]: It actually looks kind of pretty.
[SPEAKER_08]: This game looks really interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like the fact that it infuses a sort of kung fu game, a shooter, and a 3D fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you guys see of it at E3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks in advance, I like old people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and P.S., it puts the lotion in the basket.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or else he gets the hose again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw a little bit of it, and it looked cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think Bethesda has a very good way of putting style on a lot of their games, unless it was the Star Trek game.
[SPEAKER_09]: But every time I hear Bethesda, I'm always like, where's Oblivion 5?
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's Oblivion 5?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or I should say, sorry, Elder Scrolls 5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Where's Elder Scrolls 5?
[SPEAKER_09]: They're working on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I still need to go back and get the Call of Cthulhu game.
[SPEAKER_09]: What now?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I still want to play the Call of Cthulhu game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wet looked cool, but it didn't seem like the type of game I would probably drop $60 on just because, you know, I like roleplaying and different styles of games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is there a demo out there?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Henderson Man says the demo for Wet is on the European PlayStation Network store and I thought the demo was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: So go check it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Write us a review of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm curious to know more about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a profile for every region, so I can do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_09]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_04]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_08]: These chips are tasty.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: From J-Rod.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey guys, I had something to speak up about.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had two Xbox 360s and both of them ended up dying multiple times.
[SPEAKER_08]: After I sent them back to be repaired, they eventually died again and I ended up getting a PS3 in the end.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob said that his 360 just died as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now here's what I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why did Rob complain about customers giving Microsoft a free pass for faulty hardware and then in the same breath say, well, I'm probably just going to pick up an Elite?
[SPEAKER_08]: The product was rushed to market to beat Sony to the punch and it couldn't be more obvious that they took shortcuts and screwed the customer to do so.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this type of behavior is now somewhat rewarded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because all my friends have one doesn't mean I need to give Microsoft my time and money for absolute shit hardware quality.
[SPEAKER_08]: The problem is that people use Xbox Live as a MySpace page rather than a game console half the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: So they just keep buying new ones over and over.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only time a company will learn is if you tell them with your wallet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send it back, and if they don't repair it, then scrap it, sell the games, and move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate to say it, but if Rob buys another Xbox 360, he's basically just part of their problem he's complaining about.
[SPEAKER_08]: My current 360 is on its last leg with lockups, and if it dies, out the door it goes to eBay along with my games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't be a part of the problem, Rob, be a part of the solution.
[SPEAKER_08]: I absolutely disagree with you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's just the viewpoint's a little too extreme for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get what he's saying.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I said earlier in the show, it was wrong of me.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I buy an elite system, I'll meet you at that point.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I buy an elite system, I'm rewarding Microsoft for borking my old system.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I came to my realization about that earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_09]: If I get another Xbox 360, which assuming Loki can't fix mine, I'm going to have to go for the low-end system.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I see you there.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: You're smoking crack if you think that I'm going to sell all of my games back that I've invested hundreds of dollars in for a fraction of the cost.
[SPEAKER_09]: And therein lies the problem, and therein lies where I'm screwed, is that because I have invested all this money not just in that but on downloadable content, and some of which does not exist on the PlayStation 3, that yes, I do like to revisit on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to have the hardware to make it work.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: I still do think, and I think most people agree with me, no matter if you think I was being a baby last week or what, no matter where, I think everybody kind of agrees with me that Microsoft does need to be held accountable for this.
[SPEAKER_09]: And history needs to show this negatively on Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_09]: When the next console comes out, the question needs to be asked.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you tested this so that half of them do not fail?
[SPEAKER_09]: And somebody at Microsoft needs to go on record and assure the public that when and if the consoles fail, there will be a program in place to do something about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll tell you, though, what I'm going to do if this Xbox Red rings, because I think I'm on my third.
[SPEAKER_08]: But also keep in mind, we can just go to the store and Dan can get a new one.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: but I really think that well I don't know I'd still be in warranty so technically I'd get a new one for free but regardless I would still take the time to write a letter and say you know hey I still enjoy my games I own more in games than I own in the cost of the three systems so to me it's a justified expense you know it'd be like
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I just, at the end of the day though, I do think it's bull that clearly the Xbox 60 fails more than any other piece of hardware we've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atari 7800.
[SPEAKER_09]: In the last 15 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Atari 7800 had issues with the power supply and they failed almost as much as the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Any more in the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey OLR, I wanted to tell you that the PS3 Slim is real.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, we already covered this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey OLR, I wanted to tell you that the PS3 Slim is real and will be coming out the first of next month and the original PS3 will drop $100.
[SPEAKER_08]: I already saw the box at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_08]: My friend works there and showed me inside where the consoles are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, the Xbox 360 price will be going down after Project Natal is released.
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is with these women having no bras anymore?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't get me wrong, I love tits, but when someone 50 years older than you does not have a bra on, I barf.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think we should just let the emailers report on the news from now on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who did this?
[SPEAKER_09]: Juan?
[SPEAKER_09]: Juan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, this is the same Juan that emailed us before, I bet, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think.
[SPEAKER_09]: He needs a segment on this program one way or another.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like our new extrovert.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want a slice of your pizza, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me a cheesy piece.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will let you pick whatever piece you want.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: How many more emails do we have tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: This one, a few.
[SPEAKER_09]: A few, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I put this one in the name of science.
[SPEAKER_09]: Make it snappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shook here, or is it Shookay?
[SPEAKER_08]: I never was told.
[SPEAKER_08]: Last week, I sent an email about my Final Fantasy X dilemma, and your advice worked.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, oh yeah, you had the bigot dad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, no offense.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, your dad was the asshole.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh sorry, no offense.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not in the habit of talking ill of other people's parents, but really, the way that you portrayed your dad made him look to be a major bigot.
[SPEAKER_10]: But if I were to start with one, you are the winner.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, I just sold Madden 04, 05, and 06 for about $40 to a privately owned game store.
[SPEAKER_08]: I bought Final Fantasy X and Chrono Trigger and I'm loving both.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Chrono Trigger is the best RPG ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: And when you beat it, go back and actually hop on the teleport device right at the beginning of the game and you can beat Lavos from the beginning and get the...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sitting here in awe that he got that much for those old-ass Madden games.
[SPEAKER_09]: Props to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, my dad walked in on me during the opening scene with Blitzball when he asked what it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: I made up something and said it was Super Soccer Extreme 2000 and he bought it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, my huge thanks for the advice.
[SPEAKER_08]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, my username is pronounced as if the K was silent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's shoe.
[SPEAKER_08]: K.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ran across this crap accidentally coming to a PS3 near you, LittleBigPlanetWater
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a link and it looks like Sackboy will swim, materials that float will float, and Sackboy will have a hold-your-breath limit of air.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm hoping they will give him scuba gear, the water equivalent of the untethered backpack.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, we talked about that.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a video of creation mode on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't wait to see how this gives a swift kick in the pants to all the user-generated levels.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I agree with Robaba.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, I have a mouthful of pizza.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: I agree with Rababa that it would be awesome if there was like a scuba gear or something like that because that means you can make these levels that were nothing but floating and do you know how much that's going to increase the amount of clone games we see like space shooters and stuff amazing they're going to reduce space shooters it'll be easier with the water thing I think with the water though you are going to get limited air supply and that type of stuff that's going to work into it but what if there's a scuba gear like Rababa suggests I think that's a great idea yeah there will be that
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there's also another email from him.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just noticed a recent post on NeoFM.com about that old project.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not really an update, but some smart cookie converted it to Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Both are five-panel games in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's at the Game Zone at the Great Mall of the Great Plains in the Great... Is it pronounced Olathe or Lathy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kansas?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, somewhere in Kansas.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's details in the article at NeoFM.com And then the other... And yes, I do remember this dancing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is the one that was going to look like a Beatmania controller, but it was with feet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was low-worthy.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they have video of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Kansas?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's... How random.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's from... Well, Neon FM and a pump-it-up machine and... Well, because the whole thing runs off Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm saying we should send Shane to go look, but he won't care.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know he won't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I got something for him, thanks to Becky.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: He'll love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We should send it to him and autograph it and everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: He wouldn't care about our autographs.
[SPEAKER_09]: He probably already has that, but you never know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, well then, I'll do something with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, OLR listeners, who wants a copy of High School Musical 3?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do not want.
[SPEAKER_09]: Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let us know and you'll get it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because nobody in this room wants it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or nobody in the hall either, else it would not be in my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ask him.
[SPEAKER_09]: He may not have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: He may not have bought it for whatever reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, actually, it says there's apparently the code leaked out for Neon FM.
[SPEAKER_10]: Meanwhile, some cool cats managed to get their hands on two separate leaks of our code and put them in a centrifuge with some fairy dust and in the groove pumping up Linux code.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're pumping up machines to a local arcade Neon FM 2009 machine.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, their stuff leaked out to the internet a while ago in Stepmania format.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have it, but eh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look how much of it I've eaten.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except it's making me fat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, any other emails tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's time to get angsty, and I don't really have a good story to lead us into this tonight, but what would the show be without the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I actually did have a story to lead us into that.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to tell us real fast?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, well I mentioned it earlier, GameStop saying GameStop expects a UMD dump by new PSP Go owners since obviously Sony's not supporting them
[SPEAKER_10]: Tony Bartel, the GameStop EVP of Merchandising and Marketing said, we have a very clear roadmap on how we can drive profitability on sales of games.
[SPEAKER_10]: It will also be a strong contribution in our trade-in process when you have people that will have UMD games and they will no longer work on the platform and they'll fuel additional currency for GameStop!
[SPEAKER_10]: Halo GameStop.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your angst then.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had surgery again on Friday for him to pull out the rest of the suture, and what happened is that the suture was in a knot, which is why it wouldn't come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ew.
[SPEAKER_08]: It had been knotted up inside my hand.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so when it got tugged on, of course, ow!
[SPEAKER_08]: So, um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: But you've known Dan for like nine on top of that, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: We've been together for 11 and a half years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki, any angst for you tonight?
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, eh, not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess I have to wait for my arcade cabinet to come in.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to wait another four weeks, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um, yeah, that just sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um, no, that's all I got.
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU of the week... I've had a really, really shitty week, so I just want to say FU to people that want to play political games and...
[SPEAKER_09]: All that crap when I'm just not down with it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I am a professional individual.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go to places to get a job done, and I'm not interested in playing games.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I will get my job done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also, an F you to the fact that when I'm having these bad days, the person I want to turn to to talk about these things about is absent with better things to do, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've not had a good week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to go home and cry into my pillow.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get ice cream after the show again.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got to finish in the next hour because Baskin Robbins closes at 10.
[SPEAKER_09]: So step on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get you pie later.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Abbey Road will be arriving first on October 20th at the price of $16.98, or 1,360 Microsoft points, with each individual track running you $2, or 160 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sgt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Pepper's Lingling Hearts Club Band will come out in November, and I guess also the next album after that will be Rubber Soul, and that will arrive in December.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Lots of tracks coming out, man.
[SPEAKER_10]: They've got uber tracks.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what's going to be kind of cool about that, though, I'm assuming, is that each one's going to have the different animations in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: So some of those songs actually would be kind of cool to see.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm really kind of considering maybe buying this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I don't really play a lot of rock band lately.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it might be fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like some of these songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I'm totally going to have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm so mad my Xbox crapped out right before a song I really wanted to play had come out and I didn't get a chance to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here's the thing I have a little problem about, and I'm kind of confused in this sense, because some of these songs I thought were already in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember how they were showing us different songs like Octopus's Garden and stuff like that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought that was already in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for some reason, it's listed on the Abbey Road download content here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it might also be that when you download the album, you're kind of getting the rest of the album, because I think every album has some representation in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess maybe they're just listing what's on the album, not actual download content.
[SPEAKER_09]: That could be, because if these people said to the website, like, hey, we're releasing these albums, the website probably just went to Amazon.com and just wrote out the track list without thinking, oh, this song's probably in the game already.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: And apparently, I guess, the All You Need Is Love download content, which is going to be a single, will be available as a timed exclusive on Xbox 360 and the game's launch is September 9th.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then also, if you purchase a full Abbey Road album, you'll have the option to play the B-side melody, or B-side medley, I'm sorry, from...
[SPEAKER_09]: you'll never get me your money through the end as one continuous trek I may not be the biggest Beatles fan in the world and you know I'm just I'm a cool Beatles are cool I respect that you know that people are in love with them I understand why they have such a place in history and so forth but I'm actually like really excited about this game like it just it just looks so cool it's fun to watch and play yeah
[SPEAKER_10]: Other stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: This week on the Rock Band Store, they're going to have Tom Petty, Billy Idol, and Jet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Individual songs, of course, from Billy Idol.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please say it's Cradle of Love.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: White Wedding.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's already in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Money, Money, Money.
[SPEAKER_10]: and Rebel Yell.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Rebel Yell's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: And each of those are available for 160 Microsoft Points or $2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fleetwood Mac, you have Don't Stop and World Turning.
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't stop thinking about tomorrow, baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: I should sing the Rock Band songs every week.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Jet, you have She's a Genius.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tom Petty, I Won't Back Down, and Running Down a Dream
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: You've got lots of stuff coming there.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of it just previously released stuff on other things.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have a lot of tracks from Grateful Dead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Foo Fighters, Dropkick Murphy, White Zombie, that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those will all be available for 200 Wii Points each.
[SPEAKER_10]: And those will be available on the 25th.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, finally, on the PSP, you're getting two things of download content on the 27th, including the Zombies, She's Not There, and White Zombie, Black Sunshine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Each available for $2.00.
[SPEAKER_10]: And finally, Rock Band's download content is expected to hit 1,000 tracks by the holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's going to be some new tracks, of course, coming from Queen, Nirvana, Tom Petty, which we got some this week, Elton John, Iggy Pop, The White Stripes, Pantera, Talking Heads, Korn, and The Raccoon Tears.
[SPEAKER_03]: What do you have from Iggy Pop?
[SPEAKER_09]: As well as... I don't think they've given any songs yet, just bands.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they're just listing stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: As well as many more from other artists.
[SPEAKER_09]: But hey, that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know, like Elton John, Queen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Need I say more?
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to get SingStar Queen, by the way.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is out and about.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, need.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm waiting for the price drop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you know, once the game's out a month, it'll be in the clearance bin for $19.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I'm waiting for.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sweet, that was a lot of rock band news.
[SPEAKER_09]: They are busy bees over there considering there was no Rock Band 3 this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: 500 tracks a year, that's not bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good lord.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot more than certain other music franchises.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, Gran Turismo 5 is the last story we have tonight before we get to the phone lines a little later on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Apparently, this was being shown off at Gamescom, not just Gran Turismo 5, but Gran Turismo PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's some images of the game that have leaked out to the internet, and of course, they're pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: The main menu looks like what you see in... I like how you said that.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look, it's pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Grand Theft... I always want to say Grand Theft Auto 5.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Gran Turismo 5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because GT... I just want to put the A in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: GT5 Prologue uses that same kind of menu.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's going to be 80 tracks in the game, 1,000 cars, 830 regular ones, and 170 with a little more modeling.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damage will be in the game, and GTTV is back.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it can also be run on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_09]: No release date yet, which you know what that means, 2010.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's been a long time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Considering we got that prologue quite some time ago, that's a long wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a very long wait.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very cool if you're a fan of Gran Turismo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am not as big on the Gran Turismo series because I like my arcade racers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gran Turismo is a little too realistic for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's more like Project Gotham and stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not that I hate them.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they're pretty to watch other people play that are good at it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm just really bad at them.
[SPEAKER_09]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, it's your turn to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Skype line is open right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're only going to take a couple calls tonight, but we want to also get any last-minute stories that might be out there while we wait for folks to call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_09]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, you have something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I like pie.
[SPEAKER_10]: And to think that I was going to let you go ahead and go first, that teaches me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, UK is getting a pretty cool deal with Guitar Hero 5 purchases.
[SPEAKER_10]: Much like how we're getting the free Van Halen over here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Folks that purchase Guitar Hero 5 in the UK will be eligible to get a free copy of Guitar Hero World Tour.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's more songs and probably a better selection.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, we've got a call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Death Wishing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, Death Wishing.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if they check ID or anything I mean, I don't have ID I don't have a driver's license yet in California to make you pay up the ass to get one
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it is a mature rated game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but, uh, it's, you know, I just find it really lame because it's just like, it's a mature rated game and yet we're all going to get our hands on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's going to be like eight year old kids going, oh my god, I pawn you, noob.
[SPEAKER_11]: T-bag.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's because parents suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, my parents were cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was playing Grand Theft Auto back then and look at me, I grew up to be perfectly fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are there individuals out there that might debate that comment, Deathwishing?
[SPEAKER_11]: That one Californian politician who got banned.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you know who he is.
[SPEAKER_09]: No idea.
[SPEAKER_09]: But did you go to the tour?
[SPEAKER_09]: Are you planning on going to the tour?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm planning on going to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm going to try to talk my friend into taking me down to Pasadena.
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't see any coming near you guys, sadly.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: You get free stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think you get T-shirts and stuff for doing it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Whoopee.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not that big on Halo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand why people love their Halo.
[SPEAKER_09]: I used to play Halo 2 all the time with my college friends, but now I'm kind of over it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Rob, about your 360, I don't see why yours is broken down so much.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm on my second, but my first one still works.
[SPEAKER_11]: It still works.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just have to close the tray in, like open and close it to get games to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I'm letting my friend use it because his blew up, like literally exploded.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's impressive.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Amazing Exploding 360s I call mine the Jesus Box Because it won't die It just keeps resurrecting It does We're going to let you go so we can get as many calls as we can tonight And still have time for ice cream But thanks so much for the call, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Bye I should ask him if he's going to the Silent Hill house Because I still want to go I think we're just going to have to go We're just going to have to get in the car and go
[SPEAKER_05]: Fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, let me...
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm gonna get my headset.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ironic!
[SPEAKER_05]: DS Master on a PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, I'm here to do a review of a new game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Poppin' Music for Wii.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you played Poppin' Music for Wii and you don't sound happy about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please tell us all about this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's complete crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been a long time B-Money fan and this has done great disgrace to the series.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I need to know the reason why it's crap and I need to know how it's different from the poppin' music as B-Money fans know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's all, you know what they did with the DDR games and throwing those in the crapper?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's all licensed stuff like Britney Spears and Miley Cyrus stuff into poppin'.
[SPEAKER_02]: and there's no controller with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You just use the Wii Remote and Nunchuck like you would on, oh, let me see here, Rayman Raving Rabbids in the dancing section.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty much how it's played.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's complete crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ray Ayanami in chat is asking, no Konami originals?
[SPEAKER_02]: Very few, if any.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, they tried to put in a revamped B4U song in there somehow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then something out of... Like, it sounds like out of... I don't know if you heard this cartoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi Hi Puffy Ami Yumi?
[SPEAKER_08]: That came out... Oh, actually, Puffy's an actual pop band in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and... I think one of their songs ended up somewhere on the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't remember which one it was, but... Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: Those complete cred.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was one of the DLC tracks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, that's one thing this one has that all the others didn't have was DLC.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, yeah, I'm glad they're finally getting to the next gen and DLC to their music games, but at the same time, Konami's just disappointing the Beemani fans left and right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, by the way, just to let you know, that line you quoted...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's straight off one of my favorite series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bring It On.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only the best movie of all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Period.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and they just got a fifth one, and I have a review on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a fifth Bring It On movie now?
[SPEAKER_09]: I've only ever seen the first one.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have way too many Bring It On movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: I said, brr, it's cold in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, forget it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right, we're letting you go, DS Masters.
[SPEAKER_09]: We need to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go watch Bring It On on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no, but basically, I heard rumors of possibly that the choreographer from Thatch,
[SPEAKER_02]: is doing a second All-Star Cheer Camp game or whatever for Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, they are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I've actually played it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It does give you a workout twice as much as Wii Fit will ever give you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, great, bye.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess he didn't hear the part where he said I was letting him go.
[SPEAKER_09]: He just kept talking.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's important that we know about All-Star Cheer Camp, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was so rude to him.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope he hears this.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're horrible, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Horrible human being.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did I not say, okay, we gotta wrap up to get some more calls?
[SPEAKER_10]: He wasn't done yet, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's just wrong.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was talking about choreography.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
Ah, crap!
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: 1-877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Give us a call if you want to talk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our number is 555-4444.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not really.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Since it's not ringing, I'm going to give it two more minutes.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you don't call, we'll get over, Clint.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last call.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hi, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_01]: First of all, sorry about your 360.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm definitely sorry it happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dude, I don't know why you're blaming yourself.
[SPEAKER_09]: The damn thing was obviously going to break eventually.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I went down in a blaze of glory.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just joking, man.
[SPEAKER_01]: Though I am sorry about the thing breaking.
[SPEAKER_09]: I blame Microsoft, not you.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: I wanted to talk about the digital download thing you were talking about at the beginning of the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I made a comment in chat, or in Penelope, that most people have a really good connection to internet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like me, I don't have a really good connection.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have only one megabyte per second.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I know you've called in this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: You live in Mexico, and I know you've talked about sometimes coming up to the U.S.
[SPEAKER_09]: to get games or having them shipped down here or down to you or what have you.
[SPEAKER_09]: Imagine if with this digital distribution stuff, they could just say, oh, block Mexico.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's not their time yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have to wait until we get the localized version for them.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we're just going to block their IP so that they can't get the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would suck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, like it happened with Patapon 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's only a digital download.
[SPEAKER_01]: in the United States.
[SPEAKER_01]: Though, Sony made a good decision and they brought the UMD over here.
[SPEAKER_01]: So maybe if they do that in the future, if you can have the digital download or you can have the disc, you have the option that maybe it could work better.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you only have one option and it's the digital download, it won't work.
[SPEAKER_01]: It definitely won't work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like it when our callers get us to think about things that we didn't think about before.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't like thinking.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's horrible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, too bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Think about some other last minute stories while I close up Skype.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you didn't get through, hey, you can always tweet us, email us, chat with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or buy me a pony.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or buy Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Guess what I saw yesterday, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: A pony?
[SPEAKER_09]: Derby Owners Club.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where?
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's the doc?
[SPEAKER_09]: Dave and Buster's.
[SPEAKER_09]: Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love the horsey racing games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm kind of over it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They needed a sequel about five years ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, there's a new game coming to the PS3 called 3D Dot Game Heroes.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's basically kind of a 3D version of pixel art.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you were to take like an old school Final Fantasy game and make it all 3D and high res, that's what the game would look like.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that should be coming out in Japan this November.
[SPEAKER_10]: No word on it coming over to the US, but I only hope it does because that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, Castle Crashers is getting new download content in the Necromantic, um, pack, and that will feature some really cool, um, things, including a chainsaw, a golden mace, a dragon head animal orb, and also, um, two new characters, the Necromancer and the cult minion you'll get to play as.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, all that available.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, no word on what the, uh, cost or when it's coming, but, um,
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Groove is in the heart Groove is in the heart
[SPEAKER_10]: This might be the secret title that they were developing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hope not!
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope it's not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Konami is apparently location testing Poppin' Music 18.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: The new mix, I believe, was... God, I just had it too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh...
[SPEAKER_10]: I forgot the name.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I can't find it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, Pop Music 18.
[SPEAKER_10]: We don't even know the subtitle.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not important.
[SPEAKER_10]: But apparently they're going to be conducting that starting, actually it was last week, starting August 20th at AMPIA at Kangawa Prefecture.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's going to run from the 20th to the 30th.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then at Rundown at the Fukuoka
[SPEAKER_10]: and Fukuoka Prefecture from the 21st to the 30th.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you can check that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have more information on the location test site which is konami.jp slash am slash location test slash poppin18 So check that out if you live in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: and then let's see here Modern Warfare 2 of course I have talked about in the past about how Activision is trying to rip people off with the price of Guitar Hero 5 on the Wii no one seems to give a shit but now that you know it's available on PC apparently they are trying to raise the price of the PC version as well
[SPEAKER_10]: GameStop, Amazon, Best Buy are now showing the PC version with a $60 price tag.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, that may not be a big deal for people that normally buy console games, but for PC owners, most games only retail at $50 retail.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, I told you they were evil, and no one believed me, but now that it's a more important game, people might listen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Namco Bandai is releasing a new game on the PlayStation Portable in December called Queen's Blade Spiral Chaos.
[SPEAKER_10]: Queensblade apparently is a, they call it a Lost World style combat picture book game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And features characters with large boobies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, to the point that it's absolutely ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_10]: That's absolutely ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's how I try to make my character an ion with boobies that big.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that should be coming out this fall on PSP in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's going to do it for tonight's episode of Orange Lounge Radio, but first we've got to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boobies.
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is ice cream, then boobies.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, I get my arcade hardware tomorrow, but it's no good right now because I don't have an arcade machine to play it on.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I get to stare at it and caress it and boobies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, thank you guys so much for downloading and tuning into our show tonight.
[SPEAKER_09]: We really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, Tiger Claus reminded me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I forgot to mention the StarCraft II thing I was going to mention about the chick from Battlestar Galactica is voicing Kerrigan.
[SPEAKER_09]: Trisha Helfer.
[SPEAKER_09]: Six.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have an excuse to watch it.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: And so enjoy your Battlestar Galactica, kids, until next week because we'll be back next week to do it all over again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, if you enjoyed the show, be sure to tell two friends about the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Leave us a nice review on iTunes or just tell people about the show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Word of mouth is what sells the show and helps us spread around because, remember, we don't have a big magazine behind us or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's gonna do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be back to do it all over again on another edition of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good night!
[SPEAKER_00]: or allgames.com but we're probably right anyway see you next week