[SPEAKER_00]: Tonight, August 30th, 2009, is yet another novelty controller on the way for the Wii?
[SPEAKER_00]: Could your local Walmart's arcade soon be expanding?
[SPEAKER_00]: And we talk about new details on the Rock Band Network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello, everybody out there on the internet and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are that podcast dedicated to video games, video gaming, gaming culture, and the gamer lifestyle.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my lovely co-host, DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_07]: And TechMasterLoki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you guys doing tonight?
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm full.
[SPEAKER_07]: Full of what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Leftover pasta from Olive Garden because right now the Neverending Pasta Bowl is going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh damn, we need to go there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had whole wheat linguine with Alfredo sauce.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, apparently we had some type of unannounced contest that was win a night stay in the vault here at OLR Studios and Misty won it because she's actually on her way right now to hang out with us.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's not going to be on the show tonight because of the way the whole schedule works.
[SPEAKER_07]: She doesn't fly so she took a bus.
[SPEAKER_03]: She's hitting Reno tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I guess she's going to be here and kind of staying in the vault.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm thinking Misty needs to be taken out for the full OLR Olive Garden experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: We might have to make that happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about... Well, shoot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to think because...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll go ahead and say, because, you know, it's a big deal for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: My wedding anniversary is on the second, not the second, the Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking Tuesday is second day.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on Tuesday, the first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan and I will have been married for four years, and the entire time I haven't killed him.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: On both counts.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been together for over 11 years, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, just a quiet night at home with the wife?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least go out to a nice dinner.
[SPEAKER_07]: You and the wife like Benihana, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, usually the family will take me out, then her family will take me out, then she'll take me out.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I get good dinners all weekend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, I have a present for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a can of air missing the nozzle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could use that because my other can of air is kind of out of air.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here, take it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're missing a nozzle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can put the nozzle in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You don't really need the nozzle, actually.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to our chat room because our chat is always up and running.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love... Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: Totally off topic, but since we were talking about food anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, the wife has been really looking... Sorry, chat room, you've been bumped in favor of food.
[SPEAKER_06]: But this also ties in with possible birthday ideas.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, fine, fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, my wife's been really interested in watching this new show that's on the Food Network called What Would Brian Boitano Make?
[SPEAKER_06]: and, you know, I kept hearing about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, oh, it's going to be very underwhelming, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's, you know, it can't possibly be, you know, first off, there's no way that they're going to use the theme song from, you know, South Park.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no way that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this show is probably just going to suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, it came on today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not only did they use the theme song from the South Park episode, which is fucking awesome already, but the episode was a bacon episode, dedicated to all these different party foods using bacon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was just like, sold?
[SPEAKER_06]: So that show's actually pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he is very flamboyant.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm serious, he's very flamboyant.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you can't go wrong with an episode dedicated to bacon.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, all sorts of awesome stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bacon muffins.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bacon corn muffins would be really delicious.
[SPEAKER_06]: They are bacon corn muffins.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess in honor of this, the chat rooms name tonight will be Bacon.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we're going to go to Bacon right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think we should name him Kevin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: Kevin Bacon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your name is Kevin!
[SPEAKER_07]: BlackWolf, our old buddy who tapes live before us, who's not going to be live next week because he's traveling to PAX.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're not.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll get into that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: BlackWolf in chat says, she sounds as excited about being married as I am to going to PAX.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if you listen to Bobby's show this week, he's kind of like, yeah, yeah, you know, PAX.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm really excited about being married, but my excitement gets spread out over, you know, 365 slash 356 days, you know, a year.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be like being excited about my finger.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a part of me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a useful part of me, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Guys, I woke up today and I still had all ten fingers.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love this finger.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love this finger.
[SPEAKER_02]: This finger loves you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some days I wish we were a TV show because I'll just leave it to your imagination which finger I was holding up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Rob, I like these two fingers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tiger Claw in Kevin says, Good thing Dan knows the date of the anniversary.
[SPEAKER_07]: If he didn't, there's no telling what Dark Sakura would do.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anyhow, let's get into our gaming weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft follows up the Orange Lounge Foodio on AllSnacksRadio.com right after the Bobby Hot Dog Show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost feel like there ought to be a parody website or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go and talk about your gaming week, or I guess your food week if you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually really didn't play that much this week because the skin on my hand is kind of getting really sore.
[SPEAKER_02]: In that stage of healing where it gets really sore.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I haven't done a lot of gaming except for playing a little bit of RO, a little bit of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Sims, lots of that MMO on Gaia just because I was sitting here.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I started school.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my first week of school.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I played a lot of Peggle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Played a lot of Peggle before class.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my gaming weeks in the future are going to be rather dull coming up because the two classes I'm taking are going to be a lot of work and I go back to work in two weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm trying to get ahead of my school work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm being responsible!
[SPEAKER_07]: No Sims 3 even?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I need to boot that up right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's not even playing during the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm surprised.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's customary.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was like, what was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Whenever a Harry Potter book would come out, I would ignore the show in favor of reading the Harry Potter book.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've never ignored the show to play games, I'll have you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: as you were playing Flash games during the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen he's been playing Flash games or hacking, downloading torrents while we're trying to broadcast the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wasn't really ignoring the show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just caught up in my book.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I do not ignore the show to play Sims.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am multi-talented and can multitask like a mofo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Heart!
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_06]: My gaming week was alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I...
[SPEAKER_06]: I played Grand Theft Auto, because I do that every day anyways, so that's a given.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing really interesting happened there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And played more Earth Defense Force, because I'm slowly getting back into that, because I'm determined to finish the damn game!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been like 80 hours already, and it's so damn hard!
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm going to finish it, and...
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: And the trial, you know, is all in Japanese, so I couldn't really figure out what I'm supposed to be doing.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I don't know, it's a basic rip-off of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, like, it looks like they made Zelda kind of Flash-looking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't the games have to go through, like, some type of check where they make sure they're not ripping something else off?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there were TurboGrafx games that were almost complete Zelda rip-offs.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Newtopia series.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's different enough to where it's not Zelda, but it's Zelda, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's seriously a top-down Zelda game, which is all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's got a point, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you ever played Newtopia, it's a lot like Zelda 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And there were a lot of games in that era that were kind of like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then speaking of rip-offs of games, there was a Mario Kart rip-off on there as well called Wacky Karts that I tried playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was less wacky, more bland.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I played that for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was alright, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the one game I did play a demo of that was really awesome and will be coming out in a few weeks here is Wet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: There's one scene that you play in the demo where you're on, like, cars on a freeway, you know, with traffic and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there's just cars flying through the air and you're jumping from car to car and shooting people in slow motion.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a real fun action-packed game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, one that kind of wasn't really on my radar.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I like the poster for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But now I'm actually thinking about picking it up because it was pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely check out the demo.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's on live, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it may be on the PlayStation... I'm not sure if it's on the PlayStation 3 network yet, but it will be soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I really played.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Game Launching from Home
[SPEAKER_07]: This is really the first one I can think of that's really... Well, I know they do it for Resident Evil 5, and I think there's another game at home that they do it for, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is the first one that's really easy to test because you can do it with demos.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it just kind of stinks.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not that... You know, if this is supposed to compete with Xbox Live and launching games out of parties and stuff, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't... It's very, very slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd fail.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I did have... You know, I...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll put another tweet out when I'm home, either later tonight or tomorrow, and say, give me your names.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you can come visit the OLR club.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did do a little decorating.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually plopped down some of the things that I got in the Namco games.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the arcade machines are in our club.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I was putting messages on the bulletin board.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to make it not so plain so that people actually want to visit it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then maybe during the show one night or something, we can have it up here in studio somehow.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're being interior virtual decorator.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we here at Orange Launch Radio, over the past seven years, we try to be on top of every new interactive technology.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of our taglines we say here is where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: So when Skype came out, we tried to get on Skype.
[SPEAKER_07]: When Twitter came out, we tried to get on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: So now that Home's been out, we're trying to just...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Other than that, they didn't play a lot of new games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm still waiting for ION this month.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be a big game.
[SPEAKER_07]: My Xbox 360 is still out of commission.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I got a really interesting email today that I need to follow up on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because apparently, OLR has listeners in all sorts of interesting places.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I found out today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knew?
[SPEAKER_07]: So more on that next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hopefully I'll have an Xbox 360 back very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Going to the chatroom for some comments, Bochikawa in chat says, I checked out home when I got my PS3 and never went back.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's worth taking a peek.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, if you haven't been there in months, you're going to find a lot of really interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the Namco Arcade is really cool looking, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a whole little zone for the Namco Arcade where they have all the different machines set up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It kind of feels like an old 80s arcade, so it's kind of cute.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see Loki is pimping out his Loki Arcade Cabinet Fund in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is this all about, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just where people can donate money so I can finance the cabinet because it's expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: I see, so it's basically give me money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's pretty much... PayPal me money.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see, also in chat...
[SPEAKER_07]: Ray Iannami says, I'm not sure if I want a PS3 Slim.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, $300 for a PS3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell yeah, but does it have enough good exclusives?
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, yeah, it has Blu-ray, but I see no point in it because I don't have an HDTV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you don't have an HDTV, Blu-ray doesn't really give you a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say plop down to $300 and get a decent HDTV.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're starting to come down in price.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although, be careful because a lot of these cheap HDTVs only are capable of 720p.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can actually get a good Blu-ray player now for about $100 and something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think especially in the holiday season this year, you're going to see these HDTVDs and Blu-ray players big time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Price reductions.
[SPEAKER_07]: So keep an eye out for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just remember, the longer you wait, the cheaper they'll get.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's really all I have to say for my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there's one other thing I forgot to mention.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not really anything I played, but I saw it on the indie games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely check out all the Japanese games, or Japanese named games, because obviously they're from Japanese companies.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they had one on there that was a sequel to Dodgeball.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember the old NES Dodgeball game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw one of those on DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: We reviewed that as one of the Kunio games, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I saw a copy of that on DS when I was at shopping this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they have something very similar to that on the indie games, and it was pretty cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, they have some good shmups on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, the indie games are worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, there's new stuff coming on there every day, and the rating system works really well now.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: For some reason, I'm interested in the Japanese games because there's a lot of interesting stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get into some housekeeping tonight before we get into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually do have something to pimp this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our friends at the podcast, The Ultimate Quest, located at ultimatequest.net, invited me on their show this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had a little bit of a roundtable talking about MMOs.
[SPEAKER_07]: So check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's going to be episode 85.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might be wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check that out, though, at ultimatequest.net.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a roundtable.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't just me, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: somebody I run into at a lot of the industry shows I go to, Ninja Sista from Electric Sista Hood was on and her co-host Panda was also on the show and I don't remember his online name but I know his name was Wes and he was from the Control Point which is a Team Fortress 2 podcast but it's part of a larger network that unfortunately I forgot the name of but I know they had like a WoW podcast and stuff because he knew his stuff when it came to MMOs so we were talking a little bit about MMOs but it also got into other subjects like I know we were talking about actually Sony Home for a
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, it's all hosted by Xenocore, who calls into this show once in a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be out this week at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not there right now, but I'm sure it'll be out during the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, of course, we always want to pimp the ways you can follow us online.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have our Twitter at OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have our Facebook at OL Army.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just search for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course, our Facebook at username Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we do have a MySpace we check like once a month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So be on the lookout for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and of course the arcade is still going to be at $199 and the pro to kind of clear it out dropped down to $249 but once they're gone you know they're gone so I don't know it's always good to drop the prices of those and you know at least not a bad system but I guess if you don't want you know a black system then
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a slight bit of deception in this price drop, though, is that they removed the cables.
[SPEAKER_07]: The HDMI cable, I think, used to come with the Elite.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think it came with a component, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I could be wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: But those component cables, dude, those are like proprietary by Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you can get an HDMI cable cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if your TV only has one HDMI port currently occupied by your PS3 like mine does or, you know, what have you, and you want to hook up through component cables, those component cables are like $40.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they took those out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, they may have dropped the price by $100, but they also dropped the value by $40.
[SPEAKER_06]: But their excuse is that they're offering the same thing that Sony is.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Sony, in all their excuses, no matter what, it's always been just the standard AV cables.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I suppose that's fair.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, I mean, we do need to look at both sides of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that, you know, yeah, the Xbox 360 is dropping in price, but it's not quite what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they're both guilty of it look at Sony, oh they dropped the system price oh but they removed backwards compatibility or oh we dropped the system price and now we removed some USB ports or we removed this or that I don't know they're all guilty of it and yeah you can probably find cheap third party cables for a lot less than you know maybe for Playstation 3 but I don't know about Xbox 360 they've got like universal cables I thought they were proprietary on that
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No?
[SPEAKER_06]: The HDMI stuff, you can use just a straight HDMI cable, but if you want your audio to go out not over the HDMI and you want it to go out either optical or just stereo RCA, you've got to have their proprietary cable.
[SPEAKER_06]: Technically, you have to have their proprietary cable just because if you were to plug in another AV cable or whatever, it happens to block the HDMI port or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're a little fat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Why do you think they waited so long to announce this price drop officially?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, we kind of knew this was coming for two weeks based on all the rumors and leaked marketing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, was it timed to compete directly with the PS3 Slim?
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably to take some thunder out of their announcement.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it's like, oh, the PlayStation's $299.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the Xbox has been $299, and now the better one's $299.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can basically buy either system with very similar specs.
[SPEAKER_06]: and now it's just the games that kind of decide it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And really, with the games, you know, the 360 has a larger catalog anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, kind of one thing I want to ask, though, is the PS3 commercial.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you seen the new Slim TV commercial?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like, it does everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: The guy that was in it, there was the one that was about the price drop or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That guy, I recognize him from another commercial, but I can't think of what it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: But he's been in some other funny commercials like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that was pretty little tongue-in-cheek there.
[SPEAKER_07]: He looks like one of those dudes that would be in a movie with Seth Rogen.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of what it looked like to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: But yeah, I like how they're saying, I heard a rumor that it's going to drop to $2.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you have to say about this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it was kind of funny the way they kind of did that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because obviously the slim rumor has been around forever, and it only turned out to be true.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was kind of a funny way they did it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most console rumors end up turning out to be true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure we'll have more to go into that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameGuru in chat says, PS3, it does everything except play PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it plays PS1 games just fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it print money?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a real hard time buying the argument of, well, PS3s don't play PS2 games because you can just go get a PS2 to play them on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then why do they play PS1 games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that was like the Metal Gear Solid 80 gig systems.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was only a limited amount that were playable, but it had one of the two chips that were in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just emulated the other chip.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it can't do full emulation, but if they decided, hey, we're going to bring back that one chip again, then yeah, you could do it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they're not going to because that cuts down the cost of their system.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well let's move on to talking about something Xbox and of course one of the features that's coming to Xbox pretty soon, Twitter and of course Facebook.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I guess there was a little like press release that came out about the price cut and there was kind of a little footnote tucked away in it that mentioned that
[SPEAKER_07]: An Xbox Live Gold membership is going to be required for Twitter and Facebook.
[SPEAKER_07]: So apparently it is not going to be something that is going to be included as part of the basic Silver package.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in an interview with Joystick, or I guess maybe a clarification to Joystick, that's with a Q of course, the gaming blog, a Microsoft representative said to them that Facebook and Twitter on Xbox Live will be free to Gold members with a free trial period available for Silver members.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not quite understanding what the point of Twitter and Facebook is on Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I have to see it in action.
[SPEAKER_07]: But essentially, if it's just me viewing Twitter updates on my Xbox 360, dude, that's just like using the web.
[SPEAKER_07]: And why do I need to pay for gold to have that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little silly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Same reason we have it on our phones.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that if you've already got gold access, it's really a moot point.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's not something I would want to use on my Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I have my phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why I have my computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: This just seems like more ammunition for the Sony fanboys.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought the whole thing with Twitter and Facebook, or at least with Facebook, is that you can upload, well, starting soon with games supporting it, you can upload screen caps of you beating certain levels or getting achievements or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So more crap to spam your Facebook with, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that kind of what the DSi does?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can upload the photos from your DSi?
[SPEAKER_07]: It kind of interacts like a mobile phone does with Facebook.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but this is going to be a little bit more game-related, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone with Raptor!
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care!
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, I don't really... I mean, I guess some people are interested or some people think what they're playing is so important that they have to show everybody every little thing that they've done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, if I saw something funny happen in a game, then I might put a picture up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, when would I put those Blue Dragon pictures up?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, two months ago when I was up all night bored?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's one thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's with people who are like, oh, I played this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I'm uploading every day, every day, every day, every day.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, I'm just really worried that we are going to get nothing but spam tweets and Facebook status of what people are playing.
[SPEAKER_07]: If so, then that will be suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know, I kind of agree because Twitter is already kind of ruined for me as it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I don't really like to check Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's too much.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't... Like...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I try to use TweetDeck so that there's filters, but even then it will only go so far back.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if I'm only able to check Twitter once a day, I feel like I kind of lose what everybody's up to.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm really starting to just not like Twitter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just think it got too big too fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's Friendster.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to go the way of Friendster, where it just starts crapping out too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I never use Friendster.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but do you remember Friendster?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was supposed to be Facebook and MySpace, but it started crashing every day, and it was down for weeks at a time, so everybody abandoned it for MySpace.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think I looked at it and went, it was kind of, I like Facebook, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do like Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's easier to ignore shit on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, one thing I love about Facebook is that if there is an app that's publishing things that you don't want to see, ignore, and you never see it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just hope with the 360 and the Wii, if it does start publishing those types of updates, you can block those as easily.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because unfortunately, Facebook is turning into Twitter, but it's almost getting worse because of all these quiz updates and things.
[SPEAKER_07]: I may be just as guilty as the next guy, but if you don't check that stuff...
[SPEAKER_06]: Facebook is like Rapid Fire Live Journal is really what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I was using Facebook for things, you know, like my family's on Facebook, so I actually more or less, it's how I, I put a little bit more important things there so I can keep in touch with my family.
[SPEAKER_02]: My Twitter is more like, just how I, it's more for networking now in a lot of the circles that I'm in, you know, for, I use it as a communication tool for people who don't text, you know, because it comes to my phone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I only use Twitter for the networking aspect of it at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: I find that most of my personal status updates I'm putting on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm using my live journal again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you know, I can't get into the in-depth thoughts on really deal with my day on Twitter and Facebook the way I can on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm kind of sad to see lots of people abandoning LiveJournal for Twitter and Facebook and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got that permanent account and it was a gift and I'm going to damn well use it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people warn me that LiveJournal wouldn't be around forever, but at the same time I say, look...
[SPEAKER_07]: If it were not for LiveJournal, the show probably would not exist.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's pretty much a given.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would not have met some of the friends that I have in real life.
[SPEAKER_07]: My current roommate, one of my best friends, and a couple other of my best friends, I would never have met if it wasn't for LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, that website has had a profound impact on my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would be a different individual.
[SPEAKER_07]: And call me a nerd, call me a dork, whatever you want to call me, for saying that about a website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Everyone's going to go to the biggest, baddest, newest thing, but I honestly still think that LiveJournal is remaining a staple for a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think Facebook has enough in terms of diverse things to do that it's going to have some staying power.
[SPEAKER_07]: Facebook also has games, which I find interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: One topic, I think we got into it on Bobby's show a little bit last week, and I can't remember if we got into it on our own show, but I was talking about how Facebook casual games are the future of casual gaming because they're casual MMOs, a lot of these that are coming up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games like The Mafia, The Mobsters, The Sorority Life, The Farmville.
[SPEAKER_02]: The ones I hate.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like my pet society.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd play that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would be interesting if those could somehow come to Xbox 360, but I don't think that's possible, obviously.
[SPEAKER_02]: Eh, maybe that's part of the deal, actually, getting the Facebook on is you get the apps with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Ranma in chat says, Yeah, but Rob, that's not the big reason why people are leaving LJ.
[SPEAKER_07]: People don't like the new draconian rules and regulations brought in, thus the exodus.
[SPEAKER_07]: The rules on LiveJournal have never once affected me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Same here.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm blogging about my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: That has never been something impacted by the LiveJournal rules.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sometimes I think, especially live journalers, and boy am I getting off subject, but I don't care tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think live journals, almost more than anyone, want to start drama over everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sometimes they're making a big fuss about nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you remember when they banned all those accounts because they were getting into...
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that some of it they did take out of context, which is really the big thing that you run into anytime you bring in a corporate entity.
[SPEAKER_02]: And a lot of people will just look for reasons to be offended.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you know how I feel about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I think that because they do have a legal responsibility to protect, I think that they were justified in their actions.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just needed to learn the difference between a Harry Potter fanfic and what was legitimately bad, naughty stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that it would have been better if they had taken more time or had better filtering in place.
[SPEAKER_02]: and I do kind of like that now it's like if you're going if you're not logged in and then it'll ask you right up front it will let you look at certain things if you're underage if it suspects you of being underage
[SPEAKER_07]: And I didn't like how everybody was so quick to abandon LiveJournal for other just clones, rip-offs of LiveJournal, which, you know, LiveJournal was always open source, so it was very easy to make the rip-offs of, because it was always about the community.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if the community branches off in all these directions, it's exactly what happened to my old WoW guild.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody started abandoning it because everybody wanted to get something else out of the game, and some people went over here, some people went over here, some people went over here, and the game got ruined for everybody because the community was gone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, maybe I'm going to take some shit for this comment, but some people got a little selfish, and it ruined the community.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I think, in the sense, that's kind of what happened to LiveJournal in some sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think a lot of those people that abandoned it for other sites got selfish.
[SPEAKER_07]: But give me shit for that comment if you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how I honestly feel, so too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: But every time I feel like LiveJournal's dying, I just load up, oh no, they didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then I'm always like, oh, okay, there's still tons of people on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually have a new member, by the way, to our cast who wants to comment on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: What in the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Tribble.
[SPEAKER_02]: His name is Angus.
[SPEAKER_07]: Since we don't have the ferret in this studio, I suppose Angus will have to do Angus the Tribble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Angus the Tribble.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: We're Orange Tangent Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, though, in more Xbox news, on the Amazon German site, there was a listing for 250 gigabyte Xbox 360 Elite that was promptly yanked right after it posts.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was for 297.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: and had two wireless controls.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a copy of Forza Motorsport 3 which is coming out in October.
[SPEAKER_02]: We know about the price cut so this could be something that they're going to do to produce more money to put in a bit more profit but there's no comment from Microsoft yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think like most rumors, this one's going to inevitably prove true as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's kind of funny, too, because in South Africa, apparently the website xboxgaming.co.za also had another Elite console bundle with also two wireless controllers and a 250 gigabyte hard drive as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you know, I think these are probably inevitable for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think, you know, these big bundles that come with lots of games and lots of storage, I think it's the Christmas.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's setting the stage for the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds good to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's inevitable you're going to see these larger drives come out, especially what's funny, if those rumors about the PS3 Slim with the 250 gigabytes are true, this is just right on par with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everybody's, you know, aware of what everyone else is doing, and so why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: And sell it for like $150 and you would make just tons and tons and tons and tons of money.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, just like call it the red light special or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just big brick of porn or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would just sell like crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Big brick of porn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, something that's being offered, well...
[SPEAKER_06]: Best Buy Best Buy Best Buy Best Buy
[SPEAKER_06]: How about a good game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Infamous is a good game, so is Killzone 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but they've been out for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true, you probably have a lot of people who already own all those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you know what, they don't have a lot of games coming out that are made by Sony that are brand new, so this is going to have to do for now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because there's no Uncharted 2 yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's kind of funny though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why are they letting people get away with that?
[SPEAKER_07]: So people bring in their PS3s and say... Because they have a 30-day return policy or whatever, and they can go... For any reason?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then I guess it sucks to be them for putting up that reason in the first place.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should have a clause in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's because probably people are pissed off that they just bought it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They knew that the price drop was coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we kind of all knew that the price drop was coming, but essentially they may have known that the price drop was coming, and now that it has, you know, they just sold the console to a guy for $100 more for, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: Be mad at Sony, or be mad at yourself for not paying more attention to what's going on, because we all knew this was coming for months.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Be an informed buyer.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: So you would be able to imagine yourself kind of throwing this football and then hitting maybe a button to release the ball or something as you're throwing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be the type of controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently this was patented with the motion and plus as a part of the football, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: How many broken TVs are we going to see?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I'd be worried about.
[SPEAKER_07]: But apparently there's a big old strap on this football that you put your hand through.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's supposed to prevent that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know some dumb kid's going to throw this through a TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm sure they'll have all the safety warnings and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just...
[SPEAKER_06]: These are dumb.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what's sad?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that the next real idea they come out with is going to be very dumb as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii Vitality Sensor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I just want to also say about this football real quick is that it's also supposed to be able to interpret running.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it's supposed to notice your body motion and so you can actually detect running.
[SPEAKER_07]: So maybe this is for some type of full-blown...
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo-based football game coming out in the near future or next year's Madden.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds lame.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because why do I need to buy another peripheral to do something that I could probably do with the remote by itself anyways?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe to kind of match that feel of actually holding the football in your hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they should try something else more innovative instead of having to create a new peripheral for every fucking game that comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't you create some new peripherals that can be used for more stuff than just like
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm totally getting one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go out to the Fries and Roses.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had shelves and shelves of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went down there too and I saw the Rock Revolution bundles and I'm like, I gotta see how much they were.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was $20 on the PS3, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: But still $60 on the Xbox 360, which I thought was weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: $20 though for the full drum set.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, nope, still not worth it.
[SPEAKER_06]: 90 cents!
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'll buy it for.
[SPEAKER_07]: I almost picked up the game, but I still have a broken Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, it might actually be good to convert into a Drum Mania controller or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe, when it's 90 cents.
[SPEAKER_07]: comments from chat chat.orange.com excuse me Kevin going to Kevin tonight for some comments Bochikawa asks Wii Motion Plus can sense running can't it yeah I would think so I mean isn't that a part of the Wii Remote can sense running EA Active has running in it and Wii Fit has it and you're running in place Frisbee says Nintendo because we spread ourselves too thin
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: ZapperShell, Awful
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll take the perfect shot any day.
[SPEAKER_07]: GameGuru in chat says, just watch, this will be included in Super Mario Football and it will sell millions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that's what they do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then I don't want to hear any fucking bitching when they're complaining that they can't figure out why the hardcore gamer doesn't want anything to do with them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next console cycle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do they not want to play our games?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like we're focusing only on children's games like we did at the GameCube and then bitched about that too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just... I don't think you need to do this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just make better games.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, a comment in chat made me think to remind for our international listeners, when we are talking about football, we're talking about American football.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not football as the rest of the world knows it.
[SPEAKER_02]: As in crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft in chat says Nintendo, play Mario's dick with new dick peripheral.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's not family friendly, you see.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why that wouldn't happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not for the whole family.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is fun for Mario.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Wii Vitality Sensor for old people.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what they're going to put on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's going to be the slogan.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the pack-in game, you're going to die soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be like that banner ad you always see on the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, click to find out when you will die.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then you put your mouse over it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says 666 and all this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you ever seen that ad?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw it on MySpace once.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just cracked me up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's why I don't go to MySpace.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would somebody click on that, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say once I saw one with OJ Simpson and as she moved the mouse he was wielding a knife and it was so wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: But really funny and I still remember it to this day which I guess is what advertising is all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course I just don't remember what product it was for.
[SPEAKER_07]: Win a free Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was for ShamWow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, ShamWow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got release dates coming up but first another story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um... There's actually something to be in next week's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... Famitsu is a game called Okamiden.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um... Which, um... It actually was, uh... Put out for the Japanese 7-Eleven website.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it is a Capcom trademark.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um... They mentioned it in 2chan.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, uh... Now everyone's talking about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the rumor is that it's a sequel to Okami.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: What it's looking like is it could either be Okami Gaiden or Okami Densetsu, which would be either Okami Side Story or Okami Legend.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okami was a pretty critically praised game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know how it did sales-wise, but I think it did okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Certainly as well as other games that get sequels made of them.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Capcom broke with Clover Studios.
[SPEAKER_07]: SILENT HILL SILENT HILL
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, well, next week actually got some pretty decent stuff coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Starting off with, of course, Guitar Hero 5, which will be coming out on the 1st.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's going to be on PlayStation 2, PS3, Wii, and 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, if you buy your copy during the month of September, you will also get a free copy of Guitar Hero Van Halen if you remember to register it online by the end of October.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming out will be Command & Conquer Red Alert Commander's Challenge on the PlayStation Network and Xbox Live Arcade this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pinball Hall of Fame The Williams Collection on PS3 and 360 Although if I remember correctly I think that's actually the week after I think that day is wrong Section 8 on PC and Xbox 360 this week Soul Calibur Broken Destiny on PSP Seven Wonders 2 on DS and Champions Online on PC
[SPEAKER_06]: Also another Xbox, or actually I think this is on both Xbox Live Arcade and the PlayStation Network, NBA 2K10 Draft Combine.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can actually build up some of your players for the new NBA game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Fate Unlimited Codes on PSP, which is a digital download only title.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think those are the big ones for this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do need to get my 360 fixed soon because I do want to pick up Guitar Hero 5 just because I like the song list in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: I may not be the biggest Van Halen fan, but hey, free game?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of hard to ignore, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I forgot some other ones here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warriors of Rochi 2 on PSP was coming out as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warriors Orochi 2
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Definitely looks kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: A game coming out on the PlayStation 2 this week, Sweet Honey Coming is the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's C-O-M-I-N-G.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it looks kind of like a date sim game because there's all these girls and practically upskirt shots of some of them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you sure that's the
[SPEAKER_07]: And if I remember correctly, I believe I saw an article on this on Kotaku, and they've actually...
[SPEAKER_06]: Warrior's Orochi 2
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's your Japanese release dates for the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about a trip to the UK, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, what we have coming up on the second is Defense Grid The Awakening, and then a bunch of stuff on the fourth.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Champions Online, Cursed Mountain, Dissidia Final Fantasy, Guilty Gear 2 Overture, IL2's Stromovic Birds of Prey, Metroid Prime Trilogy, The Humans, and Warriors Orochi 2 on PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's just going to keep going.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this year, everybody's afraid of Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there's a lot of games that normally come out in November that are coming out early.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, SmackDown vs. Raw 2010 is coming out at the end of October instead of the middle of November.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a lot of things are actually crammed in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, like, especially next week with, like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Dirt 2 Mini Ninjas Rock Band Information
[SPEAKER_06]: Including, you may remember we talked about the Rock Band Network How you can, well first off they're going to have some original content coming to there as well But another update that's supposedly going to be coming soon, I guess this November Is they're going to allow demos of songs that are available on their actual store Which is pretty cool, you get 30 second playable samples that you can check out And um
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, that's pretty sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Rock Band Network Store will be coming to the PlayStation 3 as well, however not to the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: and you know as of right now though the development tools to put songs on the actual Rock Band Network are only available through the XNA program but they are going to pick select songs from that Rock Band Network and actually put them on to the PlayStation 3 so basically the PlayStation 3 will kind of have the greatest hits of the Rock Band Network whereas you know the 360 will still have the bulk of the songs
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, apparently what's involved with it says, not every song on the Rock Band Network will be available for PlayStation 3 owners.
[SPEAKER_06]: The option to bring over a song to the PS3 version of the store will be offered at Harmonix's discretion, and even then it will be an opt-in.
[SPEAKER_06]: The artists have to do some paperwork to properly port their songs to the PlayStation Network, a process that Harmonix believes no one will refuse.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's more revenue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am so excited, by the way, about Rock Band Beatles, can I just say?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so looking forward to this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see the demo that they had at Fry's?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't see the demo at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they have the demo at Fry's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they really?
[SPEAKER_07]: I missed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I saw some other demos, but not of Rock Band Beatles.
[SPEAKER_07]: I saw a Rock Band demo, but it wasn't the Beatles.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was some kid playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they actually had Rock Band Beatles.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know why, I'm just really excited about it, even though I'm not a huge Beatles fan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, certainly I respect them and they have a lot of great songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wouldn't consider myself a rabid Beatles fan, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just think this game is going to be so cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, what a tribute to...
[SPEAKER_07]: what they're doing over there with this game that it's making a whole new generation I mean obviously I'm a little older than most people that probably listen to this show but I would say a lot of the you know college kids that listen to this show are probably excited about this too what a testament to that that you know Rock Band's making people excited about the freaking Beatles all over again I think it's neat I agree so I'm looking forward to it you know I'm gonna get it oh yeah
[SPEAKER_07]: We should have a rock star party one night and get our Beatles on.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, hey, but if you don't want to play music games, one thing you can do with your 360 or PS3 or soon the Nintendo Wii is this new service called Play On.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually already on the 360 and the PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: But apparently the service is about to be going into beta for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: This service will actually stream both Netflix and Hulu to your Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It basically builds a bridge between your computer and your Nintendo Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: But hey, it's a way to get these services on your television if all you have is a Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a 14-day free trial, but after that you have to pay $40 if you want to keep the service.
[SPEAKER_07]: Themediamall.com is where you can pick this up.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought Diversity already did that for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, at least, I'm not sure about the Netflix, but I know, I think you can stream Hulu with, um, Diversity.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had Diversity for a little while, but it was kind of hard to figure out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, I use it all the time for our, we watched, um, a Riff Trax movie on that the other day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Prisoner of Azkaban.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, uh, yeah, we use it for streaming movies and pornography all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_06]: G4, I think it does Hulu, and then some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's free, so I would try the free solution first if that doesn't work out for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't checked that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, I haven't looked at Diversity in a year and a half, so maybe that's why.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It works pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'd be definitely curious to check that out, but of course you can't get that on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it does work on the Wii, actually.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's done through a web interface or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it did.
[SPEAKER_06]: I could be completely wrong because I don't ever use it on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the Wii can't do high def.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it stream high def if it's available?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it can stream high def for standard definition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you been watching high def porn?
[SPEAKER_06]: I tend not to download the high def stuff because the file size is larger and it takes a lot longer so no but we have streamed high def movies over on it and it works pretty well of course you know Wi-Fi probably wouldn't work well with high def and definitely not on the Wii alright well we're just about to the end of part A tonight of our show there's plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio still to come but of course we can't say goodbye to part A tonight without the classic game of the week
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Tonight's classic game is a little shooter called Robo Aleste.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if anyone else knows this game.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's, um, it was a Sega CD game, and it's actually, it really is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was put out by Tengen in 1992, um, in Japan, 93 in America.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um,
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like feudal Japan having giant mecha.
[SPEAKER_02]: is pretty much the story of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And one of the pilots is fighting against the other feudal lords.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you play someone named Kage, who is one of Nobunaga's robot ninja army.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you're flying the Aleste, which is a big robot with a gun who looks very much like samurai armor.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, pretty...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a weird storyline, but it's pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, in Japan, by the way, it was called Denin Aleste.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, it's one of those vertical shooters.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have your enemies coming forward and behind you and to the side, and you have a boss, and yeah, shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you've got different kind of weapons.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have Reisenha, which is a lightning attack.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have...
[SPEAKER_02]: Husha Shuriken, which is like big stars.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Hiei Meppujin, which is also called the Flying Shadow Formation, so you can have options that fly up in front of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the Bakuryu Hosenka, which is Exploding Flower.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's like little bombs going out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a pretty cool little game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, there's not really much else to say, it's just a shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, and by the way, it was developed by Compile, so it's in that family.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pretty cool game, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, yeah, it sounds kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm looking at this, it looks like a fun little shooter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It almost looks widescreen to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if that's just the way they capture it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I guess this is kind of a standard size, but... Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because obviously they didn't make games on widescreen back then, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: However, they occasionally did make some shooters where you could turn your TV sideways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why would you do that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that dangerous for your TV?
[SPEAKER_02]: How do you think about how shooters are built?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually quite a number of games that are made with the monitor being in the top of the cabinet and using a mirror.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the game will play reverse.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the mirror will show it right side.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I've seen one of those before, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's done a lot of times for purposes of getting the right kind of screen shape.
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100 Matt in chat says, Wait, are you saying Feudal Japan didn't have mechas?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Feudal Japan did not have mechas.
[SPEAKER_02]: It did have giant enemy crabs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Frisbee just asked, or giant enemy crabs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a movie I saw that had giant enemy crabs set in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's called The House Where Evil Dwells.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was a movie that I had been looking for since I saw it when I was like 6 or 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's one of the early American movies that did Japanese style horror.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's about these people that moved to Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of them is a writer and he wants inspiration.
[SPEAKER_02]: Except they end up being possessed by ghosts who live in the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: But there's a scene where the daughter gets thrown out of a tree by a giant demon crab.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure what to think of this.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they make grunting noises at her.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alrighty, whatever you're into.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Robo Aleste is your classic video game of the week on the Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, you can get it in English.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is available, so check that out if you're a Sega CD owner and you want to see feudal Japan with giant enemy robots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's going to do it for tonight's Part A of Orange Lounge Radio, but fear not, we've got plenty more to come in Part B, including your phone calls, your Twitter topics, and rapid-fire news, as well as we're going to be talking a little bit about Walmart and the possibility about arcades in Walmart's future, beyond just the couple of games you might see in the lobby.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to talk about all that when we come back for Part B, so stay tuned here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Welcome back, everybody, to more of Orange Lounge Radio on this Sunday, August the 30th of 2009, where we, of course, tape live every Sunday night at All Games Radio from 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time till, I don't know, around 9, whenever we feel like quitting.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the great thing about being on a flexible station like All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't have a set time limit when we have to finish, but poor Bobby, the show before us, he has to finish by 6 o'clock because that's when we're usually on, but he's flexible, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: and sadly he won't be on next week because he's going to Penny Arcade Expo and hopefully will be calling us next week from Penny Arcade Expo to give us the rundown we are all too poor to go this year actually I'm saving up to go to PAX East I don't know about my wonderful co-hosts but I know that's my goal is to get to Boston next year so we'll see I'm saving up for more pasta
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not traveling.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a big traveler?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I will represent OLR if no one else wants to.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you guys can do a show without me that week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be tons of fun, won't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, let's get back into some more gaming news here at Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, wait, I lied.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to start with Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to start off Part B with some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I actually got us a little theme song this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little smooth jazz for your Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: Starting off, reading some of the responses on Twitter at OLR and things you want us to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blade3 asks, laptop with fold-out panoramic screens, good for gamers, possibly 3D?
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't heard of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have a laptop now with fold-out monitors?
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, have you heard of this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope, but it sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It sounds cool, but isn't that kind of expensive?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would seem kind of pointless.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would be kind of ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, a PC with panoramic monitors, I can get behind that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actdeft wants to know... Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a plug for our show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you, Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sertour wants to know... From what I've been reading, there are certain aspects that are definitely slower.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, my Slim will be here Thursday.
[SPEAKER_07]: My first new console since the NES.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game suggestions...
[SPEAKER_06]: Buy some used $20 games or something It's like buying a Commando drop down price
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan Shadow says, OLR, the indie game PB Winterbottom is finally coming to Xbox Live after a great showing at E3 2008.
[SPEAKER_07]: This looks good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've never heard of this, PB Winterbottom.
[SPEAKER_06]: You heard of this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think this is actually one of the games that 2K is actually publishing on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's an independent game, but they're publishing two games that are going to be on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't heard too much about it, but it looked neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on the horizon for PS3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we know any other features on the horizon?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they have any press conferences though at PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as the PlayStation 3 goes, there's supposed to be a lot of stuff for the 3.0 firmware upgrade, like the animated themes and the What's New portion of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ray Ayanami says, Oops, I guess I read it anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that the new one that they've talked about that's supposed to be coming out on Wii?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or is this a whole new Tetris game?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's DS and Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like Tetris Party or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was different.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless that's what he's calling Grandmaster for.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, I'm getting a picture right now of what this new little dual screen laptop looks like.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, that looks actually kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like a bad Photoshop or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awful.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, one more tweet from Tigerclaw305.
[SPEAKER_07]: Imagine sitting next to someone on a plane with that watching a movie.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, as if the overweight people weren't bad enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: TigerClaw305 says Piracy protection is why PSP Go's battery isn't removable
[SPEAKER_06]: There's no such thing as not removable Apparently the whole Pandora's battery thing is the reason why the PSP Go is battery, you can't take it off Yeah, but they forget one thing No one's going to buy the PSP Go And if you really want to put homebrew and pirate stuff, you're going to buy PSP 3000 Which is also readily available for less than the PSP Go What if they stop making PSP 3000?
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not going to You think?
[SPEAKER_07]: They'll piss off a lot of people if they do that
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, there's a comment right here from John Collar, the Sony Computer Entertainment Association, America's president.
[SPEAKER_07]: You won't be able to rip your games and play them on the PSP Go system.
[SPEAKER_07]: The firmware precludes that.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no external battery, so there's a number of protections put into place on the system.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, ho, ho, ho, you're just throwing out another challenge, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just stop doing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They really want to take it apart to get to the battery they can't.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, people will take apart their systems to mod it if they really need to.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just saying that you can't do it doesn't mean it's not possible because every single firmware that you've released has been cracked immediately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, that's enough for Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you have more you want to contribute, we'll open up the Skype line a little later in the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry if we didn't get to your tweet, but we want to get to some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, some quick topics to start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tim Curry makes every game better.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, in other news, Space Invaders and Bust a Move are headed to the BlackBerry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mainly, you see a lot of new games coming to the iPhone, but yes, it's nice to see that the BlackBerry is getting some new stuff as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both of those are going to be available, I guess, for $4.99 and feature two different control schemes.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then finally, Peggle Nights is coming to Xbox Live Arcade via an expansion for Peggle and of course that will pretty much double the amount of levels that are available in there and will feature three new achievements worth a total of 50 Microsoft points or I guess achievement points, not Microsoft points no word yet on what the expansion is going to cost but it will be coming out sometime this fall
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and it's a monkey, a little monkey instead of a little seahorse or whatever it was in that game.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's much cuter than Seaman.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: N Plus is developing a new game called Scrap Metal.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, Slick Entertainment made N Plus.
[SPEAKER_07]: They are now making a new game called Scrap Metal that's had a little trailer released this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a top-down racing game and it looks kind of like, if you remember, Super Off-Road, which is like the quintessential pizza parlor game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, or like Super Sprint or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rock and Roll Racing is another game that's being compared to.
[SPEAKER_07]: All those games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But of course, a newer type of physics engine.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks like the track doesn't all show on the screen at once, but it looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does look really sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet this game will be a lot of fun to play on Xbox Live Arcade, so keep an eye out for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And lastly, some of your Rock Band updates this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some of the songs that will be coming out to Rock Band this week include The Talking Heads,
[SPEAKER_07]: and she was Cross-Eyed and Painless, Girlfriend is Better, Once in a Lifetime and Take Me to the River.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of those games coming out on the Xbox 360 and PS3 versions of Rock Band this week as well as some individual songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: from Avenged Sevenfold, The Jam, Oasis, and Rage Against the Machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gorilla Radio is coming out on Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oasis, by the way, a live song coming from them, Supersonic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently you won't be seeing Oasis live anymore as one of them threw a hissy fit as tends to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really like how it was said in an episode of Phineas and Ferb.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a diva tantrum.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I think Perez Hilton said that too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's some of my rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, let's move forward with all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: As soon as my computer catches up.
[SPEAKER_02]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_02]: They changed the date for the release of Scribblenauts in the UK.
[SPEAKER_02]: They said it's actually going to be pushed out until October 9th instead of September 15th.
[SPEAKER_02]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we're getting it on September 15th.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, but I'm being empathetic for them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there is a Star Wars adventure game using the Scum Engine.
[SPEAKER_02]: but it's actually fan made it's called Han Solo Adventures and it's one of the it's an adventure game studio game so it gets the old LucasArts type game but it's supposed to be based off the early life of Han Solo Han Solo, the early years taking Star Wars fanboy wank to a whole new level Mr. Eyeshot first
[SPEAKER_02]: And then other news, Tatsunoko vs. Capcom is getting four new characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: Two of them being Tatsunoko characters and two of them being Capcom characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's being announced at the 2009 Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe we'll get Joe from Gatchaman.
[SPEAKER_07]: Phoenix Wright, please.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frank West, Frank West, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would actually be a really good one for Western audiences too, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frank West.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love Tatsunoko vs. Capcom except the end boss is a bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: What if we're getting Kaze?
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Puzzle Fighter Dan.
[SPEAKER_06]: They could draw a bunch of red bricks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's get back into some long discussions.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a few topics we're going to spend a little more time on tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well there's a rumor going around that EA is the one responsible for holding back PS3 cross-game chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the reason being is that one of their older games, and people are not exactly going to say which one, although I remember reading somewhere that they think it's Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix, apparently doesn't support custom soundtracks, I guess, or something to that effect.
[SPEAKER_06]: What was it, uh...
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it was one of the ones I guess that didn't use an in-game cross-media bar or something like that in support.
[SPEAKER_06]: And because I don't know why your old Harry Potter game would be a big game for them still, because of that game, they didn't want the other games making that game look bad or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but what's our source on this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, is this coming from a respectable... It's from an insider.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are we talking the Ars Technica mole who's usually pretty believable?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, some other dude.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some dude on a forum?
[SPEAKER_06]: I would have more respect for him if he was called Secret Squirrel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Secret Squirrel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Secret Squirrel.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would that be your mole name if you were to spill trade secrets on a web forum, Secret Squirrel?
[SPEAKER_07]: I would be Secret Squirrel.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, SSJ100Matt in our chatroom tonight asked, so I can't play Dragon Force while I play Harry Potter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doesn't sound like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, PS3 titles... I don't understand why that would hold up voice chat, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have the cross-media bar in an old-ass game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's basically... What it was is custom soundtracks is actually what was the problem holding it back.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, PS3 titles have to be developed with...
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Boohoo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it is something the Xbox has that, you know, the PS3 doesn't have.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I also just don't like to talk to people while I'm trying to play other games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, if we're playing a game together, yeah, of course I like to talk to people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, 1 vs. 100, yeah, you have to do party chat in those games.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's way more fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, if somebody else is playing, or especially if I'm trying to focus on a first-person game, like, I don't...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't own Gears of War 2
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Max Technica
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, but apparently the other interesting thing, there's actually a test going on at a Walmart right now in Santa Clarita.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's happening at a Walmart Supercenter store.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, and this is why I wanted to bring this up, DJ Max has been location testing for quite some time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that's really news, but I think what is news about this is the fact that it's happening at a Walmart.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is being reported by MamaniStyle.com, who really keeps tabs on what's going on with these music-based games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what's interesting about this is that apparently they're trying to actually kind of move into the arcade business at Walmart.
[SPEAKER_07]: And rumor is going around that if these tests work, that they're expanding some of these arcades in certain locations, that many of the Walmarts everywhere are going to see more floor space dedicated to a dedicated arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I guess the big...
[SPEAKER_06]: Was it the Cabela's Game Hunter games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Deer Hunters and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're not bringing as much money in as they were before?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, we did have Jumbo Safari at Walmart for a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do see Walmart's arcades and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think all it really takes is just...
[SPEAKER_06]: replacing the games they have with some better games
[SPEAKER_06]: It'll make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I remember back in the day when they had arcade games, regardless of the source.
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember we used to have like a, was it a FoodMax or like a big warehouse food store that had a Neo Geo multi-game system in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I used to love playing Magician's Lord and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have that game in the vault.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, you know, I'm all for more places having arcade games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hell, there's even 7-Elevens I see now that do not have an arcade game in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: That is just blasphemy right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lots of 7-Elevens don't have arcade games anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: That was where I used to play Mortal Kombat 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: It wasn't a 7-Eleven, it was a knockoff.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was called Quick Mart.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a little place in the town I grew up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually had Mortal Kombat 2, and when it first came out, they had it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Street Fighter 2 and I remember there was a local diner that had Captain Commando oh we used to play that all the time wouldn't that be weird though if arcades make a comeback thanks to Walmart although I don't think it would be the same type of arcade like if it is a babysitting place at Walmart this is an arcade I want to stay the hell away from but it's going to be weird if they have stuff like DJ Max Technica and like the cool new games people want to play well maybe the whole DJ Max Technica testing at Walmart is to test it's durability
[SPEAKER_07]: That is going to be big resources because you have to bring in people to fix those machines.
[SPEAKER_07]: But then again, something huge like Walmart, you could have a dude that just goes around all the different Walmarts in the area and fixes all the arcade machines.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm sure the machines would make decent money.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then he'd shoot himself at the end of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You don't have to have the most top-of-the-line games, I'm sure, at a Walmart arcade to be able to make some money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, obviously these Deer Hunter games are making some money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen a dude play in those games.
[SPEAKER_02]: I played one once.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember there was a Walmart near here that had a DDR solo machine in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so Walmart might possibly be the next resurgence of arcade gaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm not sure how I feel about that, but to be continued.
[SPEAKER_02]: That makes me feel kind of dirty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that's a good word for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little dirty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, luckily you can get bath soap and all sorts of things to clean yourself off with at Walmart in the bathing aisle.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, moving on with more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic the Hedgehog, Blue Sphere, Chaos Level
[SPEAKER_02]: Then with Sonic 2, you'll be able to play as Knuckles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, of course, you know how it worked with Sonic 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, so if I have those other games on Xbox Live, I get that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or does this all come free with Sonic & Knuckles?
[SPEAKER_02]: It comes free with Sonic & Knuckles, the add-on capability.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you had the cartridges, it'd work the same way.
[SPEAKER_07]: But do I have to have the other games downloaded, do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: You do have to have the other... You have to have Sonic 2 to be able to play Knuckles in Sonic 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Got it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like owning the cartridges.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I wasn't sure if because... You know, this is different.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is in cartridges now, so I was just kind of wondering if they were coming with the download or what have you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nah, it's all in GameTap anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: If I play those games, it's usually where I go to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not really interested in purchasing those games, especially since you can just buy the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I have the Mega Collection, which I don't know if it has Sonic & Knuckles on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it has Sonic & Knuckles, but I don't think it has the add-ons like this does.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I have a feeling this wouldn't work with the Genesis Mega Collection.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just have a feeling.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll just buy the other games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or buy them again.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, speaking of companies holding back other companies for doing things, I don't know if we touched on this last week about Final Fantasy XIV and the reason why it's not coming to the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, apparently Microsoft was holding them back from putting an MMO on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, apparently the same thing is now happening with Champions Online.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently, it's just Microsoft doesn't have the framework built in place, or they're just not willing to conform to what they're looking for.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they do, but XI's a little different, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, XI had that whole play online front end, but it was a little awkward on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess it was no different from PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: They actually function very similar.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to just log in through the play online front end first, and the same thing on the PC, and then you can get into the game, but it was always kind of a little weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I guess because Final Fantasy XI was the exception to the rule, I guess, but apparently there's something that they're doing, some sort of red tape that's holding up a bunch of different games from being on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think this could be a bad misstep by Microsoft?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because PlayStation 3 is going to be getting some MMOs, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the DC Universe coming out, we know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, though, when DC Universe and the agency and stuff like that starts coming out on the PS3, that might put a little bit more pressure on them to get their act together.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am kind of surprised that we haven't really seen a lot of MMOs on 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's supposed to be that Marvel one that kind of fell through, so I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: but yet they have Final Fantasy XI but I guess I don't know if that front end makes the difference or what because I heard Final Fantasy XIV does not have play online they're doing away with that whole thing which is good play online was crap it was interesting at first but I mean the thing is that it really served no purpose unless you also played Tetra Master which very very very very very few people did play online was originally supposed to be like a front end for I think all these other
[SPEAKER_07]: I think in Japan there might have been one or two others, but there really was nothing anywhere else, and it made it kind of pointless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Final Fantasy XI, I don't have to update anything because it's still the play online viewer or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: You wouldn't have it on one console and not have it on the other unless the players were independent of each other, which I don't think is going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't see them going that direction.
[SPEAKER_07]: SSJ100 Matt in our chatroom says, Play online was a waste of space on my hard drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was pretty pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you couldn't really delete it, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you had to go through the uninstall.
[SPEAKER_07]: You had to put back in the disk just to uninstall the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you tried to delete it, it would kind of screw things up.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was just a nuisance.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a pure and utter nuisance to deal with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully they're going to be smarter about it with Final Fantasy XIV, which it sounds like they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hey, cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: In theory, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, kind of something interesting came to light this week about the new Rock Band Unplugged demo that's out there and available right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently, though, the PSP Go is coming with a voucher that you get an exclusive demo of Rock Band Unplugged for the PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_07]: So when you get your PSP Go, you'll get to download this demo for Rock Band Unplugged.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the thing about this demo, it will also play...
[SPEAKER_07]: Downloads from the Rock Band Unplugged store So the demo comes with five songs But if you don't really want to buy the game You don't have to You can just buy the additional songs you want to play
[SPEAKER_07]: and add those to your game and just continue to play Rock Band Unplugged that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, are they trying to do that to... See, I don't really get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That seems in the long run, wouldn't they end up losing some money on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, but they gain the money from the song downloads.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: You haven't really heard of a game distributed like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because the song downloads, I mean, later on if you decide to buy the game, they'll still work with the full game too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean, really the only asset then of getting the full game is getting the 40 whatever songs that come with the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because apparently the engine itself is going to download all onto your PSP Go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm kind of curious to see how that plays out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wonder if we're going to see more demos like that in the future where essentially all the sales are going to be based off of microtransactions, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, we're going to take a little break here to get to the mailbag at mailbag at orangelawntrader.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Every week you guys send us emails and we talk about them here on the program.
[SPEAKER_07]: The lovely Dark Sakura jumps into the mailbag and pulls out a few of her favorite emails and reads them here live on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dark Sakura, what do we have in the mailbag this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: We have one from Loomies that says, Yeah, we are totally far away from where all that is going on.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're in the Sacramento region, and most of the fires, unfortunately, are happening in Southern California.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's about seven hours away from us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so most of it's far away.
[SPEAKER_02]: So thanks for thinking of us, and...
[SPEAKER_07]: If you really want to do something, though, I know the Red Cross is always looking for donations and things like that, and during these times, they really need that stuff, so think about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, next up comes from Rini.
[SPEAKER_02]: Greetings and salutations to the crew, but for once I'd like to extend my admirations to DarkSakura for choosing motherfucking Silphid as the classic game of the week on episode 335.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bought that game completely out of randomness for an amazing $10 new, but that's not the point of this email.
[SPEAKER_02]: While not everyone out there will run out to play Silphid, I would like to share a bizarre yet awesome experience with the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had just started another session of the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Around the second stage or so, the game crashed.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game screen completely went to a dark screen with white text, and it caught me off guard since Silphid never did that before.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't bump my Sega CDX.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, the rare portable one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have Windows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nor was there anything within the vicinity to jolt my console.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game just suddenly glitched itself for no reason.
[SPEAKER_02]: The interesting thing about this whole event is what was on screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Pyramid Head brandishing its cleaver.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was on the screen was an apology.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, the game apologized.
[SPEAKER_02]: What makes it even better is that the game was not only able to recover and head back to the title screen, but it also shot off a free continue so I wouldn't lose my progress.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sadly, I've never been able to replicate this, nor do I believe there is a documented instance over the internet, so I guess it's a sad little cherished memory for me to have and love alone.
[SPEAKER_02]: OLR Crew, have you had any experiences with unusual game behavior that stood out for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Just pushing having to reset the Genesis in that X-Men game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna have to fuck around with mine then I'm gonna have to actually see if there's anything about that online anywhere There might be, who knows
[SPEAKER_06]: I've always thought that the game should apologize for me playing it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, not Sylphie, but maybe like Driver 3 or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry that we made this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it sucks, but hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: We got apologized to by Blockbuster after renting a game that we brought back an hour later.
[SPEAKER_02]: We rented WCW Thunder and it was so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: We called Blockbuster and asked them if we could take it back and they said they were sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: They let us get another game because it sucked that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: That sucks to have to apologize for something they really didn't do, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Blockbuster's just the... I understand that that's just good customer service to let you bring the game back and get a new one, but they shouldn't have to apologize for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: They didn't make the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I know that's good customer service and blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, moving forward.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: From Shook.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello, OLR.
[SPEAKER_00]: Shook, Shook, gay duke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello LLR, first off I want to say there was a typo in my last letter.
[SPEAKER_02]: I meant to say that the K in my name is pronounced as if it were lowercase, not silent.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Shook will suffice from now on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now on to other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: My bigot dad, you have my permission to call him whatever nasty name you want, finally discovered that I had Final Fantasy X when he saw me in the middle of a battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: Without a word, he ejected the disc, put it in its case, and put it in his safekeep.
[SPEAKER_02]: What a bummer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Luckily, he didn't find Chrono Trigger, which is a very good thing because I will guard that game with my life.
[SPEAKER_02]: No joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: I truly have stumbled upon the best thing I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yes, DarkSakura, I did do the ending where you beat it at the beginning.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Proceed to bag on my dad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now that that's over, I have a suggestion.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll come back at the end of the email.
[SPEAKER_07]: I do want to bag on your dad, but we'll come back to that in a little while.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a suggestion for the Wii inflatable chair.
[SPEAKER_02]: I bet that there's going to be some kind of fetish porn game that involves that inflatable chair so it's not completely bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can't wait to join the OLR Home Club.
[SPEAKER_02]: My PSN username is MGS654.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't ask.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your dad needs to... Hold on a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to kind of cue something up here because I... The Tribble has a comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Now he'll know about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he'll get in trouble for what you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like that kind of person.
[SPEAKER_07]: All I have to say... Okay, whether you want to replay this or not, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: All I have to say is that he should be thankful that you want to spend your time playing something that takes intelligence, strategy, wit...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how kids sometimes get involved in this is when they rebel, they rebel hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: You sound smart enough where that's not going to happen, but your dad should be freaking counting his blessings.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can vouch for that from experience.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also one from Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, there is a Marvel vs. Capcom 2 cabinet down the street from me in a pizza shop.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really want to use it because, well, they are rare, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: They are?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would totally steal that if stealing was legal, but man, none of my friends will join me because they think fighting games are gay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care for that terminology.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know a good fighting game that could turn them on to the genre?
[SPEAKER_02]: PS, don't say Street Fighter, they hate it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Love, Deathwishing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, no, I can't think of a game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, Street Fighter 2 is like the pinnacle of fighting games.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they don't like that, there is nothing you can do.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is just, there's no fighting game that's going to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you could try cutesy fighting games, but if Marvel vs. Capcom 2 is too gay, then sorry, but the other games are going to be even worse.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mortal Kombat, maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should all make them play... What was that awful fighting game with the... It was really... Pit Fighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Make them play Pit Fighter.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have better... Pit Fighter is the worst fighting game I've ever played in my life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's my suggestion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get new friends.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my suggestion.
[SPEAKER_02]: Another email!
[SPEAKER_02]: God, this is long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hello to DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for discussing and reading my tweet on the last show.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm really passionate about Extra Life and what we gamers can do to make a difference, so I'm glad you brought it up during the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me tell you a little bit about Extra Life.
[SPEAKER_02]: Extra Life was started by the folks at SarcasticGamer.com and its founders, Doc Adams.
[SPEAKER_02]: He has done some previous work with fundraisers before, but this has become something important to him.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can read about his inspiration.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the link doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: As for my inspiration, I recently put up a story on Sarcastic Gamer pointing out why I've become involved.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to read this.
[SPEAKER_02]: The reason I brought it up to OLR is that you guys have quite a great community.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been listening to this show since it became a podcast a long, long time ago, and I've since become a huge fan.
[SPEAKER_02]: I now listen to you guys on my iPhone on my drive to work or out on my morning runs.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was happy you got to be part of All Games years ago since I listened to Scott and AGI way back in the day.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never really was part of your forums or anything, but I always loved listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: For Extra Life, you can sign up through the main page at extralife.sarcasticgamer.com and click on the sign up button.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will take you to Texas Children's Hospital website and you can put up a donation page there.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will be a personal donation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, but this is something we do, not the listeners, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, unless listeners want to be... Oh, because we have a lot of people that have their own things too?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I want to make sure that people do know about this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will be a personal donation page that you can edit and change up quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: But more importantly, you can send out the link to anyone so they can give you online donations through the site.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can also use PayPal for overseas donations as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now from there, you can also create a team so other participants can join with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone else in your community can sign up and join your team as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should totally do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It takes an aggregate total of those that join your team, and you can see how much the OLR team raises overall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, so then don't go make your own page.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let us do it, which we're going to do in the next week here, and then we'll tell you guys what our little link is so we can all raise together.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can even see how much each team member raises as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: That is if you go there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, what it is is other people can make their own donation pages, but we can band them together as a team.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it keeps an aggregate amount.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have to go in there and kind of play with it and see what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_02]: He put up his donation page, which is waystogive.texaschildrens.org slash netcommunity slash Alan Ray, A-L-L-E-N-R-E-Y.
[SPEAKER_02]: So if anyone wants to take a look at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: As for the Gamer Day itself, you can do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people will be videotaping and livestreaming their gamer activities, so if you guys and gal want to do it, it'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like your theme of obscure fucking vault games.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ha ha ha, it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_02]: To continue, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds fun, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, yeah, it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just think of it this way.
[SPEAKER_02]: This will be the most fun thing you do to raise money for any charity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people train for marathons, like me, or ride a bike across the U.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'll put out way too many calories and at some point it's going to hurt.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take it from me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hurt my knee training for my marathon.
[SPEAKER_02]: You will never have more fun raising money and you just have to pick up a game controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: We would love to have you added to the list of gamer sites participating.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also hope you can reach out to other shows on the All Games Network like VGO and Bobby Blackwolf and his shows.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, thank you for mentioning Extra Life and I hope to hear some good news from you all soon.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you have any suggestions, I'm not going to share Twitter on the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for your time.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's from Alan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all going to go down October 17th.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have something posted on our website this week as soon as we get everything set up with more details.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just from a technical aspect, I'm starting to feel a little overwhelmed with how we're going to make it work because we want to do an hour of pinball incorporated in this as well, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, my best advice on this, don't waste time overthinking it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll be easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have more than one video camera.
[SPEAKER_07]: We know that Loki has the video capture card and we have a switch box.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a video camera.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can borrow, hopefully maybe Victoria will lend us hers.
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think the way it's going to work though, we're going to do games from the vault for one hour basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I don't know how we're going to pick them.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if we'll have folks donate.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I don't know if there's any way to kind of show like so-and-so donated money so they pick the next game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what we're going to do, but we'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whoever donates the most money during one game gets to pick the next game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, maybe we'll do something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to have to have a list of games or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or gets to pick a system.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we'll figure something out.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll work out the details over the next few weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although what I see happening is us having the newer systems hooked up in the front room and the older systems hooked up in the vault.
[SPEAKER_02]: We will have Dreamcastage testify.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we need to get some more of our local friends involved, so we'll put out the call this week as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: So everyone, get off your asses.
[SPEAKER_02]: Last email from Rob-a-ba-ba-ba.
[SPEAKER_02]: In reference to the August 16th podcast, my first PS2 was broken from the start, but in a very odd way that took me two years to notice.
[SPEAKER_02]: In retrospect, I should have kept the old one for the novelty of it all.
[SPEAKER_02]: It played all the games fine, oddly enough, and it never physically failed.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was something wrong with the processor clock or math processing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd play around with Ridge Racer 5, watch the playback, and it would get out of sync with the playback about 20 or 30 seconds in.
[SPEAKER_02]: The car was still maneuvering around the proper order, but being out of sync caused it to repeatedly crash into the walls.
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly thought this was a software problem with Ridge Racer 5 because it looked like a software problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: And finally we got Gran Turismo 3 A-Spec in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: The replay effect was really bad in GT3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I finally realized that was the strangest hardware problem in a game system ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: But massive hardware failures frequently covered under unofficial extended warranties.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, starting with the original Game Boy, my first two or three Game Boys had the dead-slash-solid-pixel-raster problem.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Nintendo happily repaired-slash-replaced for free.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not certain, but I believe it was because the Game Boy was not rugged enough for typical portable play, i.e.
[SPEAKER_02]: carrying around.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also needed direct sunlight to play, but that was a different issue.
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember the PSP had the problem with the dead pixels in the corner?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some massive hardware failures have been around at least 20 years, but like you said, flaming forums wasn't a big sport back then.
[SPEAKER_02]: Later, rub-a-ba-ba.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad that he's just signing it rub-a-ba-ba.
[SPEAKER_07]: Adopting his title.
[SPEAKER_07]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for the record...
[SPEAKER_07]: Mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com if you have some emails you want to send in.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we want to take a minute to get our angst on here in studio because, well, you know, sometimes we just read things on the internet that really tick us off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And when they do make us very upset, we have to do a little segment here that we like to call the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_07]: and let me read a little bit of inspiration for our FUs of the week this week and this comes from a GameStop apparently in Jacksonville, Florida apparently somebody tried to rob this GameStop but it wasn't for money
[SPEAKER_07]: No, he wanted the employee to fill the bag with games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Copies of Madden NFL 10.
[SPEAKER_07]: The robber went into a GameStop on a Monday night, unfortunately the guy's not named, otherwise we'd name him by name, was pretending he wanted a 360, but then whipped out a gun and demanded copies for Madden NFL 10 and any other 360 games that would fit in the bag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Apparently he made off with 23 games.
[SPEAKER_07]: $1,300 is what that's valued at.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two 360s as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you.
[SPEAKER_02]: My F you goes to, it's sort of a pseudo F you, just because I'm kind of happy about it at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: To 250th Anniversary Guinness, F you to being delicious, because I want to go back and drink more of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot more of you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was very, very freaking good.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: F you to having to go to work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I just don't want to go to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the weekends.
[SPEAKER_07]: My FU goes to people that can't see the faults in themselves and like to blame other people for things that they did that think they can do no wrong and some folks need to learn to accept responsibility and yeah, need to learn how to take a break.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on to some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a couple more and then we're going to get to your calls on the Skype line at 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: well there's something kind of I don't know if this is really super interesting but you know it made it into the gaming Guinness Book of World Records which having thumbed through the Guinness Book of World Records for games pretty much anything can make it in there but Arkham Asylum has now set the record for being the most critically acclaimed superhero game ever so what's that mean it was a superhero game that didn't suck so um
[SPEAKER_07]: But I mean, really, like, what superhero games have been that awesome?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, did they say what it took the... Marvel Ultimate Alliance is pretty damn awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're basically saying that it's gotten the highest Metacritic review average, I guess, among all the superhero games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But that's just like, that's almost as bad as saying it's the most critically acclaimed superhero game starring Batman that's ever appeared on the consoles.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why is that a record?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's not a record.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just people's opinions.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not like, you know... I'm sorry, but this game book is just really kind of...
[SPEAKER_06]: Watering down all the other records, being the tallest person, that's not really much of an achievement, that's just your DNA.
[SPEAKER_06]: But still, that's a physical achievement that you have there.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're that tall.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is just subjective stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: If we all wanted to get together with all the reviewers and make a game the highest rated game ever, they could easily do that and rig it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a little weird that Metacritic is being used by Guinness.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if I like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is just an odd title.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doesn't this reek of like, hi, we're going to pay these guys a lot of money to get this title so we can use it in our marketing?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want to hear something that I just thought of just now that's kind of a little fishy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Batman Arkham Asylum was published by Eidos, which is owned by Warner Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Warner Games also published a game called Guinness Book of World Records The Game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gee...
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't have close ties with them, do they?
[SPEAKER_07]: Conflict of interest?
[SPEAKER_07]: Never.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even think of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a good little comparison.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just thought of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, one more story for you guys tonight, and then we're going to get to the Skype line, your phone calls, and your opinions on the latest and greatest in gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what you're going to hear in the background here...
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yes, you know that old classic song.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a Guitar Hero 5 ad.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a new one that's airing on TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it features Playboy Bunnies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, ten of them, all rocking out to Guitar Hero wearing no pants.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the risky business.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, it's kind of like the ads.
[SPEAKER_02]: I like variety.
[SPEAKER_02]: 83 bands, all kinds of rock.
[SPEAKER_02]: Buy in September and get the unreleased Guitar Hero Van Halen on the house.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the thing that caught my eye about the ad is that they're selling that whole Guitar Hero Van Halen thing on the house.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not free.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it does say.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at the little red text at the bottom of the screen, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just says, buy one, get one.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it doesn't say free.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Can't stay free, because he'll get sued.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a very interesting way around it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, I thought that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're working that whole Van Halen giveaway into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Hef thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, it's Hef.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's a cultural icon.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's pretty cool they got everybody involved.
[SPEAKER_06]: But really, they really do need to come up with a new ad for...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there'd be plenty of guys that would argue with you that they could do 10 Playboy Playmates running around without pants on all day long and they'll never get old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next time a trampoline though.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about that?
[SPEAKER_07]: We need Trampoline Hero to come out just for that little ad to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Only if we get pantsless rage.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am totally down with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, we're going to open up the Skype line right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR is the number to call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seems like the show's kind of a little short tonight, but there just hasn't been a whole lot of gaming news this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been a little bit slow, and I think it's probably one of the whole fact that a lot of folks are going back to school right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so we're kind of at just like a little bit of lull before we're going to get slammed with game releases.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, they're trying to kind of keep it quiet as far as news goes because we just had Gamescom and BlizzCon, and now they have to save up some announcements for PAX.
[SPEAKER_06]: Makes sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we are kind of in a lull because probably all the secrets that are yet to be announced are going to be coming through on PAX pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, this is Ray Iannami.
[SPEAKER_04]: I got DJ Max Trilogy a few weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I should talk about it since the game is like 8 months old.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're under the radar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyways, so DJMAX Trilogy is kind of like the old DJMAX Online or kind of like O2 Jammery.
[SPEAKER_04]: It plays somewhat like Beatmania, but instead of using a proprietor controller, you use the PC keyboard.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a bunch of button modes in it, and... But there's one thing I really don't like about it that the other new DJMAX games have, and it's a feature called AutoCorrect.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, so this is an online game that you can download, kind of like O2 Jam, you said?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, you have to buy the physical copy, and then you have to install it from the DVD ROM inside, but once you get it set up, you don't need to disk it anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's offline, but there's an online mode.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this something that you can only import, or is this available in the U.S.? ?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's import only, but it has an English language option, though it's really crappy English.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_07]: What makes this game good enough to check out for music game fans?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I can get to that later, but anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, I think it's the fact that, like, the DMX Online has been dead for a few years now, so this kind of gives you a chance to play a rhythm game that isn't set to be on the PC again.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a feature I wanted to rant about in this game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's this feature?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm also correct, where basically if you hit the wrong node, but at the right time, you'll still get credit for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, say you're supposed to hit the J key, but you hit K, you'll still get the full judgment score for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not only the score, you still get 100%, but you have a little bit of a score penalty, but for me, that's good enough to be okay with the feature.
[SPEAKER_07]: That seems kind of easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, what's to stop somebody from hitting the key the same the whole time, just because your score will be a little bit lower in the end?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: It allows you to pass songs that you normally would not be able to pass without this feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, even Guitar Hero and Rock Band don't have this feature.
[SPEAKER_04]: And moreover, I just unlocked a new key mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: I unlocked a new key mode, and I'm trying to learn it, but when you have this feature turned on, it makes it confusing to learn, because I don't know if I'm hitting the correct keys or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd rather be penalized for hitting the wrong keys, because at least I know...
[SPEAKER_04]: That'll train me to hit the right keys instead of just guessing which keys I'm hitting incorrectly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, do you have any other thoughts for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, see ya Hi, this is Spazinator Hi Spazinator, what's on your mind tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a couple things.
[SPEAKER_04]: First off, I just got off of WhatUp.com and I saw a story on there that I think you may be interested in.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go ahead, shoot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just sent a picture to your profile for you to check it out later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently, there's going to be a new Xbox 360 bundle coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: According to this picture, they're calling it the Super Elite.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this the 250 gigabyte system we talked about earlier in Part A?
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I'm not sure what you talked about in Part A. I missed a little bit of the show, so... I just happened to see this on...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, assuming it's the same deal, what are your thoughts on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is this something that's necessary for Microsoft to do, or do you think this is just yet another skew out there in the marketplace to confuse me?
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of a toss-up.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we don't already have a 360 or...
[SPEAKER_04]: Your 360 is basically dead, then maybe you can use it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Otherwise, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: You may be able to make use of the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: What exactly?
[SPEAKER_07]: I kind of pointed this out on the PlayStation 3, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: We keep hearing bigger hard drives, bigger hard drives, bigger hard drives.
[SPEAKER_07]: But on both the 360 and the PS3, for what?
[SPEAKER_07]: What do we need these huge hard drives for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least for, you know, with both the systems, they're constantly coming out with arcade games, and, you know, assuming that you buy a lot of the arcade games, you know, for your system, or playing a game like a lot of TV shows, or at least on the
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that sounds more like it, room to buy more movies and spend more money on their store.
[SPEAKER_07]: That I can agree with.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else on your mind tonight, Spazinator?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I don't know if you saw my response to your tweet about informing the club, but yeah, I'd be interested in joining your OLR club,
[SPEAKER_04]: It should be on PSN for the rest of the evening.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later!
[SPEAKER_07]: 1877-GAME-OLR Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio if you want to give us a call.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, what was the rest of this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Buy one, get one half off?
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently this week we will have the opportunity to get one game and another game for half off at Best Buy and there's a bunch of different games that they're offering that and so you just purchase one of the qualifying games and get another one for 50% off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, I don't know exactly how far I have to go, but I'm...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you're about 15 hours away.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an hour and a half to Reno.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think about another 8.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's probably about, well, considering the bus has to stop everywhere.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I think she's taking the Reno route.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to go through Nevada, which is going to be very boring.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, how's the trip been so far?
[SPEAKER_01]: Mostly boring, especially once I got out to the mountains.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you occupying your time with any video games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you bring a DS or a PSP?
[SPEAKER_07]: Something to play?
[SPEAKER_01]: You've got your what?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_01]: Netbook?
[SPEAKER_01]: That computer I took to ASIN?
[SPEAKER_07]: At the moment, the main thing is an actual Far Far Apart because it's been so fucking long since I
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we have a Parapara in town?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we've got one nearby.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that sunrise thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't been to in forever.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't been there either.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know what she's talking about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm hoping we can make your trip fun, and you're a real trooper for taking the long way out here.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I've driven cross-country, and even though some parts are really boring, it's a beautiful experience.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I think definitely enjoy the time on the way out here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we will be seeing you soon, Misty.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care, be safe, and don't talk to strangers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll try not to.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, take care, Misty.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, give me a text when you hit Reno.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was planning on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, it sounds like I'll be seeing you either tomorrow night or Tuesday for sure, so take care.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hopefully tomorrow night.
[SPEAKER_07]: We shall see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm pretty sure we can make that happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow, but try again next week, guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: And especially sorry for the new folks that can't get through.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, I used to be able to see who was calling in, and I'd try to rotate it, but Skype changed it so that you can't  like if multiple people are calling in, only the fastest dialer gets through.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we just kind of take the calls as they get in.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you're a new caller, my biggest advice to you is just keep trying or write an email or a Twitter message.
[SPEAKER_07]: and do it that way if you haven't learned how to get fast on the phones yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do we have any other last minute stories here tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic Adventure DX is getting another remake apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh goody.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is coming from the Australian Classification Board has a new listing for Sonic Adventure DX Director's Cut and suggests that apparently
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess if that's it for Last Minute Stories tonight, it's time to go around and get everybody's final thought because we're getting pretty close to wrapping up the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know it was a little bit shorter tonight, but it's just been a slower week.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wish I really lived in this house, my sim house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your sim house.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought is coffee is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I had more cream, I'd make you some more.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_07]: The cup I had earlier was delicious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish they were still selling Blue Shark DDR pads, but they're not, so that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, believe it or not, folks, that's going to do it for another week here at Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, as always, thank you guys so much for downloading our show and tuning into us and supporting it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you like what you hear, please tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Help us spread the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's really how we succeed is through word of mouth.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's what we really want is just to help us spread the word because we don't have big advertising dollars or a magazine behind us or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it really is up to you guys to help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we'll be here to do it all again next week on a, I guess you could say, Penny Arcade edition of Orange Lounge Radio, where we're hoping we'll at least hear from some of our listeners making the trek out to Penny Arcade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sadly, we will not be there this year, but you guys will, and so we want to hear your voices next week on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you next week at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Until then, I'm Rob Roberts, she's DarkSakura, he's Loki, and we're out.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: To join us for a live show, visit www.allgames.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific Time.
[SPEAKER_00]: The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next week!