[SPEAKER_12]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello everybody, yes that's right, we are actually live tonight, believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because the man can't hold us down forever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, so we're back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you Live365 for working tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, on tonight's show, we got a whole lot of crap to catch up on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll be doing that tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also celebrating Loki's birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somehow, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just talking about TDR and some other games and things going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And oh, I had a baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, I had a baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we have to talk about my baby.
[SPEAKER_09]: You have a future tennis player.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, I have a baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to talk about my future tennis playing baby.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_10]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
Is this thing on?
[SPEAKER_19]: Believe it or not, it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are live, and this is episode number 155 for this September the 11th of 2005.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio that gamers really want, and this is Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're home for all the news and discussion on rhythm and music games, once in a while, as well as the gamer community and the pop culture world, a little more often.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like almond butter and cinnamon bread.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: You just made me think of Cinnabon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hungry for Cinnabon right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I found really good cinnamon bread.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I need an Ethernet cable, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know why Cinnabon pisses me off, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it smells like crack?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, because they have one in the mall, and it's like, right fucking by EB Games, so every time I want to go shopping for games, I go, ooh, Cinnamini.
[SPEAKER_04]: So fuck Cinnabon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, hi, Loki's here, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The tech master, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I'm here, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: I destroy Twinbee with Optimus Prime.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to talk about this game later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: That game was the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we'll talk about some various stuff tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, we've got a little bit of Bomani news to talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if it's so much a little bit, but the V-Rare's out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were going to play it for you guys tonight, except I couldn't get my hands on it, and I'm going to tell you about what happened there, because it's kind of a funny story.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll tell you about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki's supposed to be getting a copy of it from inside Konami.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also Ultramix 3's V-Rare, which we'll have first, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_03]: The guy better hurry up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Daniel's got to hurry up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bugged!
[SPEAKER_22]: I had to finish cracking out on Burnout Legends there
[SPEAKER_04]: Neuropa, because I like Neuropa.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: Gee, weren't we listening to Neuropa last night?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we were.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to hear them right now with Standing Still in Time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Join our chat room, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you then.
Yo!
Kipis Face
I can't sweat till the real first step in between betray who the what must gotcha control your meselance with the way you made up
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_25]: After this song, we'll be having a Let Them Move marathon.
[SPEAKER_15]: No!
[SPEAKER_25]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Crap-free Bavani Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey kids, we're back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode number 155 here in progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are actually live tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so freaking excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were off for a couple weeks there.
[SPEAKER_04]: One week was our choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were gone for a week because, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We deserve a vacation once in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually, secretly, some things are going on behind the scenes, including Jamie's bachelorette party.
[SPEAKER_04]: It happened to be the same night, but that was cool because I got to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was the only guy at Jamie's bachelorette party, but it was fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had a good time.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because you're special.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I saw Xanadu for the first time.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, you need to sit down and watch Xanadu all the way through from beginning to end, because that movie is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bring earplugs.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I like the music in Xanadu.
[SPEAKER_04]: That actually was one of the only things that made it worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The interesting thing about Xanadu, and I know a lot of you guys probably only know Xanadu from that song that was in DDR3rdMix.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, I'm trying to play a clip here.
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the first song a lot of people played in DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it starts with an X. An X is always better.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, because it's a one-footer.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Olivia Project, queen of the one-footers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so Xanadu is like this old-ass movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not that old.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I was alive when it was made, so it can't be that old.
1980.
[SPEAKER_09]: That movie is 25 years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_09]: It had Gene Kelly in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so what it was trying to do is trying to be like a throwback to old cinema where they would, you know,
[SPEAKER_04]: The Mews
[SPEAKER_04]: See, I'll show you how much I was paying attention to Santa too.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's because you came in and did you see the animated part?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love the animated part.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Don Bluth Studios and Don Bluth, to give it a video game connection, did Dragon's Lair, Space Days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Same guy who did that stuff and Dragon's Lair is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though Dragon's Lair was a ridiculously simple and kind of like as a game itself it was kind of stupid, like the interactive cartoon feature of it made it so worth it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The technology at the time was pretty nifty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kick-ass.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, hell, I can sit here and pay a quarter to control a laser disc.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's Rudy Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, think about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: We never got a perfect copy of Dragon's Lair at home until DVD players.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or if you are into the emulation scene, the Daphne emulator.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, true.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I should say a blessed copy of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Novellma.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not, oh, Scooby, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: He says Scooby, I think Buffy, so.
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're the wrong shirt, then.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, okay, so we were off two weeks ago because of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had the bachelorette party going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, which, by the way, was one of the more girly things I'd seen in a while.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, being the gay guy, I got to, you know, got the first look, or got the inside look at what girls really do when they get together.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_22]: I keep mishearing that as Dalzeem from like Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm like, here's a Dalzeem.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yoga.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yoga fire.
[SPEAKER_22]: Death by yoga.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yoga flame.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, last week we were all here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a shitload of people in studio too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had Mikulatov was here, Pixie Dust was here, the Orange Lounge Madam, who hadn't been here in like a year and a half, and her...
[SPEAKER_04]: Fiance now or a long time boyfriend, one of the two.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, Stylin was here and Mel B was here and we couldn't do a show because... And we were drinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we were drinking.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were quite intoxicated last week.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had three Guinnesses.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Live 365, due to some error after their maintenance window, they do regular maintenance on Saturday nights now, but they did some stupid error afterwards that caused...
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody on live 365 to be able to carry a live show, which pissed some people off royally because there's some stations out there that run live all the time, which, you know, one day in a more perfect world, I would like to be able to have Orange Lounge live all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see, you know, something we can look at for 2006.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you kind of piss some people off that they did that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So needless to say, a lot of listeners complain, a lot of broadcasters complain.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live 365 will be very careful about those sorts of things in the future, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So now we're here this week after two weeks of no show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those of you guys that are members of our LiveJournal community, though, you did get a show last week, so that's all I can say about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know we have some people listening for the first time tonight because of our podcast has still been going.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, we did a podcast last week, even though we were slightly intoxicated, which I don't think we really advertised on the podcast that we were drunk when we were doing it, or at least a little buzzed.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the beginning, I think we mentioned it, but we didn't really like, we weren't quite vocal about it as we usually are on the live show when we have three hours.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something like that was basically the thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we were quite intoxicated doing the show, but I have to hand it to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: And listening to the playback of the show, we did a pretty good job, considering how much we'd all had to drink.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was laying down in the chair with a beer in my hand.
[SPEAKER_22]: You left halfway through, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had to.
[SPEAKER_22]: You guys just let Mel B talk.
[SPEAKER_22]: He sounded pretty damn sober.
[SPEAKER_22]: Mel B was sober.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, that would be why he didn't sound that drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we did the podcast, and we have new people listening tonight because we have the podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know a lot of folks are saying that they're actually loading up their Live 365 stream in iTunes, especially now because you know iTunes 5 is out and all that stuff, so iTunes is very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong, iTunes is a great program, I use it myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, I just want to warn you guys that Orange Sounds Radio is presented in what's called MP3 Pro, and iTunes does not support
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Media Player supports it now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, if you want more information on MP3 Pro, you can visit our website.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's at orangehonestradio.com and check the FAQ.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I don't want to discourage you guys from listening in iTunes because we will sound normal through iTunes except we sound a little better with the MP3 Pro codec.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's broadband radio at a dial-up connection because MP3 Pro does something to the header or something where it encodes... It adds 10 years of maturity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Basically, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although I did download iTunes 5, it's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only thing I didn't understand about iTunes 5 is that it really wasn't that much different from 4.9, except for they changed the store a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the look.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit, but the look and feel, it's not like they changed the colors or they changed the way the buttons look or anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just kind of changed, well now it's more square instead of rounded.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I mean, it's cool and all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't get me wrong, I like iTunes, and iTunes 5 is cool and all, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it does the Outlook sync, I guess, which is cool if you're into using Outlook, which I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: Outlook sync?
[SPEAKER_04]: It syncs your contacts on your iPod with Microsoft Outlook.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: If that's something that appeals to you, you could go do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: I use Pine.
[SPEAKER_04]: For your email?
[SPEAKER_22]: Pine and Gmail, that's my two...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's pretty hardcore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um...
[SPEAKER_04]: Listeners in the chat room, blah, blah, blah, listening to some comments here.
[SPEAKER_04]: LIA365 needs to support AAC.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not the first person to suggest that, and some folks have actually suggested that to LIA365 directly.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think that would be kind of cool because I think AAC has better encryption.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what else has really good encryption is OGG, and I'd like to see LIA365 support it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Encryption or compression?
[SPEAKER_04]: Compression.
[SPEAKER_04]: What am I saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone just said OGG.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone just said OGG?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: OGG.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there has been talk amongst, you know, are we going to stay with Live 365?
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we not going to stay with Live 365?
[SPEAKER_04]: The problem, well, I guess I should say, Live 365, up until last week, has actually been pretty damn good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't complain a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got nice people running it, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Despite the fact we've gone to their awards ceremony two years in a row and didn't win crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: And had to pay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and had to pay.
[SPEAKER_04]: We had a pretty decent time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Betty's really nice, and she's like, you know, kind of... I win crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We won the remote control a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, and I won speakers by playing bingo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you actually get them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I walked out with that Humongoid box, remember?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: You actually got to take the speakers because you had come in from a long ways out of town, whereas the other folks had to have it shipped to them.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the speakers are now hooked up to my PC, where they were probably on display at GameStop on Fulton and Marconi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on, right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: Life 365 pays the licensing for songs that we play and although we've kind of had discussions on staff whereas you know is the video game music really it's kind of in a gray area you know I don't think we really need to pay licensing on it we don't really know we do play a lot of other music in our pre-show on Tuesday night show on the cage match that is ASCAP BMI all that stuff licensed and so Life 365 pays our licensing fees for that so we're all legit we're legal we're
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: So we've been listening to you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've thought about the switch up too, but those are kind of the reasons why we hesitate a little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now there's a whole lot of other suggestions there in the chat room, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go back to mods.
[SPEAKER_04]: What kind of mods?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, like MOD format?
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, there used to be some kickass stuff in MOD format.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't stream that stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: congratulations dot dot dot yeah I got married it was pretty cool um yeah nothing's really different um but uh
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: But it's still 2DX in full arcade mode widescreen on a 50-inch TV.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was hot.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was like hoo-hoo in those red couches.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoy playing 2DX on my 30-inch widescreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: 50-inch was very nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: And, you know, I've played, you know, it's more been a little bit of this and that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've just been really busy between getting married and going to school.
[SPEAKER_09]: Haven't had too much time for much else.
[SPEAKER_09]: And that, and I think I have a sinus infection.
[SPEAKER_04]: What shitty timing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Especially since I'm, you know, busy all the time now.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's going to get worse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because two more classes come up in October.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I'm going to be back to doing homework all the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: At least I can take my puppies to work.
[SPEAKER_09]: I go out on break and feed my puppies during my break at work.
[SPEAKER_09]: Addict.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, so I don't want them to run away.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm saving it for the, trying to get the, what was it, 5 million saved up so I can buy the house, the Japanese style house in my game.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's just 5,000.
5,000?
[SPEAKER_04]: 5 million's a little hard to come by in my game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, well, then I'm halfway there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, not really, well, yeah, there's a, what I'm doing, uh,
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if people were listening.
[SPEAKER_09]: We got a pretty decent tune in for it, but on the first, I did the premiere, not the first, why am I saying the first?
[SPEAKER_09]: A few weeks ago, I did the premiere for the Blood and Synth album on Pump Up the Volume.
[SPEAKER_09]: That had a pretty good reaction.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been trying to do what I can to play some of that on my station, on my show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Helping promote the indie labels.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Doing our part.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because that's also part of what we do.
[SPEAKER_09]: We try to get the new and the neat out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I really haven't had too much free time otherwise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Working on it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well I hope you get some free time pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I've also been working on stuff for a shaft too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, the tournament!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sacramento hosts another fabulous tournament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tentative date around November 17th when the DDR Xbox releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or for some of us on staff, Sacramento hosts another fucking tournament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's that, but we're working on a GameStop sponsorship right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we might have sponsorship from the Big K, too, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So more details coming on that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So DER tournaments not dead yet because we're going to throw a hell of a party.
[SPEAKER_04]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we're the ones planning it here at Orange Lounge Radio with some help from our buddies in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_04]: And bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: and we got up there and did Afranova in costume.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there was... Somebody was Devil Zuken.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had... That was actually one of our... One of the old GameStop... Golfland regulars.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then we had the Twinkie one where we had the Beatmania contest with it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: and this year it's going to be DDR and Bowling very cool you know right now there's a whole lot of In The Groove tournaments going on because they're doing like a national thing for In The Groove
[SPEAKER_04]: and various, I have to be honest, I haven't read up on it because I don't think they're doing one here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think they're going to do one at Miggle for kind of like NorCal.
[SPEAKER_09]: From what I understand, there's actually been, it's officially by, what's the point called now?
[SPEAKER_09]: Paradise Island?
[SPEAKER_04]: Paradise Island.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that they have put a stop on any In The Groove tournaments until...
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what we heard, something about Sacramento locally, and I wish Explicit was here because he'd know more of the details on what's going on because he works there at Paradise Island.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently what went on is that folks are using the old fish and wire trick where they put the fish, not that I'm telling you how to get free credits, don't do this or we'll come find you and beat you up.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: We don't want to know about what you beat off at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: My cabinet, duh.
[SPEAKER_03]: I gotta play Miss World Nude.
[SPEAKER_03]: Gotta, gotta, gotta.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have the luxury of being able to map coin buttons to any of the buttons on the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got our coin thing hooked up on ours, so we just hit the player one button continuously because it's on free play.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, so don't steal credits because then the arcade operators don't make money and then they decide to get rid of their DDR machines and then you wonder why DDR is dying.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I did play something else.
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: Arcade P.O.P.O.
[SPEAKER_09]: on the name.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I did play something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Something fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I think, I can't remember, I think the last time we had a show was before the whole
[SPEAKER_03]: GameCompanies came out to our work and that was fun because I got to meet with everybody and I got to talk to the guy Xeroff at Konami and we found out things and he's hooking me up with stuff supposedly the VRares but he's been busy because he has to travel around and stuff to talk to other distributors and companies about their games and he just didn't get a chance to send it yet but soon he promised me he'll send it so
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to wait for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the Tomo guy, who, um, they're the company that's behind the Agetech products, so, um, he's gonna send me some stuff, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um, we just, you know, EA, Microsoft, Ubisoft, just everybody.
[SPEAKER_03]: We saw all their lineup and everything, it's fucking awesome, and got to find out about the Xbox 360, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: All that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: So anyways, we did that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got lots of free games, which I then sold to GameStop to put towards my 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I now have $250 towards my 360.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then also, what else?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, let's see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yesterday, relatives came up and hung out with them.
[SPEAKER_03]: They barbecued for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: I found an ISO for Burnout Legends, so I've been playing that on my PSP because it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just the kill time until I get Burnout Revenge, which is coming out next Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, I can't wait for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I already have it paid for, it's reserved, I just have to go pick it up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Lots of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Neil, would you care to share with us how your week and your day has been?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, remember we saw the strangest thing at Fry's yesterday?
[SPEAKER_22]: Looking through the DS games?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fry's is carrying import DS games now?
[SPEAKER_22]: Might just be the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, well, I think probably just that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But they're not carrying anything super special.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had an import pool game, like Billiards Pool, and an import Mahjong game.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's all we saw, at least.
[SPEAKER_04]: At least that's all we found.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no import copies of Nintendogs or games have been out here yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because like the Game Boy Advance, there's no region coding on them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which is interesting that a major retailer such as Fry's, which I know is only on the West Coast mostly.
[SPEAKER_22]: They're sneaking out to the East.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they now?
[SPEAKER_22]: They're in Georgia, Illinois, and Indiana now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, Outpost.com too is the national site for Fry's.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they're carrying at least that one store.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some import DS games.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fremont for those in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_22]: What have I been playing?
[SPEAKER_22]: I've been playing, well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_22]: Burnout 3.
[SPEAKER_22]: And yes, I'm also looking forward to Burnout 4.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess I'm going to go put Flat Out, sell back Flat Out and put that down on it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I did not like Flat Out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Compared to Burnout, it sucked.
[SPEAKER_22]: Diablo 2, and I've been playing drinking games.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is Diablo 2 still really popular on the internet?
[SPEAKER_22]: Apparently so.
[SPEAKER_04]: The servers are still pretty damn full.
[SPEAKER_04]: Diablo 2 is like 10 years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came out in 2000.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2005 years old.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's still a long life for a computer game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just put out a patch for it last month.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's up to 1.11.
[SPEAKER_04]: And are people still playing it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I played Diablo 2 for like a month and I just suck at it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just keep making more characters.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm trying to come up with more creative names like Itchy, Scratchy,
[SPEAKER_22]: Bernie, and other nicely descriptive ones, Deadly, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_22]: And as for the drinking game, it's been going around all the breweries and getting a full sampler and seeing which of their beers really suck, and sliding them back and forth until somebody says, oh, fuck it, and just drinks it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Best brewery you've been to?
[SPEAKER_22]: Sudwork, by far.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sudworks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Subwork.
[SPEAKER_22]: No S, just Subwork.
[SPEAKER_04]: Subwork.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, is that just because it's the local one near you?
[SPEAKER_22]: That's because it's the one I can stumble to, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: All I have to do is be able to stumble back across train tracks, and I'm set.
[SPEAKER_22]: All right.
[SPEAKER_22]: But other than that, Gordon Biersch down in the Bay Area, and Pyramid Brewery, which is kind of a national...
[SPEAKER_22]: But this week I went to BJ's, which is kind of a pizza and a brewery place.
[SPEAKER_22]: Isn't that like a chain of restaurants?
[SPEAKER_22]: It's a chain.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's a national chain.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just built one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've built two here in Northern California now, I think.
[SPEAKER_22]: The one in San Jose does not have a brewery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's one in Folsom.
[SPEAKER_22]: Is there now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: They just built one up there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it wasn't on their website.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's one in Roseville.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I went to the one in Roseville.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then I went out to Lincoln to Beerman's and it was all bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: It didn't have enough taste to be real beer.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's pretty bad, I'm turning into a beer connoisseur.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last night was beer night.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh yeah, I did forget to mention that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last night was our friend wedding reception at Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I did actually play more games last night.
[SPEAKER_22]: Where I went through 50 ounces of beer in 10 minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: I went through 50 ounces of beer in several segments.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had Guinness and a Black & Tan.
[SPEAKER_22]: And played Battletech.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what I found?
[SPEAKER_22]: The eight-player, what is that, Daytona USA?
[SPEAKER_22]: They don't have drink holders.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can't drink and drive.
[SPEAKER_22]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_22]: Most of the other driving games do have cup holders so you can put down your giant beer and drive.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what's sad about that Daytona setup, though?
[SPEAKER_09]: I played the first one when it was completely brand new, debuted in Vegas when I was in 11th grade, which was in 90... A while ago.
[SPEAKER_09]: ...two.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you couldn't have been in 11th grade in 92.
[SPEAKER_09]: I graduated in 94.
[SPEAKER_09]: Holy crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're older than us.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I'm 29.
[SPEAKER_04]: I graduated junior high in 92, but I guess that makes sense because I would have started 9th grade in 92.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, amazingly enough, I did too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just for those who don't know, I've known Bugs since like 7th grade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost said 4th grade.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_04]: 7th grade.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I ran into somebody at Dave & Buster's last night that I met in
[SPEAKER_22]: I have a friend of mine who I just talked to last night.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, finish your guys' story, then I'll do my side note.
[SPEAKER_22]: We were looking at your picture and laughing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_22]: We need to scan that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry for interjecting again, but the other game I played was, uh, Midnight, uh, was, uh, Langan Midnight, um, Maximum Tune.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I kicked Dan's ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't he a really big Initial D fan, too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's quite an accomplishment.
[SPEAKER_09]: He picked an Evo 8 with the, with the, uh, the MR, with the 6th speed transmission, and I did the MR in automatic just because I hate having to deal with it, and I still won.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had 6,667 coupons on my card last night at one point.
[SPEAKER_22]: Jeez, I only got 1,900.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've bought very few things from the little Dave & Buster's redemption store.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I still haven't gone through those pixie sticks.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those of you guys who have never been to Dave & Buster's before, it's like Chuck E. Cheese or like an arcade with pizza type thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Chuck E. Cheese, an arcade, pizza, and a bar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but for adults.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they kick kids out at some point, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: Like after 10 o'clock?
[SPEAKER_22]: At any time, they have to be accompanied by an adult.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they usually aren't, which...
[SPEAKER_22]: Although oftentimes they are, that's why you're not tripping over kids all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, which is nice, because you don't have little kids running around screaming so much, and little kids in there thinking they own the place and stuff, because their parents have to be with them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, just think, little kids plus big drunken people don't really mix well, because big drunken people can punt little kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's so nice that you can be there and game with other adults.
[SPEAKER_04]: And although it's kind of cheesy, because half their games are ticket games, just like a normal arcade, but they're so much fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had a pachinko type one, but they got rid of that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they got rid of the other one because it broke to the point they couldn't fix it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the golden temple one.
[SPEAKER_09]: The one where you push all the money off.
[SPEAKER_04]: However... Did they have the flaming finger still?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, flaming finger still.
[SPEAKER_04]: I won flaming finger jackpot, first try.
[SPEAKER_04]: Flaming finger is this game that you control with your finger on like this giant touch board.
[SPEAKER_09]: The countdown speeds up the further you get up there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it does, it does.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have to move your finger through the maze as fast as you can to win the jackpot.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: but they have Exceed 2, Pump It Up Exceed 2 over at Dave Buster's.
[SPEAKER_04]: That doesn't make it any better.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm actually starting to like Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn him for making me like Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: But between the home release, which I'll talk about after the break, the home release and this recent arcade release, as much as I still hate Pump's interface, I'm really starting to like Pump a lot more, which is kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you really Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, I don't know what happened.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's a pod, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob did show me earlier, though, another reason why The Groove sucks, and I thank him for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we were playing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki brought over some games tonight, or should I say he just brought over his PS2 hard drive, which is loaded with games.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm looking at his list of games, and you know how when you load a game onto the HD loader, for those of you guys that have seen it, you can write in whatever the game is called.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, he wrote in, in The Groove, parentheses, this game sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: So we played Torn, and that's the one that goes, you know, I'm cold and I am shamed, lying naked on the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how the lyrics go, but they did...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm cold and I am shamed, lying on the floor.
[SPEAKER_04]: InTheGroove Mormon Edition
[SPEAKER_04]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: That's exactly what they're doing in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're cutting out the salt.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can imagine the Loki would be just the movies.
[SPEAKER_09]: The first time I saw that movie was off of a pirated copy from the Oscars that they gave the Oscars panel to watch.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which is how I had it on VHS about six months early.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first time I saw that movie was on HBO and it was such a bad movie we couldn't get up to turn it off because we had no will to live anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so we decided that we were like,
[SPEAKER_03]: Somebody get up and stop it, please!
[SPEAKER_02]: The end was pretty cool, with the boat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, the only reason I like this movie is because Leonardo DiCaprio died.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he died a horrible death.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what, you can see his thumb break off.
[SPEAKER_09]: When she's letting go, and he's falling into the water, his thumb is still attached to the piece of driftwood.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was really cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I still have, as I said, I haven't seen it, and...
[SPEAKER_22]: I already know how the movie's going to end.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why would I want to see it?
[SPEAKER_22]: The boat fucking sinks!
[SPEAKER_22]: How can you make a three-hour movie about something you already know of?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, then there's like JFK, Nixon.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I know people who worked on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DiCaprio dies, the boat sinks, the old lady had the jewel the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: There, I just saved you three hours of pain.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can thank me via email.
[SPEAKER_03]: The ending of The Passion of the Christ totally came at me as a surprise.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did not expect... You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: I really liked the book a lot better.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wasn't Passion of the Crest where they break out in song and dance at the end?
[SPEAKER_22]: Or am I thinking of a Mel Brooks movie again?
[SPEAKER_22]: I think you are.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, I have a dilemma.
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: Jesus Christ.
[SPEAKER_22]: November.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Depeche Mode concert or Bill Ingvall?
[SPEAKER_04]: Depeche Mode.
[SPEAKER_04]: All the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still debating because I don't like concerts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bill Ingvall's
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that funny to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, he is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then again, where am I from?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alabama, so they actually watch Blue Collar Comedy Tour or whatever down there, I guess, but not in my house.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bill Engvall is funny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Have you listened to any of his stuff all the way through?
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually had to watch one of the episodes of that show once.
[SPEAKER_04]: They all do a little stand-up in it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to bring over my friend Julie's DVD, and you're going to watch it with me.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's even better.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's Stephen Lynch's releasing a new album.
[SPEAKER_04]: or Echo Image.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're coming back.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're under a new label.
[SPEAKER_02]: We're really working on that album that will never ever come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gosh, we've been going off on so many tangents tonight, and I had so many things I wanted to say, but I forgot, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I guess I should talk about my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've actually been on vacation from work all this week, which is so nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't had to do shit at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't done a single goddamn thing, except I got my hair cut one day, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which sucks, because I have to go back to work tomorrow, and I'm not looking forward to having to catch up to a week's worth of email, but, you know, I'll live.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I played a lot of Final Fantasy XI while I was here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki...
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody got their promivians done yesterday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Son of a bitch!
[SPEAKER_04]: The mic's not on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fucking asshole!
[SPEAKER_03]: Son of a bitch!
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why the hell does everybody... Okay, how much do you want of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Does everyone have their AF done?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because they sure as hell won't help me with mine.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only level 53.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have my AF done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fucking AF.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only have, like... I have the boots, which are completely useless for a black mage, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have any of my Permovians done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't even know why I have the chains of Permothia or whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I can't, I don't go to any of those places.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're all experts at those Permovians now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can run you through them like this.
[SPEAKER_03]: I need, I've been trying to get back in and play.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just I have too many things I'm trying to do at the same time.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's for the best, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I probably won't be playing much Final Fantasy XI after this week because I won't have time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I don't have time, but I'm buying World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, at least one of us needs to be reporting on that game, so, fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because World of Warcraft is this really big and popular game, and none of us are playing it, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, at least they actually have some really cool system or game that's within the game, you know, sort of like a capture the flag type thing, but we have Ballista!
[SPEAKER_03]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_03]: Ballista!
[SPEAKER_03]: That was crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beats Blitzball.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will take the Blitzball, or I'll take the Ballista minigame over...
[SPEAKER_04]: That fucking card game in 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, thank God Tetra Master isn't in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Tetra Master was 9.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a different card game in 8.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty much the same thing though, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I never touched the card game, you know?
[SPEAKER_04]: The card game can suck my balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hated the card game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I never played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you feel like you have to or you're going to miss out on items.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't feel like I had to.
[SPEAKER_09]: I didn't care about missing out on items.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just how I play the game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I got halfway through the third disc before I was like, screw it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I watched somebody else beat the game and I never touched it again.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Loki's Birthday Today
[SPEAKER_04]: Happy birthday, Loki!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_04]: So how old are you now?
25.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, a quarter century old.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now how did you celebrate your birthday today?
[SPEAKER_03]: I went to Olive Garden and had lunch.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yummy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, since I was too cheap to get you a present today, I decided to leak Final Fantasy VII Advent Children on the internet for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So enjoy, because I know you really wanted that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, there's been a lot of people doing the same type of thing for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: For example, somebody leaked Burnout Legends on the internet, so I got to play that and Advent Children on the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: And what else was there that they leaked on the internet that I downloaded?
[SPEAKER_03]: Some other stuff, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Burnout Legends was me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um, yeah, there's... I know there was one other thing that they did.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know a DS game that everybody has been just going off about and just loving and adoring?
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to pick this up because everybody is just wanting to make sweet love to this game and they're doing it in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Advance Wars DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard lots of great things about this game, but I need to pick it up at some point.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have a site.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can make paper Advance Wars characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cheesy, but cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a very Nintendo thing to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Nintendo didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Some guy did.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's even worse.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where can they download this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't it on Digg.com?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Digg had a link to it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Digg.com Yeah, it has a link to the... It's like Slashdot, but they pat themselves on the back way too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
And the stuff's relevant.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the stuff is sort of relevant.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they're usually... The dupes get put together
[SPEAKER_22]: you don't have to wait days for them let's all profess our love for Slashdot
[SPEAKER_04]: I like Slashlight, it's a good song Anyway, there's low energy in here tonight, I don't know what it is We need diverse systems, more diverse systems We will do a diverse systems break later, I promise you But I had to do this, this break First I had a request for No Doubt Get Loud because of the new iTunes commercial Somebody said I should play that song But we'll get to that song in this break However, there's a song that's more important that I have to get to in this break And it's for Jamie, of course
[SPEAKER_04]: and we'll be back after this break with more Orange Lounge Radio and your call's coming up pretty soon in the show so go to OrangeLoungeRadio.com and click on Interact With Us and you can give us a call, say hello and Bomani News because we've been talking about all sorts of other video games but I want to talk about Pump It Up and other Bomani, actual Bomani titles so we'll be back after this Jamie, this one's for you
I feel you, I feel you, I feel you every morning I feel you, I feel you, I say to you every morning I feel you, I feel you, I say to you every morning I feel you, I feel you, I say to you every morning
I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll be your every wedding I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll stay to you every night I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll be your every wedding I'll be your, I'll be your, I'll stay to you every night
I see you, I see you, I see you every morning I see you, I see you, I say to you every day I see you, I see you, I see you every morning I see you, I see you
[SPEAKER_14]: I need you, I need you, everybody I need you, I need you, I say to you every night I need you, I need you, I say to you every night I need you, I need you, everybody I need you, I need you, everybody Coming to my neighbors with a loud white speaker Picking up my ass, big mouth in the backyard Oh my god, it's a lot, lot, lot, lot, lot I got a wide lens, a 20 inch, got a supersonic face, volcano
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Listen up, you fool, why not, kickin' up my boo, kickin' up, start to make your fool, now wake it up, lay off my bitch, why not, to suck my dick, comin' to my neighbor, wait to lie, try to speak up, she's pickin' up my ass, beat my finger back, yeah, oh my god, get the lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock
Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
Love, Love, Love
[SPEAKER_15]: Simply be in love, yeah, yeah Simply be in love, yeah, yeah In the end, love, yeah, yeah Simply be in love, yeah Simply be in love It's more than enough Simply be in love
[SPEAKER_15]: It's more than enough, simply enough, it's more than enough, yeah Are you trying to read or anything, to soak your nose or anything?
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to do an extra song this break.
[SPEAKER_04]: This one's a special dedication.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've got to forever The green grass blows and the wind is dancing It would be a much better sight With you, with me If you hadn't met me I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely when you came along
[SPEAKER_15]: So now what should I do?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm strung out, addicted to you My body aches, now that you've gone My supplies fell through And they gave me everything you had
He craved my happiness when you made me feel joy in me Just smile, but now I feel your stress Love was never meant to be such a crazy affair, no And who has time for tears?
Never thought I'd sit around and unravel your love
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi kids, we're back with more Orange Lounge Radio here, episode number 155 in progress.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in and joining us tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I notice we have a lot more listeners than we usually do tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what the heck's going on, if we just are getting more people because of our podcast, or because I actually talked about it in the live journal community, or people are just going through withdrawals because we weren't here for two weeks, or just a combination of all the above, which I'm thinking is partly that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But regardless, thanks for tuning in and wasting your Sunday night with us.
[SPEAKER_04]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're just here talking about what's on our mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pop culture things, DDR, Bomani-related things as they come up, and what have you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to talk about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nintendo pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now don't get me wrong, I'm a total Nintendo fanboy, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Ever since I bought a widescreen TV, I've come to loathe Nintendo for their lack of support for widescreen and HD formats.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know why they're doing that in my opinion, especially as HDTVs become more and more the standard.
[SPEAKER_04]: I realize right now not a lot of people have HDTVs, but if you go shopping for a new TV, they're starting to get priced pretty competitively.
[SPEAKER_04]: The TV I picked up was $600, which granted is quite a bit of money, but not that much more money than what you'd pay for a normal TV of the same size, probably about $200 more.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think as the technology gets older and older and we start getting into Christmas, I think HDTVs are really going to start taking over.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Nintendo has this absolute lack of support for HDTVs and widescreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I kind of realized that as I was trying to find a component cable for my Nintendo GameCube, because as you know, Loki...
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe not that long ago, like a year ago or two years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: They discontinued production of the component cables.
[SPEAKER_04]: And get this, your GameCube has to have a special port on the back that says digital in and out for you to even be able to use this component cable if you could find one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The new GameCubes they made after mid-2004 don't have this.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm glad I have an old one.
[SPEAKER_04]: They took a feature away from the new GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: They took this digital out port away.
[SPEAKER_04]: And their reason why?
[SPEAKER_04]: They said less than 1% of our users were using it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm thinking, well, okay, because the GameCube is kind of the kiddie system, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: The GameCube is the thing that the kid has in their bedroom so that they can play Pokemon or whatever, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: But the GameCube can also function as a pretty decent gaming system for the rest of us hardcore gamers, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, for instance, Resident Evil 4.
[SPEAKER_04]: F-Zero, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_04]: Melee, although it's kind of kiddy-like in its artwork, it's a great freaking game.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's one of my favorite games they put out on GameCube.
[SPEAKER_04]: No support for HD because they say less than 1% are using the HD feature as it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_04]: How much was it just to put that little extra port on the back?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess maybe this was one of the costs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe this was a way that they made the GameCube cost only $80 was by taking this feature out, but...
[SPEAKER_04]: Did the Famicom have it too?
[SPEAKER_04]: The regular...
[SPEAKER_04]: Bugs trying to say something about the Famicom had it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the Japanese Famicom has it too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't realize that.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, now the Nintendo America just had red and yellow wires.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, because that's all we had at the time.
[SPEAKER_22]: We didn't have any sort of connectors to really do it with.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that cable, while I guess that's kind of nice that you can take your Super Nintendo cable and use it on your Nintendo 64 and your GameCube, it hasn't changed in the last 15 years.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm a little disappointed in Nintendo's lack of support.
[SPEAKER_04]: And some of the games on GameCube actually support widescreen TVs.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played F-Zero on widescreen.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was sexy as hell, but blurry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blurry because S-Video is as high as it goes.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, it sucks, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's really limiting themselves because they were only, you know, wanting to put out, you know, family games because this whole, you know, they didn't really want to touch on the whole, you know, mature-rated games and stuff back when Mortal Kombat was out there.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like, oh, we're just going to put out normal games, you know, and make this more kid-friendly system because that's what people were looking for.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now they've kind of missed the bus.
[SPEAKER_03]: And now, you know, this whole, well, there's not going to be, you know, that many...
[SPEAKER_03]: Broadband TVs and stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: No one owns them right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, but people are going to be buying them in the future.
[SPEAKER_03]: So what are you going to do with your game system then?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm having a hard time believing that they're... It seems like they're trying to put out a system that will support what the market wants right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But no system ever really takes off at launch, except for maybe, I don't know, Super Nintendo maybe did.
[SPEAKER_04]: But PlayStation even took a while to get big.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy 7, I'm going to just say this, it might piss some people off.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Final Fantasy 7 is when the PlayStation really started picking up.
[SPEAKER_04]: When Square announced that they were going to jump ship and go over and start making games for PlayStation, that's when the PlayStation really started selling and you saw a lot more games for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That in addition to things like Spyro, Crash Bandicoot.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that was really the turning point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even PlayStation 2, their launch titles weren't humongous.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fantavision...
[SPEAKER_04]: So no system ever really takes off.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Xbox launch?
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't make me laugh.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think one of the only reasons PlayStation 2 had such a huge launch, which was probably one of the bigger ones in recent memory, which still wasn't, it's not like they were... I think it was riding on the success of the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that, the fact that it would play the old PlayStation games, and that it was a DVD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: People were buying PlayStation 2s as DVD players.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was actually really true in Japan.
[SPEAKER_09]: But one thing about the DVD player on the PS2 is that it's a piece of crap, and using it as your primary DVD player will shorten the life of the system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't believe that one bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used mine as my primary DVD player, never had a problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: You are in the minority then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard of the problems, but I've yet to see it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan has told me that just about every return within the first few years of the PS2's release were, basically, they were sliding off the track.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was everything related.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyone who brought theirs back was because they were using it as a primary DVD player.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've used both my PlayStation 2 and my Xbox as DVD players.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll tell you right now, the Xbox is a better DVD player, hands down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, yeah, because it's a more intelligently built system.
[SPEAKER_04]: It better be if you've got to pay $20 extra to use it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: The fact, oh, that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Microsoft can blow me for that.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Xbox itself, though, is a more intelligently constructed piece of equipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: In a way, in a way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's made of better parts.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a more stable system.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet if you drop a PS2 and an Xbox, less of the Xbox will break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love... Because it's so damn heavy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Microsoft is awesome because they...
[SPEAKER_03]: They're like, oh yeah, well this time around, you know, you don't have to pay extra to get your wonderful DVD remote.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can watch DVDs right out of the box.
[SPEAKER_03]: And everyone's like, oh yeah, but you gotta buy your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, so yeah, they're sticking it to you in another way now.
[SPEAKER_09]: No route to host.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was I going to talk about here?
[SPEAKER_04]: A little follow-up to something we were talking about earlier in the program.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talking about those in-the-groove tournaments that are going on around the nation.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said that Milpitas is going to be having one, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, go figure.
[SPEAKER_04]: The person who's actually helping to put on this tournament is actually listening tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: and gave me a link to more information on the In The Groove tournament that's going to go on at Milpitas Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: So for those of you guys that happen to be in Northern California, September 24th, 2005 is the date of the tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: 11 a.m.
[SPEAKER_04]: for registration.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ten bucks will get you in the tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ten dollars flat.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's no pre-reg fees, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a straight-up perfect attack, expert only.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can find more complete rules over on DDR Freak and their tournament forums.
[SPEAKER_04]: But since it's in the Groove Expert Tournament and I'm too old and too fat, yeah, I will not be entering this tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I might go just to have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just to see people, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: So check that out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki, I will not be attending this tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: You wouldn't go just to socialize with people?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just curious.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing I would want a boxer for in the first place
[SPEAKER_03]: is to have a good system to run Step Mania on.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really all I wanted for Food Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Food Mix, the arcade game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Much better use of the boxer than In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, you can find more information on an In The Groove tournament happening near you on InTheGroove.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're doing this big national thingy.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell them, Red Octane, or not even Red Octane, Rockstar, get a hold of those guys in Japan.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're making good music.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm telling you, you could...
[SPEAKER_03]: MC Groove's Dance Craze
[SPEAKER_04]: I know, it's horrible.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what Mad Catz helped put out recently, though, that's actually pretty damn good?
[SPEAKER_04]: Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pump It Up Exceed, home version, kicks ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was very surprised, but it kicks a lot of ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Despite the fact that I still hate the interface, I can't stand the way you go around and you pick your songs, it's better than it used to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about as good as that Pump It Up system's gonna get, the home version.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there's a whole assload of songs in this game.
[SPEAKER_04]: They kind of split up the songs into three channels.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have your Banya channel, and Banya's kind of like the Naoki of Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, it does a lot of these, just a variety of different types of songs.
[SPEAKER_03]: So there's like 97 songs in the Banya channel, and...
[SPEAKER_03]: 4 and the other one?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's actually pretty evenly spaced out.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it to him for that.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's about 30 songs apiece.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got the K-pop station, which is pretty rad.
[SPEAKER_04]: They've got a lot of songs under K-pop, including some songs you might recognize from DDR, such as Starion.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's the other one?
[SPEAKER_04]: Caution?
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Booby Law, I can't remember the name of the song, I just know it's the booby song because it's the video that has just the chick with the boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Soka Meki Ranran, that one, and Kiss Me is in Exceed 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: So there's a couple songs in the arcade, and then some interesting American exclusives.
[SPEAKER_04]: Crystal Method is in there, and Elvis has a song in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That one Australian band with the crazy video, I can't remember the name of the song.
[SPEAKER_04]: The song's like, forget it, forget it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but you have to read the arrows a whole different way.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just a different way of reading them with the colors and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a little bit of a challenge at first.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there are some crazy-ass step patterns that shame in the grooves, step patterns even, in regions of difficulty, if that's what you're into.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I think that kind of stuff is retarded, so I don't play that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I didn't really, just, you know, my friend made me look at a few of the really, really tough step charts, and I just kind of went, stupid, and went back to playing the more fun steps.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I actually really enjoy Pump It Up Exceed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I recommend it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you guys are into the dance games, pick this up.
[SPEAKER_04]: This will hold you over until the DDR releases.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now granted, the downside is that you have to get a whole new pad with this, so the bundle's going to cost you about $60, but the soft pad that comes with it is actually pretty darn nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a better quality than those Konami soft pads they put out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Dance Revolution Strike Dance Dance Revolution Strike Dance Dance Revolution Strike
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a very strange name, isn't it, for the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: But whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Festival Revolution Strike, the I being an exclamation point, will be shown at the Tokyo Game Show 2005, so they say.
[SPEAKER_04]: A couple days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, a couple days away.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's supposed to have that same interface as Extreme 2 and Dancing Stage Max, of course, overseas in Europe.
[SPEAKER_04]: The website for the game also had a special little page set up talking about the new Naoki song called Passion...
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost thought it was Passion in Love.
[SPEAKER_04]: Passion of Love, Naoki featuring Paula Terry.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you might remember the rumors a while back that Paula Terry was in studio recording something for Naoki.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is what it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's going to be featured in Dance Dance Revolution Strike.
[SPEAKER_04]: No word yet as to whether it's going to be inside EX2 or the European version of Dancing Stage Max as of yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure it will be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, I'm pretty sure it will be, too, but nothing's said one way or the other yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know when this game will actually be coming out, but end of year, early next?
2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: 2006?
[SPEAKER_03]: Spring.
[SPEAKER_04]: 2006 it is, then.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back from this break, did your download finish?
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost?
[SPEAKER_04]: Almost.
[SPEAKER_03]: Try me back at about 8.30.
[SPEAKER_03]: Trying a little while?
8.30.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ish.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stupid slow FTP.
[SPEAKER_04]: In this break, Loki wanted me to play something from the disc he brought last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: Finally!
[SPEAKER_03]: We picked up the new Diverse System albums.
[SPEAKER_03]: D7, all three CDs of that, D8, and also Dear Mr. Taka, plus some other special stuff like the Chorus K album and the Good Cool Ultra Expander CD, which has the most kickass remix to Absolute, which you might have heard if you downloaded our non-show last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: and lots of good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: My personal favorite for D7, and I was waiting ever since I heard the little teaser for it, was the Trip Machine Dark Core mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a remix of Ecstasy on there, which is really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And a few other things.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a remix of Love Love Shine, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so what am I going to play here?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I think we should play the Trip Machine Dark Core Mix.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's a D7.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, you have the wrong CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the one, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_04]: The Dear Mr. Talk and all that stuff?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but this is my other one.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a second CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: Put that on your thing over there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is this it?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's blank.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, crap.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have it around somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll keep looking for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there something on that CD?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we'll find them.
[SPEAKER_03]: See what's on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it might have been in a case for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I put it in a case.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that's not it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... So anyways, we've got some stuff on here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um... The diverse system stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Dear Mr. Taka, which is cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, let's play something from Good Cool Ultra Expander.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's play the Absolute Ultimate Remix again, because that's good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to play the Absolute Ultimate Remix.
[SPEAKER_03]: It definitely lives up to its name.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We heard a little bit of this last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll try to find the other CD in the meantime.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we will.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio and your phone calls.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lost sound there for a minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will get to your phone calls this next break, we promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com, click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here it is, Good Cool with DJ Taka, Absolute, the ultimate mix.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we found the other CDs.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to actually play one of the songs from Diverse 7 for you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And this is the one that Loki was hyping up here.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the Trip Machine Dark Core Mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we're going to play that, and then we're going to come back with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy this one, you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's the artist on this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just Diverse System.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
Thanks for watching!
DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_04]: Trip Machine, the Dark Core mix here on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that was some music from the new Diverse Systems 7 album.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not as new as Diverse Systems 8, though, which is also out.
[SPEAKER_04]: So look for those.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Diverse 9, which is coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Coming very soon.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alrighty, very cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And some people said they couldn't hear the Trip Machine in that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Our chat room was kind of going, that's Trip Machine?
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard Trip Machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see how you couldn't have heard it.
[SPEAKER_04]: The synth lines are the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: The synth lines are the same, but...
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's my... Mommy, can you sing Trip Machine?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where was that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Where was that?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was on the Trip Machines, like, drum and bass, and this is, like, Dark Horse, so it's a little different.
[SPEAKER_03]: I liked it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thought it was cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: But... It was okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think this is the only way to possibly like Trip Machine.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is an interesting... The normal versions are horrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a blues version of, um... Or, like, kind of like a jazzy blues type version of, um... I want to say, um... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: Not Make Your Move, but one of the older ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not Put Your Faith In Me, Keep On Movin'.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's on one of them, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll have to play that later.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Does it actually sound like Keep On Movin'?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And they also have the long version of Made In Innocent, which was in Food Mix 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or Food Mix Plus, I want to say.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm getting confused here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, Food Mix Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: While we sit there and wait for somebody to call us, because there's not a whole lot of people logged into Skype, so I don't know if we'll even get anything here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do want to make sure this gets a mention here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This was something that happened while we were gone.
[SPEAKER_04]: GuitarFreaks and DrumManiaV2 on their way out.
[SPEAKER_04]: They do have a website opened up.
[SPEAKER_04]: We link to it from our website over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com, but it's konami.jp.am.locationtest, because this is something that's currently location testing, Guitar Freaks, Drum Mania, V2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, the reason why Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania is now V is because they did a little bit of a hardware upgrade on the stuff there when they put out V. They did a little bit of a hardware upgrade, so now they have the full videos and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: The game's just a little bit prettier.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's something to be looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's take a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey Sky, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello Siggy, how are you?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm just doing fine after three weeks of being in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: What a... It's been a long while.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were practically next door.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was going on in San Francisco?
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I just made, you know, my final visit to the city because my father just moved back here in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so you had family living in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gotcha, we should have said something, we could have all met up and played some 2DX, you could have whooped my ass or something, I don't know Well, I just got some Guitadora news for ya Okay, what's going on there, we just talked about Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania V2 a little bit
[SPEAKER_21]: I got some song lists here that are official.
[SPEAKER_21]: Most songs are in kanji, so I'll say it on the air.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll just show the links on the chatroom, and then I'll mention the songs that are in kanji characters.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_21]: The artist is Terra, and the song title is Glide.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then there's a self-titled artist called JJ Road.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then there's Sing A Well by Highway61.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tomorrow by The Local Art Aino Tameni by Ueto Aya Shanghai Honey by Orange Range Tsubasa by Undergraph Natsu no Tobira by Matsuda Seiko
[SPEAKER_21]: And then there's Minamikaze or Nanbu by Romeo Roman.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've never heard of any of these people before besides Terra.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are these all new artists?
[SPEAKER_21]: The one that they have right now, it's just covers.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's like cover Japanese pop songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is just cover songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then this one's an original called Mirai no Chizu, which means Map of the Future by Mi.
[SPEAKER_21]: MI, of course.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then the original Rakuen no Tenchi, which means Paradise Angels, by Koezuka Yoshihiko.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then there's a rewrite, which is a cover by Asian Kung Fu Generation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I think they've been in a previous incarnation of some Bomani game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds familiar to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then for the long versions.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, long versions.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hoshino Kakeru, which means Star Fragments, by Yum Yum Orange.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello You by Furukawa Motoaki
[SPEAKER_21]: And then the other song is Take My Hand by Maria Eva with Dreams Wing Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember back when I first started playing Guitar Freaks, you only got one song to pick from from Extra Stage, and you liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then the comeback song is Kachaka by Maki de Yayas.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yay, Kachaka, I like that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now for the other news.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to play Kachaka later in the show in celebration.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then this was like back ago when Asaki's album was released.
[SPEAKER_21]: I will mention to you the songs for his first album called Shinkyoku, which means The Divine Comedy, which is a poem by Dante.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah, I know that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So like they turned it into a song?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: The first one is Sanagi, which means chrysalis.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then the second song is a new song called Hotaru, which means a firefly.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then the third song is from Poppin' Music 10, which is Shiawase Uta Uta, which means happiness expressed in poetry.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then song number 4 is Konoko no Nanatsu no Oiwai ni, which means 7 congratulations from Guitar Fix Drum Mania And then a new song called Yogo no Oto, which means sound of convalescence And then there's Gekkoucho, which means moonlight butterfly from Guitar Fix Drum Mania And then there's Akaisuzu, which means red bells, also from Guitar Fix Drum Mania And then song number 8 is Shizuku, which means a drop of water from Poppin' Music 12 Iroha
[SPEAKER_21]: and then the self-titled single, Shinkyoku, which means The Divine Comedy.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then the final song is Azumi no Hiyodorito, which means Azumi and Her Bulbul, which is a new song.
[SPEAKER_21]: For those of you who don't know what a bulbul is, a bulbul is a Persian songbird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_04]: First I thought you said her Volvo, and I'm like, oh, she's driving along in her Volvo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's kind of weird that she's driving a Swedish car.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called a B-U-L-B-U-L.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, got it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that is very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, some stuff to look forward to there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any idea when this is going to be official, out of the location test?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, the location test for Guitar Freaks Romania V2, I'm not certain.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're already doing the location test right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: As of now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, usually what?
[SPEAKER_04]: The location test goes on for about a month, and then they go back for a month or two, and then the game comes out, usually, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so...
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I forgot to mention, about Tokyo Game Show, I checked on their website, and they just recently announced Poppin' Music 12 Iroha for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Big surprise, not.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, honestly, Poppin' Music's been constantly coming out for the PlayStation 2, so that's no surprise at all, but that's good for the Poppin' Music fans, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good news.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now, Tokyo Game Show is happening this week, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, like this Thursday.
[SPEAKER_04]: This week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you've got to go, since I can't read the Japanese, you've got to go on some of those sites and look at the news and come back and let us know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what else is good?
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: Revolution news.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're going to show the controller and everything in Mario 128.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to get a lot of news this week from Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and one more thing.
[SPEAKER_16]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not Kekak, it's Kekak.
[SPEAKER_21]: Kekak.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like Kekak.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, you have to go to Indonesia, believe me, it's Kekak.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't doubt that the pronunciation I'm doing is horribly wrong, but, you know, I like Kekak.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Kekak.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said it once correctly just for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, and, you know, just after I go off, just announce to them about the 10th style CS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I already, you know, I already pre-ordered mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: When's the street date for that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Isn't that October?
[SPEAKER_21]: November 17th.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, don't you remember last year, November was, like, a huge month for Bomani?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because we got, like, Ultramix 2, 8-Style, and Poppin' Music, like, 10, I think it was?
[SPEAKER_03]: All in, like, the same day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember, as I mentioned on the non-show, that the new DDRs and the new...
[SPEAKER_03]: Carriker Revolutions are going to have demos for each different version.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's out there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the news sites published that in their review.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's out there now where everybody knows that you can play demos in one and the other.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I still envy those people at Rhode Island right now because they have Happy Sky.
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I was talking to Miklatov over the weekend and he said that he damn near got on a plane to go out there to play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was like, you're crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, if you got your simulators out there, I have all the key sound to BMS files.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy Sky Lobster
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, anything else you wanted to share with us tonight, Siggy?
[SPEAKER_21]: Nothing much else.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll just let you know what news are going to come out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right, nothing much else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess that's it then.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go to some new calls, alrighty?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_16]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes, I'm right here.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is one and only Ron John.
[SPEAKER_24]: What's up, fellas?
[SPEAKER_04]: My timer didn't show up there for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura is not a fella.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hi, Ron John.
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, honey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_24]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_24]: I got some information here.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know if you guys know this, but it seems that Katamari Damacy 2 or We Love Katamari came out early.
[SPEAKER_04]: It came out early?
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: The guy who works for the game distributor says no.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, I have a link here to somebody who went to Target and bought it today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_03]: Target broke street.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, they just...
[SPEAKER_24]: That's exactly what I said when I found it earlier.
[SPEAKER_03]: It doesn't come out until the 21st.
[SPEAKER_03]: It got pushed back because they weren't done with it yet.
[SPEAKER_03]: It hasn't even been pressed yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, but how do they go to Target and get a copy then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck if I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I know is they really did a really shitty job of making new box art for it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the cover art's shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: So okay, give me this link.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, let's see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what this is all about right here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, so this link got posted in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: www.orangeloungeradio.com Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orangeloungeradio.com slash chat, or I'm sorry, click on the link that says chat.
[SPEAKER_04]: And here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somebody posted, go to Target now, and they've got their little Target bag with the receipt and the little game, We Heart Katamari, Sony Software, $29.99.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm hitting up Target.com to see if it was just that store Where's that dude live?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we know?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just found a link early today when I was at my friend's dorm.
[SPEAKER_24]: We were playing video games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's find out which Target that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just to say something about on the Target website, it says this item will be released on September 22nd and you can pre-order it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's just this one story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Indianapolis, Indiana it looks like is where this person says they live.
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you are living in the Indianapolis area,
[SPEAKER_04]: Start calling those targets and see if you can't get your cams on the game because somehow they got a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or it's a really cleverly done Photoshop, but I don't know why this guy would Photoshop it.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, it could also be like for some whatever reason they got a promo copy and the dumbasses put it out to sell.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that was like the only copy that they had.
[SPEAKER_03]: But you never know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, stupid things like that happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I noticed that on the receipt here it says the Sony Software...
[SPEAKER_04]: The actual name of the game is in there, like it's a generic code in there or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: But does it have what the disk number is?
[SPEAKER_03]: You know how each disk has an ID number on it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, it had a little number on it, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the number then?
[SPEAKER_24]: Hey, there's a number there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hold on, hold on, let me check.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah, what a time for my mouse to be dying.
[SPEAKER_24]: If I can understand, somebody in California bought it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Doesn't matter anyways, I have the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, what do I care?
[SPEAKER_03]: I was just going to say, I was going to look up here, see if it matches.
[SPEAKER_03]: We live Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, that's very interesting if it did come out a little early.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some folks should just consider themselves lucky and maybe the game will be making its way.
[SPEAKER_04]: But as far as we know, no official word from Namco or any gaming site for that matter that the game has come out early.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I would think if the game shipped early, Namco would be shouting it from the mountaintops and all the gaming sites would pick that up because everybody has a boner for Katamari Damashii.
[SPEAKER_03]: Perfect example, look at... Was it Shane?
[SPEAKER_03]: He got...
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone returned Pump It Up to one of the stores and he bought it used.
[SPEAKER_03]: And this was before the game even came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, so stuff like this happens.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, people buy something or get something for free from their distributor or vendor or whatever and they'll return it back to a store and then sell it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or in this case, they might get a promo copy early because I've had a few copies of stuff early before it's treated and someone goes and sells it or mistakenly puts it out on the shelf
[SPEAKER_03]: Never know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or whatever the company is, if they're shipping it in one day.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because I remember the same thing happened last year with the PS2 minis.
[SPEAKER_24]: I mean, I found out that Target put it out three weeks early, and then a week later, Best Buy, we put it out the following week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, chat room's bringing up an interesting point.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you say your friend got this in California?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mission Viejo San Diego
[SPEAKER_04]: So if you're in the San Diego area, it's Mission Viejo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look, you can even call the Target.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should we call the Target and ask if it's in stock?
[SPEAKER_04]: I should do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone should link that to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could call them right here on Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to call them right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they open?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_24]: Targets don't close until 8 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to try calling them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, we're going to call this target and see if they have Weehawk Heart Katamari in stock, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: So we've got to let you go in order to do this, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, I'm going to call you back later with some other stuff, so later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, later, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're crazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, you guys don't talk, just let me do the talking.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, switching off the microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope to God this is the right number and I don't get some freaking... I don't know, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Either way, my caller ID's blocked, so that's what's important, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're now calling a Target store, printed on the receipt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mission Viejo, California, see if they have We Heart Katamari and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it, I just picked up another call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zach, you gotta call us back in a little bit, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still new to Skype.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Calling, calling, calling.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, here we go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Three Ringy Dingys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Four Ringy Dingys.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody's home at Target.
[SPEAKER_04]: Apparently the other two busy selling advance copies of We Heart Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live radio, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Someone let Target know their phone's off the hook.
[SPEAKER_04]: One more ring and then we're hanging up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not only that, but bad customer service.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe they're closed.
[SPEAKER_04]: They could close at 8 on Sunday, I guess.
[SPEAKER_25]: No.
[SPEAKER_25]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, fuck, they're on to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We called.
[SPEAKER_04]: No answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: What can we do?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sigh.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm looking through this one thread that was linked in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are they saying the same thing?
[SPEAKER_09]: Someone actually had a very good challenge where the guy said post a copy of the... Well, he put up a picture of the disc in the manual.
[SPEAKER_09]: One second.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to go to another call real quick here since our brilliant live radio experiment didn't work out very well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, because really you could... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you already know who this is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, Saku.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, Target's closed, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to share with you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Target's closed.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you're about almost 20 minutes late right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well... Had you known this, like, maybe, you know, 20 minutes earlier or probably 30 minutes earlier, you probably would have got through.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ron Chan, freaking earlier next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Beyond time next time.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, Saku?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just calling back.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm in school right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moved back on campus a couple of weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and I still miss playing in the groove in the city.
[SPEAKER_07]: I miss that because I'm like 30 miles of stay from the city, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just lazy.
[SPEAKER_22]: What city is this so we can completely avoid it?
[SPEAKER_04]: New York.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: New York?
[SPEAKER_04]: City of New York.
[SPEAKER_04]: City, city, New York?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the city of New York.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought they had it in the groove at Chinatown.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, not only that, but in Coney Island, Queens, Staten Island.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's starting to spread like cancer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting analogy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lovely thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and just missing playing 2DX11 Red.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just need that fixed.
[SPEAKER_22]: So it's kind of spreading like New Jersey?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, it's just... It's reddening like your mama's legs!
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, burn!
[SPEAKER_22]: Nah, New Jersey's just the smell.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was in Philly.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, what else is on your mind besides lack of Bomani?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just, you know, all that new shit that just came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the new info and whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I'm not going to be able to make it to Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted to come.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried to schedule my boss, but she had scheduled me for a full week class right there, so I'm not going to be able to do it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I hope you guys have fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will definitely come next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I just hope it still happens next year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope so too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we need somebody on the inside taking some pictures and sending them to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, take some pictures over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish I had a digital camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you practicing for your freestyle?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, I don't know about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need a job first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm still unemployed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Get your resume on Monster.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nine months now.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Craigslist.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, I've tried that already.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude!
[SPEAKER_07]: When you've been trying to find work for the past nine months, you kind of realize that it's...
[SPEAKER_07]: There's probably no light at the end of the tunnel.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to make it worse, I don't even get work study this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Apply at Target because you'll never have to work past 8 on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you'll always be home in time for Orange Line.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just hope so.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope they don't make me work on... I don't know about making me work on weekends.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope I can find a job that revolves around my schedule.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there are some employers out there that will work with you if you're in school.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's possible to find, but you are going to have to kind of look at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_22]: And a lot of schools also have temporary services where you can actually work on campus.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've already exhausted those means of working on campus.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the jobs are already filled up.
[SPEAKER_07]: And people want work-study.
[SPEAKER_07]: Find a nice clock tower.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's really bad for me because I probably waited almost a week to even find out that I didn't have work-study.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: As I said, I'm up at Schitt's Creek right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just hoping I get some jobs that I applied to.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we'll see what happens from there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope that you find something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just check with the big, big companies like the Targets, the Walmarts, the Toys R Uses and whatever.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, man.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, well, have a good one, Zaku, and good luck on the job hunt, and hope you find those Bomani games, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now, on the chat room, it sounds like that they actually looked up this target, and the damn store is open.
[SPEAKER_04]: So is there only one target in Mission Viejo, or is there more than one target?
[SPEAKER_04]: See, maybe there's more than one Target in the town, so the one you guys are looking up might not be the right one.
[SPEAKER_04]: But Mission Viejo's not that big, is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't think it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: On that one thread, by the way, someone said they worked at Target and got a shipment of it in, so they went ahead and bought us a game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: They said they got very few copies in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, here's the correct number.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did we miss-dial their number?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me look at what we dialed last time.
[SPEAKER_04]: 949... Oh, we totally dialed the wrong number last time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, let's try it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, now we've got the right target number.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, chat room.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you for calling the Mission Viejo Target Store.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_00]: Our normal store business hours are Monday through Saturday, 8 a.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: to 10 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: and Sunday, 8 a.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: to 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_00]: PM, we are located on Alicia Parkway off the 5 Freeway between Charlinda and the 5 Freeway.
[SPEAKER_00]: If you are calling the Target Pharmacy, please press 1.
[SPEAKER_00]: To speak to the store operator, please wait or press 0.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we get the operator.
[SPEAKER_00]: Please stay on the line while your call is transferred to the operator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good evening, Target.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ms.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mayhill, this is Sue.
[SPEAKER_03]: How can I direct your call?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yes, can I speak to somebody in electronics, please?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_17]: Electronics?
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, yeah, I was looking to see if you had a PlayStation 2 game in stock.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me check.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hang on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, SD?
[SPEAKER_17]: Those are on the next pile.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Appreciate it, man.
Thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, what was the game again?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, we have one left.
[SPEAKER_04]: You do have one left in stock.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, great, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: One left, kids!
[SPEAKER_04]: Holy crap!
[SPEAKER_04]: Get down there and pick that shit up.
[SPEAKER_04]: One left in stock.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll have to talk to my folks at Namco and see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go figure, you heard it here first, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: We gonna rat them out, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: We freaking called them, and they have one copy left in stock.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go post that on GameTax right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I'm gonna make a stop by Target tomorrow after I get out from the chiropractor.
[SPEAKER_04]: You wanna call the one down up the street here?
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, if they have it, I'm gonna give Neil money to get mine now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What, are we gonna...
[SPEAKER_09]: except that I have my non-reserve at GameStop and I can get it for 30% off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are we going to call them right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's 30% off later or full price now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe we're doing this live on air.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think we'd have better things to talk about.
[SPEAKER_04]: But damn it, we might get our Katamari fix tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, here's the number.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who has Katamari already?
[SPEAKER_04]: 638-4971.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bug's going to call him and in the meantime we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we come back from the break we'll let you know what happened and we'll get into the Orange Lounge Radio cage match and we've got a couple other Bomani stories for you guys tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we will be back after this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Started off with a little bit of the captain, the good captain here.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Dreamer Dreamer Take me in your dream Take me anywhere you please Boy, you're making me scream Dreamer Dreamer Life is just a dream If you wanna set me free Boy, you're making me scream Ooh, la, la, la
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: You've got a dream of your dream
Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_15]: From Step Squad to Orange Lounge, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_15]: Holla!
[SPEAKER_15]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: and the hunt is on.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you're lucky enough to be in the San Diego, Mission Viejo area, get your ass to Target before 9 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you can thank us later.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's sad?
[SPEAKER_04]: After we cover that on our podcast tonight, that poor store is going to get a shitload of inquiries about the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Power of the internet.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what's sad also?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to rat them out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't rat him out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, I'm ratting him out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Don't rat him out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm ratting him out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait until somebody picks up that game, because maybe it'll be good enough to give us an ISO.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, then they better hurry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to rat him out.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, Namco's going to call tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, what's interesting is that... The only reason I'd be pissed off is because we didn't get ours on time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because, you know, it was supposed to come out, you know, I think last week.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they pushed it back.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: That's my bitterness.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: The chat room's yelling at us here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if somebody lives in that area or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where was I?
[SPEAKER_04]: I lost track now because of all this We Heart Katamari madness here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me post that link one more time for you guys looking for that Mission Viejo target.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a slight update.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's one in the area.
[SPEAKER_22]: They have them, but they aren't putting them out on the shelf until Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Until Tuesday?
[SPEAKER_04]: Until this Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, who's doing it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Roseville, the old one.
[SPEAKER_04]: The old Roseville one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because there's like two or three in Roseville now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's the one on Douglas Boulevard.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm calling the...
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's somehow getting out early to targets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just call the one by my house and they don't... Interesting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just give me some calls made in the morning, let me put it that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, the other thought is, is that what if Namco is purposefully leaking this out to produce excitement over the game's release?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're not that smart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I worked for Namco and yes, they've done stuff like this in the past.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_03]: I doubt it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think this is just more of an error in someone's shipping department.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the chat room's going, call my target, call my target.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, call your own target, seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: The hell, we're not calling all your damn targets.
[SPEAKER_09]: We are not the goddamn operator.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call your own fucking target.
[SPEAKER_09]: Pick up your phone, dial the little numbers, and ask them yourself, just like we did with six different stores.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You see how easy it is?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did it.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: The phone is easy to use.
[SPEAKER_09]: You learn how to do this when you're three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hit the button.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have that much trouble, get your mommy to call.
[SPEAKER_03]: You shouldn't be getting this game anyways if you have that much trouble dialing a phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: You obviously don't have the hand-eye coordination enough to use the controller to play the game.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you're having trouble using the phone, you've got a serious problem and you probably need help going pee too.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you need someone to help you do the wipe?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or how about the flush?
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're getting like a million requests for the clip of the phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll, I don't know, put it in the live journal community.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Post it to our forums, please, because my work firewalled live journals, so I can't do that no more.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shame on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll see what we can do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I have a certain person I would like to send that to that is certain on certain street dates, and I would like to forward that to them, and that would be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to get into the cage match, but we can't figure out where Loki's song went.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have a new song for us?
[SPEAKER_04]: For my cage match?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I have a new one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't even realize it won last time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Technically, your song, whatever it was, should have been retired.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I have a new song that I'm picking.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's on one of those CDs, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which one?
[SPEAKER_04]: The one with the good, cool one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the one that should be already in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually on both of them, so it doesn't really matter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to get into tonight's cage match, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're starting fresh this week because we did go two weeks without a show.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're just going to go ahead and kind of restart tonight with the cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it goes a little something like this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the deal.
[SPEAKER_04]: Join our chatroom, www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to play three songs for you guys, and you guys get to pick your favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio's Bobani and Video Game Music Show, which plays 24 hours a day, seven days a week on this station when we are not live.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to start off with three brand new songs tonight for you to pick from.
[SPEAKER_04]: There is no reigning champion.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll start off tonight with DarkSakura's pick, since she's the only one that has her pick up and ready to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going to start off with her.
[SPEAKER_09]: I had it ready last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, we won't talk about last week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what did you pick for us, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's by a Czech group called Accent.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is a really weird video with a lookalike like Kylie Minogue in it, and these guys kept making out with her.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's called Kylie.
[SPEAKER_04]: AXS with Kylie
We can get into the groove, I can watch you move Later you can sing to me like a shining star But I'd rather know you on the backseat of my car Heidi, give me just a chance, let's go out and dance We can get into the groove, I can watch you move Later you can sing to me like a shining star But I'd rather know you on the backseat of my car
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure you have seen me, I'm dreaming about you every night, every night Kylie give me just a chance, let's go out and dance, we can get into the groove, I can watch you
[SPEAKER_13]: We can get into the groove, I can watch you move Later you can sing to me, like a shining star But I rather, know you on the backseat of my car You drive me crazy, you slowly drive me crazy That bloody baby, can't get you off my mind I should be lucky, I should be so lucky I should be lucky, to see you
[SPEAKER_15]: We can get into the groove, I can watch you move Later you can sing to me like a shining star But I'd rather know you on the backseat of my car Kylie give me just a chance, let's go out and dance We can get into the groove, I can watch you move Later you can sing to me like a shining star But I'd rather know you on the backseat of my car
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, though, song number one in tonight's cage match, Accent with Kylie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go around and see what everybody thought of that one, starting off with DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: That song is great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, the style's kind of, you know, an older style, but the song's relatively new.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the video's freaking hilarious, so it gets a 9.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Kind of reminds me of Eiffel 65 a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bugs.
[SPEAKER_22]: Actually, it sounds a lot like the Numa Numa song.
[SPEAKER_04]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_04]: 8 and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to agree with Arcadian42 in our chatroom, who said this song is fruity.
[SPEAKER_04]: However, for that reason, I loved it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a great cage match song, honestly.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was funny and it was dancey.
[SPEAKER_04]: 9 and a half.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm putting the video in the chatroom, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there are still two more songs to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_04]: We may have something a little better.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will find out.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's your call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number two is Loki's pick.
[SPEAKER_04]: What did you pick for us, Loki?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm off the Good Cool Expander CD.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't really like Eurobeat, and this is a trance remix of Blame by Good Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here it is, Blame, the trance mix by Good Cool.
No more your memory will last Deep within my mind I will always find you
[SPEAKER_15]: Deep within my mind I would always find emotions still alive
[SPEAKER_15]: You've only got yourself to blame
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounded like Eurobeat with extra different... Eurobeat with different synths.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, yeah, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because I really like Blaine, but I actually like the Eurobeat version better.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it gets a 7.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a 9 because I've been blasting this in my car with the windows down driving.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bug.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to give it a 6.
[SPEAKER_04]: It sounds like more of the same.
[SPEAKER_04]: I kind of liked it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't like it as much as the Kylie song, but I kind of dug it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it an eight and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Moving on to song number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boy, am I feeling the pressure tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm pretty much conceding tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to do a song where I don't care if you vote for it or not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because you might remember a couple weeks ago before we went on involuntary hiatus, I played a song called Why by DJ Sammy, which didn't get a single vote from any of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I said, F you all, the next cage match, I'm going to play something shitty.
[SPEAKER_04]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: The band is M3 Helena Walsh and Stacey D. I have no idea what kind of name that is, but it's M3 Helena Walsh and Stacey D. It's called I Touch Myself, the Love to Infinity radio mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And yes, it is an update of that song.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't want you, I don't want anybody else When I think about you, I touch myself
[SPEAKER_04]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's my background?
[SPEAKER_04]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Song number three in tonight's cage match, I Touch Myself by M3, Helena Walsh, and Stacey D. I touched myself right in the eye.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I wanted to cry because they took a song that was excellent in its original form and made it into just generic trance crap.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it gets a three.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_03]: It's remixed by numbers.
[SPEAKER_03]: Take song, add different backbeat, done.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It made me... It was like that song was the whole, and seven days later I'm going to become gay having listened to that song.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think it's a six.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bugged.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I touched myself in the eye and then the nose, and... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do not need that imagery!
[SPEAKER_04]: And song number two you can vote for tonight is Good Cool with Chorus K with Blame the Transmix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And song number three you can vote for tonight, I Touch Myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to play this song now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What song is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: The V-Rare stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we'll get to the V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I found that song that I was talking to you about.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember when we were sitting at E3 and we're watching, you know, the Groovaloos do their thing up there in that song?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm like, that would be an awesome song to remix with...
[SPEAKER_03]: No Limit
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of waiting is what's going on in the sim scene.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're waiting for a few things.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're waiting for Bomani Sale to come back up.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're waiting for Food Mix 2 to be released next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out Friday, folks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Only a few more days left on the 15th.
[SPEAKER_03]: So keep an eye on Orange Ones Radio because we'll let you know when it's up and what we think about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then we're also waiting to see what's going on with DDR East Coast Invasion because
[SPEAKER_03]: They're still doing tournaments.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: FoonMix 2
[SPEAKER_04]: Dream Mix TV World Fighters
[SPEAKER_03]: And what it is, it's a collection of characters from Konami, from Hudson Soft, and one other company.
[SPEAKER_03]: I can't remember the last company, but it is Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: with us.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, you get some really crazy matchups from Konami, for example.
[SPEAKER_03]: Starting off, they have Simon Belmont.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Solid Snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was unlockable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Solid Snake.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Bathroom Yell
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, so they have Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had like some Barbie type chick or something like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had, I want to say... Optimus Prime, bitch!
[SPEAKER_04]: Optimus Prime, motherfucker!
Bomberman!
[SPEAKER_04]: Bomberman was in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you played this game, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you played this game?
[SPEAKER_09]: Goddamn, all I heard was Hudson Soft and I think Bomberman.
[SPEAKER_04]: A Super Smash Brothers rip-off, well, clone-ish game.
[SPEAKER_04]: with Konami characters and Hudson characters and Optimus Prime.
[SPEAKER_09]: On what?
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: PlayStation 2 Japanese.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is it out when?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's already out.
[SPEAKER_09]: Ordering right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have it on my PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did a matchup with Simon Belmont versus Optimus Prime, who, by the way, turns into a truck.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was great, watching Optimus Prime turn into a truck and beat people, run people over.
[SPEAKER_03]: They have characters from...
[SPEAKER_03]: Bloody Roar Adventure Island Master Higgins It's not as good as Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not as good as Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_03]: but it's still pretty damn fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had fun playing it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's very Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I think it's
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much of a culture shock thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: and then it was, where's Jamie?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry, I was in the bathroom, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not now, before the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then I walked back here and then suddenly the front door opened.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, speak of the devil, literally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Kisses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was there too before I came here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're going to tally up those cage match votes right now and we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: In this break, DDR Extreme 2 V-Rare music.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got it, here it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to hear it in this break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some of the shorter songs from... Was that NCSX sold out on Mario Mix?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, DDR Mario Mix sold out on NCSX.
[SPEAKER_09]: Diet Channel?
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to hear in this break, because we picked some of the shorter songs, because we're not going to be able to play the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: You Gotta Move It, which is the new song that's going to be playable.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's very sexy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Destiny, the piano version.
[SPEAKER_04]: I Need You, the inside-out outdoor mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Infinite Prayer, all in this break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Enjoy!
[SPEAKER_15]: Let the music fill your cell Let your body take control Falling, my whole world is falling
[SPEAKER_18]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: I could keep on following you, never letting you go Following you, losing all my pride Callin' on you and never letting you go Following you, but you'd run You, you were the destiny I was planning for eternity
[SPEAKER_18]: Something came and took you away from me Baby, you, you were my destiny You were the only man in this world for me, meant for me But now you've brought away destiny
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not talking happiness, I know you must be aware that the lies I tell you doesn't matter when it's all together And you don't have to wait for me to let you go I'm with you, with you, I'm with you all the time, all the time
[SPEAKER_15]: Thanks for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_25]: Gaming Radio, so uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_25]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello boys and girls, welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost want to call that Target store back tomorrow morning and see if that coffee got sold or somebody went and slapped him on the wrist or what.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's out there now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, in that break, some music from the DDR Extreme 2 VRare, You Gotta Move It, featuring Julie Regard, I think it is, Destiny, Piano Version, I Need You, Inside Out, Dormix, and Infinite Prayer, all from the new VRare, which, by the way, I tried to get at a GameStop yesterday, or I should really say Miklatov tried to get at a GameStop yesterday, which I don't really get, because, you know, he kind of works for Konami, and he doesn't have a copy of the VRare yet, but we were trying to get one from GameStop, and couldn't get one.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the weird thing, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: I haven't gotten one yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this is the weird thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They said they had given some out, but they thought they had one left.
[SPEAKER_04]: They had the cover and no disc in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_04]: or just wanted to hear it, haven't gotten your viewers yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those were some of the tracks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Other tracks, some repeats from previous games you've probably already heard before on the station.
[SPEAKER_04]: Some other long version mixes, but we just don't have time to play those because they're like 7 or 8 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We can play the Seduction vocal mix, it's only 4.40.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we'll get to that if we have time, but we're running a little late in show actually because usually we get to the FUs of the week around 8.30 and frickin' now it's 9.15.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rage!
[SPEAKER_09]: My first FU of the week goes toward sleeping for 12 hours and waking up sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Also another FU goes to Battletech because it makes me motion sick.
[SPEAKER_09]: Another FU goes toward...
[SPEAKER_09]: I actually have something I can't say on the air, so just a generic F you towards something that's stuck in my head.
[SPEAKER_09]: And another one goes toward being sick, again, and having to go to work.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, one more.
[SPEAKER_09]: F you to World Geography, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's go to Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have one that's stuck in my mind, and that's basically, fuck you to the firewall that's at my work, because now I can't view a lot of sites because they're, you know, under different, like, logs, you know, like, spam or chat or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: At one point we had, like, almost the whole internet blocked because they were messing with the filters.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys use WebSense?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, they have this Barracuda spy blocker thing, or Barracuda firewall or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That sucker, you know, it doesn't like proxy servers either.
[SPEAKER_03]: I tried getting around it that way, but no luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyways, yeah, but fuck that, because now I can't read stuff on LiveJournal, and it cuts down one more page I can read.
[SPEAKER_09]: Welcome to the world that the rest of us have to live in at work.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to give an F you to vacation being over, because I don't want it to end.
[SPEAKER_04]: So an F you to the fact that vacation's running out and I actually have to go back to work tomorrow, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: And an F you to GameStop that didn't have the copy of the beer I ran yesterday, because I wanted that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And an F you to the fact that the systems at Dave & Buster's went down for a little while yesterday, which took away from my precious playtime.
[SPEAKER_04]: An F you to the fact that I can't stop eating Cold Stone, because that ice cream is delicious, and it makes me fat.
[SPEAKER_04]: and an F you to that guy in Final Fantasy XI who called me a cheap white mage because I don't have a race.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, I've tried to do BCNM40 I don't know how many times, I can't get that damn scroll.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't win it for my life, so... F you!
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate you, no cures for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like being a white mage because if I don't like somebody, I'll let them die.
[SPEAKER_04]: And let's go- oops, I'm sorry, lag, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's go to Bugged with any F yous he might have.
[SPEAKER_22]: F you to your Comcast DVR.
[SPEAKER_22]: Why?
[SPEAKER_22]: It doesn't work like a TiVo.
[SPEAKER_22]: I told you it's not as good as TiVo.
[SPEAKER_22]: Good God.
[SPEAKER_22]: I thought you meant it didn't record suggestions.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't know it wouldn't go back.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, and also since I haven't been on the show in a while, I left you to breaking my collarbone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Glad to see you up and about.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, Rob saw me, what, a couple of days afterward at a party, and I pretty much sat in a chair and vegged out, drank a lot of beer, and...
[SPEAKER_22]: And we all laughed at pictures of ourselves from junior high and high school.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, mostly just mine.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Brian's, but that's because he wasn't there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's see, oh, FQ to the ER, but... Because when I broke my collarbone, I had to go to the ER.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am unemployed, I do not have insurance, and it was actually a lot less than I thought it would be, but the fact that I didn't have insurance sucked.
[SPEAKER_22]: Next time I fall and break my collarbone, I'm going to try and do it in Canada.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I've got a plan on that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Put it on the itinerary for next time I go up to Vancouver.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fall off bike, break collarbone.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not many other FUs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that music was too happy for an FU, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chatroom FU time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sakurina says, F you to rain, the public transportation that isn't on time, trains and all of that happening on the same day, causing me to walk home from school in the rain and staying stuck there due to a train crossing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tomokun would like to say, fuck life 365, fuck, fuck, fuck idiots.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, let's see, Dark Knight would like to say, my F you goes to my Advance Wars DS game for being hard as hell, and an F you to loneliness, no one in the world deserves to be all alone in the world.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_04]: SpiritSnare says F you to Tokyo Game Action for getting Happy Sky F you to certain Target stores for releasing We Heart Katamari earlier than they're supposed to F you to others for not Not Google, but Goggle says F you to Lowe's Cineplex in Danbury, Connecticut for not letting me into an R-rated movie Also F you to school starting at 7.45 every morning I think I've been to that theater in Connecticut Go figure, I've been to a lot of really random places
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkTetsuya says, A continued FU to this crappy connection.
[SPEAKER_04]: An FU to CCL's card system.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one explained that the cards expire, so I had to find out the hard way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I read that in your LJ and I was pissed too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rini would like to say, I have an FU to diarrhea or indigestion.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, in the 155 episodes we've done of Orange Lounge Radio, you think that's something someone would have said FU to a long time ago because...
[SPEAKER_04]: You didn't flat out say diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_09]: You did say indigestion, but... No, F you to the medication the doctor puts you on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have done an F you, though, to drinking a lot of Hawaiian Punch and coloring my feces blue.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I think that kind of tops that one.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you eat asparagus, it turns your pee a different color, too.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you have honey smacks, it makes your pee smell like honey smacks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did you know?
[SPEAKER_09]: That sounds incredibly nasty in both cases.
[SPEAKER_22]: First off, why are you sniffing your pee?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, that stuff is so strong.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the aroma that wafts up from the toilet.
[SPEAKER_09]: Exactly, it's like, honey smacks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob's red, look, Rob's red.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't believe this show has literally gone into the toilet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, we can't make poo-poo jokes anymore, so... Don't want you to compile a website of all the different foods that will make your bile and... Your one and two smell like something else.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can imagine some of our listeners are now going to go, Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: and, like, drink a whole gallon of blue wine.
[SPEAKER_03]: The blue wine punch, that shit is awesome, but they don't sell it anymore.
[SPEAKER_03]: They don't sell the blue stuff, they sell green and, like, orange and stuff, so, and red, and I don't, you know, want to drink a gallon of red.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like the blue stuff, and they don't sell it, and that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to everybody, because I have a Sega CDX and no one else.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sega CDX.
[SPEAKER_08]: Duh, duh, duh, duh, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Renee's saying an F you to everybody because he has a CDX and nobody else does, but you have one, don't you?
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I have a regular say, I have both.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have like all three, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure you know what sort of context I mean in that last one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Zaku would like to say F you to being unemployed for nearly nine months and F you to not getting work study this year.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to not having to wait this long to order my books for school.
[SPEAKER_04]: F you to State University of New York University Police for giving us heat for having lots of people in the front of our apartment on Friday and Saturday nights.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sin, or S1N, fuck you to there not being any retarded Target stores in Canada.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is there Target in Canada?
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: You guys are really missing out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, there is Target in Canada.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the Walmart doesn't have a star in the middle.
[SPEAKER_22]: It has a dash.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who fucking cares?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, if you watch shows that are supposedly in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: and they're actually filmed in Canada, you can tell.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got a lot of free time on your hands, don't you?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a Walmart or Target commercial when it's showing what is out here known as Best Foods mayonnaise.
[SPEAKER_09]: It shows actually Hellman's.
[SPEAKER_04]: ColorOfSakura says, F you to silly high school drama that I keep getting pulled into because people think I care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just remember... Yeah, it gets better in college.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because there's lots of drinking involved, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ron Chan says, F you to the con I'm staffing for.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm in charge of two departments, and I got no help here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need a drink.
[SPEAKER_04]: John Field says, F you to my sudden loss of interest in Phantasy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here I'm trying to pull out a machinima?
[SPEAKER_04]: Machinima?
[SPEAKER_04]: and I'm finding I can't play the game normally anymore without feeling totally drained.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well, it was a good five-year run.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've owned that fucking game on like four different systems and I never want to play it again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I haven't played it since I got married.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bacanico says, F you for not having any targets in the area so I cannot check one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or, I'm sorry, Weehart Katamari.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh, Bob.
[SPEAKER_09]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Neko means cat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: GS191 says F you to the In The Groove for breaking on me F you to Comcast for the cable going out three times this week F you to leechers that are not seeding Advent Children F you to politics, Republicans suck and Democrats blow F you to G4 for trying to get tech back It is too late and may G4 go down in flames
[SPEAKER_04]: My dad's very happy that Leo Laporte is back on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, I am happy Leo Laporte's come back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Leo, take him in from the inside.
[SPEAKER_04]: Take him out.
[SPEAKER_04]: You need to tell him about that live taping of This Week in Tech that's going on in NorCal.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, there's going to be... There's two podcasts I'll listen to, this one and This Week in Tech.
[SPEAKER_04]: Technically, this right now is not a podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The podcast will be later.
[SPEAKER_22]: The one you guys... I know, I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_22]: And This Week in Tech will be filming in Larkspur.
[SPEAKER_22]: Not necessarily filming, but recording before a live audience in Larkspur next week.
Where the hell's that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Dark Knight says own a final FU to accounting homework for causing me total brain damage.
[SPEAKER_04]: FU to Christopher for not bringing anything for us
[SPEAKER_23]: Sure, I saw Serenity, which was really, really, really well done.
[SPEAKER_23]: I recommend it to everybody.
[SPEAKER_23]: FYI, he's a little bit biased because he's a Buffy whore.
[SPEAKER_23]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: DarkSakura agrees with me, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted to go, and I couldn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have something for you.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's a bunch of nuts.
[SPEAKER_03]: I found out the other day, because this was last week after we watched, or we...
[SPEAKER_03]: And that reminded me of the trailer that was on one of them for the whole, I guess, because it's a gay porn version of The Ring.
[SPEAKER_03]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: Our company is actually distributing that, which is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_04]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how a lot of pornos will, like, do funny, like, play on, you know, the regular movie title?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, I remember there was a porno once, um, it was Ally McFeel was a porno.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now, yeah, Word of Penis Hands I've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, I saw, the first one I ever saw was The Bonehead.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, Beaver and Buttface is another one I've seen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before You're Gay, You See the Hole.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, that, now they're doing The Ring, except it's the gay version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the hole.
[SPEAKER_23]: It's totally hot, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: I recommend that movie, too.
[SPEAKER_23]: Oh, and I saw the Exorcism of Emily Rose, which was okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: It was okay?
[SPEAKER_23]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_23]: But Serenity was great.
[SPEAKER_23]: I recommend that.
[SPEAKER_23]: Two thumbs up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Two thumbs up and... You need to come up with a gay rating system.
[SPEAKER_23]: Two cocks up.
[SPEAKER_23]: I give it two hard dicks up.
[SPEAKER_23]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_23]: Here's Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's two hard dicks up my ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow, I didn't see it going in that direction.
[SPEAKER_04]: But anyways, we got a late FU.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll like this one, Loki.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spirit Snare says, FU to Apple replacing the iPod Mini with the iPod Nano.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just thought I'd share.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, what do you got?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got a couple minutes left here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you want to say?
[SPEAKER_03]: What do I want to say?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to say that I was reading the other day...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know why they aren't sending me free samples.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why aren't you sending me this shit for free?
[SPEAKER_03]: I should be having it already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Namco Battle Collection, my ass.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just can't wait for Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's coming out next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to get Burnout Legends to tie me over.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's kind of a transitional into Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to be playing that for months.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, until Liberty City Stories comes out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did we do the Cage Match?
[SPEAKER_04]: I love that we did Cage Match Winners!
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, fuckin' A. Who did win the Cage Match?
[SPEAKER_04]: There's the vote tally.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight's Cage Match winner was... It was actually very close.
[SPEAKER_04]: All three songs got a lot of votes tonight, so everybody should feel really good.
[SPEAKER_04]: But this one won.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good cool!
[SPEAKER_04]: Featuring Jeff Koop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I'll have to find a song for next week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, congratulations there.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was a very close one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, I wanted to give a couple other plugs since we haven't been on the air in a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't forget you can really help out our podcast by voting for us on Podcast Alley.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I'm going to copy-paste the link right there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Put that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go vote for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: And also, just spread the word about our podcast and our live show.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the best way we can get more people to listen.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've been hoarding it out to the publishers.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the way to do it, my friend.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, and vote for us on Live365 player window.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can vote, like, excellent.
[SPEAKER_04]: Vote five, excellent.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I heard that the Apple iTunes, their store, their little ranking system's rigged, the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: You basically can subscribe and unsubscribe rapidly, and it just counts how many times you click the button, and it'll move your... I heard they fixed that.
[SPEAKER_03]: They didn't, because there was a little thing on Dig about it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It came up, and it's still broken, so that sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: End of show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Starting off with Bug, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: Happy birthday to me.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is, um... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: I've been married for ten days.
[SPEAKER_09]: Reject both icons.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're still a newlywed.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should have a reality TV show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hell no!
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, the final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: One word that sums up everything that we did tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll see you guys later on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bugged, what's the final word of tonight's show?
[SPEAKER_22]: Target.
[SPEAKER_12]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_12]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was homecoming night at my high school Everyone was there, it was totally cool
[SPEAKER_15]: I was real excited, I almost wet my jeans And my best friend Debbie was homecoming queen She looked so pretty in pink chiffon Riding a boat with her tiara on Holding this humongous bouquet in her hand She looked great out of Disneyland
[SPEAKER_15]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: The Cinderella ride?
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, definitely an E-ticket.
[SPEAKER_15]: Crowd was cheering.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everyone was stoked.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it was like the whole school was totally coked or something.
[SPEAKER_15]: The band was playing.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everyone.
[SPEAKER_15]: And all of a sudden, somebody screamed.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody run, the homecoming queen's got a gun Everybody run, the homecoming queen has got a gun
[SPEAKER_15]: Debbie's smiling and waving her gun Picking up cheerleaders one by one Oh, Buffy's pom-pom just flew to bits Oh, now Missy's head just did the splits God, my gun friend's on a shooting spree Stop it, Debbie, you're embarrassing me How could you do what you just did?
[SPEAKER_15]: Are you having a really bad period?
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody run The homecoming queen's got a gun
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody run!
[SPEAKER_15]: The homecoming queen has got a gun!
[SPEAKER_15]: An hour later, the cops arrived.
[SPEAKER_15]: By then, the entire Glee Club had died.
[SPEAKER_15]: No big loss.
[SPEAKER_15]: You wouldn't believe what they brought to stop her.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tear gas, machine guns, even a chopper!
[SPEAKER_15]: Throw down your guns!
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_15]: See you next week.
[SPEAKER_15]: The homecoming queen's got a gun Everybody run The homecoming queen has got a gun Half of the night She's winking, half of the night The cops fired a warning shot that blew her off the float I tried to scream stuck but it's stuck in my throat She hit the ground and did a flip, it was real acrobatic But I was crying so hard I couldn't work my isthmatic I ran down to Debbie, I had to find out
[SPEAKER_15]: What made her do it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Why'd she freak out?
[SPEAKER_15]: I thought the bullet had got her right in the ear.
[SPEAKER_15]: I knew then the end was near.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I ran down and I said in her good ear, Debbie, why'd you do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: She raised her head, smiled and said, I did it for Johnny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Johnny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, like, who's Johnny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Answer me, Debbie, who's Johnny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Does anybody here know Johnny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you Johnny?
[SPEAKER_05]: There was one guy named Johnny, but he was a total geek, and we had food in his races.
[SPEAKER_05]: Answer me, Debbie, who's Johnny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, this is like that movie Citizen Kane, you know, where you later find out Rosebud was a sled?
[SPEAKER_15]: But we'll never know who Johnny was, because, like, he's dead.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everybody Runs The homecoming queen has got a son Everybody Runs The homecoming queen has got a Everybody Runs Everybody Runs
[SPEAKER_12]: thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, we're going to boot you from the stream now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But just reconnect in like 15 seconds and you get all this great DDR and Bimani music and video game music too.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have like Luminous music and other Final Fantasy stuff and who knows what else in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: and now we're loading up stuff for the podcast and ooh, that new Sonic game looks very sweet.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should see it in action.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw the video for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, it looks very sexy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're gonna boot you from the stream now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Please reconnect in about 15 seconds to resume listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you guys as always for your support of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Heart, kisses, goodbye.