[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of September 12th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_07]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_07]: Joining me as always, my awesome co-host, say hello to the one and only, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, brains.
[SPEAKER_07]: You sound like you're in a good mood.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh... Maybe been playing a little too much Resident Evil?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, I've been playing with my puppies.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I went to Dave and Buster's last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fun, fun times.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to fill us in in just a minute here, but first let me introduce the one and only, Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm here.
[SPEAKER_07]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Usually we like to start off the show with a little bit of how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: What have you been playing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get right into it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: Puppies.
[SPEAKER_01]: Everyday puppies.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have you been good about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you actually going in there everyday?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and I walk my puppies and clean up their poopy and I make them catch frisbee and earn me money.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I pimp out my puppies to the frisbee people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think the game is starting to get to the point of it's getting a little irritating having to go in everyday?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: No?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that's what some people are bitching about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm hearing now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, then they, you know, never had a virtual pet before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendogs was not for them.
[SPEAKER_01]: They never carried around their pocket Pikachu, damn it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I also played, went to Dave and Buster's last night and played Battletech for the first time.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, that game gave me a headache, made me want to throw up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, describe Battletech for those that may not know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You get in these pod things and basically it's like you're in the cockpit of a mech.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you go around killing people.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't like it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's one of those games where the screen's up on top and it reflects onto a concave mirror.
[SPEAKER_01]: It totally messed with my sense of motion sickness.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played...
[SPEAKER_01]: Lange and the Midnight Maximum tune last night and completely owned my husband.
[SPEAKER_01]: So weird saying that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Your husband!
[SPEAKER_01]: I've been married 10 days and I still have trouble writing my last name.
[SPEAKER_01]: I haven't been to the DMV yet either.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: I also played a bunch of Tiki games and that was really... Dave Buster's the one place where playing Tiki games can be cool, not like Chuck E. Cheese.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I was trying to save up enough to get new mugs, but they didn't have any mugs, so I just saved my tickets.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had enough to purchase an Xbox game or a PS2 game, but I just, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought about getting that racing game that Rockstar puts out, the Midnight Club 3 Dub Edition.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want to play that, I've got it, I think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe I'll borrow it and check it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need a good racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that I've given you back your copy of Silent Hill 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need to play through that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, anything else?
[SPEAKER_01]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_06]: So I've been playing Burnout 3, as per usual.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then I got a copy of Burnout Legends for the PSP, so I've been playing that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just to tide me over until I get Burnout Revenge this week, which I have on pre-order and already paid for.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that one's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Burnout Legends is cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of all three games of the original three put together, plus bonus stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: God, you haven't shut up about this Burnout game for like two months already.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then other things I've been playing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendogs, of course, I have to take care of Taco.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which I do find it a little annoying.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because he's always hungry, no matter how often I check on him.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, damn, my dog never got that hungry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, why can't you just leave the bowl out for him to eat the damn food and just leave it there?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_06]: My dog never went through a bowl of water that quick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: Water should be free.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why the hell do I have to buy water?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because your puppies need special water.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_01]: That you buy at the dog store.
[SPEAKER_01]: Stupid special water.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to walk to the discount store and get it for, you know, uber cheap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why isn't there a store where you have to buy toys?
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to find used toys in the street.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, isn't that a little weird?
[SPEAKER_01]: I sell that crap.
[SPEAKER_01]: My friend got a Dalmatian.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I heard Dalmatians were unlockable in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: She found the fireman hat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Lucky.
[SPEAKER_01]: Got a Dalmatian named Lala.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just in the street somewhere?
[SPEAKER_01]: Lana.
[SPEAKER_01]: She found the... You have to... If you walk around the top perimeter, then you get more rare stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: The further away you go from home, the better stuff you get.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what the hell are those packages that... I'll be walking and all of a sudden there's a box sitting on the ground.
[SPEAKER_01]: You have to shake your leash over it and your dog, you will notice it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pull your dog back and he'll grab it and open it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Use the leash to pull back.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was shaking the hell out of my dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: You would have thought that I was trying to kill it or something, and the fucker wouldn't pick up the package.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've got two dogs that I have.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm a Welsh Corgi, and I have Menchie, who's a Shiba Inu, and I didn't realize I have anime dogs now, both of them.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're both like fish sticks from the trash can.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have Oscar, my wiener dog, who has a Mario hat now, by the way, which I found in the street.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have Taco, who has a spike collar, a news hat, and some sunglasses.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have the Japanese style collar on Minji.
[SPEAKER_06]: Takara.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like you can do fights against... It's basically like Super Smash Bros., but you can play as Simon Belmont versus Optimus Prime.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's rad.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Optimus Prime turns into a truck and runs over people.
[SPEAKER_01]: I find it funny.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, Takara is actually... Takara is a toy maker.
[SPEAKER_01]: And they're the ones who put out Transformers and, like, Lika-chan, the little Barbie doll in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, she's in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, Lika-chan's in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Master Higgins from Adventure Island.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hear Bonk is unlockable, so it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's not a new game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been out a little while, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's been out for a couple years, but it's just really weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes we discover these little import gems a little late.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, well, you know, we're not in Japan, so we can't do the stuff advertised right away.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, hey, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's still good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then, of course, I'm putting more money down on my 360, so waiting for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, lots of stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_01]: On GameStop's site, they have a $1,000 Ultimate Bundle.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think we talked about that the week you were here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it was crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were talking to the game publishers about that and they were laughing at how ridiculous and stupid it is because most of those games aren't coming out at launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know how they're going to get this stuff, but it's not coming out at launch.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to think about that before we pre-order.
[SPEAKER_07]: The games get delayed all the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who is going to pay thousands of dollars for some stew for every game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just buy them as they come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, I'm not interested in that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, rich people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rich people don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Paris Hilton, she doesn't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: She just wants her Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: She doesn't know how to freaking use an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: She can make sausage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on, my gaming week.
[SPEAKER_07]: I played mostly games that are kind of old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of rediscovering old games, I bought .hack a couple weeks ago and I finally like really beginning into it this week and just playing through it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's really a cool little game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the idea of an MMO, but it's not.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: This is seriously one of the greatest GameCube games they put out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not just that, it's one of the greatest next-gen games they put out, period.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's such a great game because there's so much to do in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to get all the little pieces and read about the characters.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's trophies.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's the single-player mode where you do the adventure.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's the mini-games, the little challenges, hit the targets.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's so many cool little things that just keep this game going.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's just, oh man, I just love the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I was also rediscovering F-Zero today.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I was trying to, because I was hooking up the GameCube again, and I wanted to try out some of these games that support widescreen TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm kind of upset, though, because Nintendo does not support component cable anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if I want to hook up to my HDTV, I have to use S-Video.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, S-Video on the HDTV makes things look blurry compared to the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: F-Zero looked blurry!
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's kind of upsetting, because F-Zero is a really sharp-looking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's an awesome-looking game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I went to Nintendo's website to try and find a component cable.
[SPEAKER_07]: They stopped making them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Third party.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't even find a third party cable at Fry's or anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, I think that Lixing carries them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's where I'm going to have to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the other weird thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, since mid-2004, Nintendo stopped putting the digital output port on the back of the GameCubes.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you didn't buy your GameCube before probably when the 79 price drop or whatever it's at now, your GameCube doesn't have this port and you'll never have the component.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It really irks me about Nintendo's lack of next-generation television support.
[SPEAKER_07]: If they're going to go up to the next level with next-gen gaming, and we all heard that story a while back where they're saying Revolution's not going to support HDTV, that really bothers me because, you know...
[SPEAKER_07]: After launch, a couple years after launch, a lot more people are going to be buying these HDTVs and they will be a bigger market share and Nintendo's going to be left out cold.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially since, you know, I've got these pictures up of the PS3 that I took at E3 with the two HDMI ports on the back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, very sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, in case you have two HDTVs sitting next to each other.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know I have five of them sitting next to each other, so that'll be no problem.
[SPEAKER_01]: That makes me think, though, remember the iLink?
[SPEAKER_01]: That probably could be for dual output for multiplayer games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: So anyway, I still love you, Nintendo, but come on, get with the times.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's time to start supporting HD a little better, and I hope they change their mind on the revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: and remake the component cables.
[SPEAKER_06]: While they're at it, they should drop the price on those plasma TVs because they're too fucking expensive.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, but I got mine at Costco and it's not a plasma, but it's just an HD regular TV and it's nice.
[SPEAKER_01]: One thing that Costco doesn't advertise, which is a very good advantage of buying things from there, no matter how long you have owned something, if anything on it goes wrong, you can take it back and they have to take it back for a full refund or replacement.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even if it's 10 years.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're gamers just like you guys out there listening, so we're just telling you guys where to get the good deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I shopped around for HDTV, and I seriously felt Costco was the best deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: We like quality for our gaming goodness.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about some news tonight going into next gen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about the next generation Sonic.
[SPEAKER_07]: They teased it a little bit at E3, but now they are officially announcing...
[SPEAKER_07]: that they are going to be making a next-gen Sonic the Hedgehog game, Sega of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's part of their Tokyo Game Show lineup, and Sonic the Hedgehog is going to be coming out for PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word yet about a Revolution release, but nobody's really talking about the Revolution yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I imagine they will early next year.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, Sega's also going to be showing them at Tokyo Game Show a mech game called Chromehounds for the 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which looks sexy.
[SPEAKER_07]: And a...
[SPEAKER_07]: A Sonic Riders game for Xbox, PS2, and GameCube.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chromehounds looks sexy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen the pictures of it.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know much about Chromehounds.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a mech fighting game.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just like, you know, just like Armored Core or something like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really awesome looking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta pull the screenshots.
[SPEAKER_06]: They looked really awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what site had the screenshots?
[SPEAKER_06]: If I remember, it's not IGN that had the screenshots.
[SPEAKER_06]: As soon as the monitor comes back up here.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I remember correctly, it was I want to say the Xbox360 Updates.com 360updates.com had the screenshots, if I remember correctly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looking this up right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, there it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, um
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: 490, man, that's expensive for a cable.
[SPEAKER_01]: Works with GameCubes worldwide.
[SPEAKER_01]: Check if you have digital AV output port.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, because if you have a new GameCube, you don't have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I'm looking forward to the next-gen Sonic.
[SPEAKER_07]: That little video that you were showing before the podcast, Loki, looked very sexy.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I didn't get a chance to go to the Sega Theater at this year's E3 because it was another one of those things that had a line.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, no, actually, the line for the Sega Theater?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: I spent less than 10 minutes in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I was looking at going the last day, and it just was wrapping around the thing, and I just...
[SPEAKER_01]: I was around the other side of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Less than 10 minute wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Darn you.
[SPEAKER_01]: And if you were waiting in line, they came by and gave you t-shirts or plushies.
[SPEAKER_06]: I lost out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I'll do it next year.
[SPEAKER_01]: They had those nice home theater seatings in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: So sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just watching it on that screen, they had, oh, we're like, ooh, pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did get to play Phantasy Star Universe, so, you know, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I got the okay from the soon-to-be wife, because our wedding day is going to be about two weeks before E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: She says, as long as my company is paying for me to go, it's okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: E3 E3 E3
[SPEAKER_01]: Gunstar Heroes is being re-released Sega Ages
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on, of course, two very, very highly talked about games this year when it comes to handhelds are the two puzzlers, Luminous and Meteos.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, of course, very similar because they are developed by the same guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Luminous and Meteos are actually going to be re-released on one handheld system.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they'll both be available on one handheld system, finally.
[SPEAKER_01]: That handheld system... The Neo Geo Pocket Color!
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: A cellular telephone will be the handheld system.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, forget it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because cell phone game ports suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's cute for the nostalgia value for about five minutes, but for the most part, at least here in America, our cell phones, the cell phone games suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the single N-Gage owner out there rejoices.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it's not coming out for N-Gage.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm getting a BlackBerry.
[SPEAKER_06]: They play mobile phone games, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm playing on a BlackBerry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Snake for life.
[SPEAKER_07]: Snake was the only good cell phone game
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys remember, this was something we had talked about when our podcast first started.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it was like back in January.
[SPEAKER_07]: Playboy Magazine did a spread featuring the Girls of Gaming where they had Topless, Blood Rain, and Melina.
[SPEAKER_07]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: In October, they're doing it again!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm gonna buy that issue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just for the show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, the sacrifice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, the sacrifices you have to make.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who are the characters you will be seeing in October's Playboy in the buff, the digital buff, or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel so stupid talking about this, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe that it was... Oh my god, digital boobies!
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe that it was so popular the first time they're doing it again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are they going to have the hot coffee mod uncensored on this?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea, but here's some of the games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jackie, who is a cheerleader in Midway's Blitz the League.
[SPEAKER_07]: Carla Valenti from Atari's Indigo Prophecy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Capcom's Dark Watch will have Cassidy and Tala, who is a vampire female.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might add that Cassidy was killed off in about the first five minutes of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Her head ripped clean from her body.
[SPEAKER_06]: Playboy Mansion Private Party
[SPEAKER_07]: but Namco doesn't want to be left out they'll have a character from Hellgate London and of course Sony's God of War getting in on it as well I know it's funny everybody's joke about this is they're all what the hell's Hellgate London they're all we don't even know what that game is I've actually never heard of this myself and I'm kind of reading this going okay must be some game I just haven't heard of I can't play them all anyway
[SPEAKER_06]: What was the original spread called before?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Digital... I just closed the story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't do any more research on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It lowers your IQ.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a very interesting story I think we ought to talk about here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because this affects us here in California.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, Orange Lounge Radio, we're based out of Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we do have a worldwide audience.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is something that's going on in California.
[SPEAKER_07]: And California's kind of been known to set the tone for the rest of the nation sometimes when it comes to certain bills.
[SPEAKER_07]: Assembly Bill 1179.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the bill that Assemblyman Leland Yee was kind of behind a couple months ago when the hot coffee thing was really big.
[SPEAKER_07]: It prohibits retailers from selling violent games to minors or else they'll be fined $1,000 for each violation.
[SPEAKER_07]: It passed in the California Senate by a vote of 22 to 9 and it passed in the Assembly 65 to 7.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's now sitting on Governor Schwarzenegger's
[SPEAKER_07]: and speaking of feeling like an idiot saying something, Governor Schwarzenegger's desk right now waiting to be signed.
[SPEAKER_07]: He must sign or veto the bill by October 9th.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word yet on which way he'll go, but probably, considering the fairly overwhelming support, he will probably sign this bill.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it would go into effect January 1st, 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: By the way, the bill will also require that the games be labeled as being for sale to adults only by a solid 18 sticker, no smaller than 2 inches by 2 inches, on the front of the package.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's very interesting because if you think about it a Game Boy Advance game is only 5 inches by 5 inches the packaging.
[SPEAKER_07]: So a little 18 sticker would take up like half the box.
[SPEAKER_07]: The bill also makes no mention of the current ESRB system.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the bill defines its own means of a violent video game saying a video game in which the range of options available to a player includes killing, maiming, dismembering or sexually assaulting an image of a human being.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, that goes for all of them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye-bye all fighting games.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, Mortal Kombat Shaolin Monks is going gold.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, this was a game that, uh, I played a little bit at E3 and I actually kind of enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, didn't think I would, um, but it's actually kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a neat little, um, it's not like a typical Mortal Kombat game because it's more of like a 3D adventure type thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, or I shouldn't say 3D, but, uh, yeah, 3D ISO, you know, perspective type game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, where you're just, you know, going around killing things, which will probably be one of the first games to carry an 18 sticker, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and that game has recently gone gold, and it'll be coming out for $49.99 on September 19th.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's next week.
[SPEAKER_01]: Our UK listeners get it on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be a week after Monday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha!
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what kind of news do you have for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, just checking the UK release dates.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did see on the 16th, E6 comes out on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Burnout Revenge on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_01]: ER The Game for PC on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some pretty neat stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Meteos on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_01]: Lots of stuff coming out on the 23rd.
[SPEAKER_01]: Including Myst5, Mortal Kombat, Rugby Challenge 2006, and Sniper Elite.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's some pretty good stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, Advance Wars DS comes out on the 30th there too, as well as Castlevania Dawn of Sorrow on the 29th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Advance Wars DS is one of those games I've got to pick up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've been hearing a lot of good things about it, so I want to check it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you've got the other two, it has a tie-in on there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, you get more options in the shop.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, like if you put the Advance game in the bottom slot?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm liking this DS interacting with the other ports.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Another game, checking out Yahoo UK and Ireland games, is Winx Club.
[SPEAKER_01]: Konami's putting out a Winx Club game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's so cute, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then lastly, Date for Animal Crossing DS, which is going to be renamed Wild World for a release.
[SPEAKER_01]: It says first quarter 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wait, so the whole game itself is going to be called Wild World in Europe?
[SPEAKER_01]: I think...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Just stuff on the Silent Hill movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me see because I found a release date on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I'm going to take this as a tentative date because I haven't seen too much official.
[SPEAKER_01]: According to BloodyDisgusting.com, it says... Great website name.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's... I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you want your zombie movies, that's the place to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: April 21st, 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know I will be there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: And also, there was an article, an interview up on IGN, where it was, I can never pronounce this guy's name, Patrick Tatopoulos, I guess, was stating that the director had told him to make, in fact, I'm going to quote, Patrick, I want those guys to look like they are made of plastic, which is exactly the opposite of what we try to do usually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: They're going for a very surreal, very this-can't-really-happen look.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then a lot of what they're trying to do is they're having to redevelop some technology for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please be a video game movie that doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please, please, please.
[SPEAKER_01]: Checking the scenery, though, it's at least going to visually be right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Reading the storyline so far, it's going to be pretty dead on.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I've seen a picture of somebody who had picked up We Heart Katamari from Target this weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: We Heart Katamari is not supposed to be out until when?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like later this month?
[SPEAKER_07]: The 21st.
[SPEAKER_07]: The 21st is when We Heart Katamari is supposed to be out.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we were curious if Target broke street or if this image was photoshopped or what have you.
[SPEAKER_01]: And on Target's website it says they're not going to have the game through their website until the 22nd.
[SPEAKER_07]: Electrolytes?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I was looking to see if you had a PlayStation 2 game in stock.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me check.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hang on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, SD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are on the next pile.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, what was the game again?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's We Love Katamari.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we have one left.
[SPEAKER_07]: You do have one left in stock?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, great.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: So get that.
[SPEAKER_07]: This store actually admitted that they had one left in stock on the shelf.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_07]: So some copies of We Heart Katamari are getting out there a little bit early.
[SPEAKER_07]: So hopefully some of our listeners of the live program ran out there to the store and probably picked up that last copy already, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did confirm that at least none of the local GameStops have gotten it.
[SPEAKER_07]: None of the local GameStops.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we actually called some targets around here.
[SPEAKER_07]: One of the targets around here said that they would be putting the game out on shelves Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which is very interesting, because the game wasn't supposed to be out until the 21st.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, are they doing an early... Did the release get bumped up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: But if you are... Not officially.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you are hearing stories about We Heart Katamari getting out there early, it is possible.
[SPEAKER_07]: We called them, and sure enough, they're selling it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's get to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's do tonight's mailbag, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, you can always send us an email, togo, T-O-G-O, at orange lounge radio dot com. ...
[SPEAKER_07]: We only have one email tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously, once again you frothed with rage about parents' responsibilities totally ignoring the point that consumers have a right to be informed.
[SPEAKER_07]: To utilize your oft-used movie analogy, let's say Paramount produces a flick called Loki Has Brain Damage.
[SPEAKER_07]: It goes through the MPAA and ends up rated R for violence, foul language, and excessive retardation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I always allow my 12 year old to see R rated movies so I let him go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now unbeknownst to the rating board, Paramount secretly slips 5 minutes of close up anal penetration at the end of the credits.
[SPEAKER_07]: This hot anal action actually means that this film should have received an NC-17 rating.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't want my kid to see this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had been duped as a consumer.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is an identical situation to the hot coffee mod.
[SPEAKER_07]: If a parent decides that they will allow their children to play a game rated M, that is not the same as allowing their children to play a game rated AO.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's completely wrong.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because unlike the hot coffee mod, you had to put in external... Okay, you had to have a third-party cheat device in order to see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other words, I would have had to purchase special...
[SPEAKER_06]: I can see it both ways.
[SPEAKER_06]: In one way, let the buyer beware.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, there is always a degree of caution that someone has to make with any purchase.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, really, and I think that when you're dealing with how many different departments you have with the game publisher, being that I know many people now who work for various publishers, what the programmers leave in
[SPEAKER_01]: is not necessarily going to be found by the testers unless, you know, you've got... True, the testers are playing on debug units and they are meant to break the game every way they can, do everything possible, and are given usually a set assignment for how the game should be played when they're testing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, something that is programmed into a game that has had that bit of programming removed to access it
[SPEAKER_01]: on average it's not going to be found.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it is very likely that nobody except the programmers had any idea that this was in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: and that some random person, it could have been found by some random person who said, oh, wow, look what I just found coding for in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, and if they find it on PC, of course, you know, the PlayStation one came after the PC one when they said, oh, it's here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's see if it's in here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Or it could just be a programmer going, oh, look what I did.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a very similar thing to what I've always said is that the programmers put it in there and they made a decision to take it out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I imagine somebody at Rockstar said, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is crossing the line.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is going to get us an AO.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take this out of the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what the programmers did, instead of actually physically removing it from the game, they just took out the pointer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Easier, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot easier.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it also keeps...
[SPEAKER_01]: instead of having to rewrite part of the code, it's slightly easier to remove part of it and make sure that your game ships on date.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing, you know, so to try and get past this here, because we could talk about this until we're blue in the face, rest assured this will never happen again.
[SPEAKER_01]: This is not the first game this has happened with either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Bloody Roar 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: You put it in debug mode, you get necky, you know, masturbatory photos of the characters in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd even talked about last week, a little more innocent, the hidden song in DDR, quote unquote.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although...
[SPEAKER_07]: Some folks have actually sent me an email that linked me to a thread on DDR Freak where some inside sources are saying that that song is actually supposed to be unlockable, just nobody's figured it out yet, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: If nobody's unlocked it at this point, I don't think they're going to, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: But...
[SPEAKER_07]: The point is that basically it was a lazy programming issue and it's brought this whole debate to the front.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that there was a large portion of Rockstar that didn't realize that this was going to be found.
[SPEAKER_07]: They did not intend for this to be found.
[SPEAKER_07]: It did.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now they're taking the heat for it and rest assured this lazy programming incident will never happen again because that testing process will be changed to prevent this from ever happening to a future game because Rockstar's taking a lot of heat for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Should they?
[SPEAKER_07]: Shouldn't they?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not an easy answer because you could say
[SPEAKER_07]: Were they ignorant or did they know what they were doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: We don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: And in the movie analogy, remember the rescuers?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, they always say they put sex things in the Disney movies and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: They did it in Roger Rabbit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: But the thing is that the only way that this would have ever really been... The average eye is going to see it as a blip across the screen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, one time I was watching a cartoon that I used to tape when I lived in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I saw the color changed weirdly.
[SPEAKER_01]: I went back and freestramed it on a picture of the American flag.
[SPEAKER_01]: The animators just happened to stick in there.
[SPEAKER_01]: or even places where there were missing frames.
[SPEAKER_01]: The average person isn't going to see that unless they take an effort to go back and look at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: and if this person is saying that they monitor what their kids are watching obviously for them to go have a third party cheat device cheat in the game then go into this you're not monitoring what your kids are doing so you know what you're the blame still and you know what you can't come and bitch about you know Rockstar saying oh no oh this wasn't supposed to be in the game the game's maturity it's for over 17 you know what adults only is over 18 one year difference
[SPEAKER_06]: We're talking nothing.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like the difference between PG and PG-13.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is really no difference.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: You really should be monitoring what your kids are watching.
[SPEAKER_06]: You shouldn't be playing the games in the first place.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you let them go to R-rated movies anyways, they're probably seeing real boobies in those R-rated films.
[SPEAKER_06]: And this pixelated representation of what is supposed to be sex, and mind you...
[SPEAKER_06]: The Carl Johnson character, the main male in it, does not get naked in this because it was unfinished.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does not get naked, only the woman.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's not even, oh my god, they saw, you know, penis and ass, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just pixelated boobies, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: And mature rated games like God of War that have
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: This, you did not, nobody knew that there would be the sex thing in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, you know, calling, you know, the racist people, murdering the blacks and stuff, and the gang violence, that's okay, but you know, boobies, not okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: But in defense, in defense though, I do think that Rockstar was at fault.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because of a lazy programmer, yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: And no matter who it is in the company, as long as that game was released, that company has a legal requirement to make sure that the product that they've put out on the market is exactly what they are advertising.
[SPEAKER_07]: I agree, and that's where I think you're getting a little off, Loki, is because this is the issue.
[SPEAKER_07]: The issue is not, oh my god, somebody saw Digitized Boobies.
[SPEAKER_07]: But the issue is that Rockstar did not tell anyone that that was in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whereas with God of War, they said, yeah, full-on female boobies everywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: But with this game, they said, oh, there's no sex.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sure, you can blow people's heads off with rocket launchers, whatever, but there is no hardcore sex in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is bonus.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was hardcore sex in the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Am I everything?
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I'm going to be a parent in a couple years.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_01]: When you buy something that, and trust me, I remember fully well what a devious little child I was.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's not the end of your responsibility.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is such a thing called maintenance.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got to move on because we could beat this top of the ground.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just, you know, I hate hearing it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I say from here on out, no more hot coffee ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or take it to the forums.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, go to our website.
[SPEAKER_01]: Go to OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: Send Loki a personal email.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki at OrangeLaunchRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just personally sick of these people going, are you a rock star?
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Certainly violence being advertised.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really think that in the end it shouldn't be the responsibility of the video game company to censor their product.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, I do think they should make sure that the consumer is fully aware of the product that they're purchasing.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can agree with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's talk about... The only hot coffee I ever want to see is the kind I get at Starbucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, that re-release without the coffee mod, it will be coming out next week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Which I suppose, as a little footnote to the story, look how long it took for that patch to come out.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's how long this game would have been delayed if they'd gone back and done what they should have done.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just food for thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Murder in China based on a MMORPG.
[SPEAKER_07]: According to the Beijing Morning Post, a young woman has been charged with murdering her fianc for, quote, too much time playing online games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: No more online games for the Chinese.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_07]: The woman in question apparently got fed up with her unemployed fianc for spending more time online than looking for a job so he could pay for the wedding.
[SPEAKER_07]: So on August 6th, allegedly, she did the deed.
[SPEAKER_01]: and he wasn't getting off his ass looking for a job.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actually, we did spend a year like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then again, we had the money in the bank to afford it.
[SPEAKER_01]: We could afford for him to not work.
[SPEAKER_01]: However, had that money not been there and I was having to support him or he was just sitting on his ass, I'd have left him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shit yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's because I have a brain in my head and I use it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, it's just interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of dumping his ass, she shot him.
[SPEAKER_07]: or whatever she did.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't say.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Either way, you're without him, you know, and now you've got to deal with finding a date when you get out of the prison, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Only they were playing more of the hot coffee mod.
[SPEAKER_06]: They would have learned that they can solve their problems by having... Stop.
[SPEAKER_01]: We said no more hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hot coffee talk is banned from the podcast.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to make a game called Hot Coffee.
[SPEAKER_07]: More than ever, we need some of DarkSakura's advice column.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because if we stayed inside and played video games all day long, we'd have no time to get murdered by our fiancs.
[SPEAKER_07]: So DarkSakura has her advice column for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: And DarkSakura, what are you going to be telling us about tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: Today's bit of advice is how to drown your co-host in hot coffee.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_01]: How to escape from a car hanging over the edge of a cliff.
[SPEAKER_01]: 1.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do not shift your weight or make any sudden movements.
2.
[SPEAKER_01]: If the front doors are still over land, use these doors to make your escape regardless of which way your car is facing.
3.
[SPEAKER_01]: If the front doors are over the edge, proceed slowly to the rear of the car.
4.
[SPEAKER_01]: Reassess your situation and make your escape.
[SPEAKER_01]: Will opening the rear doors cause the car to slide?
[SPEAKER_01]: If not, open them slowly and get out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise, use a steering wheel lock or screwdriver to break the window and climb out as quickly as possible.
[SPEAKER_01]: But my final piece of advice?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: I have two, actually.
[SPEAKER_01]: Either don't pull a Thelma and Louise or make sure that you have one of those drag strip parachutes attached to the back of your car so at least when you land, it'll be softer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or how about don't drive off cliffs?
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be my advice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't drive off cliffs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't drive anywhere but in Colorado.
[SPEAKER_01]: What?
[SPEAKER_01]: Flatland.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't talk on your cell phone while driving.
[SPEAKER_07]: Colorado has the Rockies.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm talking about the flat part.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of hard to drive your car up a mountain.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's cliffs on a mountain.
[SPEAKER_07]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The only cliffs I care about are Cliff Notes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo is going to be moving into the mobile phone market.
[SPEAKER_07]: No games just yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: No cell phone Mario, no cell phone Zelda.
[SPEAKER_07]: However, on October 17th, Nintendo Mobile will be providing subscribers with video game related content such as wallpapers, ringtones, and sound effects from the Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: series.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, one thing I should note, this is in Japan only.
[SPEAKER_06]: Durr.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I told you that.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but they actually are going to be porting over the classic games from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple puzzle games are okay.
[SPEAKER_00]: I liked that Before Crisis game.
[SPEAKER_00]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_00]: The Final Fantasy Before Crisis.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think even Before Crisis is going to suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would only be good if they re-released it to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cell phone is not the place to be gaming because at least on my phone most of the games are Java based and it's slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: A puzzle game works okay but not a fast paced puzzle game like Tetris even sucks.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen better games on a freaking
[SPEAKER_07]: Graphing Calculator I've seen better games on the Apple 2E Loadrunner, Kicks Oregon Trail, yo Loki, what's going on in the hack and crack world?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the group We Are Back is still teasing the fact that they're going to be releasing a downgrader and this will downgrade everything from 2.0 on to back to 1 and that's going to be it right there Homebrew is going to be loud for everybody and yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyways, so that's what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're also having some homebrew contests for PSP games, which is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So they have some entries for that that are actually, they're kind of plugging on PSP updates.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of them look pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also a program was released the other day actually that you can change the little intro video on, you know, have the little small clip that plays when you turn on your PSP or play a game or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can change that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they have a demonstration on there on how to do that as well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you can customize your PSP a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_06]: And other than that, really not too much else going on with the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I should also say... Oh, one more thing I almost forgot.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're actually releasing another emulator, of course, coming out.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that one was for... Oh, what was it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, enough of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other than that, lots of homebrew stuff coming out for the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, the DS isn't to be forgotten.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, we'll just have to wait for the downgrader.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're still saying a couple more weeks.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then the shit will hit the fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple last stories here for tonight's.
[SPEAKER_07]: Civilization 4 is going to be doing a little pre-order program A special limited edition collector's package, which has collector's packaging A CD soundtrack of the game, a keyboard template, a tech map, and a spiral-bound version of the manual So that's just a special pre-order edition Civilization 4, of course, coming out this October I'm interested in it I love, love, love, love, love, love, love the original Civilization game
[SPEAKER_07]: Never really got into Civ 2 or 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they just got too complex for me at that point or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked it simple.
[SPEAKER_07]: Simple graphics, simple mechanics to the game and everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the first one's my favorite.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I am very curious about 4 and I'll definitely give it a try.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm certainly wanting to see what they've done with the series since 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mega Man is going to be making an appearance at the Tokyo Game Show in Capcom's booth.
[SPEAKER_07]: The interesting thing is that the game is called Rockman Rockman, which would be Mega Man Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which game now?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's called Rockman Rockman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it's a remake of the first Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I was going to get to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: It happens to be it's going to be a remake of the original Mega Man game is the rumor about what it's going to be.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we don't know exactly what system it's going to be on, but they're saying PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they actually have the site has launched for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't know that part.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, the site has launched for it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let me see if I can pull it up here to see what the site was.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks really interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mega Man's very, it's very cartoony, unlike the original Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_06]: His head is ginormous, which I don't know why they did it that way, but it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can actually make your own levels on it, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, you can make your own levels?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it has a level editor built into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's coming out for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can't remember the website, but I'll find it out while we're talking and I'll let you guys know.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're almost at the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: I only got one more story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll be hurry.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll hurry.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last story here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We always seem to talk about these video games that are being turned into movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: MTV, hooray, hooray, bought the film rights.
[SPEAKER_07]: I said that with a little bit of sarcasm, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Midway's The Suffering Executive Vice President of MTV Films David Gale
[SPEAKER_07]: It makes perfect sense for us to work with Midway, Stan Winston, and Circle of Confusion on bringing the suffering to life as a feature film.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's why I think it's interesting that it says gaming is such a huge part of the culture for MTV's audience when I can't think of many gaming shows that MTV has aired.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe a special here and there, and a category on their video music awards, but not really a huge part of the network.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then again, music videos aren't a huge part of the network either.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're referring to their audience themselves.
[SPEAKER_07]: I suppose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we'll see when we get some stars and directors attached, but all we know for now is that MTV is producing them.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not necessarily a bad thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: MTV, even though I'm knocking on them a little bit, they've actually put out some pretty good films.
[SPEAKER_07]: Election, from a couple years ago, is one of my favorite movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And MTV was actually behind that, so go figure.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one that I like that's coming out pretty soon was Roll Balance.
[SPEAKER_06]: Looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weren't they behind Napoleon Dynamite, too?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even though that movie kind of...
[SPEAKER_07]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy birthday to me.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, happy birthday to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for your birthday, I had Final Fantasy VII Advent Children leaked to the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I forgot to mention that.
[SPEAKER_06]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, have a good night, or day, or afternoon, whenever you happen to be listening to this, everybody.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good time, have a gay old time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki wants you to have a gay old time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on that note, goodbye.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next update.