[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, week of September 19th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_00]: You're tuned in to the Orange Lounge Radio To Go Edition, your podcast home for all the latest video game news and gamer chat.
[SPEAKER_00]: Now, here are your hosts, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hello, everybody, once again, and welcome to Orange Lounge Radio To Go, a radio dedicated to what gamers really want to know.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know that little bastard on...
[SPEAKER_04]: What was that site?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not going to name it.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I just have to say that I've probably been gaming since that little newbie wannabe was in diapers.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was sitting there with my Pong machine back in the day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am more the gamer than you will ever hope to be.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had to address it and get it out of my system.
[SPEAKER_01]: Feel better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I actually do feel a lot better.
[SPEAKER_04]: But that's also proof that I'm anything but giggly and ditzy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: She's a real bitch, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_01]: I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: I really am.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_01]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm doing good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Who also is a really big bitch, if you get to know him.
[SPEAKER_01]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: No, forget it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_01]: Not much.
[SPEAKER_01]: What the hell is this you're looking at?
[SPEAKER_01]: Is this like Deer Hunter on the Xbox 360 or something?
[SPEAKER_01]: What is this screenshot you've got?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, that's a screenshot of Elder Scrolls 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a Deer Hunter game to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It looks like the deer from the deer scene in Ring 2, which sucked.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know, they will come out with a Deer Hunter game, I'm sure, for that game.
[SPEAKER_01]: For the Walmart arcades across America.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you ever noticed that every Walmart arcade, quote unquote, you've ever walked into, has some type of deer hunting machine, at least around here.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's always some type of deer hunting machine and a crane.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I know you've been doing a lot of giggling and having all those slumber parties and talking about boys, but if you actually had any time to play some games, what were you able to find?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I don't know, out of the 40-something video game systems that I own, have I not been able to find something to play?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, seriously, I've been playing my Nintendogs, trying to keep them from running away and pissing on my dinner.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's such a girl game!
[SPEAKER_04]: You play it too, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And so does Loki over here, who owns three copies of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm thinking of selling two of them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give me one.
[SPEAKER_02]: No!
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright, so Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I didn't tell those.
[SPEAKER_04]: Puppies!
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing with my puppies, and then I got World of Warcraft and installed it today.
[SPEAKER_01]: Finally!
[SPEAKER_01]: Like a year later, one of us gets sucked into World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not quite sucked in.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sort of pissed off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually really livid for the lack of controller option.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I can play on the keyboard, but the controller is so much more efficient.
[SPEAKER_04]: Especially since I got used to playing that way on that game that sucks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is the game I still play, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's my opinion on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: WarpGH.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: For the people who say, warp me to here, warp me to here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wanted a priest with only the gas time warp.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that if they say, warp me to Christmas place.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, 5% of our audience has probably ever played Ragnarok and guessed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Warp me to Ludi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gas time's like the haunted place where big horrible things kill you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was level 70-something and I still couldn't beat everything there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_04]: I played that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I played actually a few online games.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing something on gorillas.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've been playing Frogas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's things you can do on the site and collect items and do certain things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And one of the things is you collect this potion that you go up to Noodle's room and insert into Sean Ryder's head.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to get the last potion, you have to play Frogger.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's like you go there, get the potion, and come back.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's like horrible.
[SPEAKER_01]: Silly flash games.
[SPEAKER_04]: Silly flash games, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dan also picked up Nightshade and Ico because they got really cheap and he gets a discount in the store.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he picked up whatever that Burnout game is on PSP and has been playing it religiously.
[SPEAKER_01]: Burnout Legends, as I'm sure Loki will talk about a little bit earlier.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, the more I hear Burnout, the more pissed off I get because I was trying to do my fucking illustrator homework on Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_04]: and not Saturday night, I'm sorry, on Friday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he comes in, him and his buddy playing Burnout as loud as our 50-inch widescreen TV would go.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was PMS and hardcore that night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went out there, let him have it, ate a bunch of chocolate and went to bed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: So right now that game is on my shit list.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I was going to recommend for World of Warcraft, check out some of the communities out there because I bet you somebody's got a mod out there.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can't be the only one who desires to play controllers.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's got to be something going on out there, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can mod pretty much everything in World of Warcraft using Lua.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the interfaces.
[SPEAKER_02]: Someone actually created an auction interface where it will tell you what the item that you're trying to sell is going for, what the previous history is, and what they think that you can get for it and that type of stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, Loki, what have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been playing Burnout Revenge.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that game is awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first thing we did, started playing Traffic Attack because there's nothing like driving 209 miles an hour
[SPEAKER_02]: and smashing into every single car in the world on this, you know, freaking track and just having them fly over you like a wake of water.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just, it's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the most fun ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the takedown mode, when you're playing that, you can actually use the crash breaker, which makes your car explode.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's really fun as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only complaint I have about it is the new way that they're doing the crash mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have this kind of, it's almost like
[SPEAKER_02]: Golf Games Golf Games Golf Games Golf Games Golf Games
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really strange how they've done that, and I didn't quite get it at first, so I made my car explode or stall and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But other than that, it's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just can't wait to unlock more cars, because it's been pretty tough to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then Burnout Legends, I've been playing that for the PSP, and that game's fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing that sucks about that game is that game forces you to play with other people, because in order to unlock all the cars, there's six cars that are...
[SPEAKER_02]: for each game, and you have to actually go play other people with those cars.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's almost like Nintendogs, is what they're doing with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just racing games.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just burnout, burnout, burnout, all week long.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm going to try to pick... I have Urban Rain.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should try to play that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of a fighting game, but beat-em-up game at the same time.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like Tekken.
[SPEAKER_02]: It actually has Paul Phoenix and Law in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: From the Tekken series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, had I known that when I was selling it, I probably would have sold it a bit better, but oh well.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_01]: What have I been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: I had a seven-hour marathon of Final Fantasy XI this weekend.
[SPEAKER_01]: Never again will I play an MMO for that long.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it was one of those things where it was like there was a mission and we all wanted to get it done.
[SPEAKER_01]: And on top of that, I'd already been leveling.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was like I really had a lazy Saturday in every essence of the word.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so I'm sure some MMO addicts out there, they're cheering me on right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: But my God, that was just too much MMO for me on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't played Final Fantasy XI for a long time.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have enough PTO where I can take a couple days off.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else did I play?
[SPEAKER_01]: I got to check out a couple new games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually went out and bought a copy of Mortal Kombat Shaolin Monks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Deception Deception Deception Deception
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Remember when they tried to do that, was it that side-scrolling RPG type game with Sub-Zero in it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was awful.
[SPEAKER_01]: The Mythologies games were awful.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, but this one is surprisingly pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's pretty action-based.
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, the best comparison I can think of is the Ninja Turtles arcade game, except it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Mortal Kombat characters and you're just beating people up left and right and you can do all these fancy combos.
[SPEAKER_01]: And as you gain experience, you can purchase new combos and new things.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's actually a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: My only minor complaints with Shaolin Monks is that there's just some real basic...
[SPEAKER_01]: Gameplay mechanic things that don't work for me, such as the fatalities.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the fatalities are kind of fun and it's kind of cute they put them in there, but unfortunately you only get one fatality in the beginning and I don't know if I'm doing something wrong, but I've been playing the game for a couple hours now and I just got like a new fatality called a multi-ality or something like that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, they're supposed to be looking in the list of blank fatalities, like 20 different things you can do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess I haven't found any yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe I'm supposed to find them myself.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I get kind of bored with the fatality thing because I'm doing the same thing over and over.
[SPEAKER_01]: Slice, slice, slice, you know, with the hat because I'm playing as Kung Lao right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm doing the hat slice in half.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's cute at first and really funny and, you know, graphically well done.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it gets old.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think if the fatality combo meter filled maybe like half as fast, see, the fatality thing you only did half as often, I think it would have been better.
[SPEAKER_01]: It seems like the fatality thing gets really repetitive.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: and so I kind of wish that at some point the enemies went away and left you alone for a little while so you could kind of figure out, okay, where do I go next?
[SPEAKER_01]: And then new enemies come out.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it kind of got a little monotonous there.
[SPEAKER_01]: And then my only other complaint would be the lack of save points.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can literally go 45 minutes in the game and not find a single save point.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there really needed to be about twice as many save points as there are.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that was a little bit frustrating.
[SPEAKER_01]: Otherwise, though, those are just, you know, really in the grand scope of things, some minor complaints.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think the game is a heck of a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you're a fan of Mortal Kombat...
[SPEAKER_01]: in any way, you're going to like this game because it really gets into the story better so than any of the movies ever did.
[SPEAKER_01]: It really gets into the story and it does a great job.
[SPEAKER_03]: Movies?
[SPEAKER_03]: There was only one movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was two.
[SPEAKER_01]: There was only one movie.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know you're denying the existence of it, but believe it or not, there was a second movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's an hour and a half of my life I want back.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was so good that they actually made a TV series too.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right, huh?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, just to put it in perspective, just how cool this game can be sometimes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I was playing this one level, the last level I was on, I was fighting Katana, Jade, and Mileena all at once, like this level.
[SPEAKER_01]: And suddenly Katana, I don't want to spoil the story, but something happens where Katana's taken out of the picture, basically.
[SPEAKER_01]: and then it's just Jade and Mileena and you can like throw them into these traps and then hit this switch and it goes into the test your might mode from like Mortal Kombat 1 where you have to really slam all the buttons they kind of overdo that a little bit in the game but it's still really cute that they brought back test your might and like if you do the test your might thing then you'll like set a fire trap so you can set Mileena on fire a little bit just cute little things like that I can't believe I called it cute but seriously like little things like that Mortal Kombat's so cute it's not cute anymore there's no babalities
[SPEAKER_01]: or Animalities.
[SPEAKER_01]: Friendship!
[SPEAKER_01]: So Mortal Kombat, I recommend it to fans of the Mortal Kombat series.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just if you like those action fighting style games, you'll probably get a kick out of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if it doesn't sound like your kind of game, you're probably not going to like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what else?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that did get released earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was scheduled originally for the 21st.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got another fighting game coming out that looks pretty good.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually played a demo of it, Marvel Nemesis Rise of the Imperfects, which is a Marvel game they actually kind of
[SPEAKER_02]: and DarkSakura.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really quick, the other game I played this week I want to give a real quick review to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I actually got to play We Heart Katamari because as you might have heard on last week's show, Target, some of the Target stores acquired copies of the game and sold them early because the game's not actually out until this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: So We Heart Katamari is going to be on shelves this week.
[SPEAKER_01]: I did get a chance to play it via one of my friends.
[SPEAKER_01]: I only got to play like the first two levels.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I'm telling you what, kids, if you liked the first Katamari Damacy, you ain't going to be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_01]: The movies are just as quirky as they were the first time.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of like the first game was so successful, they gave them a bigger budget to go through with the second game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you really see that they've kind of put more into this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: And just, you know, it's more the same, but at the same time,
[SPEAKER_01]: It just works.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know how else to explain it.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you were a fan of the first game, you're going to like this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: If you weren't a fan of the first game, I don't think there's anything new here that's going to win you over.
[SPEAKER_01]: But if you haven't played the Katamari Damacy game, check this out.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's just such a quirky little title.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think you guys will get a kick out of it.
[SPEAKER_01]: The music, not quite as solid as the first game, but the music's a lot of fun too.
[SPEAKER_01]: And the script, the writing is just as hilarious as it was in the first game.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Katamari fans won't be disappointed.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Nintendo nunchucks or something where you've got like the one little piece with the analog stick and then a remote control?
[SPEAKER_01]: What's up with this?
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you guys think of this?
[SPEAKER_01]: You can check the pictures out on our website, orangelawnradio.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: This technically goes into another segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, one of our listeners emailed us, Brittany, who basically agreed with me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like using a big freaking remote control.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now Nintendo says, and I think part of the reason they're doing this is that they want to kind of lure in people that are a little scared of, you know, when they see like a gaming controller, they think, oh, it's a
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a gaming thing, and I'm not really hip on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, like, by making a remote control device, you know, everybody uses a remote control.
[SPEAKER_04]: They tried this before, sort of, with a system called the Fairchild Channel app.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: With a little, tiny little controller to tap in the little old stick that you hold.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little different, but that controller sucked.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole system sucked, honestly.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, do you think the revolution's gonna suck?
[SPEAKER_01]: This controller?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, the one thing that I say about a system...
[SPEAKER_04]: A system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_04]: But part of the game is how it's controlled.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a major part of the gameplay, right there, is how you're controlling it.
[SPEAKER_04]: This thing looks uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lately, my whole big thing has been ergonomics.
[SPEAKER_04]: And like I said on our three-hour show, this one looks highly uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be holding your wrist...
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, take your hand, hold it straight up, turn your wrist sideways and do like you're holding a remote control.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now imagine holding your hand in this position for an hour, two hours, however long you plan on playing a game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now do you think that that's a natural position for your hand to be in?
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine the stress you're putting your joints under.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now imagine if you are an older gamer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You work at, say, a desk job on a computer.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're already putting your arm through stress that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine the stress you're putting it through with this system that's supposed to help you relax, have some fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to be hurting.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think it's going to cause, you know, true medical issues.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think, though, that this will come out in the testing process?
[SPEAKER_01]: For instance, something I had brought up on our three-hour program when we were talking about this, the three-hour show, Sunday nights on OrangeOnlineRadio.com,
[SPEAKER_01]: We were talking about this controller issue a little bit, and I mentioned that the DS at E3, the year that the DS came out, it changed from E3 to when it actually came out, and you said it's a little more comfortable than it was at E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: So do you think that maybe after they test this a little bit, if they find these type of ergonomic issues with their testers, they might change this a little bit?
[SPEAKER_01]: Make it, I don't know how they can drastically, without making drastic changes to the controller, make it a little more ergonomic, but maybe just the way the games play?
[SPEAKER_04]: One would hope so.
[SPEAKER_04]: One would really hope so.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: But don't knock it until you've tried it, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I'll give it a fair go, but honestly, I'll get that little wave bird looking thingy that Loki posted about.
[SPEAKER_01]: Now, what was that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_01]: You posted like a mock-up on our website.
[SPEAKER_01]: Was this a real deal picture or a mock-up?
[SPEAKER_01]: A lot of our feedback is a mock-up of a wave bird controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's something that they...
[SPEAKER_02]: Was it the president of Nintendo's development or something like that?
[SPEAKER_02]: They were talking about how they were going to be adding that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just they're going to have a ton of attachments, which means more stuff you've got to buy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm not saying that the other systems aren't doing that either, Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it looks good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it'll work really well, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think it's going to be a problem at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, you hold controllers in your hand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just like a remote.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if it's light enough, it's not going to be a problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: I find remote controls uncomfortable.
[SPEAKER_01]: The thing I like about it, though, is that you can take that remote control, turn it 90 degrees, and you've basically got an old-style NES controller.
[SPEAKER_01]: And that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be more comfortable, but I'm thinking, though, the intended way, like a remote control.
[SPEAKER_01]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I know this from experience, because I played Space Ace on my DVD player.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I hurt by the time I was done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know how this is going to feel and it's not natural.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you think maybe we're being misled by these pictures a little bit that are showing it?
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe this won't be the way it actually plays because I can't see how with your thumb you'd be able to hit that control pad and the button.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you guys seen the video of this?
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't have time to download it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you guys seen the video from Tokyo Game Show?
[SPEAKER_02]: Describe it for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for example, the way it was shown, this is the video they showed everybody when they were unveiling it, is it actually looks like it's from the view that you're in the TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: and basically you're using that as you're not using the buttons on the controller the controller itself because it acts like a 3D mouse is what you're using so for example some of the things that they're showing you could say this might be the next WarioWare game
[SPEAKER_02]: A guy was chopping using the controller, acting like a knife, and frying stuff with like a knife.
[SPEAKER_01]: I had heard, now I had read that there was a video out there, the Metroid Prime 2 Echo is being kind of played on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they said it.
[SPEAKER_01]: As moving around using the Bluetooth or whatever it is that's in there that senses where you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the way it works is there's two sensors you put on your TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it basically figures out, it triangulates where your controller is going to be.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of similar to the Power Glove that came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, the other things that they showed with this is playing tennis, you know, like, you know, you would be just like racket fishing.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: And there you go, you're shooting something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you want to switch your weapon, you know, hit the button on top there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Plus, the analog has two buttons on it as well, two trigger buttons.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, really, there's no way it can't work, because if a game calls for something else, they'll build another add-on for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: As they always do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it'll be interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure we'll see more and more of this leading up to next year's E3, which I'm sure will be a big, big unveil.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's the other thing, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: Check that out.
[SPEAKER_01]: Answer it.
[SPEAKER_01]: What do you think of the Nintendo Revolution controller?
[SPEAKER_02]: Now the real question is, what color Nintendo Revolution are you going to buy?
[SPEAKER_02]: The green one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they have the green, red, the gray, the chrome, white, and black.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're going to have the red.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also on our main page, we definitely want to take a minute to recognize this.
[SPEAKER_01]: There is a banner right there for a fundraiser effort we're doing for Hurricane Katrina relief.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's not just us.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're doing it together with some other companies in Sacramento, Dark Records and Club 21 slash Rapture.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's a fundraiser for Hurricane Katrina.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_01]: if you're in the Sacramento area where our show is based there's a lot you can do to help out with this because you can actually donate at Club 21 on Thursday nights even if you're anywhere in the world we are taking financial donations and if you'd like it to be specifically for to be forwarded to the SPCA for pet relief note that and we'll collect all that money together and send it on behalf of Orange Lounge Radio so check that out
[SPEAKER_04]: We did mention that we are working with Dark Records and Club 21.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, moving on into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Obviously a lot of news coming from the Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Metal Gear Solid 4, Guns of the Patriots is the title.
[SPEAKER_01]: Eight minute long preview for this game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you check it out?
[SPEAKER_01]: I checked it out.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did you think?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Snake is quite old.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, so it's going to be like a future thing now.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, you know what I thought was the coolest thing was the little mini Metal Gear with Otakon on it that they took right out of Policenauts.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was freaking cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's definitely something to look forward to.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sure a lot of fans are looking forward to the Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was reading, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: A lot of people were thinking, oh, it's pre-rendered.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were saying, though, that they actually... What was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kojima...
[SPEAKER_02]: They showed that the actual presentation was actually being rendered real time and they stopped it and panned around Snake as well to stop those disbelievers from posting crap about it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Looks good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Speaking of Kojima, he basically said that Metal Gear Solid 4 will be his last.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I kind of think, didn't he say the same thing after Metal Gear Solid 3?
[SPEAKER_01]: That he was going to do another one?
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Hulk Hogan syndrome here.
[SPEAKER_04]: The man keeps saying he's going to retire, but he always shows up at WrestleMania.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, he also, now Kojima also says that Yoji Shinkawa, who's the art director, will be leaving with him.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_01]: Which also, by the way, was kind of a bad movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but that wasn't really Metal Gear.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even think he acknowledges it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because there was actually a Metal Gear 2 on the MSX in Japan.
[SPEAKER_01]: His direct quote was, I decided to make the real sequel to Metal Gear when he saw Snake's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, also coming out of Tokyo Game Show, those of you music game fans are going to be very pleased to hear that Konami, after a long hiatus, is going to be putting out brand new Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania games.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gita Dora, as the series is sometimes referred to, is getting the V games released.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't know quite yet if it's a combo game, but since we know that all the previous PlayStation 2 releases, which ended at Guitar Freak's fourth mix and Drum Mania's third mix, were combined together.
[SPEAKER_01]: To put this into some perspective for you guys, Guitar Freak's V, I think is what, the 11th or 12th?
[SPEAKER_01]: I lost count.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's like the 12th?
[SPEAKER_01]: something like that guitar freaks in the arcade and the last one we got on PS2 was 4 so there's a whole lot of ground to cover here with these new games that are coming out on the PS2 gonna come out in 2006 in Japan no word yet if the series will finally make a crossover into America but I think what might make or break that would be Konami if they watch the success of Guitar Hero which is what Red Octane and Harmonix are gonna be putting out pretty soon I believe before the end of the year
[SPEAKER_01]: so it'll be interesting to see if that does very well then Konami might try to take back the market that they kind of created overseas interesting way it works out there they'll take notice
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, wanting to point out some Final Fantasy news from Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: Final Fantasy XI will definitely be expanding.
[SPEAKER_01]: Treasures of At-Organ was announced officially, the new expansion pack, to be released with the Xbox 360, assumably, version of Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_01]: Some early preview videos are hinting that Blue Mage will be one of the new classes, because in the video you could see—and this is one of the videos I did download, of course—
[SPEAKER_01]: You can actually see, I think it was a human was breathing fire in one of the videos and like a Taro was shooting spider web using one of the spider's attacks.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pretty neat looking artifact armor for Blue Mage 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: Also, there's another mystery kind of job class.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not quite sure what it is, but it looks like there's another job class in there too.
[SPEAKER_04]: All you have to do is look to Tactics for your ideas.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep, look to Tactics for ideas.
[SPEAKER_01]: I thought that Alchemist or Geomancer would be for sure, because I especially thought Geomancer with all the elemental focus and stuff, but it doesn't look like that's the new class.
[SPEAKER_04]: World of Warcraft has that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, but... Blue Mage would be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: but you know there's gonna yeah everybody's gonna be a blue mage all right so we will see um we don't have any details as to when these games are coming out but we're thinking i'm thinking anyway probably early 2006 i would say it would be a good guesstimate also final fantasy related now jamie this has to be a final fantasy game that you like because if not you're just not human final fantasy 4 will be coming out for now you smiled there you like final fantasy 4 right
[SPEAKER_04]: Final Fantasy 4 is coming out for the Game Boy Advance.
[SPEAKER_01]: Final Fantasy 4 is being ported to the Game Boy Advance in Japan on December 12th.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will include new areas and get this, new characters.
[SPEAKER_01]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should be interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: My gut reaction tells me, oh my gosh, Palamonporum.
[SPEAKER_01]: Finally, we'll be able to be unstoned and rejoin your party.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that would be the perfect, the biggest fan pleaser that Square could do.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know it's cheesy, but what a fan pleaser.
[SPEAKER_01]: More Spoonie Bartness!
[SPEAKER_01]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_01]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that should be cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: No word yet if it's coming out in America, but Final Fantasy's pretty big here now, and they put out all the other...
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: I do indeedy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, if you have letters, send it to our mailbag, togo, T-O-G-O, at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: We love getting your feedback.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, who wrote us today?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sasuke sent us an email, a question we've been asked many, many times, actually just very recently tonight, about how we got our name.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because he was talking about Orange Lounge, you know, the group, doing Mobomoga, all the Bimani stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were sitting on the BART one day, saying, you know, damn it, we want to do an internet radio station.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which is a train in the Bay Area, for those who don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: The Bay Area Rapid Transit.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we just came up with the name, because our three-hour show was Bibani-related, and that's how we started off.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_01]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Orange Lounge was just kind of like, you know, you like something, you name yourself after something related to it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So we thought lounge because we kind of lounge around and have that whole Denny's vibe of just sitting around coffee and just talking about random stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's kind of what we do.
[SPEAKER_01]: So Orange Lounge just seemed appropriate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Got an email from one of our long-time listeners, Asian Buddy Paul.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Said, I'd just like to say how much I love the podcast.
[SPEAKER_04]: I used to listen to the live show Sundays, but I can't catch them anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tear.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I love it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he just got married on his Ragnarok online private server, so congratulations, I think.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, nerd.
[SPEAKER_01]: You nerd.
[SPEAKER_01]: You got married in an online game, you nerd.
[SPEAKER_04]: He was wanting us to play one of our cage match winning songs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, the Cage Match we do as part of the three-hour show when we play random music.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'd actually answered back saying, you know, sort of separate this, that, and the other.
[SPEAKER_01]: You run into all those licensing problems because our live station is run through Live 365, which pays a lot of licensing fees up front.
[SPEAKER_01]: When it comes to podcasts, can you play copyrighted music in podcasts?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of a big question mark right now because, you know, it's...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's kind of a gray area, so we don't do it on this.
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw this link.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_01]: So this is Dance Dance Revolution, except it's all Christian music.
[SPEAKER_01]: DDR God version.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's the, like they took a bunch of Christian music labels and put it together.
[SPEAKER_01]: Made their own version of DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, looking at this now, because for a moment I was thinking, oh, DDR, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it does reverse scrolling.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's kind of... Well, they have to change it a little bit, or they might get sued by Konami, just like, you know, the folks who made In the Groove got sued.
[SPEAKER_04]: Honestly, it shows them freaking playing on Konami dance pads.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a damn Stepmania version.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Stepmania, is all it is.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's Stepmania.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_01]: But, you know, if that's what you're looking for in a dance game, I go for it, but I don't see this being the next big thing in dance games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I chalk this right up there with other classic...
[SPEAKER_01]: Video games made for retail sales in Christian bookstores.
[SPEAKER_01]: It makes me think of the Bible Trivia Game.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like Bible Trivia Game and Noah's Ark.
[SPEAKER_04]: Remember the old DDR parody that had the cross-shaped controller that had the two down arrows?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I forgot what that was, but that was... Dance, Dance Resurrection.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to talk about another bad game?
[SPEAKER_02]: They have the Friends Trivia Game we've got to sell.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think I saw that for sale somewhere.
[SPEAKER_01]: I heard about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Although she had nothing to do with friends.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Her character, not Fran Drescher, but the character in it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the one who was the girlfriend?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I can't remember her name.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't watch the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one who had the really annoying one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_01]: Seriously, our listeners are going to write hate mail for that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, I gotta answer it, so I better not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anyway, if that's what you're looking for in a dance game, go for it, but I don't think the quality of the game, since, let's face it, it is being put out by a much, much, much, much, much smaller company, I don't think it's gonna be that smooth a game, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have fun.
[SPEAKER_01]: Any other emails?
[SPEAKER_04]: Other than the one I mentioned about the controller, but we've addressed that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cool deal.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, well, send us more mail.
[SPEAKER_01]: We like getting mail.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, we do.
[SPEAKER_01]: Send Jamie some email about how much you love her giggling.
[SPEAKER_01]: Her incessant giggling on this program.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am not a giggler.
[SPEAKER_01]: To go at OrangeLoungeRadio.com I'm giggling now because I keep calling you a giggler.
[SPEAKER_04]: I did find something cool internet related though.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, what's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Just a really short thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: For folks like me who like to use Firefox, there's a skin for it called Pimpzilla.
[SPEAKER_04]: that makes your top toolbar all fuzzy and then the background behind your tab is all leopard print.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just thought that people... Where can they download that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Can we put a link on our site somewhere?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll hunt it down again.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the font and all the buttons and everything look like they're straight out of Grand Theft Auto San Andreas.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're all bling-shaped and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: Cute.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let's get into some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: One thing we mentioned earlier in the program was Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Boku no Watashi no Katamari Damashii
[SPEAKER_01]: Somebody told me it turns into My My Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: Read the title again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Boku no Watashi no Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, My My Katamari.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, whatever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boku no is like boy saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Atashi no is like girl saying.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it sounds like it's little boys and girls saying are Katamari.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not a whole lot known about this game just yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Wi-Fi support, though, is rumored to be in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Branching storylines like night and day.
[SPEAKER_01]: and other kind of modes like that are going to be in it.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that would be kind of cool to see.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's being shown at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't hear if it was playable or not.
[SPEAKER_01]: I just know it's being shown.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was playable?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, there's actually people saying that the controls sucked on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_01]: You know it can't be that great.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, because you can't do dual analog, so what it is is it's the directional button and the four buttons are the two sticks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew it would be like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: That kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the person that was looking at it was saying that they hoped that it would have been like the analog and turning with the shoulder buttons, which would be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is, from what I remember on the plot for it, is that apparently there's some island that's in trouble that has animals on it or whatever, and you have to, you arrive there on a boat or something, and you have to save the animals or something by absorbing them.
[SPEAKER_01]: By rolling them over?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, but that was what I had heard, and it was pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm all for Katamari coming to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright, one other PSP story I definitely want to make sure we cover at some point, also being shown at the Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: You guys know that Suikoden 1 and 2, there are an absolute bitch to find.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you could be paying like $100 for a copy of Suikoden 2 on eBay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_01]: They are both coming out again, together on the PSP, this being announced at Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, Suikoden fans, if you've been dying to play Suikoden 2 for a while, you just can't seem to get a copy of it,
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be coming out for the PSP along with Suikoden 1.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's going to be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: No estimated release on this, but probably not until next year at some point.
[SPEAKER_01]: Again, this is only Japan so far, but heck, why not?
[SPEAKER_01]: Should come out over here too, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just a little bit of translation, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, you got some gaming news for us?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm sorry, was something going on in the hack and crack scene?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, a couple things actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: The first being that the rumored...
[SPEAKER_02]: Team Extender, they're actually creating this video out for the PSP so you can watch your UMDs and everything on normal TV and they had a demo of it what this thing does and it looks like it's a whole case replace of it, you basically unscrew the case and pop this sucker on it has actually a port to plug in a DualShock controller so you can use that as the controller and then play your games on the TV that way
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_04]: And this was even just last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I had gone back after my trip to Ikea and stopped by to see Dan at GameStop.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I was saying, they should make a TV tuner for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, wasn't it rumored that PS3 was going to have a UMD slot in it?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was sort of a rumor, but I don't think it's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what everyone was speculating.
[SPEAKER_02]: It should.
[SPEAKER_01]: It should.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would make sense, but no.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, think about it, though, especially with the success that they've been having with the movies, which is kind of odd to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I understand why they put movies on PSP, but I don't see why it's so successful.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would make perfect sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because then Sony could really compete with DVD, but they would have their own version.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it would be very smart to put it in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because then they can have it, okay, you know, you can... If you buy this version of the movie, not only will you be able to play it on your TV, but you can also take it on the go with you.
[SPEAKER_01]: It would be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be smart, but I don't think you're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, yeah, so this thing is actually being, um, I guess beta right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're working out the kinks in it, but, um, from the screenshots I've seen, it looks good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have selectable, um, widescreen and pan and scan, you know, if you want to, like, fill your whole TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, it should be cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, um... Resolution issues?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think so, but, um, of course it'll stretch it if, you know, you try to take it out of widescreen.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, you know, hey, I'm all for modding my PSP, so...
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm concerned about resolution when you get into larger high definition formats.
[SPEAKER_01]: And how about support for widescreen TVs, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, here's what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, if you want to get to the nitty gritty of this, the PSP already has a video out on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the USB.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when you're playing your games, the USB acts like a video out.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you're very interested in trying to make one, you probably could.
[SPEAKER_02]: All this thing is, is just adding some more support.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, really, that USB port can be exploited to a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyways, so other than this... You said the term nitty-gritty.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, and I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I instantly started thinking nitty-gritty derpy.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other thing, I was going to say, was it... This site, P6, who's doing this kind of a new...
[SPEAKER_02]: No, Graphic User Interface for the PSP, which looks pretty sexy, but still working out the kinks on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually have a tutorial here on how to, if you really want to mod your PSP, you can change all the menus what their titles are.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can make it UMD as in movie player, or you're
[SPEAKER_02]: system settings as I fucked your mom or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can do whatever you want and there's a tutorial on their site and that's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a link on PSP updates for that and on our site as well once we put it on there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And yeah, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's some really cool Tetris game that came out called Hack and you should check that out too.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: The link we'll have on our page as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dark Sakura, what kind of gaming news do you have for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got a couple things.
[SPEAKER_04]: About Final Fantasy, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dirge of Aseribus.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Been trying to hunt down a release date, because I want my hot Vincent action.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's speculated the date tentative in Japan is sometime in 2005.
[SPEAKER_04]: No US release date yet.
[SPEAKER_01]: Which means next summer.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: but you know with every Final Fantasy game that's practically ever been out except for like what 4 when it came out we're going to get more stuff and they're going to release an international version and they're going to get more stuff and I'm going to have to import it and it's going to of course be in English so they better have someone hot do Vincent's voice anyway could you imagine great now I can't remember his name Boreanaz David Boreanaz doing Vincent's voice he's too busy doing Squall in Kingdom Hearts
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: The Deep Ground Soldiers, who go underground after the meteor incident.
[SPEAKER_04]: We all played Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a Sahagin, Gargoyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Those are some of the things.
[SPEAKER_04]: And of course, looking at a movie file, which Loki was kind enough to show me, it looks like it's going to be an over-the-shoulder perspective, sort of first-person shootery-ish movie.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it actually sort of made me think a little bit like it's like Devil May Cry featuring Vincent.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's not a bad thing, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: But there better not be any freaking Aerith in it or I'll scream.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate her.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also, speaking about the Final Fantasy VII franchise, I was reading an interview from our friends at 1UP.com with Tetsuya Nomura, who's, as we know, the director of Kingdom Hearts 2 and Final Fantasy VII Advent Children, stating that he very much wants to...
[SPEAKER_04]: and sort of expand on the Final Fantasy VII tech demo and completely remake the game.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've said this on previous podcasts.
[SPEAKER_01]: I highly speculate it's already in the works and they're just keeping a real tight lid on it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it's going to be a surprise at next year's E3.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_01]: I might be wrong.
[SPEAKER_01]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_04]: All we can do is wait, but I'll tell you, if it's out, I know which of those systems I'm getting first.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's all there is to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now what else is coming out for the PS3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Remake of Gradius.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I heard, I had a story queued up on that.
[SPEAKER_01]: You ruined it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, it's a wonderful transition into your part.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though I have something else.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll get back to you here.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me get the story I have here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll go cry in my little giggling ditzy corner.
Gradius.
Hee hee hee.
[SPEAKER_01]: Gradius will be coming out on the PlayStation 3 coming out of the Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_01]: There really isn't a whole lot else to say except Gradius is coming out in a brand new PlayStation 3 form.
[SPEAKER_01]: What else is there to say?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's Gradius.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's going to be very sexy.
[SPEAKER_01]: Especially if some of the famous Konami musicians such as Akira Yamaoka or some of the other people they have there are doing the music for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: It will be very sexy indeed.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sign me up.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_01]: There's also speculation, according to Bloomberg.com, you know, financial blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: that Konami and Capcom may be Japan's next big merger.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: And to quote my... It's so weird saying husband.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm so married now.
[SPEAKER_04]: But he was saying, were they going to be called Capkonami?
[SPEAKER_01]: Capkonami.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, that would just be weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't see it happening.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't either.
[SPEAKER_04]: But a lot of these companies, to do a quote in here from Takashi Oya, who's an analyst with Deutsche Securities in Tokyo.
[SPEAKER_04]: So companies like Taito, Bandai, and Namco are not merging because they are facing financial ruin.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're looking three years down the road and thinking this might be a strategic choice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if these big, you know, because Taito, Namco, all of those are really freaking huge.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, it's so weird that all these game companies are suddenly like, it's like they're forming into the giant Mechatron.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Sega Sammy, which is weird all in itself.
[SPEAKER_01]: It can be very few.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, I mean, honestly...
[SPEAKER_04]: Mega Man, Castlevania, etc.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_01]: I think that would be kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's another comment in here that sort of bugged me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm just going to read this little paragraph here.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Konami is trying to break its reliance on the video game business where earnings depend on hit titles and find new revenue sources by expanding into toys, sports club, arcade machinery, and casino businesses.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which actually, you know, I saw a number of Konami-made slot machines when I was at the casino a couple weekends ago for my honeymoon.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Konami has always been into fitness equipment.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, they're even working on a mock-up of DDR to be used as a fitness, as basically automated aerobics machine.
[SPEAKER_01]: Consolidation is gaining pace and music movie broadcasting companies and internet portals are possible partners.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, looking at this from the business side, that actually does make a lot of sense.
[SPEAKER_04]: And it's saying on here that the speculated target for Konami is Capcom.
[SPEAKER_01]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right now, Konami's number four, Capcom's number six.
[SPEAKER_04]: It makes financial sense.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_01]: That would be kind of... It would just be weird.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see, though.
[SPEAKER_01]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be like taking my heart and breaking it in two and putting it back together.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I love Konami and I love Capcom.
[SPEAKER_04]: And seeing, you know, it's like having hamsters.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know how if one of your hamsters feels like it's threatened, its babies are threatened, like its assets are threatened, it's going to go kill the other hamster and eat it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's true!
[SPEAKER_04]: Hamsters do that.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I know it's not the best analogy.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, it's doggy dog.
[SPEAKER_04]: In this case, it's, you know... Hamstreet hamster.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hamstreet hamster.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything else for us, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like fire.
[SPEAKER_01]: I know you do.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's when you truly giggle, is when you set things on fire.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: But only when they scream.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um... Xenosaga...
[SPEAKER_01]: Xenosaga is coming out to the Nintendo DS.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xenosaga 1 and 2 specifically no it's not going to be the full blown 3D movie element that you see in Xenosaga no they're going to redo it all cutesy anime style in a 2D isometric type style but still that's kind of cool I mean to remake a game that was out on the Playstation 2 and just kind of like remake all the graphics and all the stuff behind it and it's still going to have cutscenes it's just going to be done differently well they're going to remake that into a DS title
[SPEAKER_01]: Xenosaga 1 and 2.
[SPEAKER_01]: That also coming out of Tokyo Game Show from Monolith Soft.
[SPEAKER_01]: Should be very interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: Xenosaga Episode 3, by the way, is coming out for the PlayStation 2, if you were not aware.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki, did you have anything else for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_01]: I saw you had a story up there, so I'm curious.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just looking at some of the stuff that they've been showing at, you know,
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: My favorite, though, is just some of the detailed shots that they've been showing for Metal Gear Solid 4.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just the amount of detail that's in this is incredible.
[SPEAKER_02]: The other game that looks really cool is the Ghost Recon 3 Advanced Warfighter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some of the stuff in there actually looks like CNN footage.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's how detailed it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And also, what really scares me is they're talking about making a Lone and Dark for the PS3, so that might give Bowie Bowles some inspiration to make another movie.
[SPEAKER_02]: We can't have that, so... I hope not.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got one more story for you guys tonight, then.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a brand new... This is usually the type of thing you talk about, Loki, but I'm stealing this from you tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Um...
[SPEAKER_01]: Recording video via your PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: A company called Hori is making a brand new PSP accessory.
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically what it is, it's a little rectangle looking device and what it does is you can hook it up so that you can record video straight onto your memory stick.
[SPEAKER_01]: So that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: You can record video using your PSP right onto your memory stick.
[SPEAKER_01]: About $115 is what it's going to cost.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's 12,800 yen coming out in November in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_01]: on PSP.
[SPEAKER_01]: But remember, if you're making adult films with your PSP, don't leave it where people are going to find it because they'll get put all over the internet like, you know, those celebrities like Pam Anderson and stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: On that note, that's going to do it for tonight's episode of Orange Lounge Radio To Go.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in, subscribing to us.
[SPEAKER_01]: Tell somebody you know and you love about Orange Lounge Radio and help spread the word.
[SPEAKER_01]: In fact, tell somebody you hate about Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tee hee, tee hee, insert bad joke here.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_01]: And a reminder to check OrangeLoungeRadio.com and check out our Hurricane Katrina relief we're doing with the other Sacramento companies, Dark Records and Club 21.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'll see you guys next time here on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_01]: Final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_01]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: JackThompson
[SPEAKER_02]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a whole bunch of emails or fake emails I should say that are on the Liberty City Stories webpage so go check those out as well.
[SPEAKER_01]: My final thought is I'm still craving a milkshake now that you both had them during the three hour program earlier this evening and I didn't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm suffering for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_01]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two sort of final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm correcting myself.
[SPEAKER_04]: It wasn't police knots that had the mini RC looking metal gear like Otacon was using.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was Snatcher, which is another Kojima game that was on Sega CD.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good luck finding it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And your second final thought?
[SPEAKER_04]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_01]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go ditz my way off now.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have fun with that.
[SPEAKER_01]: And from us to you, have a great day, afternoon, or evening whenever you're listening to this.
[SPEAKER_01]: And we'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio To Go.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the end of another Orange Lounge Radio To Go edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: This podcast is a proud part of www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_00]: See you next update.