[SPEAKER_01]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of Bukkake.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are not fucking live.
[SPEAKER_11]: And this is an episode that didn't fucking happen on September fucking 4th, 2005.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you very much, Live365.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're tuned into a special pre-taped message for our fans who tried to tune in tonight but couldn't anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: We had a fucking hell of a show for you guys too.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm so mad that this didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have so much booze mahal.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio, radio the gamers really want.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Orange Lounge Radio Unlive.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're home for all the delayed news and postponed discussion.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is Orange Lounge Radio Dead.
[SPEAKER_11]: On rhythm and music games as well as the gamer and angst-filled community and the poop culture world.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're plugged in and fully interactive through our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com but not tonight because you have to be a member of our live journal community to hear this message.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go, go, go, go, go, go!
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_10]: Dead365
[SPEAKER_11]: How you doing, Mel?
[SPEAKER_11]: What do you want to say to the listeners that are listening postponedly?
[SPEAKER_12]: A delayed aloha to you, and aloha means hello and goodbye.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aloha is the theme of tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: I am so freaking mad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Guinness is gone?
[SPEAKER_11]: Guinness is gone.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_11]: Somebody get this bitch another Guinness.
[SPEAKER_11]: More booze!
[SPEAKER_11]: Happy wedding day, or whatever you call it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, see, I'm double, I'm quadruple pissed at Life 365.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't going to be here this weekend, remember, that was the plan, because I was supposed to be getting laid.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I mean, I mean constipating my marriage.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, and that was constipating my marriage.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was going to come be on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, thank you, my puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: and have such a good time and be all happy and say how cool it is to eat and drink a lot.
[SPEAKER_11]: And now... Now your microphone's breaking up because it knows that you're angst-filled.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, when you treat your microphone like that, that's why it acts like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I need more liquor because I took the time out of my honeymoon, my five days off from work, to come up here for this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Although, I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: I love you too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Happy wedding.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, oh, oh, shit, I gotta get that song queued up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, first say hello to a guest that hasn't been here in like a year and a half, if not more, and the bitch was here tonight, and we didn't get to do a show tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: So say hello to the Orange Lounge Madame, Pixie Dust.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're a bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I haven't been fucking gone for a year and a half.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, you have.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bitch, when was the last time I saw you?
[SPEAKER_03]: When I brought you those fucking ho-hos you asked for.
[SPEAKER_03]: You the ho-ho!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you the fucking ho-ho.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bitch, when was the last time you got laid?
[SPEAKER_05]: This morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just rolled over and it fell in.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first thing I ever had was some of that sliced bread.
[SPEAKER_11]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Four years ago, buddy.
[SPEAKER_13]: Four years ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, now that I think about it, I think that was my fault.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it was DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: DickSakura, is that what you said?
[SPEAKER_13]: DickSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ass.
[SPEAKER_11]: DickSakura?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hitch.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, Ditch, now listen to this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Plug, plug.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plug it in.
[SPEAKER_13]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to the mod of the month, Dick Sakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can bite my ass, okay?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hand.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, here's my hand.
[SPEAKER_11]: We are not loud, Sean.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's because Rob's drunk.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's not John, that's Shane.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sean?
[SPEAKER_11]: Shane.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Sean.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sean.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, I'm going to buy another puppy right now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Say hello to Shane.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't say hello.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yo.
[SPEAKER_11]: So Miklatov was here.
[SPEAKER_11]: For tonight's show, even though we're not doing a show This is a special pre-tape message for our friends on the LiveJournal community Who are pissed off that we didn't do a show tonight So we're doing this for them So three people?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know But this is great, you know, Miklatov was here tonight And he was going to tell us the entire song list for Extreme 2 But now, thanks to Live365, it's gone, not going to happen Oh no 4400's awesome!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, this game is pissing me off because I'm getting every Shiba Inu except for the white ones so that I can name it Menchie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like in Exile Saga.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dork.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can always feed Menchie to the other dogs in case, you know, you didn't have enough food.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here's what we're going to do.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to do a couple of our favorite segments here on Orange Lawns Radio for our, you know, a few dedicated people that are downloading this program.
[SPEAKER_11]: The first one we're going to do tonight is How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_11]: But there's a twist tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we're talking about our bandwidth and people are going to be downloading this program unless we put it on a CD later for them to buy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we're talking about that, you have to do How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day in one sentence.
[SPEAKER_11]: How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day in one sentence.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, semicolon, I got married.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: One sentence.
[SPEAKER_10]: Game publishers came to my company and are giving me cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mel B, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: One sentence.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sega Genesis Games owned me all week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pixie Dust, the Orange Lounge Madam, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: One sentence.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vicodin's the shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes it is, yes it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: NoStylin, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: One sentence.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hi, I'm your salesman.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: It has a semicolon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mr. Mel B. Mel B, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck, I've been drinking.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's mine.
[SPEAKER_11]: No encore performances.
Here, give it to that guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Give it to the tall guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mikolo Tav.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mazel Tav.
[SPEAKER_11]: The 4400 season finale was awesome.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you guys are playing Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_11]: How's the Nintendogs thing going for you, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have puppies.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm gonna get another puppy and I'm gonna name him Menchie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Menchie flavor.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you know that we're a little bit angsty.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have the fro.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_11]: He has the African fro.
[SPEAKER_11]: My dog has a pirate hat.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have any hats, but I have a ribbon now.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can give you a present when we do bark mode later.
[SPEAKER_04]: I want a hat.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: I gave you a ghetto tennis ball.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm getting off track here, not that that's anything unusual.
[SPEAKER_11]: Penguin Penguin No styling, good job
[SPEAKER_03]: What color is it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you say what this is?
[SPEAKER_11]: Bottle.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob with a bottle.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, why is it we do the FUs of the week every single week even when we don't get allowed to do a show?
[SPEAKER_11]: Because we hate Life 365.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not that I really...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I'm sorry, I was playing jump rope with my puppy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, Live365, when they announce a particular time to do their maintenance, needs to actually fucking stick with it!
[SPEAKER_04]: And I need more booze, that's all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, one more thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Getting married at the Department of Justice is like going to the DMV of weddings, thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your wedding, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was short, and Dan kept making faces at me to keep me from violently heaving all over the performer.
[SPEAKER_11]: Iguana Girl said that she only had to go through, like, two pieces of Kleenex.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, she went through two pieces of Kleenex?
[SPEAKER_11]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: Two pieces of Kleenex.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was about to, like, you know, start heaving violently, and Dan's like, By the way, I'm going to make faces at you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You bastard!
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, I'm married now, and all of this stuff is mine.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's an awesome way to look at it, FYI.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, let's go to Loki with his FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's my screwdriver.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, um, my excuse of the week, first off is to Nintendogs because I actually have to take care of the dog, I have to feed it every day.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's like having an actual dog.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why do I have to pay, you know, have an actual dog?
[SPEAKER_10]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyways, so, I do it for the hell of it, and I don't have a jump rope, so that's sad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, but anyways, um, then also, uh, fuck you to Stupid Drivers because they're all out there, just, you know, hordes of them, especially the holiday season.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just sucks, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess Live 365 because I had a lot of music I wanted to play and that sucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I will still be drinking next week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do you get to drink next week?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what is next week?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, your birthday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, damn.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm taking that Monday off.
[SPEAKER_10]: So hopefully I can drink next week, you know, depending on if I can get a ride.
[SPEAKER_10]: But depending if I can get a ride, I'll be drinking next week.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's all.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: MyFUs MyFU of the week goes to Live365 for fucking up our live show and disappointing all our listeners.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hate you guys.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, I know, in case somebody from Live365 actually hears this, I don't really hate you guys, but you done pissed me off with this.
[SPEAKER_11]: This was not good for business.
[SPEAKER_11]: And if we go somewhere else because of this, I don't want you to be surprised.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, but that's that for now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, otherwise, I give an FU to Miklatov for forcing me to buy Pump It Up, although he did pay for half of it, so I love him for that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Miklatov?
[SPEAKER_11]: I know, I ended up paying $20 for Pump, so I guess I shouldn't complain, but that's more money than I've ever spent playing Pump It Up, so... Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you, Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, and let me think.
[SPEAKER_11]: What else?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: I give an F you to the fact that I have a whole week off of work, and because of the price of gas, I'm not going to be able to go anywhere.
[SPEAKER_11]: That kind of pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_11]: Gas prices suck.
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't believe you drove up here today, Mel B. Because gas prices fucking suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nah.
[SPEAKER_04]: In Georgia, $6 per premium.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here, it's hard to complain when we're here and not somewhere that was affected by that horrible, horrible hurricane.
[SPEAKER_11]: But...
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, it still sucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: I still want to bitch.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, at least if there's any consolation, the Attorney General of California is actually looking into investigating the gas companies out here for price gouging because we're basically not affected by any...
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_11]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, we're going to go around and see some other angst in the room tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: And tonight's music we're going to use as the background for the FU music was something we were going to plug on tonight's show, except we didn't fucking have a show.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is a compilation, Blood and Synth, a compilation, and it comes from Dark Records.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you should visit their website, darkrecordsn, the letter N, darkrecordsnclothing.com.
[SPEAKER_11]: So not and, but an N, darkrecordsnclothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the song we're going to use is In Vitro with Foreign Land.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mel B
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh gosh, definitely EffieTheLife365 for not coming through this time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even when I listen to you guys at work, man, I listen to some of the worst ads that they put out.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, like after three songs, I have to hear some booty-ass R&B singer who ain't never gonna cut it in any kind of... I mean, they're not gonna be American Idol, Botswana Idol, none of that shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Botswana Idol!
[SPEAKER_11]: I swear to God, we are seriously contemplating moving after tonight's little shindig, so just...
[SPEAKER_11]: We know that our listeners will move with us if we go to another site, so not to sound like a pompous ass, but we know they will.
[SPEAKER_11]: We love them.
[SPEAKER_11]: They love us.
[SPEAKER_11]: So anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: So yeah, F you to them.
[SPEAKER_12]: F you to $3 gas, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's, I mean, yeah, I'm a sucker for driving up here, but hey, you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would be a fool for you guys any week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mel B, can I... Is this supposed to be a secret or can I say thank you for this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, Mel B gave me copies of Orifice and Zonk's latest albums.
[SPEAKER_04]: Orifice.
[SPEAKER_11]: Best name ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or-if-is, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like saying Orifice because it sounds like a butt.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, we're going to put the song Basil in the rotation because that's their new Ultramix 3 song and Zonk... We're going to play that CD at some point because they're cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that was kind of like, uh, what was that, you can't do it on television, we were into opposites where we're actually giving props instead of giving FUs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I don't know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, anyway, back to reality.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, FU also to, uh, my Atari 2600, man.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like, I went to Classic Gaming Expo two weeks ago, I go out and buy an AC adapter and, like, a cable so I can put it into, like, a real TV and not those, like,
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, RF adapters from like the 80s.
[SPEAKER_12]: What happens, you know, I get all this stuff that, you know, now I can finally play Circus Atari and Breakout, and guess what?
[SPEAKER_12]: My Atari 2600 is dead.
[SPEAKER_12]: Aww, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, man, 20 years, couldn't have just held out another, like, 6 months?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, what system?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, my 2600.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, um, depending on how long you're gonna be in town, um, the auction out here, usually sells 2600s pretty damn cheap.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe, might be crashing out of frame.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll hunt one down for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, good times.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I think that's about... You can mod those new Atari, whatever those... Flashbacks?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Flashbacks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Flashback 2 to have a cartridge slot.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's all pinned out for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you just solder some wires and you're good to go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I'll be damned.
[SPEAKER_12]: And on that note, I'm going to pass it over this way.
[SPEAKER_11]: Miss Pixie Dust, the...
[SPEAKER_11]: Orange Lounge Madame.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck me, baby.
[SPEAKER_11]: Fuck me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck you hard, huh, baby?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Fuck me, bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, fuck you to people that think they're Paris Hilton and they can bring their dogs in the fucking grocery store.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's fucking nasty.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm specifically pointing out one fat bitch that comes in on a scooter and smells like shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: That comes in all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bitch, no one wants to see your nasty-ass fucking chihuahua mutt.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you really want to bring a dog in the store...
[SPEAKER_03]: Drop down the $200, go get Nintendogs, and be done with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because no one wants to see your dog climbing up your titty.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have a nice day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Viking is the shit.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm all good for now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: No styling.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_13]: How again?
[SPEAKER_13]: Hi everybody.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to do a sales pitch on the phone.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Actually, I've been doing a great weekend.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's no FU, so I'm going to pass the mic.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_13]: Positive.
[SPEAKER_13]: You've got to be positive about this weekend.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you and your positive.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know where that goes?
[SPEAKER_13]: Anywhere.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, here you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I ain't drinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: You ain't getting any ass tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: You ain't getting no... No butt sex for you.
[SPEAKER_03]: None!
[SPEAKER_03]: As if there was any to get.
[SPEAKER_02]: Miklatov.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dude, my dog is really good with the soccer ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: FUs!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to not being next summer for the next season of the 4400.
[SPEAKER_02]: FU to... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have any FUs.
[SPEAKER_02]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: So that's it for the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_11]: What else can we get out of the way on this show here?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Music.
[SPEAKER_11]: Music?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess we could do one song.
[SPEAKER_11]: I bought another dog.
[SPEAKER_11]: Two songs?
[SPEAKER_11]: Why do we have to do two songs?
Okay, fine, one song.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, we'll do one song.
[SPEAKER_11]: One thing I wanted to get out real fast though, news that happened this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Ultramix 2 unlock code.
[SPEAKER_11]: Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A. Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A. Control report for in the credit screen and you unlock all the songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: That was announced this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, of course I knew that for like God knows how long.
[SPEAKER_12]: V-Rare Tracklist Xtreme 2
[SPEAKER_11]: Destiny, the piano version, Feelings Won't Fade, Extended Transmix, Midnight Blaze, System SF Mix, Can Be Real, Soulhouse Extended, Seduction, the vocal remix.
[SPEAKER_11]: So basically a lot of shit you've pretty much heard before, except we've got Yuzo Koshiro with You've Gotta Move It, but otherwise you've got Sakura, Can Be Real, Colors, Infinite Prayer, Quickening, Un De Trois, Belovin', I Need You, La Morle... Yes, I know Seduction's brand new, but you know...
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sure it'll be a kick-butt V-Rare and you should all go buy it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Put down your five bucks, go get your V-Rare.
[SPEAKER_11]: Guitar Freaks, Drum Mania, V2 is on its way, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_11]: DDR Extreme won the Video Music Awards for Best Soundtrack, but you didn't see it on the actual show because it was one of those pre-show awards they gave away.
[SPEAKER_11]: In other words, MTV doesn't give a shit about DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: But that's okay because I don't give a shit about MTV, so it works out.
[SPEAKER_10]: A few other things that I'd mention.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, go for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: In case you didn't know, there's going to be a demo on the two new DDRs, DDR Extreme 2 and Ultramix 3 for Karaoke Revolution Pop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now that's some juicy tidbit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't know this.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the same thing for Karaoke Revolution 4 or Party or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be demos for whatever one.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't think I've heard this anywhere yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, wow, our listeners just got a real juicy tidbit there, so if you were able to put up with the show at this point, it was worth it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, let me just say, well, I don't know if I can say anything, but Konami's going to be spending more time in the courts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me just put it that way.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ooh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: So you made a new friend at Konami that told you all sorts of stuff, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, he's my new friend.
[SPEAKER_10]: He's going to send us actually the...
[SPEAKER_10]: V-Rares for Ultra Mix 3 and Extreme 2 pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we'll get the first tidbits on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hopefully at Ultra Mix 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said whatever he has, so... Stay tuned to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we got that, and I got a ton of Diverse System stuff we've got.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, lots of fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, we're going to play one song on this little special show.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is actually from not Diverse System.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is from Good Cool, the Ultra Expander.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a remix of Absolute, the ultimate remix, and it definitely fits that title.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright, so here it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: We're going to play this for you guys on the Orange Lounge Radio Not Show that we didn't have tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good Cool with DJ Taka, the absolute ultimate mix.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here it is on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good Cool.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Good Cool with DJ Taka Absolute, the ultimate remix here on the Orange Lounge It Didn't Happen episode.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it won the cage match that never happened.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, it won the cage match that never happened, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: That pisses me off because I had a really funny song.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, Miklatov picked my song tonight, too, and we didn't even get to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: I need some Guinness to go with these cookies and Mel B, your final thought where were my drinks?
go get one!
[SPEAKER_04]: Have a Guinness.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're good for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're full of vitamin G. And vitamin I. The final word of the show that didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pixie Dust.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bike it in.
[SPEAKER_06]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_06]: For more information about our station...