[SPEAKER_01]: Tonight, June 7th, 2011, we kick off our live E3 coverage with press conference reactions and special correspondents Bobby Blackwolf and Miklatov in LA on the show floor.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: To those of you that are brand new to Orange Lounge Radio, welcome.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you found us through Ustream or what have you or some of the other referrals, which we'll talk about in a little bit, welcome to our little show.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are the show where every gamer has a voice and boy, here's a lot of voices about what has been talked about from Microsoft, Sony, Nintendo, to a lesser extent EA and Ubisoft, but there's just a lot, a lot of talk today and we're going to get right into it, but I need to introduce everybody on the panel.
[SPEAKER_10]: First off, my name is Rob Roberts, sometimes known as Sky, and I'll be joining you with my co-host.
[SPEAKER_10]: Say hello to the one and only DarkSakura, Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_00]: Meaty.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Feeling fresh and meaty?
[SPEAKER_00]: Meaty.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: And say hello to the one and only, and I'm so happy he can make it here tonight, Techmaster Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: We were a little worried that Techmaster Loki wouldn't be here tonight because of family commitments, but here he is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Screw the family.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hope Nelly's not listening.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_10]: So welcome to you, and we're going to ask you about Nintendo in just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Also joining us, we've got other people joining us.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to have the one and only Bobby Blackwolf from The Bobby Blackwolf Show.
[SPEAKER_10]: He usually does a show right before us on our normal live shows Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, we're live every Sunday night at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: And more information about all of that is at our website, orangelonestradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby Blackwolf is in L.A.
[SPEAKER_10]: at E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: He will be joining us momentarily to talk about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: He has played the Wii U. We're going to talk all about that in a little while.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to introduce somebody else here in studio though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan the Man is joining us.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: What a pleasant surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: How are you Dan?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, E3.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wish I was there.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to get into all the press conferences and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me just start with this before I plug everything and do the usual plugs.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is one word on your mind right now that just if E3 right now can just boil down to one word, what is that word right now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan?
[SPEAKER_10]: Underwhelming.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to get to that later in the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to join our chat room, please note we do not have a Ustream chat.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a IRC chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: More information is available at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: So please, by all means, pull up a chair, sit in the chat room, and join us there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Orange Wright in the chat room will start us off tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of all one word slammed together says, third party saving first party asses.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess my runner up would be, seriously?
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously?
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's a good one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is it going to be all negative tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I swear to God, all I've been reading on Twitter is just cynicism, skepticism, negativity, and I'm like, this is why everybody hates gamers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, there's not an ounce of positivity I'm seeing on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I don't feel 100% negative.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are there things that I think should be done better?
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: But is it all negative?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't necessarily think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: But is anything mind-blowing?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, but probably not from any of the big five that we're going to talk about today.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll leave it at that.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, anyhow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also want to plug us on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_10]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby Blackwolf, of course, he'll be joining us in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're teaming up tonight to do the coverage.
[SPEAKER_10]: He is also on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter.com slash Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the reason why I plug that is that
[SPEAKER_10]: Today he was pretty dominated at the Nintendo booth all day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, he wasn't dominated at the Nintendo booth, maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: But his day was dominated by the Nintendo booth because he was at the Wii U event today.
[SPEAKER_10]: But tomorrow, he will be taking your orders.
[SPEAKER_10]: You will be dominating him on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he is going to be your man on the floor at twitter.com slash bobbyblackwolf.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you're like, hey...
[SPEAKER_10]: What freaking Konami games are there that weren't at the press conference or whatever?
[SPEAKER_10]: And he'll tweet you back and say, Glee Karaoke Revolution with Rocky Horror.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_06]: Reggie's bitch today, your bitch tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So twitter.com slash Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also want to say thank you to those of you guys that have retweeted, helped promote these special shows.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know it's a little weird because we're not in our usual home, but we had to kind of think fast and this all really came together last minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I want to thank everybody involved.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to give a special shout out to Video Game Outsiders who has a show usually live tonight at All Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't end up doing one tonight because of personal reasons, but they sent a tweet that was like, go listen to OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I thought that was very nice of them to do and so I wanted to give them a shout out and a thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be a night of varying opinions.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be fun so remember kids, play nice and be respectful.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Halo, Halo Anniversary Edition, Halo 4, neither of which, interesting enough, had Kinect shown.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was one of the only games, in fact, I think, at that whole press conference that didn't have Kinect shown.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there any excitement whatsoever about the new Halo 4 or the Halo Anniversary Edition?
[SPEAKER_06]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you hear the...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm into it, I like Halo, I'm stoked for more Halo
[SPEAKER_06]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_06]: It did mess with my head not seeing the Bungie logo before the Halo trailers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I was just like, oh, it's Halo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, there is no Bungie making Halo anymore.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's kind of sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: It did seem like that trailer had a very different look to it as well, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, it just didn't have that Bungie feel.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: It didn't have that big orchestra.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's okay, I think, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bungie had kind of ran their course, I guess, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't want to even say they ran their course, but it's just like, okay, there were the Batman movies from the 80s and 90s and stuff, and then there's the new Batman series.
[SPEAKER_09]: The beginning of one was good, and the other one is also good, but it's refreshing, I guess, to have a new style of gameplay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but it's hard to deny the fact that it's Bungie's franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it was Bungie's franchise.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Microsoft's franchise now.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's weird that it won't have their stamp on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unless the new developers are just sick copycats, which is about the best I could hope for.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me jump over to Anniversary Collection for a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huge speculation on the internet before that it was going to be very Kinect heavy.
[SPEAKER_10]: In fact, I believe there was a domain, halokinect.com or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, granted, there could be more announcements between now and when the game actually comes out, but unlike most of the other stuff that Microsoft was pushing at E3, wasn't seeing Kinect in this Halo game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think they changed their mind?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think this is yet to come?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's because that would have required them to do some extra work because basically they're just upgrading the assets slightly and they're porting it over to the Reach engine.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it would have required them to rebuild a portion of the engine and adjusting the physics so that it's like Halo 1.
[SPEAKER_09]: But it would have required extra work for them to do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe Halo 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, you can bet your ass Halo 4 will use Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you find that little footnote that came out after the press conference about that the multiplayer is all just multiplayer maps for Halo Reach?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is not actually a part of the Halo Anniversary Collection or whatever, Anniversary Edition?
[SPEAKER_10]: It is.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had read this thing online about... No, no, no, here's how it works.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that can't be right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Please, please share me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, it's very similar to ODST.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically, you have one disc that has the single player campaign on it and, of course, the co-op for that disc.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then you have also the multiplayer disc.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now the whole multiplayer disc is the full Halo Reach multiplayer portion, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the maps do exist on the Reach servers, but since it's also on the Reach engine, that's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_09]: These maps are for Reach, but you can play against other people that also have Reach, I believe, as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I guess that's kind of cool if it kind of bridges that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, because ODST did the same thing they did.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was Halo 3 they were playing on.
[SPEAKER_09]: So it's not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And considering the fact that it's also going to be a budget-priced game, too, it's going to be a $40 game when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just because they know they can't make a better multiplayer engine than Bungie did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk Kinect for a little bit because obviously Kinect dominated a lot of Microsoft's press conference and it's taken a lot of flack on the internet because of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I noticed when I was watching Twitter over the press conference there's a lot of people hating on Microsoft right now because their conference was very Kinect heavy and it didn't seem to address the hardcore gamer which is funny because that's the battle Nintendo's been fighting for years.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bullshit, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have the best stage.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's important.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, it was important.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, we're going to get into it later on, but they're not the only ones that, you know, okay, other than, you know, PlayStation, I guess.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're not the only ones that really focus on their motion gaming stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And yeah, what they showed, I think it's a little bit of everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: You had some stuff for the hardcore players and you had some stuff that's like, well, this shit's on, you know, could have been on the Wii or, you know, it's very kidsy, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask a question of our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com again.
[SPEAKER_10]: For those that are joining us for the first time because of the Ustream connection here, our normal chat room is at chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Answer this for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there a Kinect title you want to try?
[SPEAKER_10]: And I want to talk about some of those Kinect titles that were announced at the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I want to go to DarkSakura for a minute because I know you must have perked up when you heard about the Disneyland Kinect game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you hear about the Disneyland Kinect game?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I didn't actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, there's this whole... I relied on somebody to fill me in.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, Dan didn't fill her in on the Disneyland Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: You didn't ask.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, there's this whole Disneyland Kinect game going on where they really harped on...
[SPEAKER_10]: You're going to get to be in Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they actually showed, you know, like you're going through down Main Street and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: But then as you walk up to a ride like Peter Pan's Adventure, they had these little overacting kids on stage demonstrating it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was just mini games.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you know what it made me think of?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if you guys remember an old 8-bit game by Capcom years and years ago called Adventures in the Magic Kingdom.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was an old-ass NES game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was the same thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you know what this game is?
[SPEAKER_09]: What?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's another Connect Adventures game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Seriously, Connect Disneyland Adventures.
[SPEAKER_09]: Connect Adventures.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why you're flying through stuff and collecting coins or whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Except it's in Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Disney Hub looked cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: The minigames looked like butt.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's exactly where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_06]: Exactly where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, exactly.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's fine because it looks fun, but... Let me put it this way, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: They seriously need to tone down the acting for the people that they have on stage.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was...
[SPEAKER_09]: It was to the point where it was distracting.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I understand you wanted to make it look fun and stuff like that, but oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you have any idea how many Red Bulls those kids drank?
[SPEAKER_06]: They worked their little hearts off, and they're probably dead right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They burned out showing you how fun that game was.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to know what this horror is
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think anybody here in the room got Minecraft, quote unquote.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get it, but I just don't want to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I think that's where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get it, and I understand why people love it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That being said, it's not for me.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just I don't have that much free time in my day to play something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: We have some more feedback in our chatroom on the Disney game, Disneyland Adventures for the Kinetic Tiger Claw.
[SPEAKER_10]: When they showed that Disneyland game, I was reminded of that Universal Studios game on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_10]: Remember that game?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I don't, so that doesn't bode well for this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it was bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't even remember it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Universal Studios Mini Games Back to the Future
[SPEAKER_06]: was Woody Woodpecker.
[SPEAKER_10]: That would be like, okay, we've got a Disneyland game coming out, but unfortunately all the Disneyland characters, like 98% of them were too expensive to license, so we got Herbie the Lovebug to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we decided to do Knott's Berry Farm.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be expensive because it's Disney.
[SPEAKER_06]: That would be it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: We couldn't get Minnie Mouse, Mickey Mouse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Connect Knott's Berry Farm Adventures.
[SPEAKER_10]: At least they'd have good chicken.
[SPEAKER_10]: Savalas in the chair says, Connect Disney is for families in Nebraska who are not able to get to a Disney amusement park.
[SPEAKER_10]: I see it as more like the thing to just shut the kids up.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure that my store, Nebraska Furniture Mart, will sell plenty of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really do hope somebody hacks the Disneyland Connect assets and makes a Grand Theft Auto style port.
[SPEAKER_09]: Come on now, let the kids have something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who hasn't made Grand Theft Auto and GTA yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I hate fucking Elmo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, maybe with less Elmo.
[SPEAKER_06]: If it had like Cookie Monster and Big Bird in it, I'd be like, this game's going to be tight.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to buy a copy and I'm going to play it.
[SPEAKER_10]: If Linda the Deaf Lady was teaching me how to sign.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dude, Linda the Deaf Lady was hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: BlackWolf is in our chat room right now talking to the chatters there saying, I had Sesame Street games on my Intellivision.
[SPEAKER_10]: Word fun and Electric Company math fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dude, the Electric Company game was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to know more about this whole live streaming TV thing they were talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was I the only one that didn't really get it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It flowed really weird in their presser for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: They were watching Castle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they're watching Castle apparently.
[SPEAKER_10]: I caught a little ad in the sidebar.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if it was just a marketing placeholder or whatever, but it said The Connect Show.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that made me think, is Microsoft producing their own content for this too?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or was that just a placeholder?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think it's a placeholder, but here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically going to be content that, say, for example, I have Comcast, so it's going to be Comcast programming.
[SPEAKER_09]: Great.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can just turn the TV on and watch TV.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't need to watch TV through my 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will my 360 act as a TiVo?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because if so, I could actually kind of use that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what it's doing is, you guys know what the review is, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Harry Potter, and it'll show you all the games, all the CDs.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, will it like search the internet too?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, do we have a legit... No, it won't search the internet because it doesn't have a fucking web browser in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will Kinect finally respond to me going, Xbox, Bing, gay porn.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll probably look up gay porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then it'll be My Little Pony.
[SPEAKER_10]: It'll come back with some indie gay... Yeah, it'll come back with My Little Pony.
[SPEAKER_06]: Care Bears.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Smurfs.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lady Gaga on HBO.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate the new interface.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: It took me a minute to figure out that they were actually demoing a new interface.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I'm not stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: I saw that it was a new interface, but I thought it was kind of like a spinoff for the TV thing, like the Kinect thing is.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a little separate thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't think I was looking at a whole new dashboard.
[SPEAKER_10]: and I was kind of like, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looked like the crossbar a little bit, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, it's modeled after Windows 7 phone stuff and then also Windows 8 is supposed to be very similar to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good for them to do that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: First off, Windows 8, that shit is optional.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like the fucking media center.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't have to use media center if you don't want to.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, on the Xbox 360, it's not fucking optional.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hitting the guide button again to get my fucking blades back is not fucking optional.
[SPEAKER_09]: I want the blades.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's a thought.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know this is crazy and out there, but...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: Techness in our chatroom at chat.orange.studio.com says, I think it's great they added complete voice search.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's pretty hard and quite pathetic that in the current dashboard it's hard to find shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's kind of my problem.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, Connect Fun Labs was on the thing like right after the press conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had to dig to find it.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, you didn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was not on the main bar.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had to go to the E3 coverage.
[SPEAKER_09]: You didn't look hard enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then you go to Connect.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Moving on to some other announcements.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the non-connect things at the top were actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was the Modern Warfare 3 demo that they demoed.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, I'm not into those games, but I was kind of looking at the footage going, oh, that's really pretty.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's pretty cool if I could actually do that when I play the game as opposed to just running into walls constantly and shooting my friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: You mean there's a Modern Army game where I can shoot things and shit explodes?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's revolutionary and brand new!
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to admit, I thought it was pretty cool when they were doing that whole little getaway in the raft.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, it's like Super Army Cart.
[SPEAKER_06]: They had a raft at the end of the last game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, shows you how much I play those games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the truth is, I like Modern Warfare.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, and I love this, the Tomb Raider demo was hot.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought that was like my favorite thing I saw.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tomb Raider was neat, but once again, you know, I've already, I've kind of set that franchise aside for, well actually since the first Tomb Raider, I just never got into Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_10]: But it looks cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the thing about this new Tomb Raider is that it didn't look at all like the old ones, because it didn't look like a reboot at all.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it looks like Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, maybe that's why Microsoft wanted to show it in their conference And then they have Adventure Sense, which is like saying, hey, you can't figure out the puzzle?
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll do it for you I'm gonna need that It's Tomb Raider for idiots Well, what I loved about it though is that there were scenes very reminiscent of that movie The Descent Which is like one of the few movies ever to legit scare the shit out of me So I can kind of see where the survival horror thing is coming from for Tomb Raider Because some of that stuff did look kind of scary
[SPEAKER_06]: Tomb Raider needs something, and if this rejuvenates the franchise, great.
[SPEAKER_06]: But just the same, it's like, it's Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_09]: How many times have they tried to reboot Tomb Raider?
[SPEAKER_09]: So many times, and it's failed every time, so hopefully this time it's a little different.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations Xbox, you get Uncharted, it's Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, but Tomb Raider is not exclusive to the 360 either, so I thought it was weird that they demoed it as Microsoft Prime.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but PS3 people can just play Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, that's why they didn't demo it.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't want to show Uncharted and then, you know, Tomb Raider.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, this looks kind of similar.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, oh, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uncharted is awesome and Tomb Raider is trying again.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw in our chatroom says, the Tomb Raider demo got kind of creepy with all the moaning and panting from Lara Croft.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: GameGuru says, Tomb Raider looks too much like a survival horror game.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Randy U says, dude stabbing Lara and closing her eyes?
[SPEAKER_10]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_10]: Janai in our chatroom says, Uncharted is so bro, bro, bro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uncharted is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did watch that little bit of the demo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of the Uncharted demo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: When Dan was watching it, it was, let's drown for a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's press A repeatedly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's not drown for a while.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's Uncharted.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I was like, yeah, I won't play it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's shoot people.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then QuickTime events.
[SPEAKER_06]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then, of course, Connect Fun Labs was shown, and I wanted to see the look on Loki's face when that was being demoed.
[SPEAKER_09]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here's the thing, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: All this stuff got spoiled.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, right before the press conference, oh, look, our E3 page got leaked out.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, all the big, you know, announcements, they were already out there.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Connect Fun Labs, that shit leaked a while ago, but...
[SPEAKER_06]: and here's what you know Connect Fun Labs is it's hey look here's all the tech stuff that we said we could do before and couldn't do now you can you know remember the whole hey I can scan my skateboard in there and you know play the first thing that they show did you notice even the lady said finally she's like and now you can scan in your skateboard finally so you know she's been catching shit about that for a year like the first thing they show someone scanning a skateboard in and then jumping on a virtual skateboard and playing and now they're like oh you can do it
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and the thing about Connect Me too and the whole Fun Labs is that it is not changing your avatar.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not like how the 3DS will make a me out of taking a picture of you.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is just like a temporary thing to do fashion magazine poses.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then what the fuck is the whole thing where, oh, you don't have to fumble through menus anymore to pick your avatar.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then you're full of shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not trying to be rude.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a fucking lie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, screw it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not hooking up our Connect after all.
[SPEAKER_10]: you cannot make the avatar out of it you know what I did what I wanted to test I wore my Pikachu shirt to see if it would take a picture of the Pikachu shirt and like actually show Pikachu if it would just be a yellow shirt and it came through as a Pikachu shirt I mean it was a horrible scan of it but it was definitely Pikachu and I was thinking well obviously this won't be the main avatar because they can't show all that copyrighted stuff that people scan in somebody will wear a dick on their shirt I haven't tried it yet but that's gotta be wrong
[SPEAKER_10]: I am not... See if you can figure it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat, is anyone playing Kinect Fun Labs?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tell me if you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do not believe you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hook up our Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Save your avatar.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's your Kinect.
[SPEAKER_08]: Someone was supposed to lend me Dance Masters.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dance Central 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think of Dance Central 2?
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like Dance Central 1.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to admit, I'm a big fan of Dance Central, but I didn't see, besides, obviously, Durr, the two-player thing, I didn't see what was new about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's what's new about it, and I only know this because I saw the actual feature list.
[SPEAKER_09]: What they did is they improved the break-it-down mode where you can actually repeat individual moves or practice individual moves.
[SPEAKER_09]: It needed to be retooled.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can also repeat whole sections of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also...
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm trying to think what else there was in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: The two-player at the same time, they also have the ability where you can get rid of the freestyle stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: Say you don't want to do that where you flail about randomly during the song, you can take that out or you can change the way it looks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of that stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, the new music that they're going to have in there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I don't think they did a whole lot with Dance Central 2, and honestly, they probably could have just left it alone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's also one of those things where it's like, if it ain't broke, why fix it?
[SPEAKER_06]: How many dance games are on the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, I'm sorry, the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Kinect, there's Dance Masters, Just Dance was announced, will be coming, and there's that Dance Paradise, is that what it is?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's Dance Masters, Dance Central 2, Just Dance 3, Dance Paradise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Available right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dance Paradise, Dance Masters, and Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's three?
[SPEAKER_06]: I like how they're like, it's the number one selling dance game on the Kinect.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Michael Jackson, The Experience.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess maybe that's four.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, because it is the number one selling one by a mile and with kind of good reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, because it's the only good one.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just Dance, though, I mean, it's good on the Wii and stuff because of the limitations of that, but when you...
[SPEAKER_09]: Kind of bring that in with Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if it's going to be able to hold its own.
[SPEAKER_09]: People will buy it because they're like, oh hey, Just Dance, it's popular.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I think Dance Central does a better job though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think Just Dance sells well because it's got the right name.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dance Central, Just Dance Dance Paradise
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, except only ones I'd seen were Dance Masters and Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: The only one I've tried is Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would love to see a dance game with like half Konami-ish songs, half Dance Central-ish songs in the Dance Masters interface because I think there's some cool things that Dance Masters brings to the table.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want more Parapara.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, then you would be talking about part of my pitch for a new DDR game, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: You see...
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, let me get to some quick, quick thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: We want to get on to Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to get to Bobby and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quick thoughts.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fable the Journey.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's my problem with necessarily... Fable the Journey looks good.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it looks nice because it's in Unreal 3 now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here's my problem with the Kinect games, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything's on fucking rails.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything is on fucking rails.
[SPEAKER_06]: Doesn't a Halo rail shooter make more sense than a Fable rail shooter?
[SPEAKER_09]: Everything is on fucking rails!
[SPEAKER_09]: The Ghost Recon game, on rails.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Fable game, on rails.
[SPEAKER_09]: Star Wars, on rails.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all they can do is on rail shooters.
[SPEAKER_09]: They can't actually do...
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything where you have actual control.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's where one thing that PlayStation has over, you know, the Kinect is, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a navigation controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can navigate around the map whereas you guys are stuck on a rail.
[SPEAKER_06]: You need the Xbox nunchuck.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm coming off of Fable 3, which I talked about on last week's OLR, and I was not feeling that great about Fable 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: So when I saw this preview, I was just kind of, eh, if it's $20 maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it looked alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: It would be a pretty cool Xbox Live Arcade game, and I liked how the perspective's a little different.
[SPEAKER_09]: It actually kind of reminded me of, because it is an on-rails shooter.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: I felt bad for him but of course the games are still early on so there you go did I miss anything else?
[SPEAKER_10]: Tom Clancy game was shown as well Gears of War 3 actually the one that looks kind of cool is Rise the new Crytek game the Roman one I saw the dude kicking in that and I was like he's gonna kick his Kinect right off the TV I can't play that in my house
[SPEAKER_09]: I can see the achievement now.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Sparta!
[SPEAKER_09]: Every time I do that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's why a game like that will sell because there's going to be a lot of 17-year-old guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: It looks good, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, that's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's an actual... But as long as the combat's good and not clunky like Fighters Uncaged or something like that, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: There was a lot of cool stuff that they showed.
[SPEAKER_09]: Forza 4 looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the head tracking stuff in that, once again, also kind of laggy.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't really know how you would be able to do that anyways because you can't really turn your...
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan, you're a racing game fan, Forza?
[SPEAKER_10]: Forza looks great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a great looking racing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did you see their new steering wheel that they have?
[SPEAKER_09]: That looks like butt.
[SPEAKER_09]: $60 wireless steering wheel.
[SPEAKER_09]: What's the point?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, you can wave it around in midair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gears of War 3, Ice-T reuniting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why does he always look angry?
[SPEAKER_09]: He's like, I'm hardcore.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's Ice-T.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, it's like every, I don't understand why he, he's just like scowling the entire time.
[SPEAKER_06]: He looked angry because he was playing Gears of War.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is a testosterone game for men.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody in Gears of War looks angry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you don't have to like be all, you know, fronting like you're just, you know, I'm gonna murder somebody after I'm done playing this game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Although I gotta say though, the Gears of War 3 limited edition Xbox looks pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_09]: The black and red one?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Looks good.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, quickly, I got to get to Bobby.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to quickly just mention the EA press conference that happened.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mass Effect 3, interesting voice command thing going on there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Useless.
[SPEAKER_10]: How quick?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would never use that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I would never.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, is it a great demo thing to show off your console to your friends?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, look at this space minority report technology.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's fun for like five minutes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Commanding your troops or whatever to do different things.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know if that was like...
[SPEAKER_09]: Part, yeah, I could see that.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, like, doing the actual dialogue trees and stuff, I have a directional pad right in my thumb.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why do I need to even bother with this bullshit?
[SPEAKER_10]: Star Wars The Old Republic What was up with that guy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mr. Caffeine by the way, when you actually go to a show and see Mr. Caffeine in person, he's amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Far Cry 3 was the only game I'd really seen and I was like there was part of the dialogue to me felt like it was trying to be too edgy I was like this game is fucking edgy when it showed the dude doing the stealth kills where he like walked up behind the guy pulled the knife out of the guy's pocket and stabbed him with it a little part of me my heart grew three sizes the game parts were cool I mean I'm not gonna play it but man
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the fact that you don't have malaria
[SPEAKER_10]: I am here, what's up guys?
[SPEAKER_10]: How's the weather in L.A.? ?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, not as warm as it is in Atlanta right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: What an interesting change of pace.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been raining up here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, forget the weather.
[SPEAKER_10]: E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: How did day one treat you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, my feet hurt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was a lot of standing around.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a lot of standing around.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, because you waited all day today to play Wii U, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I was about two hours before I got in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then I had about an hour and a half.
[SPEAKER_05]: to kind of go through their eight demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two hours actually isn't that bad, all things considered.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did they have entertainment in the Wii line this year, or Wii U, excuse me, line to keep you going?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, and actually, when I walked up to it, it was about two o'clock, and the show floor closes at six.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I walked up at two, and there was a lady at the end, there was the sign that said, line closed.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I said, is it already full?
[SPEAKER_05]: And she's like, well...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we've cut off the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're more than welcome to stay in here, but realize you may not get up to the front, and you may waste the rest of your day here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I said, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got up there and it wound up two hours later, you know, four o'clock, I'm starting to play with the Wii, Wii, Wii, Wii U. That's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess they were just trying to scare people away.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's not that bad, all things considered, because the lines in the past, like the 3DS line was atrocious last year, and then of course the original Wii line, we all saw those videos on the internet of just the line keeps going and going and going.
[SPEAKER_10]: That line was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, anyhow, we'll get to Nintendo in a minute, but let's start by talking about Sony, because Sony happened yesterday, and you were there at the press conference, right Bobby?
[SPEAKER_10]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, how was it?
[SPEAKER_10]: You got, like, right in the front, practically, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it was kind of funny because I got there a little late.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I took the shuttle from my hotel at, like, and it started at 5, and so I got on the bus at about 4, 4.05.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in L.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: traffic, it was, like, 4.55 when we finally pulled up to the Los Angeles Memorial Sports Arena, which is on USC campus.
[SPEAKER_05]: So...
[SPEAKER_05]: We finally pull up and I'm like watching everybody and we can't get off the bus.
[SPEAKER_05]: It takes us like 15 minutes just to get around the corner into the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we're all like kind of walking in and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I missed all the food in the beginning and all that stuff because I was hungry because I hadn't eaten since Atlanta that morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I made it all the way... You guys still there?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we're here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Something cut off on my phone.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was walking in, running in, and before I went through the door, there was a guy saying, hey, there's more seats if you go down this ramp to the VIP area.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm like, okay, I'll go down that ramp.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so we went down that ramp, and it went underneath, and we were on the floor area, and people were just directing us, and they pointed to these seats, like folding chairs on the floor, and
[SPEAKER_05]: right in front of the stage and there were like a lot of Sony employees sitting there and so I was sitting there with them and then all the Sony employees got kicked out and more people came in and I realized everybody else that was sitting around me like Michael Pachter and them all had these red VIP lanyards and I didn't have one of those so I was kind of like covering up my shirt or something so it looked like I had a lanyard and they never noticed you were just in the right place at the right time
[SPEAKER_10]: Every time the camera was on me, I was tweaking.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk a little bit about what happened at the Sony press conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: Obviously, we're going to get to Taboo when we come back with the Orange Launch Radio next Sunday, the regular episodes, but I lost a point in Taboo because Sony just opened right off the bat with somewhat of an apology, and one that it seems like most people accepted.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki's shaking his head a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was retarded.
[SPEAKER_09]: Really?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, yeah, we learned a valuable lesson with this PlayStation Outage set.
[SPEAKER_09]: We realized how much you like playing online.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all they fucking learned.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's all they learned.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was not like, oh, hey, we're sorry that your credit card information was compromised.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was...
[SPEAKER_09]: Hey, you guys like playing online.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to focus more on online play.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me ask the chat room how they feel about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chat room at chat.orange.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were you satisfied with Sony's apology?
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, how did that go over in the crowd there and with you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, first off, it was kind of interesting because you notice he never said they got hacked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: They called it an outage.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't say why it was an outage.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: But a lot of people around us, and you gotta realize since I'm in the VIP section, I'm around people who've been in the industry 20 years and all that stuff, and they kind of were more understanding than the people that were probably up in the normal seats and people at home.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they were like, okay, he did mention it, and Jack, he always, he does really good on stage.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like every year, you know, because he always goes up there and something is like bad press for Sony whenever he walks up at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: and he and his script writers handle it really well.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was scripted because I can see the teleprompters from where I was.
[SPEAKER_05]: I knew how much of the entire press conference was actually scripted.
[SPEAKER_05]: He did a good job and it stopped people from heckling him because that was one of the things somebody asked me on Twitter is how many people were going to interrupt the conference yelling about the PSN hack and nobody did.
[SPEAKER_05]: because they addressed it right in the beginning and said, hey, here's the elephant in the room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Going to some comments from our chat room at chat.orange.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranma in the chat room says, that was not an apology.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was more of a thank you for the fans for sticking out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's a good way of putting it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Technus says, yeah, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was mainly a canned response.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkTetsuya says, better him than Kazurai.
[SPEAKER_10]: Techie Q says, where was Kevin Butler?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good question.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you spot Kevin Butler there?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I did not spot Kevin Butler.
[SPEAKER_05]: He was there last year, but I think they're like, okay, we did that joke, and now we can move on.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just had to say, though, that it really did sound quite a bit more sincere than the other canned stuff we had before.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it was one of those things where it could have been a lot worse.
[SPEAKER_10]: But seeing as most of the Twittersphere at the end of the day seems to be dogging on Microsoft and Nintendo, again, I'm making broad generalizations, but most of the Twitter that I'm looking at is dogging on Microsoft and Nintendo, but is kind of praising Sony, I would say, distraction successful.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that Sony... That was a distraction event.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's exactly what their PR needed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Speaking of audience reaction, Bobby, since you were there, how was it when you, in the theater, when it was announced that the PlayStation Vita is going to be exclusive 3G on AT&T?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I can tell you, we heard it pretty clear.
[SPEAKER_10]: How bad was it where you were?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it really a lot of groans?
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't loud, but I mean, I heard like all the laughter of, yeah, we figured it, and all the groans.
[SPEAKER_05]: and we could even see Kaz was kind of like not expecting that I think if he had said the word Verizon instead it would have been a much different reaction but no it was very that was the one negative part of their press conference was that yeah I thought he didn't present it very well because honestly enough I was in the chat I was watching online and so I was watching the people chatting in the sidebar and those people are absolute blithering idiots but they were just like does that mean I can only get it through AT&T
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's like, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_06]: Please, just die.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it just struck me as interesting because I feel like he started to say something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like that deal had just been sealed within the past 48 hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wasn't quite prepared to say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how it came across to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what E3 is all about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have AT&T on my iPhone.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm one of those people that's like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm hoping there's a deal.
[SPEAKER_06]: As we have iPhone plans, that doesn't mean that we get on for free.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not buying a 3G PS Vita, Velveeta, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Screw that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just tether to your iPhone or tether to whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, let's talk about the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, I'll let you start it off since you were there.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was kind of the reaction to the Vita that you saw?
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you observe?
[SPEAKER_05]: The people that were around me, they're like, okay, why are they saying that this is the first time we've ever had augmented reality on a handheld because of the cameras?
[SPEAKER_05]: And why are they saying that this is the first time you've been able to do such and such when they're listing features of the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: But a lot of people are saying, okay,
[SPEAKER_05]: I can see why they're doing it.
[SPEAKER_05]: They think it's priced too high.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's also not the first time they've done it on a PlayStation Portable.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have the camera for their stupid iPad game and also for the Invisimals and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, interesting because a lot of the folks I was seeing online were really happy with that price point saying, oh,
[SPEAKER_10]: and here's one of the things that somebody said was that if it had HDMI output sold interesting what about that whole go ahead
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not get to play the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had it there, but it was a long-ass line, and I decided that taking part in their distraction booze was more important.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I haven't been able to play the Vita yet, but they did have it there.
[SPEAKER_05]: but nobody I knew had stood in the line because, like I said, there was distraction booze.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You were kind of talking about the whole HDMI out and all that.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of the games, and I'm sure this was the one that caught most people's attention, was The Ruin, the dungeon crawler, where they were playing it on the PSP and then did the trans-farring...
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and the question that I have about that is, do you have to be a PlayStation Plus member for the cloud savings?
[SPEAKER_10]: I would think so, yes, but obviously those are the details they want to leave out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me get to some of the immediate chat comments about the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: TigerClaw says, I gotta admit, the PS Vita for $249.99 is a pretty good price given all the tech that's in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Savalas in our chatroom says, does my new Vita have a firewall to protect me from hacks?
[SPEAKER_10]: Janai says, I will buy one, but it will feel like an updated PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: FrisbeeU says, nope, price is okay, but doesn't have any good games.
[SPEAKER_10]: Zappy says, I need a Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uncharted, Wipeout, Little Deviants, and LittleBigPlanet look great.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, TigerClaw said something here, and I want to kind of point this out.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said the PS Vita produced PS3 quality graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is incorrect.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is comparable to the PS3 because the Vita has a smaller resolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it could not do 1080p PS3 quality graphics.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's because of the resolution of the screen is not 1080p.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's able, and it's also the screen is smaller, it's able to get away with making something that is comparable to the PS3, but it is not exact to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hence why maybe the HDMI output may not be such a good idea.
[SPEAKER_10]: It may kind of ruin the quality.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right.
[SPEAKER_10]: It went over well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody liked that.
[SPEAKER_05]: A lot of people around me are like, why are they... Because the people that were around me in the VIP section, they're older than me.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're like, God, do we really need more 3D?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why are they pushing the 3D stuff on me?
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was kind of mixed in my area.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it got more pop up in the seats.
[SPEAKER_05]: but what's interesting is that they had Ken Levine come out to talk about him doing the Vita and they did not show Ratchet and Clank which they had back there and they didn't show Twisted Metal which they had playable on that floor at the end and so they left some of those out the only game I played after that was LittleBigPlanet 2 with the move support oh what did you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: They did kind of what we expected.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not Sackboy's prehistoric move.
[SPEAKER_05]: They did something a little different.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got to play some of the story levels in one of their minigames.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the main tool that they give you is I think it's like the Braininator or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's where you actually move things.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you're still playing a little bit exactly the way that you're used to with the buttons and the sticks and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you're just moving things around and bouncing yourself off with some of these
[SPEAKER_05]: and they did a really good job with it and then they've got a mini game that they had me play where it's one of those like it's kind of like cut the rope a little bit where there's a ball at the top and you're trying to get it to the end but you have to place things and then when you release the ball it kind of goes through this Rube Goldberg machine that you've created and that was kind of neat so this is something that's going to be like free patch free upgrade for LittleBigPlanet 2 right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I believe so.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not something I'm going to have to buy separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: They better, because on the box of LittleBigPlanet 2 it says better with PlayStation Move.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got the Move logo, but it's not part of the game right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I think that'd be kind of stupid if they put that on the box and said, oh, but you've got to pay extra to get that part that's in the blue sticker on the front of the box.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just better if you own it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It just makes you feel good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good job, Jeremy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wasn't that the same guy that showed out the stupid medieval tech demo last time when they were first showing off the move stuff?
[SPEAKER_05]: The medieval tech demo last time was the sports champions thing, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was another move being shown.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kobe Bryant came out and sucked at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just about to say that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, the other big guest that was at Sony's press conference was the Kobe Bryant moment.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I tweeted you and I'm like, quick, throw your shoe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but I like my shoe too much.
[SPEAKER_10]: What kind of reaction did Kobe get from the crowd?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it sounded very mixed.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was, I mean, he got some pops.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, yeah, I guess, you know, when he kind of made jokes about himself or something, that got some reactions, but
[SPEAKER_10]: It was a pretty resounding endorsement by him as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, I'm sure he gets paid handsomely to say it, but still, you know, you couldn't help but feel the little punch in the gut to EA after what happened to them last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: HGMI Cable, $499
[SPEAKER_10]: 3D Monitor.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, so it won't actually get TV signal.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it probably doesn't have an antenna built in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, and it's probably going to be sized like your computer monitor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I don't know if they said what size it would be.
[SPEAKER_10]: 24-inch.
[SPEAKER_10]: 24, so you're right on the money.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, 24-inch.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's not really TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a monitor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, I want to just mention something because I know I'm going to go back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm watching chat, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Randy, you...
[SPEAKER_05]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_10]: Me too, because that means traffic on Thursday won't be as bad as it was the year before.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was interesting the way he marketed it when he was mentioning the new monitor.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's perfect for a dorm room.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought that right there was a huge, like, we know exactly who needs this and who our audience is for this.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I think that was right on the money.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's going to cause this thing to get on a lot of college wish lists this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: except for me except for you, not interested?
[SPEAKER_05]: oh yeah, because you don't do 3D I can't see the 3D and actually, it screwed me up because I was so close and at an angle and I put those glasses on because they were showing a lot of us a lot of trailers in 3D it was actually messing me up because I usually if I'm looking straight at it it's fine, it's just a darker 2D except for maybe some things at the edges
[SPEAKER_05]: but being at that angle, it sucked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now one thing that they said they were going to do with the 3D technology, this is the stuff with the technology that I really am looking forward to and I would actually be confused, is because they do the shutter technology, they have, you know, they've actually implemented, and I don't know if they're showing it here or not, where, you know, instead of having each eye shutter differently, they have each pair of glasses shuttered differently,
[SPEAKER_05]: You can actually have two different screens or people seeing two different images on screen.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I thought that was pretty cool too and very wave of the future.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very much so.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to get to Nintendo here in a minute, but a couple of things I've got to mention out of the Sony press conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: We won't have time to hit everything, but DarkSakura, I know you had been looking at Star Trek The Game and some of the announcements that were made around that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you hear about the PlayStation Move that's going to look like a phaser?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to get an appointment to see the game I hope so too I want to count the lens flares
[SPEAKER_08]: But with anything that new, I'm going to keep my judgment reserved.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think you can count that high.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I mean, they are investing a lot into this because it wasn't just this official game, but I guess a PSN precursor.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess what comes to mind, Dead Rising 2K0-esque thing for the Star Wars game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, excuse me, Star Trek game is supposed to be there as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: More information next year, a little closer to the movie's launch, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, I gotta let you have a moment because they did mention at the PlayStation 3 conference exclusives coming to Saints Row the 3rd and I know you've gotta have an opinion on that game
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't really care about the exclusives that they have coming to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still getting it on 360.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: But what about the game itself?
[SPEAKER_09]: The game looks fucking amazing.
[SPEAKER_09]: I saw some gameplay footage they had during an interview prior to one of the conferences.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have the guy just doing rustling moves on random pedestrians.
[SPEAKER_09]: They even showed the giant purple dildo weapon and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to admit, I approve of that approach.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Go big.
[SPEAKER_09]: But here's the thing, too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Like, I watched this morning the trailer.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have a new trailer out there for Postal 3, and I gotta tell you, it looks like shit.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they're like, oh, look how edgy we are.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: Saints Row 3 blows that shit away.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like, who gives a fuck that you have, you know, a guy dressed up like a nutsack?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a weapon that's a giant purple penis that you can hit people with in Saints Row 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you want to do edgy, you're going to have to make a game based on the Human Centipede Part 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know how much room we have for masturbating with barbed wire.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, did you see on the PS Vita, and Dan, I know you are a fighting game fan.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hang on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to interject on the Saints Row thing real quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't seen it yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have done the most genius marketing here at E3.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_05]: They bought or rented out for the week that parking lot across the street from Staples Center and offered free parking to all E3 attendees that get in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they have bikini models at the entrance trying to direct people in.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got tents in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've got it all decked out in Saints Row.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know where we're going Thursday.
[SPEAKER_10]: No doubt.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan, I know you're a fighting game fan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie's giving her husband a stare down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie, come on.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know you want to see.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, this is radio, so no one can see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie, even you have to admit, boobies.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a 2D fighter?
[SPEAKER_06]: Made out of a 3D fighter?
[SPEAKER_06]: That got very little reaction.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, the thing was it was weird to me because as much as I like that idea of Street Fighter X Tekken, then they announce, okay, so it's Street Fighter World and Tekken World collides, and then we're going to throw in Cole from Infamous.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's like, what does he have to do with anything?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Namco likes throwing in random characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're like, if we're going to put our Tekken franchise on the line here, we've got to have random people who have nothing to do with the universe in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We can't have Darth Vader, so here's Cole.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_09]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: You can have shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I can make it all the way through Tekken Street Mode with Gon.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we gotta get to the next press conference this morning.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's talk about Nintendo for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm gonna leave the room so that I can actually hear Loki without going deaf.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_10]: You don't want me to talk about Jane's Addiction?
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah!
[SPEAKER_10]: I totally forgot to ask Bobby about what happened behind the scenes at the Sony press conference before we get to Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: When we're watching at home, it cuts out at the end, but you were there for what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like two and a half more hours, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, it ended at ten.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what was happening?
[SPEAKER_05]: At the end of the press conference, the entire stage went away and that's where all their demo kiosks were.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they brought food, lots of food, like grilled cheese sandwiches and pasta salad and cookies and cupcakes and other, like, it was great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then beer and alcohol flowing open bar.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then at 9 o'clock, James Addiction comes on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which, you know, I'm like, okay, I saw them in Activision last year, so I'm good.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they came out and did an hour set.
[SPEAKER_10]: and for no particular reason then, hey, we got Jane's Addiction because we're so many.
[SPEAKER_08]: They better did Bin Cut Ceiling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they had Mix Master Mike there too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love him too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it would be like him, like they were like just, they had all their trailers of their games but like it was messing with the color and everything and that was kind of the visuals around.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they also like had all these like scantily clad women like on top of the stages, areas that were like
[SPEAKER_05]: still doing like doing slow dances and stuff and it was to the techno music and it was kind of weird because we're sitting there playing video games while there's like a hot chick above us like kind of doing a pole game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I guess they knew their audience.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So and how many Sony beers did you have again?
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: How many Sony beers did you have again?
[SPEAKER_05]: Honestly because they had crappy beers only one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tonight is the night that I'm going to have way too many beers.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had crappy beer?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: We gotta get through Nintendo's press conference so that Bobby can get to the beer drinking.
[SPEAKER_10]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, with all due respect, I gotta let Loki kick this one off.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, Loki, why don't you give us a little report on Nintendo's press conference?
[SPEAKER_09]: So Nintendo came out and basically showed off some of their 3DS stuff and no one cared.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, they started off actually by talking about the Zelda 25th Anniversary Edition.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which was awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: which you know they had like an orchestra they had an orchestra they had Miyamoto out there and my Zelda fanboy Saul was like yes it was beautiful and then they were talking about how they're kind of celebrating on all the different platforms for the 3DS of course you had you know the Game Boy Color Zelda game that's available for download on there it's gonna be the first one the Game Boy Color Virtual Console I bought it
[SPEAKER_09]: Sucker!
[SPEAKER_09]: And then for the Nintendo Wii, obviously, Skyward Sword is going to be available later this year.
[SPEAKER_09]: For the DSiWare, which I'm assuming also means the 3DS as well, they're going to have Zelda The Four Swords Adventure as a free download, which is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Too bad it's not playable by itself, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then...
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, they're also going to do some sort of pre-order bonus for the 3DS with Ocarina that you're going to be able to get a music CD with the soundtrack from the game for if you register the game quite early on the Nintendo Club thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then, of course, they're going to do some sort of orchestra...
[SPEAKER_09]: Live shows and stuff like that with the Zelda music.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's going to be all over the world.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're going to have a CD for that that's going to be available with the Skyward Sword game.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then 3DS stuff, they showed off the new Mario game, which looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's kind of like a cross between Mario Galaxy and Mario 64, which is not bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Star Fox, they showed a little bit of that.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just souped up Star Fox 64.
[SPEAKER_09]: Um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Luigi's Mansion 2
[SPEAKER_08]: It was cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has its fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, the best part of it was when you went into the attic, and then the lightning would flash, and then his shadow would be hanging by a noose.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, and then, okay, so they do the Kid Icarus and all these 3DS games.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Kid Icarus, and then Mario Kart, what the fuck's up with Mario Kart, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Mario Kart, now with, you know, monster trucks and, you know, hang gliders, and that's innovative.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they're like, you've never raced this game before.
[SPEAKER_09]: And all the first few tracks that they were showing were all tracks from other games.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm like, actually, yes, I have raced every single one of those.
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: and then they go to say hey what are we calling this thing uh well you know how everybody hated the name Wii but then they eventually got used to it and stuff we got another one for you Wii U what I like seriously they said Wii U is the name of that I was like my brain hurts for how stupid this is but you know people will get used to it they can still change their mind
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan and I were saying before the show, what if they just called it the Nintendo U?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that would have been like U as in Ultra IDK.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think Nintendo U would have been fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have to do Wii because people are fucking stupid and they're not going to understand.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can use my Wii stuff.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, then they know that they can use their Wii stuff with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Great.
[SPEAKER_06]: The big problem is already everyone's kind of half assuming, I thought it was a new system, not just a new controller.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is a new system.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is a new system.
[SPEAKER_06]: People don't know that.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're just like, oh, I just use it with my existing Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know Bobby is dying to jump in here in a minute here, but let me let Loki wrap up here.
[SPEAKER_10]: What other impressions did Wii U leave you with?
[SPEAKER_09]: Um, it's a neat piece of hardware, but it's just, it just seems so gimmicky to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, I'm sorry, it's just, how expensive is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, some of the graphics, like their little tech demo pre-rendered thing look kind of cool, you know, what it does.
[SPEAKER_09]: But the whole conference, they didn't fucking announce anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, okay, they hinted that Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: is coming to, you know, the Wii U and 3DS.
[SPEAKER_09]: They hinted at that, and then they said, oh, but that's going to be, you know, a while down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, just like they hinted at Pikmin coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: And how long has that been?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh wait, it's still not out yet.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, you know, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, let's get them all excited and promise this game that's not going to come out for two years.
[SPEAKER_09]: And then Wii U. And I'm sorry, it's just like the tech demos they showed off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh hey, look, I can play Wii Sports Golf and I can put this controller on the ground and make it so I can see a ball there and stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Bobby's been waiting patiently.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, what do you think about them showing just a controller and not really showing the specs of the console off?
[SPEAKER_04]: Wee-oo-wee-oo-wee-oo-wee-oo-wee-oo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gunpow entered the pit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is there a fire truck driving by?
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, first I want to jump in because we started with the 3DS stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I do want to mention that I have like 100 Street Pass me's now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've almost got like all the puzzle pieces of all puzzles.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I played Mario Kart 3DS because they had a couple of games out in tents and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I actually did play it and I enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean all did the same tricks on how to boost around corners and stuff is still there.
[SPEAKER_05]: and stuff, but to me it was Mario Kart meets Diddy Kong Racing.
[SPEAKER_10]: How so?
[SPEAKER_05]: With all the different ways that you could, you know, like either you would be a plane or you'd go underwater which they didn't really do underwater in Diddy Kong Racing, but like with the planes and stuff and monster trucks and having the different types of vehicles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's kind of what it reminded me of, but it was still Mario Kart and, you know, it's
[SPEAKER_05]: For fans of Mario Kart, they'll love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do people really give a shit about more vehicle types?
[SPEAKER_09]: What they want you to do is they want you to come up with some new tracks and stop fucking repeating tracks from every goddamn game that you've already released.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would be nice to hear just a tinge about the online capability because 3DS already has better online than the Wii.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I would like to hear more about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Bobby?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, the tracks that they had in the demo that I played, you know, because the ones like that went underwater, you know, and there is, you know, different physics underwater.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, you know, gliding through the air and having to determine where you're going to glide and when you're going to go up and down.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I mean, the demo had new tracks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't recognize any of the tracks that were in the demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the trailer probably showed tracks that you might have seen, you know, segments of tracks that you've seen before.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, like, yeah, there's a track that looks like the Donkey Kong tracks from the N64.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's not the same layout.
[SPEAKER_05]: It just has the same scenery.
[SPEAKER_05]: So don't write it off based on the three second snippets in the trailers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it does, it changes enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, granted, yes, it's still Mario Kart, and yes, it's still, you know, not new but fun, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, a lot of people are like, what's wrong with more of what I liked?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just like how they thought it was necessary to put motorcycles in the Wii version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's a kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_09]: You don't need fucking motorcycles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, now let's put monster trucks in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excite Boats
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me throw out this question for the chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: For all you folks in chat who do not currently own a 3DS, are you interested in 3DS now?
[SPEAKER_10]: They showed more titles.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought it was interesting, and that's the question I've got for our chat, chat.orange.radio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you interested in a 3DS now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I thought it was interesting because leading into that, Reggie just showed why he was Reggie.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he said something, and Bobby, maybe you can help fill me in here.
[SPEAKER_10]: He said something like,
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, you want to see the same old stuff again, but you want to see innovation.
[SPEAKER_10]: He goes kind of like, conflict?
[SPEAKER_10]: Fine, we can handle that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's our industry.
[SPEAKER_10]: Here you go.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're fucking Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Suck it down.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, let's see innovation.
[SPEAKER_09]: And you will like it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk innovation, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's start off.
[SPEAKER_10]: Innovation is deeper and wider.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what she said.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, um...
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's talk innovation here, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you can sit on park benches and go swimming.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's the same fucking game still!
[SPEAKER_09]: Same damn game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Same everything.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's the same patterns.
[SPEAKER_09]: I even saw the screenshots.
[SPEAKER_09]: The same fucking patterns that have been in that game since it first came out on the goddamn GameCube are in this stupid game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, it came out on Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I understand that, but over here... For God's sakes, it's fucking Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_09]: I care, because you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: They get away with this shit with every goddamn franchise that they have, because their fans love it.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: Fucking Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: is coming out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I bet you it's going to be all the fucking same characters again.
[SPEAKER_09]: Fuck, they're just going to port that shit from the Wii, is what's going to end up happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's what makes it a franchise.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want the Smash Brothers 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, I meant Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was officially going to start playing my GBA one again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I have to ask you, as a follow-up, why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I watched the anime last night.
[SPEAKER_08]: The other night.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it was super cute, and I was like, I remember this in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I miss playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can ask Dan.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was here the whole time.
[SPEAKER_06]: As soon as they took out Unlockable Nest games, fuck that franchise.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, do you...
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you think it's odd that they left Animal Crossing and Paper Mario out of the conference totally?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, except for, I guess, logos at the end?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that they felt they had enough that they were showing that, you know, they didn't keep you.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I was actually surprised at is that there were no live demos of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't bring those two out to show people.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder if that, is that maybe because of the whole 3D, 2D thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, I'm talking about the Wii U. Oh, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I moved on already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sorry, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they didn't bring it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: They showed videos.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm like, is it even here?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm seeing all these conceptual videos and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even think it was even at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because usually they would have brought it out or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Tethered to lovely looking ladies, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me get to some of the feedback from our chatroom on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, we'll move into Wii U. For the non-3DS owners, are you interested in a 3DS now?
[SPEAKER_10]: Geovidea says, no, can't use the 3D on the 3DS anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: Burr says, still not interested.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dungeon Buster, not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blender, not interested in the 3DS at all.
[SPEAKER_10]: So there's some of the negatives, but then we get some other positives.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dartesia, oh, definitely.
[SPEAKER_10]: New Mario Kart looks neat.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay, Tanooki suit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was Tanooki suit in Mario Kart, or is he just blurring the other Mario games?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Defective Candy says, Interesting, because there's not a lot of yeses.
[SPEAKER_09]: And here's the thing about Star Fox, that he was talking about fucking innovation, how you can tilt it to, you can optionally, I guess, tilt it to control your ship.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, except it fucks up the 3D when you do that, dumbass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, no kidding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's put tilt controls on a 3D game that requires you to keep the system at an actual view so that you can see the 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess that's for people that don't give a shit about 3D.
[SPEAKER_09]: But then again, why the fuck are you buying a 3DS sim?
[SPEAKER_09]: Or better yet, why the fuck are you buying a game that came out on the Nintendo 64?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, because that's an innovation for Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_09]: We can port old shit and make it slightly better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby wants to jump in.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, I have a 3DS because it's a higher resolution top screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: for me as well I bought a 3DS because I skipped the DSi and I skipped the DSi XL and the last one I had owned was a DS Lite so I thought it's time for upgrade why not that's why I did it but anyway let's move on to Wii U because I know Bobby wants to move on let me throw a question out to chat that we'll get to in a minute
[SPEAKER_10]: and then I want to talk Bobby your time with the hands-on Wii U on a scale of 1 to 10 chatters 10 being very and 1 being not at all I'm sounding like a club Nintendo survey but I'm just kind of curious here 1 being not at all how interested are you in Wii U scale of 1 to 10 1 not at all 10 very Bobby you got your hands on it after 4 hours of waiting right what do you think
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, what I want to say is I want to give a history lesson.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back in 2005, at Nintendo's press conference, they decided that they were going to show this brand new revolutionary control scheme.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they showed the remote, and they did, you know, that was when, you know, Miyamoto came out, slashing Zelda doors and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they showed it, and when you played the games, you realized they were running on GameCubes.
[SPEAKER_05]: and that's where the whole joke of two GameCubes duct taped together came from.
[SPEAKER_05]: In 2006, they actually showed the console that the controller was for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fast forward to 2011, they are showing the controller for their next console, but they're not telling you that much about the console itself.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're focusing on the input mechanism.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next year, we're actually going to see more of the console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, the demos that they're showing here are running on new hardware,
[SPEAKER_05]: But, it's not, they even show a box there, but I was actually told that's not running anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like running a, there's a PC back there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Running a, you know, a souped up wheat weed dev kit.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's what they're running things off of.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, they're not ready to talk about the console yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're trying to get people to concentrate on the controller and the conceptual demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: There is not a single retail game
[SPEAKER_05]: being shown, except, well, okay, there's one retail game, and it's a third-party game that's being shown here at E3 for the Wii U, so I kind of wanted to straighten that out.
[SPEAKER_10]: Which one is that, the Lego game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which, which, what's the third-party game, the Lego game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, no, they're showing Ghost Recon Online.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know what though, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_09]: You're wrong because those are going to be an actual game because that's what Wii Sports and Wii Play ended up being.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's all those tech demos and they've had, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to be innovative.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to slap that shit together, kind of duct tape it a little bit and throw it out with a controller because people are suckers and they want free controllers.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Bobby, that should make Bobby happy because that Chase Me is basically Pac-Man vs. Pac-Man vs. is awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what I'm saying is like,
[SPEAKER_05]: People are, you know, when people look at these stuff, they're going to be like, wow, they're going to make me pay $50 for Chase Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they're not going to make you pay $50 for Chase Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going to make you pay $50 for Chase Me, Battle Me, and all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, I mean, they were very adamant with me when I talked to people that actually worked at Nintendo and weren't just hired for the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which you could tell, by the way, because the people that worked at Nintendo have QR codes of their knees on their badge that you could scan.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they actually were very adamant saying, these are conceptual demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are not final products.
[SPEAKER_05]: These are to get your mind working and trying to tell you this is the type of stuff you can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, we may see the Shield Pose game and Chase Me and Battle Me in some kind of compilation, but not as standalone games.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only standalone games, like they had the Mario game running there and then Ghost Recon Online running.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the rest were tech demos.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just so you guys know, the feedback on a scale of 1 to 10, 10 being very, 1 being not at all, how interested are you in the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_10]: I see lots of, it's just all over the board.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's some nines, but there's also some ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's a zero from Jovidea.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of fives and fours.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then like a six.
[SPEAKER_08]: So there's a universal meh.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all over.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's because it's all conceptual right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: People aren't seeing final products right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: and, you know, even the hardware isn't finalized.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so, and they didn't really emphasize enough that, you know, this is a new console.
[SPEAKER_05]: You could actually walk away there and, I mean, even I thought this is just a new controller for my Wii.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, you know, right now they've, you know, right now you're playing some of the games with Wii Remote.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a Wii sensor bar underneath each TV, even though there's a sensor bar in the Wii Wii Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, it's
[SPEAKER_05]: Essentially, I beat this out of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: The console is called the Wii U, and they haven't named the controller yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to name it Bob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Dan?
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wonder this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are we ready for the era of the game controller to cost $100 plus?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't think it will because that touchscreen is not, it's the DS touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I called it on Sunday's show in some regards.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's a six and a half.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's larger.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a lot larger.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: 79 maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's larger, but it's not multi-touch.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's one big thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Finish your thought.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't seem to be like I couldn't do any multi-touch stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe their current demos don't have multi-touch, but yeah, it's just a larger version of the DSi screen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, were there any demos that were using more than one of those controllers on the same system?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because that was something I noticed at the conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: None of the games were using more than one of those controllers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everything was supplemented with additional Wiimotes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get a good look at Battle.me.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the only one that might have, but everything else it was either, you know, it was a one-player experience or, you know, it was one person using that and then four Wii remotes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think I watched a video of Battle.me on Nintendo's website and I want to say the person flying the spaceship was using the controller and everybody else was on a Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_10]: So no, if the videos are to be the definitive answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: I thought that was interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like maybe the price of the controller really isn't going to be such an issue because they aren't really going to have you or want you to have more than one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe the games aren't really going to need more than one.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's baloney.
[SPEAKER_08]: That sounds to me like just the whole thing with the GBA connector.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the same theory.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't they just make a connector for the DS?
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: The controller is not creating any graphics, and I think that might be why.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're actually, the graphics on the controller is being created by the Wii U, and it's being sent wirelessly with very little lag to the controller.
[SPEAKER_10]: That makes sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's some technology you can see right now in the PS3 and the PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can log into your PS3 on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a very little advertised feature, but you can fire up your PSP and log into your PS3 and see the image on your PSP, and it does work.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, remember back when Kasarai was first showing Ridge Racer, the original concept was that that PSP was supposed to be your rearview mirror.
[SPEAKER_10]: We never saw that really fully realized, but the idea was out there a while ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: If no one minds, actually, if I go back to an old point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because she just made the point to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ciara has said that as a person who bought around eight different versions of Final Fantasy VII, I don't care if it's the same game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Talk about back to the Animal Crossing thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fans will buy it if they like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's why it stays the same.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then the fans can't complain when they say, oh, well, it's just the same game.
[SPEAKER_09]: They didn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Four, not seven.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, you're in a unique position that none of us and probably most of our chatters and even listeners are in tonight where you're the only one that's actually held one of these Wii U's.
[SPEAKER_10]: So coming out of there, how are you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I know you said at the end of the press conference you were feeling a little mint, but coming out of the demo, are you thinking you're going to buy a Wii U or are you kind of like, I need to see more next year?
[SPEAKER_04]: I want to hand Nintendo my wallet.
[SPEAKER_05]: and just say, here, take it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what was it about it that just made you go, I'm sold?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I can see kind of more, you know, I can actually contextualize a lot more and I can see where they're going with it and a lot of the neat stuff that they're doing and the neat gameplay that they're doing with that and what they can do.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can kind of see where they're going with it, which a lot of people usually can't.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, when they first announced the DS, everybody's like, why would I want a touchscreen on my games?
[SPEAKER_05]: and now, you know, what's, you know, iPhone games are really popular.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, and I could see where that was going and nobody else could figure out why would I want a touchscreen gaming system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually saw when I first saw the DS, here's why you'd want a touchscreen gaming system.
[SPEAKER_05]: I could actually see it and it's true, you know.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of people are like, oh, this is a gimmick and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a lot of Nintendo's innovations have been copied by everybody else and they were called gimmicks at first.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, like Rumble was a gimmick.
[SPEAKER_05]: and now we have touch screens on everything, motion controls are on everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that Nintendo is going to innovate in this space and you're going to see in a couple years other companies copying them and it's not the first time they've done this because they've already done the GameCube, Game Boy Advance thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they've already got a track record of some of the stuff they already know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Holiday 2012 It'll be Holiday 2012
[SPEAKER_06]: Just from being in retail, Nintendo always saves the machines for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_06]: But not the 3DS?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, not the portables.
[SPEAKER_05]: The consoles.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is something from one of those guys that has the QR code on his badge.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's the official word then.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bobby, what did you think about the Analog 6 being above the actual D-pad and the face buttons?
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a little backwards compared to the controllers now.
[SPEAKER_10]: 3DS is that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: It felt natural.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because of where the triggers are, there's the triggers and then the LB and the RB, but because of where they are, that is the exact position your thumb would really want to be if you wanted to use the dual analog sticks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, if I'm not mistaken, you were kind of in this wee line yourself and doing this whole thing, kind of going in there by yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, I know, when I'm in a big environment like that by myself, because I did E3 myself one year, or at least one of the days, and one of the things that I couldn't help but do was listen to other people around me and do a little bit of people watching.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I was being a little nosy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were you doing any of that, maybe in the Nintendo booth and kind of picking up some of the buzz from people around you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really, because everybody around me spoke different languages.
[SPEAKER_10]: Touche.
[SPEAKER_10]: The controller is actually lighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's about the same as my iPad.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I don't have a cover on it, it feels about the same weight as my iPad does.
[SPEAKER_10]: And how did it feel?
[SPEAKER_10]: And as for...
[SPEAKER_05]: It felt natural, like, I mean, you'd think it's big, but then you hold it, and, you know, I mean, I have normal-sized hands, and it felt fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you're not reaching all the way down to the bottom, like, all the buttons are easily accessible.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, it's, you know, yeah, it's also, I mean, it's also a prototype controller as well, it could change at the end, and it was also, like, tied down, like, four different ways, so you couldn't take it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that probably added to the weight as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: But no, it felt natural.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was lighter than I expected.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it was wired when I played it.
[SPEAKER_10]: ah so maybe it's feeding well no because they they showed in the other concept videos it's going to be wireless and they talked about beaming the image wirelessly but it's too early it's early on the proto pictures I've seen online look like they have a charge port on them I want to know what this parrot has to do with anything Bobby what I'm sorry but you were gonna say something we were cutting you off
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's wired here.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a prototype.
[SPEAKER_05]: Things change.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 3DS didn't really change all that much, but I remember the original DS was different when it came out.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is a prototype thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It could change its layout.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even think they know what the tech specs are going to be in the final product.
[SPEAKER_10]: How is it ergonomically?
[SPEAKER_10]: Like I said, when I held it
[SPEAKER_05]: My fingers went to all the right places.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the back, which you don't get to feel that much, there is actual grooves for you to hold with your three fingers that aren't playing with the triggers.
[SPEAKER_05]: It felt good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked it up and my hands were in the right place.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't hurt.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: On the back, it's got curves on the back for you to hold on to and for your fingers to naturally curve around.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, I was thinking the same logic, though, with the Saturn dual analog controller on the front.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't look like it would be very comfortable, but it's one of the most comfortable controllers there are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, I was wondering if it was along the same lines.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had an appointment with EA Sports, so I got to play the pre-alpha build of the new SSX.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I can see that people who like SSX are really going to like this.
[SPEAKER_05]: They've talked about how they've got this snow avalanche system that is dynamic.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not like split-second or anything that has these predetermined catastrophic events.
[SPEAKER_05]: They actually say that they take the stability of the area, how stable it is, to see if that actually affects more snow or stops the snow, and that's one of the modes where you're trying to survive.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not die.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're trying to get down this mountain without getting crushed by snow.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very uplifting.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, you know, they did basically Google Earth.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: They licensed with NASA topography data of the entire world.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they said it's nice to have friends in high places.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was their pun.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they had all the major mountain ranges, and you can pick those mountains.
[SPEAKER_05]: to go down, and it's the actual mountains from the actual NASA topography data.
[SPEAKER_05]: And those are the mountains that you go down.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they've done some things with it, like one of the mountains that's on the China border, they decided they were going to put pieces of the Great Wall of China in there that you could grind off of and stuff, so it's not completely realistic.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it's still, it's a lot more than they've done in the past.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it worked well.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it's not a final build by any means.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was some lag in it, but I mean, that's because it's a pre-alpha build.
[SPEAKER_05]: so basically I saw that and they showed me some stuff about FIFA which I'm not a huge soccer fan but it was kind of neat some of the stuff they did so I saw that and then I walked through Microsoft's booth to see what was kind of in there and I'm going to go play that Disneyland Connect game because I know where I'm going Friday and Friday is a research trip Friday is a research trip
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But apparently in the demo, like I guess in the briefing, because I didn't see the briefing, I was in the air, but apparently I guess it cuts off at the end of the Peter Pan ride.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the presser?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just thought it was a time thing, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it cuts off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently you do actually fight Captain Hook.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now they showed that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it was in a video or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: What else?
[SPEAKER_05]: There was that, and then I walked by and I immediately thought of Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh dear.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because there were these four chicks wearing black dresses up on a stage doing the time warp.
[SPEAKER_10]: From the Rocky Horror Picture Show?
[SPEAKER_10]: And I just had to get pictures.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so this means they're doing a Rocky Horror Picture Show video game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_08]: yes, it is called Glee Karaoke Revolution 2 no you've mentioned the four letter G word therefore I must go I even took video for you oh wait, here we go you mentioned the four letter G word now I must go throw up yes, and I did get the picture thank you Bobby did you get some hands on time with anything else?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not really, I mean, I did, I stopped by, I have a friend who works at Double Fine, and I walked by and played Trenched, which is their Xbox Live arcade game, which is a third-person mech tower defense game.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Where you're fighting waves and waves of enemies, and you can drop turrets and different things like a tower defense game, but then you're also in this mech shooting at them.
[SPEAKER_05]: and running around and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was two player online because I was playing with the person standing next to me on his console.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, this demo, they dropped you at a mission that's like in the last third of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've already gone through the tutorial by this point and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was a little confusing because I haven't really done much with the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can see people liking it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's
[SPEAKER_05]: Not over the top like you'd expect from Kim Schafer, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: So what's on deck for you tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_10]: What are your plans?
[SPEAKER_10]: And I know we mentioned it at the top of the show, but I'm sure you want to talk about your Twitter project.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have two appointments tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_05]: And other than that, I'm letting people direct me.
[SPEAKER_05]: My two appointments, just so people kind of know, at 1 o'clock I'm going to visit a Georgia company because being in Georgia, I actually have contacts there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go to CCP Games where they just announced that Dust 514 is a PlayStation 3 exclusive.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they're actually going to show the connectivity between Dust 514 on the PlayStation 3 and EVE Online, the Excel spreadsheet simulator on the PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm very curious about that because we missed that with so much coming out of Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I'm very interested in this whole how does this game impact the MMO of EVE Online.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interested.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, and I am too because I have played EVE a little bit so I actually understand the universe and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm going to go in there and see them.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then at 4 o'clock I do have a Bethesda appointment where I'm going to get to see the demo of Skyrim that everybody else has seen already.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I guess it was on TV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we saw a portion of what will be a longer demo for you.
[SPEAKER_10]: I heard it's a 30-minute demo behind the doors.
[SPEAKER_10]: So very curious about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: So good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Those are two games we can definitely talk more about tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so if folks want to follow you on Twitter...
[SPEAKER_05]: Bobby Blackwolf and tomorrow also I'm going to be trying to hit Atlas so if you have any specific questions about Catherine or any of other Atlas' games I'm probably going to hit them after the CCP because they're next door.
[SPEAKER_10]: And our Chibi Wolf picture?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go try to find Natsume and get your Chibi Wolf picture Need to go play Saints Row 3 I need my cow Actually, the one thing not to load you up with assignments, Bobby maybe you already know the answers to a couple of these but there's two things that are kind of missing right now where I'm like, what happened to... One of them is Grand Theft Auto V Everybody was convinced Grand Theft Auto V was debuting at E3 and we have heard nothing It's gone, it's not there, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: I have not seen it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the other big question mark is what the hell is Activision doing?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they've got a booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll go stop by them.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I think they're doing this little game that's called Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, all right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't know if you've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, but still, when Activision's a huge company like EA, and EA, I could name easily like 10 games EA, we know they're doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Activision's got maybe a couple.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, they have more than that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but where's the Bungie game?
[SPEAKER_10]: I just thought there'd be more coming out from Activision.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe because of the lack of press conference.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any music games?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they've scaled back.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, it's Modern Warfare 3 for them, X-Men Destiny, Spider-Man, whatever the... Spyro.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, the Activision, if I'm not mistaken, was also... Spyro, Cha-Ching, Skylanders is what that's called.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's basically, hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_09]: We're going to charge you $70 for the starter kit, and then if you want your individual, you know, collect-them-all figurines that you can use for playable characters in the game, those are each going to cost you $8.
[SPEAKER_10]: If I'm not mistaking, wasn't Activision also at one time the company that said, we're just not doing E3 anymore?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Their big title now is so big that they're just like, we don't need E3 really.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they're going to do a show, we'll make an appearance, but we don't want to spend the money or the time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then I hope Battlefield 3 blows the shit out of them because that game looks nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: everybody wants to see Activision put in their place everybody wants to see Activision I just watched like a mission there was like a tank mission or whatever that they're showing with Battlefield 3 it's just amazing I mean Call of Duty it's pretty action packed it's an ultra realistic looking war game wow another one it looks way better though they all look great but I mean it's just like
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_05]: We gotta let Bobby go find some... No, no, hang on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta respond to something in here in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kaijudo says the reason why there isn't a GTA 5 is because Agent is coming out for GTA 5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, I can't remember who exactly I heard this from, but it was from somebody I trust.
[SPEAKER_05]: Apparently they heard somebody ask, I think it was Jack Trenton, is Agent still a PS3 exclusive?
[SPEAKER_05]: And his response was, you'll have to ask Rockstar about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby, we got to let you go find some good beer in LA.
[SPEAKER_10]: But before we do, I can't imagine anyone that listens to Orange Lounge Radio doesn't already know about your show.
[SPEAKER_10]: But just in case there's like the one person that doesn't, tell us a little bit about your show.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the opening band.
[SPEAKER_10]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I am on at 8 p.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eastern, 5 p.m.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pacific, right before Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's me talking for about 30 minutes, and then I take calls, and everybody tells me I'm wrong for the next 20 minutes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I goof off with Rob and DarkSakura for 10 minutes, and that's my show.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is high entertainment.
[SPEAKER_05]: All Games Radio is where it's live, or bobbyblackwolf.com is the website where I've almost, you know, I'm not as old as they all are,
[SPEAKER_05]: But I'm coming upon six years next month.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's still very impressive.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very impressive.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're still a big boy.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can sit at the big kids table.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Bobby, we'll be talking to you again tomorrow and have a lot of fun at E3 tomorrow and just play as many games as you can, all right?
[SPEAKER_05]: I will.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Thursday also is wide open.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have any appointments on that day.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, if I don't get through it tomorrow, I want to get through it Thursday.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I want to say...
[SPEAKER_05]: because some people don't believe me when I say this and they started asking me, go ask Microsoft if they're going to charge for Skype.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, no, I can't because I don't have that kind of access.
[SPEAKER_10]: Right, right, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Try to keep your questions to games that maybe aren't AAA titles or from AAA developers.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to find, you know, like this year's Scribblenauts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Scribblenauts I had never heard of until I saw it in the back corner of WB's booth a couple years ago and it blew me away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Katamari Damacy I really hadn't heard of until Namco showed it off a couple years ago at E3, or many years ago at E3 now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm looking for those games, and if you hear something that maybe you want to hear more about that GameSpot and IGN at the big sites aren't going to cover, those are the games I want to find.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to be able to ask Peter Molyneux about Fable the 30.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not going to be able to ask Sony about if they're going to be doing this or that with the Vita, because they're not going to talk to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the smaller desks,
[SPEAKER_05]: They will answer my question.
[SPEAKER_05]: And those are the people I want to talk to.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Internet, you have your homework assignment.
[SPEAKER_10]: Twitter.com slash BobbyBlackWolf.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I just want to clarify, even though Bobby will still be at the show Thursday, we will not be having an E3 special Thursday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything Bobby does on Thursday, he will be doing on his own show this upcoming Sunday when he broadcasts live.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we will not be here live on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all weird, this programming thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to have to draw a grid.
[SPEAKER_10]: But follow our websites and stay tuned for all the information in our Twitters.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's how you can stay on top of the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: and on my show Sunday night I will actually talk about the actual demos of the Wii Wii Wii Wii Wii Wii that I played and how each of them felt and played and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well Bobby we're going to let you go so we can get to some other calls and I've got to call Shane too who's also there waiting to talk to us.
[SPEAKER_10]: So take care buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I get to go watch Nerds riding a mechanical bull now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome, have fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you Thank you
[SPEAKER_10]: That was pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I've been going on Twitter and seeing random, this is bullshit!
[SPEAKER_08]: Wii U what?
[SPEAKER_08]: So my Twitter's been a source of hilarity.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dan, what about you?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been streaming all the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I've been going to the game sites and...
[SPEAKER_10]: just experiencing it as much as you can from the comfort of your computer chair that's right and where the food is reasonable we should be there I know we failed next year next year alright let me ask this question too Loki I know you've had some hands on with this some of the stuff that's been released during E3 we've had a few not just Connect Labs was it's out today but there was also Excitebike 3D came out did you get a chance to grab the Excitebike 3D on 3DS
[SPEAKER_09]: I did, and I checked it out.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm glad that it wasn't just them kind of offsetting each individual sprite layer.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, I mean, it still wasn't that great.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was like watching Excitebike on a really tiny screen, because when you do it in 3D, it's just really tiny.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have that here with you?
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_09]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do you have it, Rob?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I do, actually.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give to daddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's go!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just too expensive.
[SPEAKER_10]: They probably will before too long, so here you go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to give that to Dan.
[SPEAKER_10]: He can check that out right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do like how when you use the 3D slider on it, how it zooms it back into the original game, which is kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, I mean, beyond that gimmick, I just can't get too excited about it, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's just... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's as exciting as Excitebike is, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well we are going to give Miklatov a call and ask some more questions about Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to hear another perspective.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't know if, I don't think he got hands on with Wii U today.
[SPEAKER_10]: But he was, he was there at the Nintendo presser.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Dan's like, this is widescreen, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we're going to give Miklatov a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just punched in the digits, one ringy dingy, two ringy dingys.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Microsoft bored me to tears.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they didn't have anything interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were all, here's the Kinect that we've been pushing for a year and we're trying to keep it relevant.
[SPEAKER_05]: And by the way, here's Gears of War with probably a drunk or high iced tea.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why he was angry.
[SPEAKER_10]: He wasn't drunk yet and it was 11am.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: and really they had me with Band Central and that was it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing else was interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then Sony?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sony?
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually really liked.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked their monitor.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't see it yet in action but I liked the idea of two people looking at it and seeing different things and it's cheap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the idea of the Vita.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked Uncharted 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: talking about Pico and Shadow of the Cloth.
[SPEAKER_05]: This also makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: So overall, they did really well in my eyes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really liked it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'd like to go again.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was also...
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, while I liked it, and I thought it was cool, like, they had the orchestra, and that was neat, and, oh, a golden remote was cool, I was also kind of dull, and it went by really fast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they're really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, I was seven rows from the front.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't remember them showing it off in person.
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't bring it off in person.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you haven't done hands-on, or did you do hands-on today, or no?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I went there first thing this morning, and of course all the visitors were in line first, that's what they do, and it looked like it was like a three and a half hour wait from where I was at, so I was like, screw it.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I'm just going to do it tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's why I decided to go and look at other things today because I knew that tomorrow and the next day would be mostly Vida and you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, everything that they talked about today for the 3DS, I got to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that they had
[SPEAKER_05]: They're titled at the press conference and they're like, oh yeah, and everything we're talking about, don't say it now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, so Kid Icarus was playable too?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, oh my god, I love Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow, tell us a little bit about how that demo played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so there were two, well, three demos.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did two of the three so far.
[SPEAKER_05]: The first demo is an aerial mission and a ground mission combined into one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So with the aerial mission...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty much, if you played Sin Infinishment, you've got your little target that you control with the stylus, and then the circle pad is how you straight and move up and down.
[SPEAKER_05]: And your firing is all based out of the left button at the top, the L button.
[SPEAKER_05]: And before you actually do the mission, you actually had like, I think around nine...
[SPEAKER_05]: options for what you want to use as your weapon.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went with Pan Blast because I thought that was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: So when you're playing, if you target an enemy with the target, I don't know how to pronounce it, it'll lock onto them, kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you hold down the L button, it'll shoot a rapid succession of shots.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you just target them though and just single press it, you will deliver like a fully charged blast that can actually take out several enemies in that area.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, did you say the other one was the multiplayer demo?
[SPEAKER_05]: There were two other ones.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a multiplayer demo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not get to do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think I wanted to hang around at that point.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the other one they had was AR cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: which actually if you did the demonstration with them you got a pack so I have a pack of Kid Icarus AR cards once the game comes out they'll be able to use but all it really is is just putting characters on through the AR on the card and then they can battle each other it was that thing that some were joking like hey didn't we see this already when it was called the Eye of Judgment yes that's all it is
[SPEAKER_05]: That's pretty much all there is.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting that Nintendo just slaps Kid Icarus on it and now people are going crazy about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't that funny how that works, Loki?
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, was the bet still on if a million copies of that game sell?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, there is no bet.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's done.
[SPEAKER_09]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: What else did you play on DS?
[SPEAKER_10]: 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played Luigi's Mansion 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: it played like Luigi's Mansion it was some big shocker there the one thing that I did not like is that I know it's early in development but the frame rate chugged even when you weren't doing much of anything okay well hopefully they get that ironed out I mean yeah that's an early development thing I'm sure but they'll have to fix that Mario Mario was cool um
[SPEAKER_05]: It played like Mario Galaxy on the stages that didn't have the 3D worlds where you're running around the entire planet upside down and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing much really different there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You've got your raccoon suit back, but it looks like the Tanooki suit, but it has the raccoon suit powers, so it's kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mario Kart was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: 60 frames a second from what I was told.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even in 3D?
[SPEAKER_10]: Even in 3D?
[SPEAKER_10]: Even in 3D it does 60 frames?
[SPEAKER_05]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who would play it in 2D?
[SPEAKER_05]: Losers would play it in 2D.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I'm thinking of Dead or Alive Dimensions where they were saying, oh, it'll do 60 frames in 2D and 30 in 3D.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was kind of split, so I was wondering if they were kind of doing... Yeah, same with Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but no, this was 60 frames 3D
[SPEAKER_05]: It was hard, which was amazing, because Mario Kart has not been hard in years.
[SPEAKER_05]: The paint gliding mechanic, when you had the jumps, that was interesting because you either had to slow down in the air to collect coins, or you knocked to the ground as fast as you could to continue racing.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was a weird trade-off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: The propeller, when you're underwater,
[SPEAKER_05]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: It did nothing for me.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Star Fox?
[SPEAKER_05]: Star Fox?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it had a single player.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played multiplayer, though, and it felt a lot like the multiplayer that was from the DS game, which I kind of like.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just really nice-looking.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was cool, though, is that out of our four-people battle, I totally killed everybody in one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the little...
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, how funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can see what they're looking at, like if they're going to look up in the upper corner or something, or if they make a weird face randomly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's continuously refreshing, but fairly slow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So no picking your nose and playing Star Fox then?
[SPEAKER_05]: You could, but it'd be hard because of the way you have to hold the system.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, so that's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it sounds like you got your hands on at least a lot of the 3DS titles today.
[SPEAKER_10]: What was your favorite out of the bunch?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably
[SPEAKER_05]: A tie between Mario Kart and Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I forgot to say Kid Icarus, beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: Absolutely beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: The water in that game, as Nintendo is known to do, just was amazing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It blew me away.
[SPEAKER_10]: One more 3DS question.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sure if you're aware, but Nintendo unloaded onto the eShop today trailers for Animal Crossing and Paper Mario as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Were those games anywhere to be seen?
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that I saw because I really wanted to play at least Animal Crossing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did download the trailer though when I got back to the hotel room for Animal Crossing and I'm not sure if you guys talked about it or not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, Loki had a thing or two to say about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I said it's got some really cool new features.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not sure if you guys... Yeah, Loki had a thing or two to say about it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sitting on benches and swimming?
[SPEAKER_09]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was your mind blown by swimming?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was like, oh my god, I can sit down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wait, Mikulatov, did Animal Crossing have colored balloons?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, it wasn't that cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, what else did you do at the show today?
[SPEAKER_10]: Since you didn't stand in line for the Vita all day like Bobby had to, what did you get your hands on today?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I also want to quickly throw in that I played Zelda as well on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: and it was fan-freaking-tastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was a close call for my tie for best 3DS game I played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Could you tell you were playing a 13-year-old game?
[SPEAKER_10]: What made it so great?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not sure I could say I was playing a 13-year-old game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will say that the graphics are definitely much nicer.
[SPEAKER_05]: The frame rate is crazy nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: The 3D effect, I didn't really care for.
[SPEAKER_05]: It didn't really do anything for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did like people switching to the slingshot or the hookshot would...
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what else did you get to play at the show today?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I firstly walked around, which is kind of, you know, a waste of a day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played the new Silent Hill game, both in 3D and in 2D.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Crap, is what I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was terrible in 3D and it was terrible in 3D, so this is definitely a pass for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not even interested.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why was it terrible?
[SPEAKER_10]: What did it play like?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it more like the Wii Silent Hill, which I don't see?
[SPEAKER_09]: Was it more like Alan Wake?
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it Alan Wake?
[SPEAKER_10]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I wish it was like Alan Wake.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know, I like Alan Wake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or even Shattered Memories.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like a generic survival horror that ran really choppy
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, and was boring.
[SPEAKER_05]: And not scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, at least in every other demo that I've played at E3 for a Silent Hill game, something has been kind of freaky about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just boring.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not Silent Hill if it's not freaky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was just dull.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, oh, there was an enemy that jumped out and I think was supposed to scare me, but this more annoyed me because they aren't scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: The only thing I ever saw for Tomb Raider wasn't on the floor It's during the Microsoft conference So I was over in Square Enix's booth for a bit today And I didn't see it anywhere
[SPEAKER_05]: but I was also playing the entire demo for Final Fantasy XIII too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh, what'd you think of that?
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually really like XIII despite what other people think.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I like this one a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: They added some interesting features like a what's that called?
[SPEAKER_05]: The real-time segments like God of War and Heavy Rain have.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which was, you know, it's a little out of place but it was still neat
[SPEAKER_05]: But no Dressphere.
[SPEAKER_05]: No just fears.
[SPEAKER_05]: I definitely don't know who the main character is that I was playing as.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but there's a lot of Sonic stuff for their new Sonic game.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it actually didn't look that bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get to play it though yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, you'll have to let us know when you do finally get your hands on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: What else?
[SPEAKER_05]: There was this really neat Kinect game by Konami.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was called Lead Me's, I believe.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's both Kinect, and I believe it's a download title, they said.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it plays a little bit like Lemmings.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you stand in front of the Kinect sensor, and you become this wireframe character, pretty much.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you have these little adorable things that fall down and you have to get them to safety by using your limbs as bridges, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you use your body to build the path to get these guys safe, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know you're a big fan of music games too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Any music games that you saw besides Dance Central 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I saw DDR, but it's laughable nowadays, so it's not even worth talking about.
[SPEAKER_09]: Aw, but I kind of wanted to know how laughable it was.
[SPEAKER_05]: They had four licenses, I believe, in the Red Fork Nominee Originals, and what I watched looked like the character models looked like DDR PC quality, but not as awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: because there was no Mr. Spanky or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They were just like really poorly done character models.
[SPEAKER_10]: Nobody loves Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Forget it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not hear you because I'm hearing me talk every time I talk.
[SPEAKER_10]: No Dance Masters 2?
[SPEAKER_05]: No Dance Masters 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do know the only thing that's behind closed doors at Konami because I still have my hookup.
[SPEAKER_05]: is Pro Evolution Soccer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So everything else that's on the floor is all they're showing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's pretty sad also.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, this E3 has been kind of let down in terms of what's being shown despite having two new consoles.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about Dance Central 2?
[SPEAKER_10]: Didn't you say you had some hands-on time with that?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I played Dance Central 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fantastic.
[SPEAKER_05]: but it was just in Central with new characters and new moves.
[SPEAKER_10]: Is Harmonix showing anything else at their booth?
[SPEAKER_10]: Aren't they supposed to be unveiling a new game?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I didn't see that at Harmonix booth.
[SPEAKER_05]: I haven't seen a Harmonix booth at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was at Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_10]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it must be kind of a behind closed doors thing or in a conference room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anything else that you had some hands-on time with you want to share with us tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm wracking my brain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: What's your plan for tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm...
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be in a coin later to decide if I'm standing in line for Vita or Wii U. Personally, I'm leaning more towards Vita because I don't really think I care much about the Wii U at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, yeah, we need someone to go play the Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if Bobby will get around to it tomorrow, so I think you should do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do the Vita?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll try that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, anything else you want to share before we let you go so we can get to some other callers from our chat room at 1-877-GAMELAR?
[SPEAKER_05]: The first thing, okay, this will be cool to some of those people out there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's start with the lamer one first.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I was walking down Hollywood Boulevard yesterday because that's where my place I'm staying at is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if people follow reality TV at all or gay porn, I totally ran into Dustin Zito from either Real World or Flat Pad.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_10]: The one with the sordid past, apparently, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wanted to just go up to him and be like, hey, I've seen you naked.
[SPEAKER_05]: That might have been awkward.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, just slightly.
[SPEAKER_05]: But the actual cool thing that people may care about is right when I walked out of the Nokia theater today after Nintendo was done, I ran Snapchat instead of Kiriyama Oka.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was really cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you get a picture or anything or say hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I got a picture.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: We shook hands.
[SPEAKER_05]: I tweeted him actually after the fact, and he tweeted back.
[SPEAKER_05]: And him tweeting back at me, somehow G4 is not following my Twitter, which is a waste of their time.
[SPEAKER_10]: It might be one of those spam Twitters, so look out, because I see a lot of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a real one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, Miklatov, enjoy the rest of the show.
[SPEAKER_10]: Get some hands-on with Vita tomorrow and whatever else, and we'll talk to you again tomorrow, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, sounds good Alright, and try to stalk more celebrities for us Yes, I will do that Take care, buddy Alright, bye
[SPEAKER_10]: We're running a little long tonight, but we will open it up for a few quick, quick calls if anyone wants to call and just talk impressions.
[SPEAKER_10]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: Where are you at?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are we completely off base with what we're saying about Wii U or Kinect or the Vita?
[SPEAKER_10]: Give us a call 877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all one word.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you are going to use Skype to give us a call, please make sure you use Echo 123 first.
[SPEAKER_10]: Before you give us a call again What were your impressions?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure many of you You know, I didn't want to just recap the news tonight with you guys Because I'm sure most of you were watching it Although I'm liking hearing about these hidden things Like that Konami game that sounds like Lemmings I want to hear about more of those types of games
[SPEAKER_10]: So, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, again, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Quick programming note, we are live tonight, we are live tomorrow night, we are off Sunday because Bobby Blackwolf and some of us here at OLR are going to go celebrate E3 broadcast by going to Disneyland.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, we're doing research for Disney Connect Adventures.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got to make sure that Disney Connect game is accurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we will leave no stone unturned.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there have to be hidden cats in the game for it to be accurate.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we will be back next Sunday on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: That will be June the 19th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bobby Blackwolf will be here June the 12th.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not here, but at allgames.com where he's usually at June the 12th and of course on his podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's where you're going to hear his Thursday impressions since we will not be live Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I hope everybody got the programming worked out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Again, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: And...
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to point out, Sega did not announce a system
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, apology, that's kind of a gray area.
[SPEAKER_06]: He said they weren't even going to mention it.
[SPEAKER_06]: True.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which they let off with by saying, mentioning.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, let me get to the phones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, it's Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey Sterlok, how you doing buddy?
[SPEAKER_10]: Pretty good.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's E3 going for you?
[SPEAKER_07]: What are your thoughts?
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really want a Vita.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Street Fighter vs Tekken.
[SPEAKER_10]: But can't you get that on the PS3 or the 360?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but come on, man.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a portable version.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's just awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think about this whole announcement that Cole's in it as well?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of random, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's pretty common for Namco, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you've got Tekken characters and, like, Urban Rain, so...
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do that kind of stuff all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I still can't get my head around this name.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I know, the name's a little weird, but remember, I mean, and I don't like the name either, to be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think they should have just called it the Nintendo U, and we could have just all said, oh, the U stands for Ultra, or something like that, you know?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or if they wanted to go back to, like, the old school, they could have called it the U-Force, like that old peripheral.
[SPEAKER_10]: The Super Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the Wii, Wii, Wii, Wii, Wii, Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I've been doing that all day, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just like, oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: Dammit, where was I going with this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Everybody's got an opinion on the Wii U. What do you think of the console itself besides just the name?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which I do think everyone will get used to eventually, by the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, do we have a network outage?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we did.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we had a drop.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are we still on Ustream?
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know if we're even still broadcasting at this point.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we are.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we had an internet... Okay, we had an internet downtime...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh wow, we just reconnected right away with Strelok.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, yeah, we had a weird drop thing happen there, so that's weird, but we're back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Silly internets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, silly internets.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, what's on your mind with the Wii U?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd like to see more from it, just, you know, this Ectema stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: The controller is kind of interesting, even though I honestly really can't...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't want to use too much of it but it's an interesting concept but really what has me excited is something from the Microsoft it's not the only thing that I really cared about from the Microsoft press conference but something they kind of touched on briefly was the whole Bing thing with Kinect where you could you can
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell it what to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to search for a game and then play it by voice, you can do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's really exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: Xbox, Bing, pornography.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Indeed.
[SPEAKER_10]: A lot of people are kind of on what Microsoft showed.
[SPEAKER_10]: What did you think of the press conference overall?
[SPEAKER_07]: Overall, the Microsoft conference, yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just kind of like, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: More shooters?
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't care.
[SPEAKER_10]: Too many first-person shooters, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: Too many shooters.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's oversaturated.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to let you go as we get some other calls.
[SPEAKER_10]: Before we do, any other final thoughts for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want more.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want Konami to announce the Snatcher game, but that didn't happen.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sadly, it's probably not going to.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't hold your breath.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to let you go to get some more calls, but have a good one, okay?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, thanks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for putting up with the internet outage, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just another day here at OLR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I've been having... Hey, what's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_09]: This is Kaijudo.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey, Kaijudo, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_13]: I just wanted to say that the Wii U, the controller, scares the fucking hell out of me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why does it scare you?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it looks like it's going to break.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, all the stuff they want you to do with it,
[SPEAKER_13]: doesn't seem very safe for the controller.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, like putting it down on the floor, sticking it on that gun and swinging it around.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just looks like a lot of kids are going to break that thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I think you're kind of on to something here because I can't tell you, and this is kind of embarrassing, but I can't tell you how many headsets I've broken on my computer because I'll sit it down on my chair when I get up to go to the bathroom and then when I come back, crunch, my fat ass sits on it and crunches it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you have to be really careful.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like you're going to need, everybody needs a coffee table to put that controller on and that's away from the dogs and the cats that tend to eat things.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's like the big...
[SPEAKER_13]: The big glass on it, it's like, you know, it just, to me, it seems like it's going to just break within a couple of weeks.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hold on, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not really glass.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's that cheap plastic-y thing that the DSs use.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the same touchscreen from a DS, just bigger.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't know that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It looks like glass to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, they will get, it'll still get broken, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, well, let's say that controller is invincible.
[SPEAKER_10]: What is your thoughts about Wii U otherwise?
[SPEAKER_13]: As far as being innovative, I think they're going somewhere with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm going to agree with Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_13]: I saw a lot of potential with what they were showing that you could do with it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's still not something that I want to run out and get right away until I see something that I really like, but I do appreciate them for trying to bring some innovation to the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Even though they're recycling the same old games, just putting Mario on everything, but
[SPEAKER_13]: Other than that, I mean, they are innovative with their shit.
[SPEAKER_10]: I get a lot of feedback, by the way, just to let you know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like hearing myself talking.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, we have an echo thing going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you have the Ustream running?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because you've got to pause it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other thing is, at what price do you think the Wii U becomes too expensive right now? $3.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if it's $3.98, you might be there.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I get it at $2.98.
$2.99, $2.98.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, well, Kajudo, we're going to let you go to see if we can get another call, but thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, goodnight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Later.
[SPEAKER_10]: 877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_10]: And as we start to wrap up here while we wait for one more call, where are you guys at?
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, a lot of people feel the need to rank Microsoft, Nintendo, and Sony.
[SPEAKER_10]: But let me kind of leave it here with this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Out of what we've talked about tonight, what are you most excited about?
[SPEAKER_10]: What are you most interested in hearing more about?
[SPEAKER_10]: Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_08]: Animal Crossing.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be honest, I'm still actually kind of meh about a bunch of it, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were things I had hoped to see that didn't pop out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And really, it was a lot more of what I expected, although I do really like that new controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm more excited about that controller for the Wii U, even though the name is, you know, stupid.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, we'll get to the other feedback in studio here in a minute, but we do have another call coming in, so let's get to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, this is Blender from Napa, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: Blender, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing, I just, one thing, I don't know if you guys mentioned, I was like five minutes late getting into the show, and nobody mentioned, I was really interested in the Bioshock Infinite
[SPEAKER_03]: with the move support.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll finally get to wipe the cobwebs off of my move.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, kind of like Gabe Newell last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, oh, we like money.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, all right, put move support in your game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they're like, oh, okay, and say something good about the move for us.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, I can do that because I like money.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like Gabe Newell last year with the whole Valve thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, what else caught your eye, Blender?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Uncharted 3, of course.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just a huge Uncharted fan.
[SPEAKER_03]: The multiplayer looks fantastic.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: But other than that, well, see, I only own one system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I only own the Sony, so... So there's not a lot for you on the other ones.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did maybe, I have to ask it, did Microsoft or Nintendo maybe make you think twice about picking up another one?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not Nintendo, but Microsoft, I mean, I'm still kind of on the edge.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, I'm not a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I had the money, I would pick up another system, you know.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Mainly, what I've been listening to is just for the Microsoft thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Would be like, if they did it, they'd need to make a Kinect, like an L.A.
[SPEAKER_03]: Noire Kinect game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That would tell me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Where I can just slap the bitch if I think they're lying.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
Pop.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or have your partner do, hey, go over there and go investigate this for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to go have a beer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Blinder, any other last thoughts for us before we let you go?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that's it.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you later.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: You too.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_10]: We are going to go ahead and close the Skype line, guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm very sorry to those folks that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't forget, we're going to be back tomorrow, and we'll have a little more time to take more calls tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you didn't get through tonight, don't be mad.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can also email us, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: We will go to the mailbag tomorrow because we won't have press conferences.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to hear about other games tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: We still haven't talked Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_10]: We've got to talk a little bit about Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the other games.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll probably dive into Bioshock a little more.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever it is that Bobby and Shane can get their hands on, we're going to talk a little more about tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: And your calls will really help fill in and emails tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Chibi Wolf.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Chibi Wolf, let's hope.
[SPEAKER_10]: For now, I want to go around and get everybody's kind of last thought here.
[SPEAKER_10]: And again, guys, sorry to cut it off, but we were only intending on going until 9 and it's almost 9.30.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I want to try and wrap up and everybody's being a real trooper for staying with us.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Dan, what are you walking away from this most excited about?
[SPEAKER_10]: The Wii U. The Wii U. Why is that?
[SPEAKER_06]: It could be really awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or it could fucking suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's exactly it.
[SPEAKER_06]: If Nintendo comes through with the price, they come through with the games, and some people do some great development for it, I mean, it could be really, really smooth.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it could do a lot of cool stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or it could be an absolute waste of technology.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Nintendo's scary because Nintendo does that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sometimes Nintendo hits something and they just knock it out of the park.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then sometimes Nintendo's just like, yeah, look at our great thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have no fucking idea what to do with it
[SPEAKER_06]: I was like, okay, maybe Sony's learned a thing, but it's just a better PSP where the Vita could be something completely new.
[SPEAKER_06]: They didn't just say, okay, here's a new Wii controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said, here is a new different thing that no one's done before.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that could be pretty slick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm with you there.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to go to chat real quick because one of the other games that's being brought up in chat right now that we didn't get into depth about today, Randy Yu says, Batman, Batman, Batman.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Blender says, did you see the Catwoman trailer, Randy Yu?
[SPEAKER_10]: Which was shown at one of the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, I got to say, there were two things out of the whole three press conferences that made me audibly say, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I said wow twice during the press conferences.
[SPEAKER_10]: One of them was the $499 3D monitor.
[SPEAKER_10]: I said wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: The other one was when they announced that Batman Arkham City was going to be on the Wii U. Batman on Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know why.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just crazy to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they don't have to make huge graphic compromises, it means that the Wii U has at least the horsepower of the current generation of consoles.
[SPEAKER_10]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's going to be interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, I know you still need to answer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Let me go first here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to say the thing I am most excited to see more about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm going to go kind of off the beaten path here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Although the Wii U, yes, of course I'm going to see more of that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I really just feel like...
[SPEAKER_10]: Everything is fucking speculation until next year.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's so, so early.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now we know that most of the rumors were true and we've seen where they're going with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for me, the more immediate question, I actually want to see these hardcore games with the Kinect functionality.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see how the public responds to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I want to see...
[SPEAKER_10]: When I play Connect, I do really like it.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I really want so much more out of the Connect.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I'm really curious how some of these shooters are going to play.
[SPEAKER_10]: I kind of even want to play the Ghost Recon game just to check it out.
[SPEAKER_10]: That is never a game I'd be interested in otherwise.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's so weird.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll save you the trouble.
[SPEAKER_06]: The response is going to be, eh.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe two people are going to buy it.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what Twitter will say, but what will the dollars say?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what the dollars are going to say.
[SPEAKER_06]: You think?
[SPEAKER_06]: I disagree.
[SPEAKER_06]: In my life, I've dealt with a lot of mainstream gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've worked at game stores for 10 years, and I've seen those guys come into the store, and the Twitter crowd, as much as I hate to say it, is kind of the voice of the quote-unquote hardcore gamer, the guy who cares enough to be
[SPEAKER_06]: Sitting on the computer watching that press conference and not because he's going to come on here tonight and talk about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's just not going to be a lot of interest.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd be sweet if they could pull it off.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm the first guy to admit I have an unopened connect.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's Jamie's.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Ghost Squad on the Wii is fucking awesome Ghost Squad is an awesome game
[SPEAKER_06]: and the Wii Zapper is a good Ghost Squad controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted the Ghost Squad rifle.
[SPEAKER_09]: No, okay, that's a little too far there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's got the little trigger and it's got the pull thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Leico perfect shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, that's a little better.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted the Ghost Squad rifle to be the Xbox 360 rifle and it just never happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like that new Kinect looking rifle.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, not Kinect, the Move rifle, by the way.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: I gotta say though, Dan, I'm not disagreeing with your perspective necessarily about who the hardcore gamers are and all that, but I gotta say, I really think that with no Wii U this year, Microsoft kind of has that Nintendo soccer mom casual market cornered this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's just going to be interesting to see what Kinect games rise to the top.
[SPEAKER_10]: Will it just be Dance Central 2, number one seller this year?
[SPEAKER_10]: Or will that Kinect functionality float a hardcore game up to the top?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they need to come up with their Wii Sports Resort or with their Wii Fit.
[SPEAKER_06]: That one game that just every Kinect owner has to have.
[SPEAKER_00]: Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it's not Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the dance fans love Dance Central, but the common folks aren't just like, oh man, Dance Central, because I was in a room full of common people the other day, and nobody really liked Dance Central.
[SPEAKER_06]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: See, I would say Dance Central, not just like music fans like us who've been following it for years, but like rock band fans, which is a much wider audience.
[SPEAKER_08]: Air guitar freaks!
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, we gotta get towards wrapping up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've gotta let Loki have his say.
[SPEAKER_10]: Loki, what left you wanting more?
[SPEAKER_09]: Saints Row 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Earth Saints Row the 3rd.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: And goddammit, I wish they'd just announce a new Grand Theft Auto and be done with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: No kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Half-Life 2 Episode 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you, Valve.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fuck you right in the ear.
[SPEAKER_09]: We know it's coming.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just come out and say it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's really it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, fuck that!
[SPEAKER_09]: What titles Nintendo is going to have that are exclusive to this that are actually going to be worth my time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Instead of saying, hey, look, we got this really cool thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're hoping that the publishers are going to be creative enough to use this technology that they built.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last time I checked, it never was a problem that, oh, these games aren't creative enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's...
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we just don't give a crap about fleshing out this game to the point of, you know, attracting other people other than casual gamers because, eh, casual gamers still buy whatever as long as it's $19.99.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, anything you guys are hoping... Well, Loki, you're not going to be here tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, I'm not going to be here.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Dan will be here and DarkSakura and myself.
[SPEAKER_10]: But since you kind of have... This is your last chance to say whatever you want on the show here about E3 till next Sunday.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anything else you kind of want to get out about your thoughts on the show?
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, other than just like some of the stuff that's already been out.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's nothing really that's like brand new.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing out of those conferences that was really just caught me off guard.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: It was just no real surprises.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nothing like, oh my God, that's so amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you could see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: The crowds weren't into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were like one or two pops when something that they were supposed to pop at came.
[SPEAKER_06]: There were a lot of pauses where the companies expected applause and nobody was into it.
[SPEAKER_06]: it was a very apathetic attitude even the big stuff that people were supposed to be into just didn't win people over
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back tomorrow to do some more E3 coverage.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, myself, Dan, and you guys in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_10]: And of course, in LA, a big thanks to Bobby Blackwolf and Miklatov are both in LA.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they'll be back with more game opinions tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_10]: But for tonight, we say goodnight.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have a wonderful night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you back here tomorrow at our little temporary space here on Ustream.
[SPEAKER_10]: 7 o'clock Pacific, 10 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_10]: No video yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: But hopefully you stream in the future, and not tomorrow either, but you stream in the future, we might have some more video features, kind of like we used to back in the day on OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Besides that, I'm so completely unglamorous right now, I can't be on video or it will explode.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's going to do it for our E3 coverage tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll be back tomorrow, 7 o'clock Pacific, 10 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_10]: We'll see you here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Email us, mailbag at orangeautoradio.com.
[SPEAKER_10]: Follow us on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: Follow Bobby on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_10]: See you tomorrow.