Tonight, June 8th, 2011, we bring you further impressions and opinions on E3 Live with special
correspondents Bobby Black Wolf and Miek Latov on the show floor.
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to night number two of E3
Live coverage here at Orange Lounge Radio in conjunction with Ustream, our little temporary
home for the shows and of course the one and only Bobby Black Wolf who does his own show
on Sunday nights and is also syndicating the show to his feed as well as our feed so it's
just it's just all out there for everybody so I'm glad you guys are enjoying it. My name
is Rob Roberts I'll be joining you over the next hour hour and a half however long we go tonight
with my co-hosts here in the studio say hello to the one and only Dark Sakura.
Carrot. So you've gone from meat last night to carrot tonight. Yes because I want something
crunchy. All right and also joining us tonight say hello to Dan the man is here in studio. Hello
hello. How you doing? I'm doing good. Good you're on Loki's night so or excuse me Loki's mic so
you're not as loud as you were last night. I get to sit in my own desk. The guest mic is so
freaky in here but oh well nobody cares about that. I blame you. We are live of course live on
Ustream if this is your first time listening to us here on Ustream this is not where we're usually
at we do a Sunday night live show every week at All Games Radio. More information about our
podcast and all that good stuff www.orangelaungeradio.com and you can listen to last
night's two and a half hour opus of the Wii U and Xbox and Kinect and and the Vita. We're gonna
actually get more into the Vita tonight. It is live of course you can join us in our chat room
at chat.orangelaungeradio.com if you have any live comments you want to give us as we're
broadcasting here live. Speaking of live sometimes interesting things happen and we actually have to
mix things up a little bit tonight. We're not gonna start with Bobby tonight. Bobby's caught
in traffic. He's still in LA downtown. I guess the last text I got is that a transformer blew
out somewhere. So sorry Bobby fans we're gonna have to go to him a little later but we're gonna
go right into today's coverage of E3 and from what I understand our correspondents out on the floor
got some more hands-on impressions today. As you know yesterday Bobby waited for quite a while in
that Wii U Wii U Wii U line to about what like four hours to finally get his hands on the Wii U
and gave us his impressions yesterday. Tonight we're gonna go straight over to Miek Letov who
was on the show floor and I think he was waiting for like three or four hours today to play the PS
Vita. So it's kind of interesting that both of them have very long lines waiting to play them.
So we're gonna go to Miek Letov right now through the magic of the internet we're gonna call his
little cell phone and see what else he played today because I know the show hours are usually
longest on this second day so hopefully got to play a lot more today. I don't know if he got to
go play more Konami stuff like Silent Hill which he said it wasn't that great which made Jamie sad.
Very sad in my soul. But of course it's just his opinion it's just one opinion so we'll see maybe
Bobby got to play it today we'll see if he thought the same thing. Hello? Hey is this Miek Letov?
Yes. Hey it's Rob from Orange Launch Radio of course you should know that I just texted you
thanks for letting us. I know it's so surprising. Thanks for letting us mix things up a little bit
and bringing you on first tonight. Bobby's caught in traffic where are you are you are you back at
your hotel? Yes I made it back. It's fine after 50 minutes of commuting. Do you how do you get now
yeah for those who have never been to E3 and have heard about LA traffic it really is a nightmare
that's why I'm not looking forward to being in it tomorrow when we go to pick Bobby up at the
convention center but uh it'll be all right. At least we'll have each other right Dark Sakura?
Yes. Right Dan? Of course. All right anyway so Miek Letov how was E3 for you today?
It was well I would say I only really participated in E3 today for about
three hours if that because today was my stand-in-line day. Today was your stand-in-line
day so I already mentioned that I know you stood in line for the PS Vita right? Yep. Good I'm glad
we get to talk about because yesterday was a little bit Nintendo heavy with all the Wii U
talks so I'm glad we get to talk a little bit about the PS Vita today so tell us about your
experiences everything from standing in line how long to when you finally got your hands on the
goods? It took about four hours for me to get through that line and I got there at about 10 30
so it was a bit ridiculous for the line but to make up for it if you can consider it that I
did play with it for about 20 minutes so I got some good hands-on time with it. Not bad yeah
what are your thoughts? I really like it it's definitely a great successor to the PSP
for the design part of the system the screen is beautiful it's really big it's really vibrant
you really don't see any pixels whatsoever definitely a nice high-desk screen
the the back part with the touchpad I don't like that so much because the touchpad takes up too
much of the back so you're constantly accidentally tapping it and in the game that you know you use
the touchpad on the back can kind of screw you up but that's just a minor uh minor complaint I'm
sure if I held it the right way because it's grips it would be a little bit better. I wonder
if you can just turn that crap off do you think do you think you just turn off that back touchpad
altogether because I didn't even think about that but yeah if you have a tendency like tap on the
back of your device or something it's going to totally mess with that back touch stuff right?
Yeah it will um I assume that some games will have that I don't think it will be a system setting
but so yeah there's that part and the one thing that I actually do not like about the system is
that the face buttons are way too small like I was playing Uncharted and I kept trying to hit
the x button but instead I'd hit an analog stick because that's where my fingers felt like the x
button should be instead of these really tiny little buttons that they give you to play with.
So it sounds like maybe there's some design things that need to be worked out or is this
is this pretty much like the final thing that you guys are seeing did they say anything about
prototype or how far along it is? Um I did not ask and they did not say I assume because of how
close to I mean really if you think about if it's supposed to be this this holiday it's only a few
months out so I'm pretty sure that this is probably the final design. I thought the ds was shown
and it went through a lot of changes I mean this is many years ago it was shown at e3 and it went
through many changes before it was released uh but maybe not because I think that might have come out
the ds came out what March or April I guess so thinking of the ds as being many years ago is sad
I know that was my first e3 I think all of ours was the year the ds was yeah anyhow uh so okay so
this isn't about the ps or the ds though it's about the ps vita um so tell us about some of
the games that you play and what they were like okay they had a station set up for us to go to
about five minutes on each or was it four I don't remember I can't remember the amount of stations
but I'll whisk them off um the first one we went to was the little big planet station so we got
to play um or you got your choice of a couple different um options in little big planet you
could play a stage or you could play um a two player game using just a touch screen and you
would play with the demo guy I opted to do just the stage because I wanted to see how it would
really work in the practical play um and I was really impressed uh I used everything from the
the touchpad to tilting the system or not touchpad sorry the touch screen to tilting the system and
it played like little big planet and it looked like little big planet on the ps3 so like I was
really impressed um one of the puzzles that had me do was there was a keyboard in the background
and I had to play or I had to push the keys for the musical note and then LBP and it opened the
door and I thought that was really cool uh and so you say it looked just like little big planet on
the ps3 so did it feel like it was just kind of a port of the ps3 you know original with maybe some
uh frills that incorporate the vita stuff like the the back touching or whatever did it feel
like like just a whole separate experience like it's not you know just a port I would say it felt
more like a separate experience because the vita special features really made it feel that way um
so like there was a part where I had to hold on to a one of the little uh spinning wheels
and it wasn't spinning yet so while I was holding it with the uh r trigger um or whatever it's called
the r button um I had to use my uh left hand to actually spin the wheel around so he would go up
to the top I was like that's awesome you know this is cool well I would expect talking about
the design of the system again in your hands and the way that whole works uh kaijuto is in our chat
room at chat.orangelandreay.com saying this guy must have fred flinstone thumbs do you just have
abnormal hands no no these are really small like I my hands are not big at all and these I swear
were like the size of mini m&ms something people might know okay there you go that's a good
comparison okay so what else little big planet and okay after that they sent us over to virtual
tennis which um so far these two games I was told are launch titles for the system um so virtual
tennis really nice looking um they had you play it first with the just touch screen so you would
press the spot on the court to move your guy you hold your finger down your guy would move
and then you could flick up to do a top spin and then flick down to do a back spin and it actually
and it actually worked really well um then I was introduced to control how is that touch screen
stuff different from like playing an iphone game or is that really what it felt like like oh I'm
playing an iphone that's really what it felt like with nice graphics okay and it was on a bigger
screen okay and um yeah so then uh he told me to do all my um hits uh with the touch screen and
I could move with the analog stick like okay this actually I kind of like the way that one played
um and then it's like oh just play normally and you know I could play normally it wasn't like
super impressive but it was still really fun because virtual tennis games are pretty fun
so after my time was up there um I went to the what's that super game called
little deviants that game is pretty much what I feel like they're trying to one-up
nintendo with um it seems to be a collection of mini games for the most part um there were three
that we got to play the first one was an ar game just like face rater to a t like with the
exception of putting somebody's face in it uh you just look around with your screen all over
all over the actual environment for these little spaceships you had to
destroy before they destroyed your little deviant characters um the next one was a whack-a-mole
style game that used both the touch screen and the touch pad on the back so windows would open
up and if they were facing you you had to touch the touch screen on them um and if they were
back turned to you you had to press from behind underneath um and watch out for the humans because
you lost points for that these all definitely sound like little like gimmicky demos that
to be fair is probably the same stuff the same stuff they're demoing the wii u with right now so
exactly um the last one was uh this uh it's the one that probably everybody's seen where you have
the touch pad on the back and you make the hills and you roll the ball the bvm ball guy around
into the whirlpool that one was probably what really frustrated me most with the the touch pad
on the back just because i mean it feels inevitable that you will rest your fingers on the back of the
pads the way they don't want you to do it um and there was no clear definition on the back where
the touchpad started where it ended so that one was really hard for me so little deviance though
it sounds like it's just a mini game collection i don't know to me it kind of sounds like a pass
i've seen it before what did you think uh i'm it's not a not a purchase for me at all um it was like
bundled in with the system i'm not gonna delete it but i'm not gonna purchase it okay all right
um the next one i went to uh was sound what did i call it sound something or other sound sound
something was it a music game um yes it kind of was um man now i feel bad because i was talking
about how much i love that game sound shapes i'm looking at your text from earlier sound shapes
yes so thank you sound shapes which is interesting because this was not even something that we saw at
the press conference so when you texted me that i'm like what the hell is that that must be like a
game they didn't say anything about otherwise it's been talked about before i know that um it's made
by the guy that did i want to say like either pixel junk or everyday shooter i don't remember
it's one of those two um but in it it's got two modes it's got a platforming mode which is very
simplistic shapes um you're just like little blue spiky ball looking thing but the object is to get
through the level and to hit these blue orbs and every time you hit a blue orb in that screen
it creates like the drums for the music or it creates the guitar or the keyboard so you keep
going looking at the audio you guys are hearing in the background i'm looking at a video of this
because i want to see more about what he's talking about here oh the guy's talking through it
yeah we can't have two people talking i'll i'll just look at the video then but uh yeah so you go
through uh different screens trying to collect all the blue orbs to create the music it was very
much a music-y platformer that caught my attention right away um i was told again launch title and
that people would be able to create their own stages and upload them for other people to play
oh cool that's really cool and that's the other part of the um demo it was he was showing me how
to create my own stage and placing music at certain points and placing the orbs and traps
and it was really cool i liked it a lot interesting as a music game fan uh this is kind of a must-have
for you because i'm looking at this going this does not look at all like other music games but
i'm i'm glad because i think it's you know i don't always need to see falling notes that you hit
whatever device too you know so this is kind of nice yeah i i think it's it's not only a game for
music fans but also for um possibly platforming fans because people who like to get high and play
video games what was that people who like to get high and play video games no because they'll
probably like try to eat their psv or drop it thinking it's some crazy monster okay we need
we need we need new crack since moja ribbons already out that's kind of like it's simplistic
like that like like the brib and stuff so i think it was great um definitely gonna be the first game
i buy because it was the one that impressed me the most which makes me sad because the next demo
playing too was uncharted and that was the game that at first announcement had pulled me on the
vita before it was called that and before i played it um and it didn't disappoint me per se uh i think
it looked beautiful and played like uncharted my problem with it is those tiny little m&m buttons
that um like they just got in my way i couldn't perform moves as well uh i definitely got shot
and killed twice during our demo because i couldn't get the button properly um that wasn't
any of the top screen controls of what was that did you try any of the touch screen controls
stealth takedowns jumping stuff like that see that that's what i'm about to i was about to say
is that like i like the what they called painting where you move your finger across like ledges and
he would move there that was cool but once you used it for hand-to-hand combat i hated it i
absolutely thought it was stupid because i have to instead of like you know position myself with
the camera and my body for the next enemy after i'm done punching this guy to death it takes one
hand off of that and i have to focus on tapping the little fist icon which was stupid i thought
you would like that because when i was seeing that in the trailer i was like that looks like
elite beat agents and that's like belita's favorite game no no it's nothing like that
at all it was frustrating and kind of annoying but um i'm sure that that will not be the only
way to play um i don't even could probably use the little m&m buttons to hit too but uh the demo
i didn't get a chance to try that because like oh use the touch screen only for combat it's like
okay thanks for getting me killed but um yeah that ended the ps vita experience so it was
worth the four hour wait yes i think so because i think i have waited in long lines at e3 to four
and not come away as satisfied as i did with the vita okay all right so now what's interesting
though is that you even though you enjoyed the vita and you're like okay i definitely want this
sound shapes game and there's a couple other things i played that i want i really need them
to fix some of these design issues even though there might not be any time now yeah i i don't
think the little buttons will hold me back from purchasing one because i think a lot of that has
to do with my hands being more accustomed to holding like a psp so it like my my fingers
gravitate to where um i think it's going to be at because i mean let's be honest it looks just like
a psp it's a little bit like longer um a little bit wider and a lot lighter actually it's like
nothing in your hands whatsoever um let me ask this question real quick because you know you
said that you definitely want to get the ps vita and i walked away from the sony press conference
saying i'm not really sure i understand why i need a vita still and and my whole thing was that
okay it just looks like it's a uh you know psp with a back touch thing a front touch thing and
slightly more power so what once it's slightly more power a lot more power a lot more but we'll
see i think the psp as it is still holds up and looks really really good there's a lot of really
good looking games on there so the psv is even better yes interesting i guess maybe the
screenshots online is such just don't do it justice so i'm looking forward it doesn't like
when you see the screen in person that that's what got my attention first and then the weight
in my hands got it second and then it's just a really nicely designed system for once now i kind
of asked bobby about this yesterday because he waited in line for the wii u uh most of the day
you waited in line for the ps vita most of the day did you catch any kind of like buzz from people
around you now see the funny thing was bobby was standing around a bunch of people who didn't speak
english yesterday so there was like no one for him to listen to but did you did you kind of catch
what was the buzz what were other people saying about the vita were people complaining about the
controller like you were or i didn't hear any complaints about the vita except for the long
wait time like i had people behind me leave a couple times because they were tired of waiting
clearly this must have been their first c3 because you know you have to wait forever for stuff yes
um i didn't hear any buzz about vita i did over here i'm not sure if this is considered i'm sure
it probably has but i heard something about skyrim randomly um from a dev saying that the uh it was
a bethesda dev so it wasn't like some random person but they were talking to um one of the
naughty dog people that were over there and they said that um skyrim is going to have about 30
hours of main quest and 300 hours of side quest nice uh i know bobby got some i i don't know if
he got no he didn't get hands-on he got like a 30-minute demo with skyrim today so he was
he got a little special bethesda show so uh we'll talk to him more about the details there later
i do like over maybe i'm just nosy but i like one of my favorite things at e3 is to just like over
here people because people do talk about rather loudly so i can hear them about um interesting
stuff kind of like what you're just saying yeah so all right so the ps vita took up most of your day
but you were you were happy with it at the end of the day what else were you able to get your hands
on today um i got to play child of eden um which was definitely not totally what i was expecting
but i still really liked it um the control scheme's a little weird and it was a guy the guy that was
explained to me a wasn't from ubisoft b was from walmart and c you look at b again and realize the
amount of knowledge you probably had about the game um he didn't really tell me how to play
properly i don't think so it was hard to just jump in randomly and start playing but it felt a lot
like rez it looked like rez it sounded like rez um but the two firing mechanisms are different like
your left hand is like a rapid fire gun that only works on like these pinkish um enemies and your
right hand is your lock on gun gun and i couldn't tell if i was supposed to like lock on fully and
then like swing my hands forward to shoot or if it was just automatically shot i think i had to
point my hand forward but i definitely was getting hit a whole lot in that game but it was on no die
so it didn't matter and the music was really good i imagine uh what little i could hear yeah because
if this one was outside underneath the tent oh lord which is of course the optimal playing uh
you know environment for a music game and a connect game they must have been at that booth
where i think rock of the dead was shown last year and it was not a great location there's amongst
all you know you want what that booth was that booth was where a long time ago i think you were
there for the c3 where they have the balls tent set up i don't even think i remember that but
that's all right it's been a long time that's like not even on convention grounds it's across the
street oh geez oh oh god okay you were like you weren't even in the convention center at that
point yeah that's when i was walking there this morning and then they're like hey do you want to
come play some games we got brinks i was like no no i can't try out the theater it's like yep let's
go over there because i i still haven't found it on the show floor and i've been looking it's
probably not there because it's out like what next week so i don't think there's a lot more to
say about it so all right well what else did you use hands on um i didn't get my hands on it but i
did get to sit through the presentation for saint throw the third um and that was pretty funny i've
never liked open world games and i don't like gta or anything like that so i just kind of went in
with an open mind and that game looks freaking hilarious and they didn't censor the the dildo
bat thing that they hit people with that was really funny and they also said that you can make
your character naked in play i was like how is this going to get an m rating at that point
unless they're like built like a barbie doll naked naked to them might mean like booty shorts
you know it might be like just nothing but you know well so my male character i'd make would
have beauty shorts i guess that's your i i don't know if you just heard damn but la noir i don't
know if you play that that got an m rating and that's got full-on beaver so totally oh yeah
i don't know i haven't i i've got it i haven't finished it yet or even some clothes spoiler
well i guess yeah i guess if it's not like an actual fashion it won't get anything bad but
um that was really funny uh i liked what i saw they showed up off some open world stuff which
was just humorous and then um like you can put people in a cannon that's on a car and shoot them
out and everybody loves you because uh you're you're getting the things are like like celebrities so
no matter what you do they like you so you put them in a cannon you shoot them out at things and
you know they die and people are all excited because they're meeting you um this is gonna be
a totally obscure reference but this reminds me of um one of the movies that stars divine if you uh
know who divine is i think it's female trouble or something and you know it's always she's very
filthy and over the top and stuff and there's a scene where she's like who wants to die for art
and everybody's like me me me and so she shoots one of them and i don't know why but what you're
describing sounds to me like that but that's the over the top craziness is what they're going for
in this game so they've succeeded yeah definitely um and then they showed a mission which they were
uh robbing a bank and it turned out to be like you know some rival gangs bank or whatever so
fighting ensued and at one point during the gunfight which was really gory too um just
some random person in the hood he came up and asked for your autograph and you get like extra
points if you sign it i was like that's hilarious awesome um so is this even though you don't play
the gta style games it sounds like you might be interested in getting this one yeah i might try
this one this one looks really funny so i mean that's one thing about grandpa does it takes
itself pretty seriously and i don't know this just seems like like kind of like smoking aces
that would be or was it lucky number seven i don't know no that's broken aces yeah i'm not
looking over seven um but that's really all i got to play today i think like i'm racking my
my brain but the vita took up so much time that i don't think there was much else for today all
right so uh uh anything you're gonna try to look at tomorrow i mean i know we're not doing a show
tomorrow but anything you might want to look at i was debating on doing the wee or not and i think
my final decision is i'm not gonna go to it because i don't think it's worth the time um
so i think tomorrow is going to be catch up day like i'm gonna go try to do uncharted 3 because
you get like a t-shirt and some stuff for doing uncharted 3 i'm gonna go back through the 3ds
lines because you get pins um when you play the games and i want more pins because it's swag
and i and risen heaven is there for the we and i haven't got to play it yet and i really want
to do that because i like rhythm heaven so i might just hang out in the we and sony tomorrow and
just completely avoid the other hall because i mean most of the cool stuff is either behind
closed doors or just in video form so you're kind of finding the uh usual e3 thing that seems to be
more and more popular the last five years to be true where all the really good stuff is behind
closed doors and there's very little out there on the on the floor for the rest of you yeah yeah
that's too bad i don't understand the the media restrictions this year because it doesn't look
like it really changed anything i felt like if they did the restrictions it would probably mean
like more stuff on the floor but it feels like there's less stuff on the floor like 2k and
Activision all have their stuff behind closed doors i think Bethesda has all their stuff behind closed
doors ea has all all their good stuff behind closed doors huh wow i guess they just don't
want the general public forming opinions on games like we're doing right now so so and well cannot
be needs to take that advice and you know hide like silent hill when they want because it's awful
i tried it again today that's right and it was still bad so that whole day did not make a difference
how funny i was just asked it's because dark soccer is very sad to hear that silent hill
isn't very good i'm sad to hear it too but uh you need to try the alan wait game that's supposedly
xbox where is that i would have or else i haven't seen it uh i think it's a microsoft boost somewhere
unless it's uh behind closed doors like everything else i don't know oh let me just have to hear that
hall again ask bobby he's in chat oh wait you're not in chat i was just asked bob bobby's in the
chat room he might be able to tell you well maybe you can relay the message to me right now since
we're live and you can read a chat room you will just have to do some research all right all right
well uh me glitov thank you very much for uh joining us past couple days and giving us your
thoughts and impressions on what you saw on the show floor anything else you want to get out before
we let you go no i ran to kira yeah kiriyama okra twice today why are you stalking him yeah i did
another time i did not text you about because i was like at that point is it really worth it like
it's like a daily occurrence now are you asking for his picture every time are you are you making
eye contact with him and giving him flirty eyebrows did you give him a hug he loves i've already given
i've already given him like a side hug before no full-on manly pat on the back hug go for it
and close your eyes you don't know what to do because christian side is really bad
he what i missed that last part what did you say i said you only give christian side hugs
yeah okay that's probably true oh i said uh every time i've gone up to him i keep you know
realizing how bad his english is and he had like a translator chick with him today so it kind of
helped but yeah it's kind of hard to talk to him and i don't think that me running up and trying
to give him a hug would help you know break down that language barrier or anything fail
yeah see you know saying dice he really long elongated because he would be running away
why you no hug
speaking broken english that's like i was thinking of the the little men
main thing the so-and-so why you know this all right mijot we're gonna let you go uh i gotta
get bobby on it's uh here too tiger call said he'd be like security exactly you don't want to
get thrown out of the last time someone's not even near the convention center so he has no security
to call if you are gonna get thrown out of e3 though if you are gonna get thrown out of e3
though do it on the last day yes all right so what like try to make out with them if you want
i know that's your call all right i'm not endorsing it all right bye thank you again
for joining us and have fun tonight at whatever parties you're going to are you going to any
parties tonight what are you doing tonight uh i'm supposedly going to an old konami employee meetup
and that's not really a party more uh let's complain about our lives tell them we miss
them because konami games were good like five years ago all right oh yeah all right take care
all right goodbye bye all right miklotov ladies and gentlemen joining us here live on orange
lounge radio our second and final day of e3 coverage what do you guys think about what
you've heard and uh seen online and so forth about the ps vita so far since that dominated
most of miklotov's day he it almost sounds like he waited longer for that than bobby did the
weu yesterday i want the music game yeah the music game was pretty cool doesn't it yes that sound
shapes the d-pad looks lame and very small yeah i'm worried about this you're lame and very oh i
meant and i don't know if you missed it but he he called those buttons m and m minis and i'm like
that does not sound i would not want to play a system with m and m minis for buttons i would
like to eat some m and m minis i do have fred flintstone thumbs and that's going to be a problem
dan's got bigger thumbs dan's got big wide thumbs one two three four i declare a thumb dance pretty
vicious all right well uh i think we're gonna go ahead and give bobby a call i think he's back well
i know he's back because he's in the chat room and uh he should be standing by so i just gotta punch
in his digits i have to look up his digits so i can do that live radio it's great if you want
to join us in our chat room chat dot orange lounge radio dot com as we are broadcasting live on you
stream tonight not our normal home but our special home just for the night this is our box out in
front of the building there might also there might also be some like video things coming
in the future i promise keep the keep the ustream thing bookmarked and we're gonna go to bobby right
now you know whenever he picks up the phone hey is it bobby hello hey how you doing i'm doing good
well better now you're better now that you're not in traffic yes just think about it bobby
i'm not near the transformer that blew up or whatever well we're going to disneyland tomorrow
we get to sit in that for hours it's gonna be fun hey incidentally you have to walk to anahim to
meet us well you know it's funny but i i know we want to get into games here too but i'm gonna do
a tangent real quick originally i thought well why don't i have you meet me somewhere and the
place i had picked i believe was that place where the sony press conference was held so after you
said it took me 55 minutes in traffic to get there i'm like maybe that's not such a good idea so i
think we're just gonna yeah i think we're just gonna come down to la live i'll text you tomorrow
but anyway we talk about that offline we will make it work we will la will be our bitch
have you made la your bitch bobby fuck la
la l.a bows to me i heard you uh had a lot of Bethesda beer last night
uh yeah i don't remember how much that's a good sign i lost count at about five and so
there were heinekens no there were there were new castles and that's when i met new castles
why did i say heineken yeah new castle is the best ever how was it how was the Bethesda party
did you ride the bull no i didn't ride the bull i mainly felt like it was so packed like everybody
was there but i mean it was so packed like i tried to go out and mingle and it was just like i'm
going back to my table with electric sisterhood and i'm just gonna sit here and when they did
karaoke we changed the lyrics to every single song to friday because that's for the journey
song that was the only one we didn't turn into friday but everything else somehow became talking
about friday and front seats and back seats and you know which which one do i take because that's
what's funny when you're drinking a bunch of Bethesda beer that's right beer thesda and we
look if we look it was not a karaoke song or i would have sung it did ninja sister get on the
bull no no no they didn't somebody one of the people from their crew did and he sang as well
ah okay but uh neither of the sisters did all right all right well anyhow let's let's talk about
your day at e3 today you got to actually get a little more of the games today because yesterday
obviously your day was like all we you well not all but mostly right today you got to get a little
more into some of the other games so what tell us about some of the stuff you got hands on with
today i know i know skyrim was a big demo you got right you didn't you didn't get hands on but yeah
right yeah it's a it was a demo and and some of the things i mean it it looks really nice
um it crashed on us which is great um it crashed they're like hmm we need to do we need to switch
something out until like the skyrim logo came up and he like did some stuff and flashed some
things and then you know okay now we're continuing again out of curiosity did they tell you to shut
off your video cameras did they tell you to shut off your video cameras in that demo oh yeah yeah
no no photos no video cameras um that one you could record audio like i could have recorded him
speaking uh but yeah no video cameras or anything in defense of anything you know and um but it was
sorry to answer something that came up when miklotov was on the show earlier that's why a
lot of stuff is behind closed doors so they can take away cameras and things like that and not
let you use them because of what just happened when when bobby was seeing skyrim is that when
the game crashes then they don't want people running to youtube going look at this piece of
shit game and how it crashes well i was gonna say though you remember when we got into bethesda
um when we got the appointment with bethesda the first year and they just like go ahead and
film star trek that's cool i think a star trek was was coming out soon i was filming call of
cthulhu too all right they're just like please please film anything just just get it out there
no now with the rise of camera phones yeah leaks are you know they're instant you know you're
oh recorded oh it's on youtube and they just don't want to take that chance i understand sorry for
the tangent bob and they were watching they were watching for people if they happen to be holding
up a phone or something and they had tried to be discreet so now here was one thing is um you know
a lot of people i heard a lot of people bitch about another rpg that came out a couple years
ago uh that i played the sequel to today final fantasy 13 and why am i bringing that up in
reference to siren because that whole chrysanthemum whatever it's called that's your skill system in
skyrim interesting huh the way that you uh basically you unlock these constellations in
the sky and that's how you choose your skills and inside that there's a little ring where you get as
you get more skill points you go to the next point of the ring and it creates a little circle and
stuff like that that i mean it does like i looked at it i'm like that's final fantasy 13 right there
wow and like people hated it in final fantasy 13 but they're probably gonna love it in skyrim
of course of course double standards drive the gaming media what are you talking about
yeah see i got it because i didn't bring this up last night the public is an idiot
i think um because i i have heard so much like snark and hate and stuff from the gaming community
about like everything like it's like you know sitting in the chat room during the press
conferences like you think that you know microsoft took a big old dump in the middle of the stage
and gave you smell-o-vision so you could smell it at home because like they just
hated everything they're like why don't all this stuff that connect oh modern warfare 3 i don't
want to see modern warfare 3 oh oh it's another halo oh wah wah and you know and then like nintendo
like hey this is like something you've never seen before i don't want that they don't want another
mario you'll suck you know and it's like i mean there's a lot of people out there like dude if
you don't you know i gaming may have moved on past you and you may need to just stop gaming if
there's nothing that has been shown that you like you're a little bit too jaded to be a gamer i think
and i've been seeing that a lot it's not here at the show floor like there's not that much hate
here it's all the people at home i like that in the absence of loki tonight we get bobby doing
the ranting that is not what i expect i thought it would be damn but we get bobby doing the ranting
bobby's ranting seems to come off a little bit more cerebral i'm trying to let bobby
rant because he sounds like he has some things he needs to work out i think he knows what i
think he's right on oh exactly all i can say is agree like times 10 likes this post people yeah
exactly like people are idiots they just can't handle it it reggie hit it on the head you know
and it's funny that he walked out in public and he just said it he's like look you guys want things
that are different but you want something you're comfortable with fine we'll fucking do that we're
nintendo it's what we do sony's just like whatever here's a better psp and uncharted microsoft's like
connect and everybody's just like oh my god why can't there be something mind-blowing it's because
the people are spoiled they got used to these blockbuster e3 announcements every year and now
the blockbusters aren't good enough because the gaming companies got practically nothing left
or they're just not willing to show it off yet do you think the microsoft thing
might have come off a lot different if it hadn't been spoiled literally 30 minutes before showtime
yes halo 4 i think so too much much more important had everybody not i think gamer
underpants everywhere would have needed to be changed if that had not been honestly they should
have led with halo 4 you think exactly all right anyway i don't want to recap the press conferences
i gotta i gotta move forward here but um bobby skyrim was it as beautiful as it seems to look
when i'm watching it on game trailers or wherever online yes and now i mean they probably souped it
up a little bit it was running on a big movie screen uh but it looked and sounded beautiful
um you know and then you have all the weather effects and changing the weather effects and stuff
like that does does it look like and then right go ahead yeah uh go ahead go ahead now i was gonna
say does it seem like you'll sink as many hours into skyrim as you did with oblivion because
oblivion you could easily sink triple digit hours into that game it was disgusting yes absolutely
because they even showed like these they walked us through a town and like here's all the stuff
you can do in the town and you could just go over here and chop wood you can do jobs like a table
and you know all that stuff so there's you know lots of other side quests a lot other than the
main story that they're packing in here and you know the the dragons are awesome just you know
watching you know how they fly around and it's quick and you know all the stuff they're doing
and and it's not like a you know pattern boss fight is what they they said they said they've
got ai so no two dragon fights will be the same and even like our guy got you know hit around a
couple times probably didn't expect so i mean they showed a couple different like two dragon
player they showed dragon five we ran away from and then we met up with that dragon again and
then a bigger dragon showed up and it was just you know here let me show you how you can do these
spells and you know i do this and i can shout this at him and i'll use this fireball on him and
you know injure him so he hits the ground and you know runs up to a castle to see if other people
will help him and the dragon goes up and eats those people it was awesome do you think it'll
make the release date of 11 11 11 uh i believe they will it was i mean it was you know they
showed us all the menu systems and so all that stuff's coded in and i think that they're in the
polishing phase right now other than that one bug that crashed the thing but um you know i i think
they will i think they'll make that and um i i think people will be pleased with it now i mean
the fez obviously does have the track record of releasing buggy games and uh games crash and stuff
so i i would not be surprised if that's the case here um but you know they've done that and uh you
know like all the stuff they've done with the menu system and the map system and kind of makes things
more exciting and seamless and stuff and you know they simplified the combat your the right triggers
your right hand your left trigger your left hand whatever's in it that's what goes so you know
there's your shield and you know your sword and stuff like that do the monsters still level do
the monsters still level up with you they did not talk about that interesting but i i would assume
that they would because they're Bethesda and they're evil like that all right well so uh was
that the only thing that Bethesda showed you or did you get to see anything else i went to see
their prey to demonstration okay and and uh you know where you know it's alien noir is what they
were calling it and stuff and and you know running around um basically in this game you play as the
u.s marshal on a plane that crashed in the first game that you actually saw in the first game so
he you know you start off there and then you actually it fast forwards six months later to
when you're like the only human on their alien planet and you're now doing jobs oh i didn't
realize that's how they were tying it together because when you see that trailer you're like
what the hell does this have to do with prey yeah that was my literal reaction this looks awesome
and i showed it to alan who loves that like cloverfield and and blair witch kind of stuff
that's all and that's very much what the trailer is like right and it was like wow this is awesome
it's it's it's prey yeah yeah so i mean basically and you do meet up with the character they did
say spoiler alert you do meet up with the character from prey one eventually interesting story
but basically you're you are uh a mercenary for hire because you used to be a u.s marshal so
that's why you had a gun on the plane when it crashed into whatever in prey one uh so he
basically took those skills and now he's a mercenary a human mercenary on this on the
home world of the alien and he's actually takes jobs for the aliens he can go through and help
people or hurt people and he can corral people in and there's you know thugs will attack you as you
go through it's a big open world thing on their alien planet so that that was kind of interesting
and and uh you know i watched that until that crashed oh because he was like i need to go up
to this guy and there's a climbing thing and so he starts climbing up and his arm starts going
through the wall and then it just freezes so it sounds like uh that that would go ahead and then
so that that was like and i'm like you know i've seen this it's cool i'm sold i'm gonna go check
out something else because you know that was 15 minutes into the demo and i didn't know how long
it would take them to get the demo back up and if they'd be in the same spot so that's all i saw
pretty too and then i uh since i don't like shooters i still went over to rage and the racing so i
could see how that was and it's very smooth and very fluid and i did the little three-lap race
and stuff um but it's it's a very those enemies are a little cheap because it's i couldn't figure
out how to defend myself against the missiles that they kept throwing at me so i anytime i would get
into third out of four anytime i got into third place i would immediately like blow up and there's
nothing i could do about it like incoming i'm like okay what do i do okay i'll go around this corner
oh it's a homing missile damn i'm blown up again at least you gave it the good old college try
i did so um so yeah so i got to that's what i did in the Bethesda booth um and uh so i'm trying to
think of what else i uh looked at and played today i mean i i went in and my other appointment was
with ccp games and it was it was a powerpoint presentation uh with some videos embedded in
about how they're going to be working dust 5.4 into eve online and essentially they were talking
about their vision and the technology and it is it's really neat and i've learned the reason
they're ps3 exclusive is because sony has relaxed a lot of their rules on what they can and can't
do on psn and microsoft wouldn't do that dust 514 is a multiplayer only first-person shooter and it
is running on the exact same servers of eve online as in you're going to be in the same corporation
as eve online players you can transfer money and items between eve online and dust 514 basically
dust 514 is the only way you can be on a planet and eve online is the only way you can be in space
wow and so and so corporations that already have wars going on now will have the added dimension
of the wars in dust 514 and they will be fighting on the planet and yes i because i as you see this
in the trailer and they're like yes this is exactly how it works the people playing dust
514 can call up to the people playing eve online and orbit around the planet say i need an orbital
strike i need a you know laser strike and the people playing eve can then call down
this big massive laser that's in orbit to incinerate something in the dust 514 multiplayer
match going on at that same time that sounds awesome i've never played eve online in my life
it's just not something that's really jumped out as something interesting to me but that sounds
amazing like i i i love how the two different games tie together like that that sounds just
awesome and dust 514 is tailored for first-person shooter fans who felt eve was too complex or out
of their league a little bit you know they couldn't get into it but they still like the
idea of being a part of this universe uh single shard server they said that they've had i think
64 000 people concurrent is their record of how many people have played eve online at one time
on one for her wow and and uh and also uh dust 514 it's going to be like a it's going to be a
psn title downloadable uh 20 or 30 bucks i don't they didn't really pay the price it's somewhere
around there so it's a downloadable title and then it's free to play there's no monthly fee
oh wow and that money and the coverage they call it a cover charge is what they call buying the
title and that money that you pay for that gets turned into in-game currency so you start off with
money already in your account which is basically the market value of what you just pay for that
cover charge isn't that kind of how eve online works too i i i think you can buy like they
support uh real money trade because they they they endorse it or they they do they monitor it
they they provide it yeah well yeah well it's there's a monthly subscription for eve online
but if you're good enough you can actually buy they're called plex pilot license extension cards
in the game that gives you 30 more days oh right okay okay that's how and you can you know trade
them in game and stuff like people and that's how you know some corporations will actually pay
people to play the game for them by giving them plex wow and you you can do that so you know yeah
so it's an amazing economy and they were even talking about you know some of the wars and stuff
that have gone on and they even like actually referenced one of these player corporations in
their trailer video where it was um i can't remember it might have been like the netherlands
or something was where this corporation was from and they were fighting a russian corporation
corporation in this one sector of space and you know the russians were out out out powering them
and out maneuvering them and in stuff but the the the dutch kept coming back and they couldn't figure
out why and so there was espionage in the game by these corporations ccp had nothing to do with this
espionage in the game where they kind of figured out that the americans were funding the dutch
because they didn't want to fight the russians directly so they cut off they cut off the trade
route wiped out that dutch corporation and that was the end of it wow so it's stuff like that
that they're you know because they say you know games like world of warcraft and everquest those
are theme parks where there are quests given to you and you know it's the same thing every time
and stuff like that eve online it's the sandbox they give you the fan the bucket you know the
the area and you make the story and that's what they're saying that you know dust 514 is going
to do with the same type of thing where you know and and the reason it's geographically like that
is because of like time zones and stuff that's when people are playing and so they expect that
that's going to be the same way and they did say that uh for latency if you're worried about lags
it's the first person shooter eve online is not you know it can handle latency uh the first person
shooter they're actually going to have battle servers in various parts of the world so you'll
be connecting to that instead because their main eve online server cluster is in london
so currently when you play eve online their supercomputer is in london and it's like they
said like it weighs more than a ton but i think they said how many machines it was uh but they
didn't i can't remember the number but they're going to have battle servers in uh geographic
locations so you have a low ping you know when you're playing dust 514 because this most console
games are peer-to-peer where one of the other ps3s is the server right in this the server is eve
online and sony was the only one that allowed them to do that interesting and they also said that uh
i asked you know you're you're infuriating a lot of pc players and stuff and they're like eve
online's been around for over eight years you can read between the lines on that wow i feel like
i've learned more about this game than anything else at e3 and like i i kind of just went no okay
and it might tie into eve online that might be kind of cool but the way you describe it i'm like
wow this this this almost makes me want to try eve online at least it sounds interesting yeah it
sounds really interesting if they pull it off that's that's fast that's fascinating how the
one game could impact the other like that so cool kai judo asks uh when can i get my hands on some
stuff they are doing a very closed beta at the end of the year which is going to be closed in
the sense of it's going to go to the high end eve online players and you know hand-picked people
but sometime next year uh but they've been laying the groundwork for dust inside e
for the last three years with their expansion uh like you know planetary building planetary
formations and stuff like that you could build refineries on planet that started two years ago
that was in preparation for dust and that in introduced some of the server aspects that would
handle dust and you know stuff like that so it was i mean it was the reason i'm talking so much
about it because they gave so much interesting technical information for me as a technical
person as well um that you know it's just they didn't show the game like they didn't play the
game they did with the powerpoint they showed some movies it wasn't even real like some of it was
real gameplay footage but you know they didn't actually have a playable where they had a playable
in other places before um you know they've just said you know we're talking about our philosophy
and creating games and here's what we're trying to do and here's what we've already done and you
know we're awesome and that's okay you got so much information about it that you're still a little
hype for the game i mean at the end of the day it'll really be about well how does it you know
how does it pull off because although it sounds awesome in theory like what if this breaks eve
online you know like but these you know again like you said eve online has been around for
eight years you know it may not be a quote-unquote competitor to wow but it's always been a great
like alternative to wow but i just like i think of a game like star trek online which i played
just a little bit during the beta but jamie you were really into and the thing with star trek
online for me is that i loved the away team stuff but i did not like the space combat at all but
like what if that was two separate games and like i could just play a game that's nothing but away
team stuff i would have been all over that see it actually kind of got turned around for me that i
liked the space see you could play eve i could play dust and we could still kind of be in that
same universe that's always something i'd kind of wanted you know that you had your position i mean
yeah it's a little different with star trek but i think that i get the thing it would be really cool
wow so interesting fascinating you don't get off the ship you're stuck there the most fascinating
part of my day wow all right well i i don't know if you can follow that up with other impressions
and other things you saw that maybe fascinated you a little bit okay well no i can and actually
i got an interview with this guy because you know i was kind of walking around
and i passed by nico's booth you know they make all those you know the the extra peripherals or
whatever and i'm like usually i'm like eh it's nico all right this time i actually stopped and
looked and what they've got is a device that might improve a lot for a lot of people motion gaming
it's called the zoom and what this does it's for the connect and it basically because connect
fires out all these infrared lasers and that's how it determines the positioning it actually
modifies where the lasers go and it gives it a wide angle lens so now you don't have to stand
as far away from your tv nice so it basically instead of being six to eight feet away you can
now be four to six feet away and two players of connect adventures can be you know stand kind of
where one player would stand before and it seemed it worked pretty well from what i was seeing on
there so i have a little i have an interview with a guy talking about that and uh you know how much
it's going to cost which it's not that expensive it's only 30 bucks and it's coming out in august
that could be great for those of us that live in like apartments and things where we're a little
more cramped up or just if you have a lot of stuff like some people do that sounds great or not not
want to have to move the coffee table every time you want to play connect i think that's that sounds
like it could be an awesome peripheral you know if it works but it it seems like if you were watching
people play it at e3 that were they're normal people playing it right not not all their people
right it's you could have i could have walked up and played it nice you just didn't want anyone
to get that on video yeah so uh but um let's see what else did i um i did play uh final fantasy 13
too how was that and i don't know if i don't know if shane talked about that or not uh it is uh
uh it is uh final fantasy 13 plus shamu because of the with the quick time events and stuff um
and and it built some uh other neat camera things and it is going to be a little bit more open
uh no open-ended and stuff you can you know because like final fantasy 13 it gave me that
sense of urgency of the linearity of it and stuff and then when you get more as urgent then you
could roam around well that sense of urgency is probably not going to be there as much in 13 too
you know i let you know go ahead yeah i was just saying i looked at the trailer for 13 too online
and uh i did notice it seemed like they were emphasizing even in the trailer that there was
more open world and open environments you could see in the maps they were not linear so i mean
that was one of the biggest you know complaints about 13 so i i could that was one thing i noticed
right off the top yep and uh one of the things that happened to me is that a monster joined my
party so i had i had a monster in my party i had my two humans and then like this monster suddenly
was in my party i don't know why it was you know i couldn't hear anything so i didn't know if it
was explaining dialogue but uh you know so and it depending on what paradigm you were in that
monster change like he was a little fire plant in commando mode or when you turn him to ravager he
turned into this big server thing huh so it was it was that was kind of cool and they introduced
this um and i didn't really understand it all that much once again because i was on the show floor
uh but it's like you've got a little mod with you and when enemies appear a little countdown timer
appears and however quick you hit the enemy uh that you know that determines if you get this
first hit or if they hit you first or whatever uh that was kind of interesting and then they did
some of like these cinematic events and live events and stuff uh while you're just walking
around and you know you can still walk around and like the camera will change to show something
happening hmm so it was kind of cool um you know i'm you know i'm sold on it but you also like 13
right what you also like 13 and a lot of you also like 13 though right and a lot of people didn't
yes i like 13 so you know you keep that in mind when i say that that i you know since i like 13
you know i like 32 i like what they added to it but it is you know the core gameplay of the
paradigm shifting all that stuff that's that's still there 13 it didn't change at least not what
i saw um do you think that maybe there's enough there to kind of squelch the haters a little bit
oh no haters are gonna hate all right sounds familiar gamershateeverything.com right that's
right okay exactly um so let's see i'm trying to think of what else i kind of walked by and got to
see it was i was running around and stuff um i did go into atlas's booth a little bit in the
little meeting room area that was open so i could get into it um and they were showing uh rock of
ages which is the only one rock of ages and they were showing catherine and they were talking about
other things but those were kind of the only ones they were showing um and i played rock of ages and
i'm it was it's kind of hard the thing about e3 that people don't realize is that a lot of times
they dump you in the middle of things and there's not always a tutorial and there's not always a guy
standing there telling you okay here's what's going on so i had no clue what i was doing it's
like it's a tower defense game and then it's katamari damasi but not really because it's not
tank controls and you're trying to break down another guy's castle and it was it was kind of
interesting i'm sure that i'd like it more if i played it you know knowing what i was doing
but um that one was kind of cool i didn't you know there was too many people for catherine
in the place was getting cramped so i didn't get to go in there um so uh trying to think of what
else did you do you remember seeing anything on my twitter that i've been missing no i i mostly
wanted to hear about skyrim though but that you were getting some feedback on twitter today any
good uh any good questions you were able to get answered for people on twitter at twitter.com
slash bobby blackwolf i i did i started answering questions and then loki actually answered them
better than i did because like they weren't they weren't giving me exact dates and he'd be like oh
no that's coming out on february 12th um one thing i didn't get to play this yet um but uh you know
a good colleague of mine shadow next gen he's actually sitting right across from me right now
howdy um he he was uh able to get in to see the demo of fable the journey oh we learned something
but not many people are talking about what's that the game is not on rails oh it sure looked like it
was on rails okay okay it sure looked like it but according to mr molyneux who apparently gave that
particular demo just because he had nothing else better to do he said it's not on rails and you
know you can believe everything that molyneux says yeah it's always dead on accurate not not over
hyped at all so okay well then maybe maybe we'll just need to see more videos of the game in actual
well i wonder how do you move around yet you have the connect thing going on that's why i always
assumed a lot of connect stuff was on rails because like well if i'm not holding a controller
but i i also kind of thought connect was supposed to allow me to sit my big butt on the couch
with my controller yeah and maybe i'll maybe i'll lift my hand and wave it for something you know or
or at some point it could actually see fingers i don't know yeah now the game i did play today and
this is the reason i forgot about this because it was the first one i did this morning i went
to disneyland already i've already been to disney you went to play disneyland adventures huh
i did i played connect adventures with disney characters and that one the way the way that
you move in that and it's kind of interesting funny like in the overworld the the disneyland
area they actually have like the quest markers that look just like tabled like the little yellow
circles around things um but the way you move on that is you just put your hand down and you
start moving and then if you go right and left that's how you turn your character um and i did
an alice in wonderland video or mini game and uh it was um you remember the whitewater raft rafting
thing that was in connect adventures yes yeah it's that it's that with alice in wonderland characters
um so it basically you know when you guys are saying it's connect adventure with disney that's
pretty much what it is also i guess to me like i didn't get to do the the peter pan one but it's
been a while since i've been there but it's not a one-to-one representation of the ride at least i
hope the alice in wonderland ride is not you in a golf in a golf ball with alice hitting you and
sending you down and all these cards are trying to you know get in your way and you have to jump
over them i can guarantee you the ride is not like bobbie you will not have to worry if we do end up
going on that ride on friday we will not get pelt golf balls at you unless you want that full
experience because we are going for research purposes that's only on it's a small world at
least that's what you feel like by the time you get out of it when a small world breaks down the
puppets start pelting oh i've been in there when it during christmas all those people are actually
people who are trapped inside of the ride when it broke down and they were turned into little
mannequins and then you sing forever so was it was it enough to make you go gosh i i might actually
kind of want to get this game or were you like nah this is just the same crap with a new label
i i said gosh i might want to put this game on my gamefly queue
okay kind of in the middle all right get it from gamefly get my achievements then get out right
yeah fair enough yeah um so other than that i'm really i mean i talked to the playstation home
developers a little bit oh uh and i'm probably going to be doing an interview with them because
blender uh asked me about you know because there's this big freezing bug and they you know you
i was talking to people that actually work on i think content creation stuff but they were like
yeah we addressed that finally like this you know yesterday and you know blah blah blah and they
have like things that they want people to do if they encounter like we want this far
wide i'm like so you want to go on the air about that and they're like oh i'd love to
but i got to talk to pr so i may have this huge ps home interview tomorrow i'm soliciting questions
on twitter tonight some people have sent me some real good ones wow but i may be able to
report an interview there i know there's a lot of questions people have about playstation home
like when's it getting out of beta is it a google product yeah so um i think it's all data didn't
they take the word beta out of home no no when i launched it earlier today or not uh last night
you know how i went into playstation home it was completely on accident i met to go i meant to go
in the store and i accidentally like because my thumbs are fat like fred flintstone i went up and
i went into playstation home instead and i was like well shit now that i launched this i might
as well just kind of look around i clearly noticed the beta tag still on it and i was like hasn't
this been around for like two years now at least so uh and then uh i did kind of walk through the
indicate booth which is all the independent games where they had nerd twister as an actual twister
with a voice telling you where to put your next hand or foot on what color but the way that they
did it it's it's the i think they call it twister anapolis 5000 it's a race so everybody starts at
the end and i posted a picture of this on twitter and it says real long twister board and everybody
starts one end of the twister board and it says okay right hand blue and so you put your right
hand on blue and you know and you're trying to go forward and whoever makes it to the end first
without leaving one of their you know without waving one of your other hands uh they declared
the winner so that that was interesting and they had something else like what they had like it
looked like a four square court but i couldn't like they were throwing cups or something i don't
know what that was but i also saw in there i was just saying because the twister but the twister
was nerd twister what happened is that when you got to the very end the mat was pulled away and
you all fall into a cologne bath and that's how they kept e3 sane now that was not the craziest
thing that i saw in the indicator oh dear okay and i was i wanted to get a picture of this but
by the time i thought about getting the picture of it uh they were not playing it anymore it is
called a kiss controller a what where a kiss controller okay as in i thought he said a little
device you kiss this little device and that actually like they were shown like it does a
bowling game and the better kissers you are the better you bowl and you're actually kissing this
it is i i didn't want to approach it because i didn't want to you do it myself i wanted to
get a picture of somebody else doing it interesting wow they were putting those
booth babes to work weren't they i was like and there was this other game that had like a gas
mask and i didn't know what that was i don't know what that was but the guy was wearing like a full
on gas mask and playing you know might have been like some virtual reality type of thing as well
but it also tried to breathing or something i don't know maybe that was just to protect him
from the fanboy wink this clearly would have been the type of thing that used to be in kensha hall
yes awesome yeah that this stuff that stuff would have been intention because i mean the
indicate stuff so it was a lot of the independent games and stuff and then they had normal games in
there too that those were like on the edges you know that was the oh i've never thought of that
before well now bobby i know you've got one more day left at e3 and i know as part of your day
tomorrow you're going to twitter eric can twitter continue your twitter adventures where you let
the uh listeners of your show and and the olr listeners who jump in there and want to follow
you and direct you around too look at whatever but what else haven't you seen yet that you're
like i've got to get this tomorrow before this stuff's done okay well um i want to see what
everybody's talking about with saints road the third i want to see child of eden if i can find
it you just need to talk to miklotov because that's exactly what he talked to us about today
were those two games yeah so i i this is not for the shame for all this show but no i mean i want
to see both of those because also like even like loki was twittering me have you seen go see saints
row go see saints row and i'm like okay i will i promise i just wasn't in that hall i've been in
the cell for two days now i've pretty much been in the hall that like sony and nintendo is in so i
think i'm done there and i'm going to go try to spend as much as i can in uh the main hall i'm
considering trying to get in the line for the vita but if it's really longer than the wii uu line
i think i'm gonna skip on that yeah miklotov waited four hours today so take it or leave it
i guess and he said it was worth it but of course then he continued to say i'm not waiting in that
wii u line so i don't know yeah yeah so so i don't know i may or may not do that i don't think so i
really need to like catch up on some stuff i want to see that i want to see if i can get into the
fable room to see that um and really just kind of go around and see you know see the stuff that's
in that hall because like that's where they've got a retro video game museum has a booth here
and that's the as said i want to kind of stop by and see that and um you know see there's the
other like kenshaw hall type companies in that area but i haven't gone in and see um i haven't
seen dead island yet you know i saw where it was in square enix's booth but i haven't actually seen
it yet you gotta go down there's all that i need to go and kind of hit everything yet if you're
gonna go see dead island you gotta run up to aubrey and talk to her like she sends out her
emails to everybody omg she she is not on the floor she's up in the meeting room suites and
i was unsuccessful in getting an appointment up there ah bummer i've even tweeted her i'm like
look i just want to say hi how does this happen i don't have an appointment to make an appointment
to say hi for 30 seconds how does this happen and i gotta respond she's probably like ew a creepy
stalker you i'm just kidding it's a creepy stalker all right um well bobby i know uh some of the
stuff you're going to see tomorrow at the show you will give more impressions on on your own show
which of course sunday night at all games radio or more information available at bobbyblackwolf.com
right that's right all right 8 p.m eastern 5 p.m pacific i'll talk about that stuff and
like i said i'll actually talk about the Wii Wii Wii U games because we didn't really talk about
the games we just talked about the controller itself right i'll talk about some of the
conceptual demos and stuff then and uh more of that stuff and you know hey you might we might
have a very famous person's bumper premiere this sunday oh exciting so that that'd be very very
cool uh and um oh unfortunately we won't be here to hear it because we'll be on our way back from
la so so bobby if you want you can go along i i i could you you'll hear it tomorrow you'll hear
the bumper tomorrow oh okay okay good i'm excited oh i get a sneak peek all right awesome that's
right awesome exciting early preview but bobby's gonna make me sign an nda so sorry guys i won't
be able to tell you what it is you'll tune in sunday so nda or i get thrown off the matterhorn
all right um well bobby thank you so much not only for um contributing to our show but but making
it your show as well we really appreciate that you've supported us forever and uh we just we
appreciate you sharing your e3 with us and being so dedicated and missing bethesda beer for a
little bit last night to talk to us and whatever you might be doing tonight so i i really appreciate
it we all do and and one last kind of off topic thing as we were leaving e3 yeah i'm like walking
along and there's a guy walking toward me i recognize him somewhat he's not looking up so
he almost runs into me because i start trying to you know get his attention by getting in his face
and uh dj tyrant almost ran right through me
i didn't think he was going to the show floor today i wonder what he did all right well
no no no he's got he's going to a party tonight and since his girlfriend has never been to e3
he basically took her over there just so they could see what was in the lobby and stuff like
pin three is in lobby and the fourth stuff so i got you but but they're going to some party one
of the e3 parties we got an invite to tonight cool though that's why they were there he was going as
the place was closing and we were leaving and i recognized him so i got him you know he almost
bowled me over how funny it's a small world i met i met up with dj kyron today nice nice all right
well we'll be meeting up with you tomorrow bobby of course sadly those antics are not going to be
broadcast but we're looking forward to the post e3 party in the magic kingdom so at electronica
friday night so yeah we hopefully will get maybe maybe a little bit of video at flint's i don't
know if dark soccer wears something pretty and she's willing to be on camera maybe we get
something at flint's that'd be fun perhaps perhaps all right anyhow and i can't i cannot wait for
that gift shop to take all my money i know it's gonna i wish they could take all my money it's
gonna be like some of the reaction i saw to uh the wii u just just take my money nintendo just
take it here you go all right all right take care buddy uh be safe uh tomorrow and tonight whatever
you end up doing we'll see you tomorrow all right all right take care take care bobby the one and
only bobby blackwolf of course doing the show before us at all games radio sunday nights he
starts at five pacific we start at six pacific on sunday nights uh we will not be live this coming
sunday but he will and it sounds like he's gonna have a hell of a show he's gonna have a celebrity
bumper more impressions on the wii u so he could just take the whole four hours for all i care
well that's it for our guests but i i you know and i i'm gonna go ahead and open up the skype
line at 1877 game olr or our username on skype is orange lounge radio i noticed we don't have
nearly the turnout tonight live that we did last night i think a lot of that is that you know most
of what you guys have been able to watch and see you saw in those press conferences so maybe you're
it's kind of out of your system at this point but i don't know if it's open if anyone does want to
call us give us a call again it's 1877 game olr or our username on skype is orange lounge radio
um well we just actually had a facebook post by naoki oh what did naoki say on uh facebook hot
news the guy who is behind uh he's a music producer of ddr recently right the 2011s new
ddr has been announced for we its name is dance dance revolution 2 its title concept is back to
basic the originality of ddr is the part where you play with your feet we have concentrated on that
part and created the content so that it will pursue the gameplay of traditional ddr ps not
only for the casual fans but we consider this title will be something that could be enjoyed by
core ddr fans for a long period of time as well we are aiming for the release of the title for this
fall we will do our best to respond to your expectations so please look forward for it
very interesting so now keep saying the ddr 2 on the we is going back to basics it basically
without saying it none of this balance board and flinging the wiimote around gimmicky shit he's
saying it is back to feet because that's what makes back to the feet sure forget it is it a
new feature har where's my sad trombone i don't have a soundboard right now so dude you guys
harmonize that was awesome all right well some of the other stories i have just to go over quickly
some of these have developed in the pastio day or so uh that we didn't get got i feel like with
bobby's little like dust thing i was like god i learned more about that than i've read anywhere
or heard anything that was great but uh talking quickly about some of the other things that have
come up uh just in the past 24 hours a lot of it has to do with nintendo i don't know if you guys
heard about this and what you guys think make of this nintendo stock apparently went down five
percent yesterday after the wii u was revealed and my question you guys do you think that's a
big deal it was right after the keynote uh it went down to sixteen thousand nine hundred seventy yen
that's roughly 212 dollars but that is down five percent a low that the company has not seen since
before the launch of the original wii is this damning for them or is this eh whatever i think
is people being fickle and then you know not thinking about it so but but if i'm not mistaken
most of the gamers i'm seeing posting on twitter i mean no offense guys but i don't think it's the
same people that are that are are following the uh japanese stock exchange or having a lot of
impact on that or even know what stock is apart from chicken now hold on hold on i won't go that
far i'm sure people have investments in things but it's a knee-jerk reaction you know the the
stockholders gauged what they thought the public reaction was it wasn't like oh my god it's the
second coming nintendo quick take our money except for a few people who were like take our money
i wasn't like that but i'll buy one so it dipped it's five percent i mean that's a significant drop
but over the next you know what year and a half two years demand will build nintendo will make
it happen they'll announce a price i think right now everyone's worried that this thing has to be
expensive they'll announce a price it'll be reasonable they'll sell a hajillion of them
nintendo stock will be a hundred gazillion dollars and everything will be fine for nintendo and more
fictional amounts well you know uh one thing that i did read about price is that even though
nintendo has not said anything i guess there's been hints from things like you know conversations
with executives indirect it will not be out for 250 oh no so we're looking at least probably
299 for this thing if not maybe even jumping up 349 or something well with all the competition
you know out there at what is it sub 200 now for a 360 oh yeah and and 200 bucks for the top end
360 or ps3 you gotta wonder how far nintendo can push that without seeing the uh the competition
gets some some bump from it uh now speaking of stock and i wanted to mention this but i'll let
the chatters say it because uh they said it too chat.org.com zappy says stocks fluctuate not a big
deal apple went down too after worldwide developer conference that's that's the first thing in my mind
is that well don't these things usually dip after apple press conferences and especially when all
the stuff happened with the antenna you know and their little apology press conference they did
with that i'm sure stock dips for them a lot too but they they're apple and they're still doing
just fine all these years later yeah they're making a couple bucks just a couple bucks not
doing too bad now several people in chat have mentioned this and uh black wolf's now saying
he's in chat now kind of cooling off with the listeners they're talking to them uh did you
guys cover that nintendo announced that they were ditching friend codes i had not heard that until
i walked into studio somebody posted it in chat earlier but apparently nintendo will be ditching
friend codes for the wii u good finally applause good job that's one way to get the hardcore gamer
base back that's smart i wonder if they've said much more about online let me look tiger claws
giving us a little link here so we can take a peek let's see i'm going right now to this story
at mtv multiplayer blog because nintendo or mtv is all about the video games i know what's that
about actually i hear i don't read a whole lot of these big blogs but i hear the mtv ones pretty
good i just i don't have time there's the knees in action well yeah that's the whole super mario
brothers me yeah they were talking about i think it's cute let's see um on hand at e3 ubisoft
producer adrian blunt according to him the day of friend codes are gone demonstrating ghost recon
online for the wii u um i asked him equivalent to a gamer tag on xbox live yeah exactly he said uh
what else is there there's a few things on that the first is the ability for individuals to make
accounts rather than a machine having an account each individual user has an account so
that's an account uh he continued saying also the ability to easily find friends rather than using
friend codes which we've had in the past we're able to connect players in a much easier way
which allows us to have a community that's playing together in the game blunt wasn't willing to get
more specific about the online functionality you know what that sounds like to me remember a couple
weeks ago on the show we were speculating that the system tied into facebook somehow i don't
like exactly facebook but i bet you anything this whole like find your friends online is going to be
some type of maybe that's where the nintendo stream comes in folks maybe the nintendo stream
is the online component and the stream is so and so has been playing super mario we and so and so
just got caught and catch me i see dan laughing over there you think i'm full of it or oh no no i
was laughing about the fact that nintendo has products called the we and the stream
but now now that i think about it hearing that i'm like oh the nintendo stream that would make
perfect sense it's like you know funny it's what aol aol calls it the live stream right there um
updates and stuff yeah yeah so now you can make a stream which i don't use of course i'm i'm
obviously the nintendo stream thing was like total fanboy wank speculation i don't think there was a
lot to back that up but i'm just having fun with the what ifs but i i still think the facebook
concept of nintendo record i i got mildly curious and there are already a full page of search
results for weu fan pages uh tiger claw in our chat says i bet the gamer tag thing nintendo
has coming is tied to your club nintendo account your club nintendo account has a username that's
definitely possible um sure why not why not you have a database you own nintendo hardware there
you go well that sucks because i didn't get the name i wanted then bitches and frisbee says oh
shit more facebook like crap you know it's one of those things that could be done very well or very
crappy i mean how vague is that but seriously like i hear facebook i don't necessarily think that has
to be crap because i think a lot of us think of facebook crap as my feed filling up with come play
farm bill with me and you know and you can hide that crap and so and so filled out a survey and
said something about you hide yeah exactly hide no i do that too but it's just frustrating that
bullshit shows up in the first place yeah but if nintendo were to somehow kind of contain all that
a little better might be interesting i'm ignoring all those fucking people anyway
again the phones are open if you do want to call 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on skype
is orange lounge radio um if we don't get any calls i'll kind of close quote unquote with this
story the weu reel that was showing off some of the third-party games this has been igniting the
internet today is apparently using 360 and playstation 3 footage and a lot of people are
going fail nintendo oh nintendo why didn't you tell people this is 360 ps3 you're be it you're
lyin nintendo and uh i'm kind of thinking is this really a big deal like i can't believe like i kind
of figured it was pc or 360 footage because i don't know the system's a year away i know right
but they've got the licenses for it they've and keep in mind for all the third-party stuff it's
probably what they've been provided by the developers absolutely right absolutely right
and i bet a lot of these things were a lot of these deals were probably sealed a month a month
two months ago very short time yeah these games are concepts still i and i can tell you this just
okay and this is from designer when you're working for a client and you say okay well you
want your want me to advertise this product for you i need some of your images they will send you
what they have of the item they don't care how big it is they don't care what it originally was on
they're just sending you pictures of the item what you know their pr has approved so
you get you know you get what they give you whatever you're nintendo how stupid can you be
seriously it's i know exactly what you're saying i remember back in like the genesis days and the
atari days where they'd show a screenshot of a game and it'd be for all these systems and you
know it was the the screenshot of the best looking version but nintendo's out there to make a
statement nintendo's out there to say this is our system and this is what it could do okay fine do
what you got to do put the put the code on your pc mock-up of of the wii u and play the game and
hope that it runs and if it runs great put it on your video don't throw these pictures out into the
world and be like this is what our system will do and then like a day later be like oh by the way
yeah that that's that's the competition system no no at least don't admit it lie you're nintendo
you've lied before dungeon buster says they're placeholders to give the crowd an impression of
what it could do right exactly i understand that i have a problem with that you have a problem with
everything no i don't i'm not mad i have a problem with you yes of course you do i it it wasn't i
mean the smarter thing to do would have been to put in super tiny print in the bottom corner like
conceptual video based on existing game footage or something you know something just to cover their
ass whatever but they didn't do that they put those pictures out there they put the pictures
especially you know the one the one game in there that really got a pop was when ninja guy den showed
up right and everybody was like oh fuck it's ninja guy den and it's on the wii u and it looks really
really cool yeah you should have known that was the ps3 version of the 360 version kids the one
that kind of left me like okay maybe it wasn't smart to do that was the ghost recon where they
were showing like the scope and it gave you that impression that somebody was using their little
wii u controller as the scope like it just that's what it looked like to me but it was off in the
360 version of the ps3 version but if it's true about the guts of this machine it's gonna be
basically a 360 with some extra little frills maybe a boost in the ram a boost in the shading
graphical components of it and so forth i mean nintendo's going all in that their system has to
be at least as good as the 360 or the ps3 systems that have existed for five years now so i think
it's safe to say their system will be graphically capable of more than that absolutely it's going
to at least be this level of graphics this generation and that is why they showed they did
show that little you know for what it's worth that little random ass asian flower face
asian flower flying in the bird into the the the pool and everybody went shit what is that looks
really good that was the wii u that doesn't exist anywhere else well that was the wii u's
development system right so you know is is a high spec pc so and if and if i see okay well that's
capable then i'm sure they can pull off the 360 ps3 back in the day when the when the playstation
demo disc was out and it had all the ducks and you know all over the water and that t-rex and
the t-rex and when everyone's like oh wow that's neat how many games did we get that really look
like that until the end of the playstation's life true well right it's just that kind of thing you
know it's it's all it's so early people are people are obsessing over the tiniest detail of a system
that's a year and a half away and will change and will not be the same when it comes out it'll be
better it'll be better than the stuff that's out there now well it can't not be because you cannot
buy graphical components that are as weak as the stuff that's in the ps3 and the 360 now it doesn't
exist they're gonna be better they're not gonna be next generation better they're going to be peak
of this generation better that's how nintendo rolls it's a bridge i didn't you know this whole
like generation to generation nintendo has basically said with this that they they're
not following that rule they're just following what the markets want or what have you
what was that uh from the chat room colibri for yeah that was me that was jamie um i i kind of
though one of the fears that i have is that it's gonna pull a dreamcast that since it's coming out
well before other systems of uh of this nature
do you think that it might actually end up shooting itself in the foot no because it's
nintendo and sega only ever really had sonic you know i mean and i'm saying like as far as like
catching and getting people and drawing them in and so forth i mean if nintendo's launching with
the smash brothers game they got nothing to worry about nintendo's not launching with the smash
brothers game it won't be out until that system's uh first holiday season interesting which will be
the season i think the only system that ever launched with the smash brothers game at least
close to launched was the cube right which by the way we found out today you won't be playing that
on the wii u because the wii u has taken out the game cube compatibility that's right i you know
what we've got a game cube don't care i know i'm kind of like that i'm not too surprised about
that because nintendo usually doesn't do backwards compatible two generations back it's kind of like
your ds your ds 3ds or whatever won't play gameboy advance games you know they took that out way back
in the dsi right yeah right yeah so i mean that however our ps3 will play ps1 games
you couldn't play gameboy games on your ds even though the slot was the same size your ps3 will
play atari 2600 games it's not even the same company it's amazing all right well i guess
everybody's being shy tonight we're not getting any calls that's okay what's up with that people
fuck you people i mean i mean hi i've closed the sky so now you guys can't call and talk to me
that's right i've decided let's go get pinkberry not to do it i already had pinkberry so and it
sucked you're trying to make me fat all right no we are going to uh wrap up our e3 coverage however
and uh call it a night i know we didn't go as long as last night but let's face it all the news most
of it was yesterday but i want to thank again bobby blackwolf and me glitov for their on the
floor impressions i learned a lot from that i learned a lot more from that than i did
for some of these press conferences so big thanks to them as well um and uh thanks to you guys for
tuning in and listening to us over the past couple days just programming notes coming up we will not
be doing this said he was going to call but he was in the bathroom loser goddamn lie all right
fine i'll open it up again hold on i just called him a loser we had the freaking line open for like
10 minutes that must have been the biggest poop in the world all right some people are like just
intolerant rob hold on i'm logging in yeah fuck lactose hold on firing up skype see we made these
exceptions for ronma this is professional radio i know right we don't care about your shit we just
care about your call not your poop all right live radio 1877 game olr or our username on skype is
orange lounge radio programming note we will not be back tomorrow we will not be live as usual on
sunday which means there's no additional show on the podcast feed this week dark soccer and i will
be in la well we'll be coming back from la on sunday we have to go stop at the bravo cheese
live from the bravo cheese farm we will be back says it shows you offline rob call anyway i am
on i i guarantee you it's on so call anyway get bent did you just tell someone to get bent
i told ronma to jamie shut up all right june the 19th we will be back live at all games radio for
more information visit our website at orange lounge radio yeah missy is a cheese farm they
grow cheese on vines not letting us go all night you know what i'll just try calling him do it
fuck this well i don't see him online either this is a problem skype fails skype emergency there
we go hi you're on orange launch radio whoever could this be wow you guys you guys are just so
loving you know four weeks later loving yeah yeah what do you want well i just have one thing to say
pretty much yes that um i'm actually i can't take it anymore i'm sick of it and um i'm finally going
to file divorce from nintendo oh my gosh somebody called judge mabel why do you make nintendo hit
you ronma after that presentation and my friends going nuts on twitter about about their pre
about their presser we kind of came to agreement that nintendo is that abusive girlfriend that you
always take back just thinking that things are going to be different the next time around there
is genuine concern in the chat room what will happen to black luigi he will be replaced by
shadow the hedgehog oh my god that's trading down really really really far
and i'm a sega fan my shadow really at least be knuckles
dan if it's any consideration is this a black thing when i walk into a block brother stay
black let him talk look dan if it makes you feel any better joe vidya will kick my ass
when she sees me dressed as shadow because she is not a shadow fangirl well she's more of a sonic
and tails fangirl joe vidya three more times for the rest of us all right uh i i gotta talk more
about why why this nintendo hatred what about when i i have to admit i loved it when reggie
came out and we've said this before and said gamers want this and they want this so whatever
you guys are confusing but here i don't know what gamers he's listening to but i didn't ask for a a
six-inch android tablet with a hacked classic controller on each side i had one of those
i just want one of those as a system you don't want to put it on your table and play othello
no that would be awesome like ben heck to make it what about though the fact though rama that
we are still a year away i mean the reason why i'm i'm still kind of like it was all right their
presentation was fine i'm not like super excited about it i'm gonna buy one anyway because i'm a
consumer whore and i buy them all and help but i'm like we're not really gonna see this system
for another year maybe by then they'll actually get their shit together so are you basically
giving your abusive girlfriend a year to shape up or ship out i suppose so but it's okay because
i will be i will be marrying its younger sister the 3ds ah so the 3ds you were a fan of all the
stuff you saw there okay yes uh mario kart yes even i am a mario kart whore like nobody else's
business that that's a given and i missed super mario but i went back and watched a trailer for
it and i said this is the mario game i've been looking for a 3d platformer that plays like 2d
but it's three this is what i wanted right i will sit here and play that i'm not too fond it's
called super mario but hey whatever i think it might still be a working title so it seems so it
seems to me that you've got this uh relationship with the big sister but really you just want to
sleep with the little sister well well yeah that's why i have a ds okay wow all right
well rama any other closing thoughts on e3 before we let you go uh let's see then microsoft was a
bit of a snore sony had me with with the vita and i'll say this right now yes the vita with 3g
powered by at&t it's gonna be 299 but i'm telling you when it comes out you'll be able to get it
for 99.99 with a two-year contract mark my word that's not that's not how they sell ipads though
that's how they sell iphones ipads iphones netbooks with 3g hell it worked for the taco
didn't it well kind of yeah but we got ours for free i think this is a relevant question
rama since you are black luigi and we call you that just so people know we call you that because
whenever you you you cosplay and you're black and you you dress up as luigi you make your way
on camera no matter who's there and we always see you on tv oh it's black luigi there he is
that's why you have that name and so tiger klon chat says rama what do you think of luigi's
mansion too since you know it's a game starring luigi nintendo finally showing some luigi love
i'm all for it because you know i've always said this i've always said that
peach is nothing more than a than a whore because mario's always chasing after her to save her
she doesn't freak out when bowser kidnaps her you know happens three times a month i know and look
they're a coupe of kids we all know who the mother is you know we already know i feel like you have
designed this really weird sick mario rp world while really really fucking high
i actually i was so brett the time it was very loose and i said this to a friend of mine
and it broke him and all my other friends are like holy shit that actually makes sense
bowser you are the father all right anyway look luigi has a nice mansion
a nice car his girl is in check he's got the good life i mean really
but really luigi's mansion a 10 year old game coming back you're all for it yeah i actually
believe it or not i actually liked the first luigi's mansion i thought it was a fun game
hey i think it's a neat hey rama princess daisy don't want no scrub
dad she has an eyeball in the back of her head all right rama we're gonna let you go
she stays in the castle okay hey she also plays a mean round of tennis why do you think
why do you think luigi got on one knee and proposed rama i'm ending this conversation
right now have a good one stay black all right bye you know the daisy does have an eyeball in
the back of her head oh it was a graphic glitch but someone that was awesome still i like that
someone in moogan actually programmed an attack with the weird eye in the back of her head it's
because people in moogan have too much free time i know it's great okay you're sitting on the
internet doing a podcast about e3 and you're telling the moogan people they have too much
free time way too much free time it's true all right that's it we're uh ending the show thank
you guys for tuning into our e3 coverage especially those of you that are tuned in be it live or
through the podcast feed we really appreciate it so we're gonna take a little uh break you know
because there's it's gonna be dead next week with uh with e3 being done uh tomorrow you know we've
pretty much brought all the news from e3 so it's gonna be kind of dead uh we'll be moving into
though a lot of big releases when we come back on sunday the 19th child of eden will have come out
so i'm sure we'll get some impressions on that and uh it's gonna be ramping up for the summer
and lots more games so thank you guys very much for tuning in again and uh you know if you like
what you heard here at orange launch radio uh all we ask remember we don't get paid for this and we
don't have big money advertisements for this so just tell a friend or two or five about the show
word of mouth is so so important and if you listen to this show for the first time because of the
ustream presence because it was a new place for us come join us at our normal place orange
laundry.com sunday nights at all games radio and tune in and hear us there so that's it we're
closing up shop final thoughts real quick though dark soccer your final e3 thought pinkberry
does that have so much to do with e3 my final e3 thought is uh boobies in saint's row
uh dan the man thank you for being here by the way and filling in appreciate it i live here i
know uh your final thought peace love recycle oh and quit fucking bitching good night everybody
we'll see you next time in orange lounge radio