[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_09]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_21]: And this is episode number 121 for this
[SPEAKER_21]: December the 5th of 2004 You're tuned in to the B-Money Scene's most longest running radio station of all things B-Money My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm Back from her vacation Say hello to DarkSakura Oh my god, they wanted to keep me No, you can't let them keep you But I had grits
[SPEAKER_03]: Real Grits, I Ate at the Waffle House, and I Had My Hashbrown Smothered Covered Chunked in Dice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: All she's missing is her accent.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll talk more about the trip a little later on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also with us, as always, say hello to our tech massa who's setting up the webcam right now, Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Say hello to our tech master, Loki!
[SPEAKER_21]: Joining us tonight are some very special guests.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the usual crowd.
[SPEAKER_21]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a very happy hello, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: And also say hello to Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to talk about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_21]: That is crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because we just had an 80s pre-show and it kind of ties into that.
[SPEAKER_21]: That little thing you're playing right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we got a whole lot of interesting stuff to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, I'm lying.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's really not a whole lot going on, but we're going to try to film three hours best we can anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know I want to talk about 8th Style tonight, Pop Music 10, because I got to play both those this week for the first time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, How's Your Week, How's Your Day, Cage Match, all that fun stuff when we come back after this break featuring...
[SPEAKER_21]: Music from DDR Third Mix, because Third Mix was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you want to join us in our chat room, there's quite a little crowd there already.
[SPEAKER_21]: Head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be right back after this, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_15]: Go left, go right, go pick up step Go left, go right, go left
[SPEAKER_08]: One!
[SPEAKER_08]: Two!
[SPEAKER_16]: And now, let's listen in to an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting as they debate some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_09]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_09]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_08]: The hot thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_08]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: The lovely and wonderful Jamie there in that promo.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, sort of.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was played by Lucy Liu.
[SPEAKER_21]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_21]: A long time ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: This was probably the first year of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's sad that that could be considered retro, but it really is.
[SPEAKER_21]: You remember way back during the first year of this program when somebody had talked about... I want to say it was Dark Tetsuya was somehow involved with this.
[SPEAKER_21]: Brought up the casting of the Orange Lounge movie.
[SPEAKER_21]: And they took votes in the chat room and they said that you should be played by Lucy Liu.
[SPEAKER_05]: How ironic.
[SPEAKER_21]: Which is, yeah, how ironic.
[SPEAKER_05]: A little too ironic.
[SPEAKER_21]: Especially considering you're not Asian at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, but, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I finally got something new when I went to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_21]: That would be like me being played by Denzel Washington.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, Alabama.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got, I believe it was, I thought you were taller.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, this is a good segue.
[SPEAKER_21]: We've got to get into how was your week, how was your day, because I've got to figure out about what this is all about.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, Jamie, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: My couple of weeks were pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very, very, very, very, very busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: With my trip to Alabama, I got there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mom got us lost on the way from New Orleans.
[SPEAKER_05]: We ended up heading up toward Hattiesburg.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's something stuck in this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, we ended up going up to Hattiesburg.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then right when mom realized where we were, we had to go around a different way, so we headed home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got there, I didn't get in bed until 6 in the morning central.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means I had been up an official 24 hours because I woke up at 4 Pacific in the morning.
[SPEAKER_21]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: My house crashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next day was Thanksgiving, but we didn't do Thanksgiving stuff, we just slept.
[SPEAKER_05]: And...
[SPEAKER_05]: Did some hanging out, you know, it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then on Friday I went to Dothan, saw my daddy, my Uncle Dale.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Uncle Dale and my daddy are having their second childhoods.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Uncle Dale has a... A.K.A.
[SPEAKER_21]: midlife crisis.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2004 Mustang GT.
[SPEAKER_05]: My daddy has a Camaro.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, my daddy is cute on the internet because they have this old 500 megahertz kind of crappy thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my daddy is so cute playing on it because he just hunts and pecks for the little keys and it's so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my daddy sends me everything in 72-point font and email.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's adorable.
[SPEAKER_21]: I used to be that way on AOL Instant Messenger.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would type to everybody in huge 72-point font and they'd be like, knock it off!
[SPEAKER_21]: but I figured my chats are very important and I want to make sure they're not missed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, so Saturday we had our official Thanksgiving at my uncle's house and we had fried turkey
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then that night I went to Ground Zero, which is a sort of a... Okay, it's like a comic book store with gaming tables.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were lots of people playing Yu-Gi-Oh!
[SPEAKER_05]: and I felt really nerdy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then, but downstairs there's like an arcade there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a very strange name for an arcade in light of recent events.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't it great?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there was a DDR Extreme, there was a 4th Solo, there was a... 4th Solo, that's hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: There was a Virtual On.
[SPEAKER_05]: I played the hell out of Virtual On.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a Super Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my god, so one of my favorite... And I had a Dance Maniacs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a Beatmania 6 mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Keyboard Mania 3rd
[SPEAKER_05]: I met quite a few people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I met the... I'm supposing that he's in charge of the machines there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He goes by Pyramus Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very cool guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to a... I went to a Bomani party!
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: You went to a Bomani party?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: You just randomly got invited to a Bomani party down there?
[SPEAKER_05]: They were all heading over, so I went over and played Ace Style on a widescreen TV, and that was rad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, you just...
[SPEAKER_21]: You went over to strangers' houses to play video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: He actually lived about a block away from where my extra mates lived.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was very close.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I went over, of course, to hang out with my mama's son and my papa's son.
[SPEAKER_05]: and Kay Kitty and Bobby and we had a pretty good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We watched movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw The End of the Day After Tomorrow and no offense but that movie sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think... That's my very professional opinion.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know a lot of people are going to disagree with you there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mom loves the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: They love the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really want to put down anyone else's opinion of it but my opinion of it is crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um...
[SPEAKER_05]: We also, I learned the fine art of DVD duplication, and so I was able to deliver a copy of Kill Bill Volume 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Orange Linger does not advocate piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got, actually, you know, there's that show, Kindred the Embraced, that came on, based off of the White Wolf Universe, and I have all the episodes they ever made of that, because I think that the actor died, the main guy, who's playing the prince.
[SPEAKER_05]: But, um, I have all of that, I still have it on my, uh If anyone brings me DVDs, you'll get copies Um
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Sounds Radio does not advocate piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually, no, they're not... I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not licensed right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I want to find out more about this Bramante party because basically you went over to a stranger's house.
[SPEAKER_21]: I sang, Rob.
[SPEAKER_21]: People that stalk us on the internet, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: You got invited... A few people are our listeners.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, okay, so message to our listeners, stalking us works.
[SPEAKER_05]: And... I just hung out with a lot of... A lot of the people, though, were people from DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, no, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, yeah, I mean, you got...
[SPEAKER_21]: You've got the moderatorship on DDR Freak, so a lot of people know who you are over there.
[SPEAKER_21]: The show's getting pretty big over there, thanks to the syndication on Friday nights over there on Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just a bunch of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I met a lot of good people.
[SPEAKER_05]: We basically were just playing 8th style.
[SPEAKER_05]: We brought out Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, you don't sing karaoke.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't, but I got the line from Adventures in Babysitting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody leaves without singing the blues.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's all it took?
[SPEAKER_21]: They didn't have to feed you Guinness or anything?
[SPEAKER_21]: I was begged.
[SPEAKER_21]: They didn't make you drink Guinness or anything?
[SPEAKER_21]: You just did it perfectly sober?
[SPEAKER_05]: I just figured it was going to be about another year before I'm back.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you knew that there were no recording devices present, so... So I sang Bizarre Love Triangle.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, no, that's a good song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, see, you missed some karaoke action here on the show last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I didn't miss it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I actually, I was really... Loki's still pissed at me over it, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually was going to be trying to tune in on my laptop, but I had promised my mama-son I was going to take her to see The Grudge, which after having, since I was glad I saw Ju-on first, very glad I saw it first, because then, it was neat noting the differences in the movie, I'm not going to spoil it for anyone who hasn't, and actually, the thing that pissed me off is that I don't know the reason why they think they have to explain every single last fucking detail to a U.S.
[SPEAKER_05]: audience,
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Steak and Shake.
[SPEAKER_21]: Only in the South, which you have a place called Steak and Shake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's these thick hamburgers, really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a little diner type place.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can get these humongous milkshakes and they make a half and half.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's literally split down the middle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Half one side is one flavor, half the other is the other.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I actually mixed it up and had banana eggnog.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh God, it was good.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was orgasm in the glass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway... No, it didn't taste like tuna.
[SPEAKER_05]: It tasted like banana and eggnog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to meet lots of good people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monday, my brother was being an ass the whole time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not too proud of my brother Matthew.
[SPEAKER_05]: I talked to my brother Phillip while I was there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's supposed to be down for Christmas, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: and he's getting married.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, he's already married.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is my brother who's a Marine and his wife's a Marine and they're actually going to Texas to have a humongous big Mexican wedding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because this is going to be a big party.
[SPEAKER_21]: Will there be margaritas involved?
[SPEAKER_05]: Likely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, people that know me pretty well know that I'm actually not a big tequila fan.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll drink margaritas because you can barely taste the tequila, but I cannot stand straight up tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you had that cheap shit here.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I still don't like tequila.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can give me Cuervo.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_21]: I still don't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can do shots of tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's nasty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the Blue Agave tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: The stuff that Anita had way back at the Nasty House.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went back to New Orleans on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hung out with my mommy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fussed at my mom.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: and then Jamie Fuss had the most long boring flight back and like the last leg of my I hung out at the Dallas airport for nearly two hours airports aren't so bad now though they have wifi there yeah they got wifi I was just chilling on my laptop and not just that but you know just everything there is to do they're practically shopping malls as well although I would never buy anything there but it's fun to look you know airports aren't that bad anymore well some of them are yeah
[SPEAKER_05]: But I was having a pretty good time, I mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I got on a plane.
[SPEAKER_05]: I read the entirety of Ramsey's The Damned on the plane.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, I have to say, safely the best Anne Rice book, because all the rest of her stuff since, it's kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's been gay porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's also been crappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really crappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woman needs to get her groove back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not rest on her name.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_21]: You talking about that Babani party makes me nostalgic.
[SPEAKER_21]: Remember when we used to do that stuff?
[SPEAKER_21]: At the old studio, which was a really great house for having parties.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'd have the Babani parties.
[SPEAKER_21]: We need to do that shit again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, we kind of had a Babani party last night.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it wasn't like a hardcore Babani party, but I'm sure we'll get to that as we go on through How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember the stuff I would bring with me?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: People would say Babani party, and I'm like, oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: You bring, like, your old... I remember you brought your Dreamcast pads to one party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was insane.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, okay, this is what DDR was like in the old days, before we had this vivid nonsense.
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember when one of our old guests used to be on the show a bit, Zombie Magus, when he put on his girlfriend's top and was playing Power, Power, Paradise.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the picture made some rounds on the internet after that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember Loki would haul his computer and his Delight Delight reduplication and his pads he'd made for it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm nostalgic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would carry around the Drum Mania, Keyboard Mania, 2DX Controller, the bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the old Beat Manias, my ASCII pad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you think that when this DDR thing is dead, which could happen any day now, do you think these Bomani parties are still going to be going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, we'll just go back to porn.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll just have to go back to the orgies, you're right.
[SPEAKER_21]: How silly of me to ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we'd have to get that copy of Ally McFeel again.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_19]: Anyway, anything else you want to share about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_19]: Moving right along.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, it had a cameo by Ron Jeremy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, I was looking up, there's a site online that's like these paper dolls online, and I was trying to make a new avatar for myself on my live journal, and I accidentally came across the real doll site.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very, very icky.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have a request for a new DDR Freak avatar, because the gay pimp one you made me is really cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have a request for a new one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want Xander from Drawn Together, just to make Seeger jealous.
[SPEAKER_05]: From what?
[SPEAKER_21]: Drawn Together, that show on Comedy Central.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, girl, you are so far behind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do not have anything but basic channels, but local channels.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're missing out.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a funny show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hardly ever watch TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think the TV is retarded.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't even watch Survivor or The Apprentice or any of that reality bullshit anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: Drawn Together is the only show I watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when did Hell Freeze Over?
[SPEAKER_21]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: You want to talk about Hell Freezing Over?
[SPEAKER_21]: I came this close to joining a gym on Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: For, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: For the people who didn't have that visual, Rob held his fingers the length of, um, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we're not going to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because we don't bring up old drama.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: What?
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says that when you said Xander, I started thinking of Buffy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I need to respond to some stuff in the chatroom going on right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: First off, Sigurd's telling me he hates me because of the Xander thing, and he says his is better.
[SPEAKER_21]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: And somebody else, where was it?
[SPEAKER_21]: A couple people commented, DDR's not gonna die.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well...
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm only being half serious.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think the death of DDR is anytime soon, especially when we just got Ultramix 2 and the home versions are looking very promising for the future.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think DDR is seriously going to die, but I think it's a little more cultish, maybe.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I also have an announcement.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I no longer am on the Atkins crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's good for a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was not good for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can have sushi again.
[SPEAKER_19]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sushi is wonderful.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, and, and, and, and, and, and.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing else.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob, Rob.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm back!
[SPEAKER_19]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_19]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_21]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: School was... School and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saturday was nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to waste the week away until Saturday came, because, uh, well, I had a birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually hanging out with everyone was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Um, and we had played lots of Bomani, uh, 8th style,
[SPEAKER_04]: and Poppin10.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I got to see those for the first time, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the best thing of all was obviously hanging around with the people that I don't usually get to hang around with, so that was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: And just enjoying my birthday weekend so far, I guess.
[SPEAKER_20]: And now, Bradley, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, uh, this week was
[SPEAKER_18]: Work, of course.
[SPEAKER_18]: And an interesting thing happened at work.
[SPEAKER_18]: There was a person, my kind of work is, it's sort of a training.
[SPEAKER_18]: They train people to do stuff, so.
[SPEAKER_18]: One of the students came back, so he had some questions for, because he was going to do a test, a state test for his line of work he wanted to get into.
[SPEAKER_18]: And he came back, asked some questions, and he and the instructor had a nice, somehow a disagreement, or something about the instructor doesn't like this guy, so
[SPEAKER_18]: He actually misspoken said that he didn't like him.
[SPEAKER_18]: So this causes him to get really angry and start ranting and raving.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then he had to go outside.
[SPEAKER_18]: The manager had to take him outside and talk for like an hour to try to calm him down.
[SPEAKER_18]: And he came back on Friday.
[SPEAKER_18]: And his wife told him to bring along some candy just to give to us or something like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And he comes back and... Okay, so here's this candy.
[SPEAKER_18]: And then he comes...
[SPEAKER_18]: And then he starts launching this big thing about discrimination.
[SPEAKER_18]: He discriminates against me.
[SPEAKER_18]: He doesn't like me.
[SPEAKER_18]: For some reason, some bullshit like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: And so, just me and the receptionist are in the room and he's like, blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_18]: Some kind of weird shit like that.
[SPEAKER_18]: So, good thing the boss came in like a minute later and then started to talk to him so we could sneak out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Were they getting paid for this?
[SPEAKER_18]: To talk?
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, it's a business, so it's part of the work.
[SPEAKER_21]: I always found that humorous when, you know, there's big fights going on and we have to sit down and have a discussion, but we're all getting paid for it type thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: We just wasted three hours of productivity to talk out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not that I ever get into disagreements with people, but, you know, I've had to sit in on them.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, I didn't have anything to do with it.
[SPEAKER_18]: I just went and sat in the hall because I didn't want to get involved.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you got paid for it, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, so it was a nice one hour, like an hour break just to not do anything.
[SPEAKER_18]: Just wait until it cooled down.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay, and on Monday I got Katamari Damashii, and that was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry, every time somebody... It's like how when everybody says friends, you think of NBC, or when somebody says 90210, with Katamari it's... Shut up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, actually, I think of that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think of that song, too.
[SPEAKER_18]: and played that most every day this week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, I did play this every day this week, except for today, because I got up.
[SPEAKER_18]: Because last night was the party for Angel and Anita, or DD Archipelagic, for their birthdays, and that was a lot of fun, because Navi brought over 8-style and poppin' music.
[SPEAKER_21]: God bless the town's poppin' music whore.
[SPEAKER_18]: I got to play on those arcade-style controllers.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, and...
[SPEAKER_18]: and that was fun.
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course I didn't do all that great on 8th style because basically you had it up on a stand and then the TV was down like two or three feet, several feet away.
[SPEAKER_18]: Of course I hadn't played on an arcade style controller in a long time.
[SPEAKER_18]: And of course there was the, I just played the hard news songs like, oh god, what the hell is it called?
[SPEAKER_21]: Nebula Grasper?
[SPEAKER_18]: Nebula Grasper is a fucking impossible game.
[SPEAKER_18]: Well, at least for a first try, it's like, fuck, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_18]: Like, all over the place.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I always love non-Bamani peoples, like the people who don't really play 2DX, DDR and stuff, I always love their reaction to stuff like that, because there were a few people at the party last night who don't really play DDR, 2DX, and they were just kind of watching Navi playing, and just, like, he was just crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: He was playing, like, Nebio Grasper another or something, and just everybody was just kind of like, that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_01]: That is so crazy.
[SPEAKER_18]: Mr. Loki, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_20]: Today did not start out too good due to certain events that have taken place outside of our apartment complex in the street.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was not fun.
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, we'll get into that later, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then yesterday, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_20]: Went and...
[SPEAKER_20]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know, most of the week I've been just playing Final Fantasy XI, leveling my summoner to 20, which I just finished right before the show.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, um... What else have I been doing?
[SPEAKER_20]: I've played a little bit of Grand Theft Auto, finally passed this mission that I couldn't beat for a while, and now I have to run errands for some pimp.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, um... Went and saw Closer, I'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, um... Eh, that's about all.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's been like kind of a week just crashing into the ground.
[SPEAKER_21]: That sucks about your grandma, I'm sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have you used your machine to try and contact her yet?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, I have not, you asshole.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Did you ever open your portal to hell?
[SPEAKER_21]: I was gonna say, you went on a ghostbusting trip yesterday, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_20]: Hunting.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ghost hunting, not busting.
[SPEAKER_20]: We just, we went, walked around Knights Ferry, which is basically this old abandoned, it's not really an abandoned mining town, it's just an old, um, mining town, it's got like a bunch of dilapidated, it's not really a mining town, I guess, they have an old, um, mill there that's kind of been, um, it's just the ruins of it, so we just walked around there, and they also have a very long, um, they have a 150 meter, uh, covered bridge, which is pretty neat, and we walked down that, and we went to their, um,
[SPEAKER_20]: Graveyard that was there and walked around that for a little bit but you know I mean these are just for it's just kind of just to get out of the house because we you know we're looking for like an actual place that my my example was something that's more trauma there than you know old you know because necessarily just visiting any old place is not going to work you need to have something where oh yeah 50 people murdered there you know that kind of thing
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, just something, you know, traumatic, like, uh, Insane Asylum or something like that.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, you know, no luck with any of that stuff around here, so.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, well.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's what I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_18]: Isn't this place the Insane Asylum?
[SPEAKER_20]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have to haunt this place first.
[SPEAKER_20]: I haven't quite gotten around to that yet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Soon enough, you know, I've been, like, I have my priorities.
[SPEAKER_20]: Like, I was gonna work on the cabinet today, and then I just got tired.
[SPEAKER_20]: Those fuckers this morning.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: And by tired he means looking for a party in Final Fantasy XI so he can get his summoner to level 20.
[SPEAKER_20]: Addict!
[SPEAKER_20]: No, I was tired from other things, but yes, I just got bored of that too.
[SPEAKER_20]: But the other things in the morning made me tired because I'm exhausted right now from having to wake up early yesterday and having to wake up early today.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, my turn, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got to play 8th Style and Pop Music 10 twice this week, actually, because I hung out with Navi on Monday.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll talk about those games a little bit later, because, you know, I want to talk about my money stuff a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: But Navi and I, after playing some of that, we got to go to the mall, and I was going to help him do some Christmas shopping over at Arden Fair, which is a big mall in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a huge mall.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so we ended up walking out of there.
[SPEAKER_21]: He didn't end up buying anything.
[SPEAKER_21]: He just kind of looked around at some different places.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I fucking bought an iPod at the Apple store.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I wanted one, really.
[SPEAKER_19]: I wanted one really badly.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm still two away from my free win.
[SPEAKER_20]: Why not just buy a fucking iMac, you know?
[SPEAKER_20]: Just join the cult.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've thought about it, actually.
[SPEAKER_20]: Good, it's a big flaming piece of shit that doesn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_21]: You make Apple users cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you're into graphics.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or media, which, you know, this show happens to be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because all the pros are on Macs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe we wouldn't have the freaking buzz on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just wanted an iPod actually because the stereo in my car broke a while back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, it was Sigurd's Echo Image CD that broke my CD player in the car, actually, because it ate it and wouldn't give it back one day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Once it heard Echo Image, it could hear no other music.
[SPEAKER_21]: Basically is how it all boiled down.
[SPEAKER_21]: So...
[SPEAKER_21]: It won't eject CDs anymore, and now I won't even play the CD that's in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, luckily though, it has an auxiliary port in it, so I can plug anything I want in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I'm just like, fuck it, I'm gonna get an iPod, and I'll just use that as my car stereo.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it's worked out really well, except for the fact that if you think I'm bad when I'm talking on my cell phone and trying to drive, you should see me when I'm trying to find the song on my iPod I want to hear and drive at the same time.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_21]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: They can pass all the laws they want to say I can't talk on my cell phone and drive, but I don't see them making any law anytime soon that says I can't play on my iPod and try to drive at the same time, so look out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I believe the law is operation of electronical devices while driving, so your iPod's included.
[SPEAKER_05]: God damn it!
[SPEAKER_05]: Extraneous, like CD, well, like laptops.
[SPEAKER_05]: Peripheral devices.
[SPEAKER_21]: Secret in our chatroom right now over at Orangelandradio.com, he says that that day where his Echo Image CD got eaten by my car stereo player, he said that that day kind of pissed him off.
[SPEAKER_21]: Except for the Classic Gaming Expo and the little girl that was hitting all the buttons on the restrooms that she rocked.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that reminds me, I actually found the picture of Jamie doing that at Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had my heads in the air.
[SPEAKER_21]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_21]: We paid you $10 to do it?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I spent it on Pac-Land for the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we bought some game for you, basically, for you to imitate a little girl.
[SPEAKER_21]: I found the picture.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to send it to Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, we're going to Classic Gaming Expo again this year.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's in Burlingame.
[SPEAKER_05]: The only reason that last year's was in was because they had that thing a few days before.
[SPEAKER_05]: But Classic Gaming Expo this year is going to be in Burlingame.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means trips to network video.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the store that sells the airsoft guns.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, and I guess that was pretty much my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_21]: I spent a lot of time playing Final Fantasy XI as well, because basically I got stood up Friday night, so I decided to wither away my sorrows inside a nice game of Final Fantasy XI, so...
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_21]: The freaking game took us three hours to play.
[SPEAKER_21]: The last time I played Cranium it only took two.
[SPEAKER_21]: Turbo Cranium ended up taking longer.
[SPEAKER_21]: What in the hell is up with that?
[SPEAKER_21]: And no, it's not because we kept taking breaks.
[SPEAKER_21]: It just was a long-ass game.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was no shorter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody's gonna get this joke but you, Rob, but you can be my puppet master anytime.
[SPEAKER_21]: How foul.
[SPEAKER_21]: But how long did the... I ended up having to leave around midnight because I was kind of afraid.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, A, I was tired, and B, I was afraid I wasn't going to be able to park when I got back here if I waited any longer.
[SPEAKER_21]: But how was the rest of the night?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We ended up playing Hear Me Out for, well, the majority of the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we played Poppin' 10 also, but yeah, that other game was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, DDArcoholic made sushi from scratch.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was really good, but it was kind of interesting because she used wieners in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, she used hot dogs instead of fish.
[SPEAKER_21]: She put, like, hot dogs in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it was actually really good.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just thought it was neat.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was very resourceful.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was a good idea.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, we're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_21]: When we come back from this break, we're going to talk a little bit more about 2DX8 style.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to talk a little more about Pop Music 10.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to play the new remix of I Feel for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: We played it on Thursday night, but I know nobody listens to Outside the Box on Thursday night, but more of you guys listened tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to play the new I Feel mix from Service Pack.
[SPEAKER_21]: I keep calling it Service Pack.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song Pack 7 from Ultramix 2 because a lot of people don't want to hear that.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to play that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: and plenty more when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_21]: In this break, though, some music from DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because we haven't really gotten to hear much music from DDR Festival yet, but we have some songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to hear Superstar, Diamonds, and Cutie Honey on this break.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Slide it on a piece of paper Got a feeling I'll see you later There's something about this, let's keep it moving And if it's good, that's to hear something cooking Is that what you want to wrap it through?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm feeling some connection to the things you do
[SPEAKER_08]: What is it that makes me feel like this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know who you are, but you must be some kind of superstar Cause you got all I need, no matter where you are You just wanna make me feel like this What is it that makes me feel like this?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know who you are
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Kurohayari no Onna no Kou, Oshiri no Chisana Onna no Kou Kono Uke ga Hai, Datte Nandaka Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei, Saisei,
Honeyfuck!
I'm a hot girl, I'm a hot girl, I'm a hot girl, I'm a hot girl, I'm a hot girl,
[SPEAKER_08]: Mr. Random Person on the Street, who by the way is not an actor,
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think of the Orange Lounge B-Money Music & More show?
[SPEAKER_12]: The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's unearthly.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like being at a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Festival has some strange music in it, it's honestly, I didn't bother to buy Festival, I just, I didn't think there was enough in it for me, because I had Extreme, and I have an Xbox, so, and I had Ultramix One, which is where a lot of songs came from, but Festival certainly has some quirky little songs in it, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although I love Superstar, I, it's almost worth buying the mix for that, but not really, because that's like 80 bucks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Also, it has different steps.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it does have different steps for a lot of the songs that were on Ultramix 1, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Honestly, with Ultramix 2 now and the fact that you can make your own edits, I have a feeling that any day now we're going to start seeing those steps get uploaded to Xbox Live, so I'm not really too concerned about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just somebody has to take the effort, and that person's not going to be me because I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, 2DX8Style.
[SPEAKER_21]: Got a chance to check it out over at, um, Navi, Pop Music Horror.
[SPEAKER_21]: He has it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got to check it out earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: And man do I suck at 2DX now.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh my god, me too.
[SPEAKER_21]: I haven't played 2DX seriously in quite a while.
[SPEAKER_21]: I didn't really get into 7th style.
[SPEAKER_21]: I played it one time.
[SPEAKER_21]: A lot of this has to do with the fact that my controller is broken, and I'd rather buy myself a lot of other useless crap, like iPods and, uh, things like that, than buy...
[SPEAKER_21]: A new 2DX controller.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I seriously think that's the reason that I haven't been playing a whole lot of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_21]: But 8th style is pretty sweet, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_21]: It has a lot of great new songs in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Those of you guys that listen to the show regularly...
[SPEAKER_21]: You already know how I feel about Everyday Lovely Day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, I love that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then, of course, it has a bunch of 2DX Red songs in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, not a bunch, but three, which I consider to be a bunch for, you know, preview, because usually it's only like one or two.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then, some of the new consumer videos are pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, Step Into The New World.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't really like that song a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_21]: The song kind of, meh.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: And then also another video I love is Lovebox.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know if you guys got to see this video at all, but Lovebox is the one that has, I think it's Meg and one of her cohorts or something, I don't know, an uncredited person.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're dressed up as these like Austin Powers dance chicks, kind of.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like they're all dressed in these like 60s hippie, like things you'd see on Laugh-In.
[SPEAKER_21]: You remember that old show Laugh-In?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like when the people would be dancing?
[SPEAKER_21]: It was kind of like that, and they're just driving around the city and singing, and they're wearing, like, glow bracelets and stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's really great.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lovebox.
[SPEAKER_21]: I highly recommend this one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although the song kind of sucks, but the video's great.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, you guys have gotten to play 8-Style a little bit, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you guys think of 2DX 8-Style?
[SPEAKER_05]: I suck at Let Me Go, Ribera.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, I remember that song was so great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the scene kept falling out of my lap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss arcades.
[SPEAKER_21]: Look pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is this something you think you might have to break down and purchase?
[SPEAKER_18]: I already have purchased it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, have you?
[SPEAKER_18]: I just haven't gotten it yet.
[SPEAKER_18]: You probably mentioned it and I forgot.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I mentioned it like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_21]: Any particularly favorite consumer songs that you like in any song?
[SPEAKER_18]: I haven't heard them enough to truly say yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I played a new 7 star, I think it was Don't Be Afraid Myself, was one of the, like it's the J-pop one, it's got a really, it's actually got a pretty That song was great!
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a pretty cool video to it Didn't it have the video in the bathroom?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the shower?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think so?
[SPEAKER_05]: It looked like they were dancing in like a locker room shower.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I think that might have been it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I could only kind of half see the video because I tried to play the song.
[SPEAKER_21]: That song was cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, the song is cool, but man, I fucked up that song so bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, it really shows like how out of it on 2DX I am because I can't sight read anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, I was able to play Attitude and Star Dream and all these songs I used to play all the time on 8th style.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was able to play those just fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: But man, throw something new at me and I just, like, the rhythms and everything didn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was so sad.
[SPEAKER_21]: I cry for my 2DX skills.
[SPEAKER_21]: But Dancer, 8Style was worth it just to be able to play Dancer again.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although, is it just me or is something kind of weird at the end of the video?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like it freezes kind of at the end of the video.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like I remember it kind of faded out in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe I'm just crazy, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: But a lot of 8Style machines had broken videos in the first place, so that's probably the first time a lot of people got to actually play 2DX with the videos.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel, what were your thoughts on 2DX 8Style?
[SPEAKER_04]: Love is Orange, Attitude, and A. That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, I used to watch you guys play that all the time, and I was always all envious, and I still am, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: A is technically a 7th style song, but it does make a repeat in 8th style.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's interesting, they took some of the most noteworthy 7th style songs, like A and Stoic, and they ended up repeating on 8th style after all.
[SPEAKER_21]: So now I'm kind of like, do I really need to get 7th style?
[SPEAKER_21]: But then I remembered, yes, I want to whore Beauty of Silence in the privacy of my own home, is basically what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just like, remember the old arcade days?
[SPEAKER_21]: Frickin' everybody whored Beauty of Silence.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, almost everybody.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know I was a big part of that, but...
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, players best would be 5-1-1, because all the noobs would play 5-1-1, and then, like, Beauty is Silenced.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, moving on, Poppin' Music 10 was another game I got to check out earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pretty cool, I have to admit, I think I kind of like the way 9 is set up a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought the unlock system in 9 was a lot cooler, because 10 has this wacky roulette thing, and Navi had the timing down perfect though, so that he was managing to unlock quite a bit of stuff on the roulette wheel, but it was kind of...
[SPEAKER_21]: I was a little disappointed by that.
[SPEAKER_21]: But the song list was pretty good in 10.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a lot of great songs I love in 10.
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, Goonies, you know, we hoard that song like crazy here on Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arabatia, the Revenge song, love that song, and I actually passed it on, what's the second one up, not EX, that's the third one up, Hyper, is that the second level, it's like Basic and Hyper, see I don't know my poppin' music, it's so sad, the middle one, wherever it's ranked, like a 30 or something, 29, 30, I don't remember
[SPEAKER_21]: Somebody needs to get me $1,000 for Christmas, so that way I can buy an ASC for 2DX, an ASC for pop music, and then import 8Style and as many pop music as I can before I'm bankrupt.
[SPEAKER_21]: So if you guys want to get me $1,000 for Christmas, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you play Poppin' 10 at all at that party that you went to, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_05]: Poppin' 10
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty, and watching Navi play is just insane.
[SPEAKER_04]: He plays faster than anyone else I've seen, you know, but I just ended up watching it because I knew a lot of people wanted to play Pop Intense, so I just kind of left it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus, we were busy with Cranium anyway, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, by the way, if anybody wants to call us, we just opened up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you want to figure out what that's all about, head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we want to take some phone calls asking you guys that have gotten a chance to play 8th Style or Pop Music 10, what you guys think of it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I have to say that the final verdict on 10, I kind of...
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, obviously I need to play it more, and obviously I still want it, but I still think I kind of like 9 just a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just think 9 had some, it was just set up a little better, just kind of had some better songs, but 10's really good, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would still buy 10 in a heartbeat, but I just think I like 9 a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, anyway, Arcadian, you got to play a little bit of Poppin' 10, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_18]: Not bad.
[SPEAKER_18]: I can't compare it to any other ones, because I haven't played any other ones.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, I thought you have played the other ones.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, this is the first time I've ever played it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, wow, okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that's why you were playing 5-key in the beginning there.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was kind of like, Acadian's playing 5-key.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, that was like three songs, and I said, let's go tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's okay to play 5-key when you're first learning pop music.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to take a call real fast.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, you're on Orange Lines Radio.
[SPEAKER_10]: Hey there, Sky.
[SPEAKER_10]: Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_21]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: I finally figured out what you were talking about last week with the 2DX8 style.
[SPEAKER_21]: You remember how you said there was something in it that looked like extreme US?
[SPEAKER_21]: And a lot of people in the chat room were like, what the fuck is he talking about?
[SPEAKER_21]: You remember that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: I got what you meant now.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was the menu in the beginning kind of had that like round wheel thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, it's the menu.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you got your copy of 8th style, yes?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: And how have you been enjoying it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was one of the lucky ones who got the 2DX Red e-amusement card because after November 18th, they don't have it anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: Really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, is there anything special about the card or is it just the fact that, hey, I got a card?
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I wanted to use the 2DX Red e-amusement card at AI because they have the e-amusement card readers.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, I'm actually going to be able to go to Arcade Infinity next week, I'm hoping.
[SPEAKER_10]: The e-amusement card over there
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I don't have any amusement card because I'm ghetto poor and I haven't bought anything yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's what I'm thinking about doing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm thinking about buying, depending on how much they cost, I might buy a bunch and give some away here on the station.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, recently I double-aid a V35 on 7-key.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, V35 is one of those songs I used to be really good at, but then I just suck it up now.
[SPEAKER_21]: What is that you're holding up there?
[SPEAKER_21]: A Namco?
[SPEAKER_05]: My Tekken 5 character data card.
[SPEAKER_21]: Get on topic!
[SPEAKER_21]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have you gotten to play Pop Music 10 at all?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last time I played Popping Music was Popping Music 9 back in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_21]: See, but isn't Pop Music 9 great?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think so, anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, anything else you want to share about 2DX8 style, your experiences you're having with it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, um... There's a thing about the...
[SPEAKER_10]: Getting the hidden songs, 2DX Red songs, you don't have to, you don't have to, about the easy things, it turns out to be false.
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you mean?
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't play easy songs by unlocking, by using an easy option.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you can't play an easy to unlock those songs?
[SPEAKER_10]: You can.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, you can?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, shit, that makes it easy, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_21]: And what is the requirement again to start unlocking some of these 2DX Red songs?
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I actually don't remember.
[SPEAKER_10]: Play at least about a hundred songs to unlock Spiral Galaxy and Taiyou.
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: A hundred songs?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah, just mostly light sevens or, you know, light sevens to seven key songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not afraid of playing 7-key.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've got to play some more to get better at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think it's... Play more Light 7.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just for the heck of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just for the heck.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would play... Now, see, Light 7 would be the kind of thing I would play to whore my VJ Army account up if I had one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hypothetically, if I had one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'd be all, look at all these triple A's I got!
[SPEAKER_21]: Of course, it was on Light 7.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, man, I'm good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I know that there's people out there that do that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, Light 7s are songs, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have every right.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, you know,
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's another for Random Plus.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to play at least 100 songs to unlock Random Plus.
[SPEAKER_10]: And what exactly does Random Plus do again for those that... Random Plus is where the turntable is now included in the shuffle.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, okay, I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_21]: That would be so hard if you got some scales that... Oh, God, that's pretty crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Especially, you know, especially war games.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can only imagine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, Wargame on 7Key was never a big problem for me.
[SPEAKER_21]: For some reason, Scratching, I'm like, I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Checking You Out was the second 7 star I ever beat, and now I understand it's an 8 star.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, like, I beat an 8 star, like, when I was beating my first 7 star.
[SPEAKER_21]: That is so crazy to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, for some reason, Scratching has never bothered me.
[SPEAKER_10]: After you play 100 songs with random, just hold key 2 and then wait for the random to go red.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's how it works?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_21]: So those of you guys that are feeling a little crazy and want to play some random with the turntable, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: What would you say would be your favorite new video in 2DXA style?
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't seen all of them because I'm really busy playing them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Playing the seven key songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I'd say I like Nebula Grasper a lot.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nebula Grasper's got a pretty good video to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's one of those futuristic, typical kind of things.
[SPEAKER_21]: It kind of reminded me of Hyperboundary Yate a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because, you know, that was an LED song too, and it had all the futuristic graphics with it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Kind of reminded me of that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I bought a 2DX Red, so I really like Spiral Galaxy as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: Were you able to get the V-Rare when you got...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, no, no, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just a regular one I ordered.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, anything else you want to share about 2DXHTEL?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, nothing much else.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, we'll talk to you later then, I guess.
[SPEAKER_21]: Have a good one, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Later.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like getting phone calls.
[SPEAKER_21]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: People say in our chat room right now is that they're talking about 2DX too much.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, it is the news that's going on right now, you know, you guys, but fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to talk about a little bit of DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to try and get the I Feel, the new remix for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki's going to get that taken care of during the next break, right?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_01]: Good.
[SPEAKER_21]: Then I guess we're going to go to a break so we can get that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to hear some music from DDR Festival, some more music.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: Udoru...
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's like a new version of it in Festival, so we're going to hear this.
[SPEAKER_21]: I haven't heard this one yet, so I've got to check this out.
[SPEAKER_21]: A remix of I Need You, which was a song that was kind of eh in DDR Max 2 USA, but we'll hear it and see if it's any better.
[SPEAKER_20]: Here's the thing about I Need You, and it wasn't in, well, yeah, Max 2 USA.
[SPEAKER_20]: This was the one that was on the VRare for the last mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, that wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, so we'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to check out these songs, and we'll be back, and we're going to talk a little bit more about Ultramix 2, some of the news there, and play that new song from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, of course, the cage match, FU's of the Week, all that good stuff coming up.
[SPEAKER_21]: And in the chat room, they're saying, look, since you're so white, Sky, just say Dancine Pomponcolin.
[SPEAKER_21]: And even that I can't say right.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just, I wasn't cut out for radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Inchiki, Oji-san, Toujou,
[SPEAKER_08]: P, Chara, Odoru, Pompokorin P, Chara, P, Onaka ga Hitta yo!
[SPEAKER_08]: Ano ko mo kono ko mo minna isoite aruite iru yo Denshinbashira no kage kara oowarai keinin to toujou Itsudatte mayowana iki o tsuku wa
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_08]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't feel like I'm going to study, but at this point in time, I do.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gaming Radio, so uncensored that even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: God bless you, Tom Brokaw.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, he finally retired.
[SPEAKER_21]: He did?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is his last week.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had time.
[SPEAKER_21]: One of the most highly rated episodes of the show of all time or something like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, we are going to be playing the new I Feel remix.
[SPEAKER_21]: We just...
[SPEAKER_21]: We ripped it during the break there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, our tech massa, is working on it right now, trying to get it all perfect.
[SPEAKER_21]: I said we should just rip it out of edit mode, but apparently if you try to rip it in edit mode, it cuts off the very beginning little speech thing, because it starts off and goes, Do you feel it?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, it sounds like one of those, like, speaking spells or something saying it.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, uh, Loki was like, No!
[SPEAKER_21]: We can't have that!
[SPEAKER_21]: So he made us go back and do it in edit mode, so, whatever.
[SPEAKER_19]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Pump Up the Volume where I just go crazy and play whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although if you're in our chat room, you can make a request.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I think that it doesn't totally suck ass, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then Wednesday nights is the Oldie and Moldie Orange Lounge Radio Show where basically we play a show from two years ago for your listening amusement.
[SPEAKER_21]: Listen to how much we used to suck.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you think we suck now, like we really sucked then.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then Thursday nights, Outside the Box at 7 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_21]: myself, RicePrincess, and LikeyStyle talking about the latest and greatest in video gaming.
[SPEAKER_21]: This last week was a pretty good show.
[SPEAKER_21]: You missed a good time if you missed this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had a good time.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then Friday nights, it's not on this station, but it's over on The Freak on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: The Rewinds, in case you missed a previous episode of Orange Lounge Radio, you can catch it over there, up to date.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, the show they're going to be playing this Friday is last week's show, which was the one where we had the MidiHead interview.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you guys missed the interview with MidiHead, awesome guy, awesome interview.
[SPEAKER_21]: You have to check it out, so go listen to Freak on Friday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, the karaoke cage match, by the way, was on last Friday, and of course, Loki won.
[SPEAKER_21]: Was there any surprise in anyone's mind?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've got to plug the LiveJournal community, because we haven't plugged that in a while.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you guys have a LiveJournal, which I know a lot of you do in this day and age, we're starting to move into a LiveJournally-centered internet, head on over to our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's just username OrangeLounge on LiveJournal, and if you join it, you get some of the latest announcements on what's going on in the station.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sometimes we propose ideas for changes to the station on our LiveJournal, and we get your feedback there, so it's just a nice little community.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a way for you to meet other listeners of OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Crazy people like us.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: Been a game we've been talking about a hell of a lot lately, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_21]: But SongPack, I keep calling it Service Pack.
[SPEAKER_21]: SongPack 7 came out this week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Finally, a lot of us were expecting that SongPack 7 was going to be out when the game came out.
[SPEAKER_21]: But for whatever reason, there was a delay.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sounds like there might have been some kind of bug that prevented things.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: A lot of people bitchin' and moanin' because SongPack 7 has a lot of old songs in it.
[SPEAKER_21]: We were talking about this a little bit last week.
[SPEAKER_21]: But SongPack 7 has End of the Century and La Senorita and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_21]: A lot of old classic DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I guess played out to a lot of people as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: Era as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you get some tack finally in DDR Ultimix 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: But a lot of these songs, since they're old, they're kind of played out.
[SPEAKER_21]: So they're getting a lot of kind of...
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: is another artist that's over on a different drum.
[SPEAKER_21]: The background for this song has the website address.
[SPEAKER_21]: You may have noticed a lot of the different drum songs, a lot of those, like the Jesper Kidd, a lot of the new songs in Ultramix 2 have websites in their background.
[SPEAKER_21]: So it's kind of interesting that we're getting those in some of the song packs as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I think in visiting Junk Circuit's website, I think there's actually a lot in common between Junk Circuit and Nuropa, who does the song Standing Still in Time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because they have the same website contact email So, kind of interesting Alright Anyway They're telling us in the chatroom to stop talking about the song and play the damn thing already That's fine, we'll get to it I'm going to copy it over right now Loki's put the finishing touches on it So we'll go ahead and play that for you But really first, Loki, what did you think of this remix?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's better than the other one You didn't like the other one?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why's that?
[SPEAKER_20]: The other one just kind of sucked I don't know, it was just kind of eh, not much different This is a lot better
[SPEAKER_21]: I do like this one a little bit better too, but I kind of like the old one as well, I gotta admit.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, I don't know, what do I know?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I gotta copy it over.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess there was a big tournament on Ultramix 2 tonight, online.
[SPEAKER_21]: There was a lot of people talking about it over on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_21]: I missed it.
[SPEAKER_21]: It wasn't something, I knew I'd get my ass kicked so I didn't want to participate, but I guess it went pretty well from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'll stop talking and start playing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Launch Radio presents the brand new I Feel remix.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the Junk Circuit mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy, guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you feel it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you hear it?
[SPEAKER_21]: I feel the Junk Circuit Mix
[SPEAKER_21]: Nothing top secure, Yamoga.
[SPEAKER_21]: What'd you think of that, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_18]: I liked it, except I think that I feel that little... Hold the bottom of the mic, it's breaking up a little bit, the cord's loose.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's alright, we're ghetto here, we don't have good equipment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, now you're cutting out completely.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you are.
[SPEAKER_14]: Am I here?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, you're here.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, now you're gone again!
[SPEAKER_21]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_21]: We need to buy a new mic, I think, something's going on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Steal this one real fast.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dough.
[SPEAKER_21]: That one's dying.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to cry for that microphone.
[SPEAKER_21]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Try that one.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I thought it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_18]: Except I think that little computer I feel it voice is a bad touch.
[SPEAKER_18]: If they left it out, it would make it better.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jazz in our chatroom agrees with you.
[SPEAKER_21]: He says the whole can you feel it samples just sounds fucking cheesy is what he says.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Jamie's yelling from the laundry room that she agrees.
[SPEAKER_21]: Overall, I like it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I think it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think the, uh, can you feel it is a little weird, but it, I don't know, it's different.
[SPEAKER_21]: I give them points for trying.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a good remix.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a fun song to play.
[SPEAKER_21]: The steps are kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: It took something good and added a bunch of extraneous crap to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: The steps, is there any DDR remix that you've liked so far?
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the Let This Face one that you interviewed last week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Middy Head?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: That one was good.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's his face?
[SPEAKER_21]: I wasn't here!
[SPEAKER_21]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR Console Games Forum?
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a little sticky announcement thingy where you can ask MidiHead a question.
[SPEAKER_21]: So if you missed getting your question last week, because we took some questions from our listeners, but if you missed your chance to ask MidiHead a question, they are taking question submissions right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: So go check that out if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_21]: What did you think of that remix, Angel?
[SPEAKER_21]: You like everything, so I know you're going to have something good to say about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I liked the first one from Silent Hill when we first did that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to take some calls on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you want to give us a call, head on over to www.OrangeLaunchRadio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm kind of curious about some of your guys' feedback on Ultramix 2, specifically SongPack 7, if you've had a chance to check it out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Any online experiences you might have had on Ultramix 2, and even if you want to talk about a DDR Festival, because we haven't talked a whole lot about DDR Festival, and that's just because none of us in Sacramento, I don't think a single person in Sacramento that I know of, anyway, has bought the game, so we don't know what to say about it.
[SPEAKER_20]: and to add to that, if you'd like to talk about Drawn together as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, that's not... What?
[SPEAKER_21]: I have an opinion, no I don't.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you ever get a chance to play Ultramix 2, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_19]: Did you guys pick that up at your place?
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you going to get it?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's fun!
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_19]: You should.
[SPEAKER_05]: The house has been rearranged in Halo 2 land position.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no room to put any dance pads or anything.
[SPEAKER_21]: Look at this place.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hello, you can sit on our camp.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have infinitely more room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan's got the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Normally in my living room we have the TV on one wall, the couch on one wall, and the loveseat back on the far wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now the loveseat and couch are back to back with just enough room to have a place to put your legs and an Xbox between TVs.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is currently in LAN mode.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you guys hosting a bunch of Halo 2 parties or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dan did on his birthday on Monday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, his birthday was Monday, huh?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Happy birthday, Dan.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wasn't here for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: He told me I should feel guilty.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, now that's not true.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, I don't think anybody's calling us on the Skype line, so what can we do?
[SPEAKER_21]: Damn it, they suck!
[SPEAKER_21]: Except now they're talking about Drawn Together in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_21]: You freaking ass, Loki.
[SPEAKER_19]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, now you keep telling me that you're going to start playing Ultramix 2 because I notice that every time I've been playing it, you're like, yeah, I need to play that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, I need to play that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you actually going to be playing?
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, we're finally getting a call.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going to reprieve for now, but as soon as this call is done, we're going to ask you about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Legend of Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_21]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have that much to share because, you know, as I said, you know, I'm a college student.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then get off the phone!
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a PS2 or an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_02]: I might get one this Christmas, but I'm kind of iffy on which one should I get.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Bomani-wise, that is.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you don't have a PS2 or an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you're asking the age-old question, which system should I get?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but with regards to not only, you know, games, but also Bomani as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm adding a little kick to it.
[SPEAKER_20]: And you have nothing to add about Drawn Together.
[SPEAKER_21]: He didn't hear that.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: And you have nothing to add about Drawn Together.
[SPEAKER_20]: I did see South Park last Wednesday, but that was about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_21]: Quit trying to derail this program, Loki, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shame.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: As far as Xbox versus PS2, here it is, basically.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're interested in something that's going to remind you of the arcade, something that's going to bring the arcade experience to the home, something where there's a lot of different songs available, something with iToy support, if you want to get your hands involved, go for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you want to get something where you can play online, and you want to play against other people that live around, go for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_21]: But here's the thing, you being the starving college student, that means you're going to have to pay for the Xbox, Xbox Live, and then five bucks a song pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: What are you looking... Yeah, but also with the PS2, I might have to mod it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to mod if I'm going to play 2DX or any of those lovely Pomani games besides DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, that's very true, and that's going to cost you money as well, I mean, if you want to play the Japanese games.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's the other thing, if you plan on modding your PS2, which, you know, can have mixed results, I guess I hear now it's pretty easy to mod it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I live in the city.
[SPEAKER_02]: Chinatown's not that far, and I can always get it modded there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: So you can get it modded PS2.
[SPEAKER_21]: So if you're interested in 2DX or Poppin' or any of that stuff, you're definitely going to want to get the PS2.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's the other thing to consider, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: We have PS3 and Xbox 2 likely to be out in stores before next Christmas.
[SPEAKER_21]: We don't know for sure, but if I were a betting man, I would say those things are going to be in stores next Christmas, which means the systems that are out there now, their prices will be halved.
[SPEAKER_21]: or they'll be $100 or less.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I probably already took notice of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I think 9th style, if it does come out next year for PS2, I don't know if it's going to jump into the next console or just be the last PS2 2DX game.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm kind of hoping that there is a 9th style and a 10th style pretty back-to-back.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm kind of hoping that those games come out pretty quickly.
[SPEAKER_02]: PS2 or just one for PS2 and the next for PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hope they both come out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's a given that PS3 will play PS2 games, so they ought to just both come out for PS2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, seeing as, you know, I already noticed that 2DX games come out, you know, there's always 2DX games coming out for PS2 every single year.
[SPEAKER_02]: And basically, from what I'm speculating, from what I'm predicting, Nightstar might come out in May next year or something, or near the summer.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nobody really knows.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just taking a guess here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, taking a shot.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just taking an educated guess from...
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, alright, I think pretty much I... Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: Then again, 9th style would make a lot of sense on PlayStation 3 because then they could fuck up the timing.
[SPEAKER_21]: By putting it on a new system, just like the arcade one.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I get a PS2 for Bomani, I'm gonna have to pay money for the 2DX controller, poppin' music, so it's gonna be equally the same if I'm gonna have to try going after both.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because one will have more peripherals and the other will have more services and things to buy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, also to even confuse things even more, there's also the Phantom console that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_20]: How is that confusing?
[SPEAKER_20]: Who gives a shit about the Phantom?
[SPEAKER_21]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_20]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, I've got pictures of the dough on orangeonradio.com.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I hear rumors of a...
[SPEAKER_20]: Engage 2 that's shaped like a banana.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have rumors.
[SPEAKER_21]: Better than a taco.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've heard rumors of a bowel movement.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm about to have after this show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're looking for Bimani, assistant for Bimani, don't get a GameCube.
[SPEAKER_02]: of course not, hell no, gamecubes are not worth the money hey, don't you be knocking the gamecube, it's a beautiful system I'm not knocking it, I mean, it's cheap, but I mean don't make me come out there and cut you, because I will what, you're going to travel 3,000 miles to cut you?
[SPEAKER_02]: to cut you, yes do you even know where in New York do I live?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll send my minions yeah, sure, and do you want a cookie for that, Skye?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Live 365 has it all on record, I think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure it does.
[SPEAKER_02]: What IP and what school am I doing this from?
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going to the school of hang-up in about five seconds there, buddy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks a lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks a lot, Sky.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_21]: Take care, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now I know what to choose later.
[SPEAKER_21]: Zaku's always fun to talk to.
[SPEAKER_21]: I like bullying him a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's a fun guy.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to go to the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_21]: We've got to get into that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, Loki was the winner, but it doesn't matter because that was a one-time thing, so...
[SPEAKER_21]: That gets thrown out and we go back to the cage match at hand.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our reoccurring winner, Gwen Stefani, What You Waiting For?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's the song I put in the cage match, believe it or not, three weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_21]: So because it won last week by default, this is the last time it can win.
[SPEAKER_21]: And if it wins tonight, it'll become the second song in Orange Lounge history to be retired from the cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki seems convinced it's going to be gone.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, you have something you want to say?
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: What a woman.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Here's a clip of last... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: The way the cage match works.
[SPEAKER_21]: You've got to be in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_21]: You've got to be listening live on Sunday night.
[SPEAKER_21]: www.orangellandradio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: We're going to play three songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: One song from each host.
[SPEAKER_21]: We only play a clip of last week's winner, though, because you already heard the song back when it first won.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because you listen to Orange Lounge Radio every week, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, then you're going to send in your vote and the winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio 24-7 Balmati Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enough talking.
[SPEAKER_21]: A clip of song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gwen Stefani, what you waiting for?
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, that was song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Gwen Stefani with Whatcha Waitin' For.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's so goddamn funny?
[SPEAKER_05]: Talking about combining different groups.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got Britney Spears and Flo and then B4U.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have B4U.
[SPEAKER_21]: You guys are crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, let's get to song number two in tonight's Cage Match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, it's your pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mine's an apology for making everyone listen to that bad remix of Emerge.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I put in the original instead, just because I really wanted to play it and I don't care if it wins or not.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the last one I did was Ersatz, so this is Fisher Spooner with Emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fisher Spooner with Emerge, the non-remixed version.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to say, I thought you had a Fisher Spooner song in before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did Ersatz before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, well, here it is, you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number two you can vote for tonight, Fischer Spooner, Emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't need to be much from nothing You don't need to step up
[SPEAKER_08]: Looks good, sounds good, looks good, feels good too, feels good too, feels good too
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DaDaDa
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh-huh, that's right
Hi, that was song number two in tonight's case match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Fisherspooner with Emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go around and get everybody's emerging thoughts on that song, starting off with the lovely DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: I always like that song, so it gets a 9 from me, but I don't really care.
[SPEAKER_21]: An apathetic 9 from DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seriously, I just put it in just because I wanted to listen to it.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a good enough reason to send me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcadian, see if that mic will work again for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is it on?
[SPEAKER_21]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is it okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's alright.
[SPEAKER_18]: No, I don't really like it all that much, so I'll give it a six.
[SPEAKER_21]: A six from Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_20]: I didn't get it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Was that supposed to be a song?
[SPEAKER_20]: Because it sounded just like some stupid synth in the background and them talking over it.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm trying to go, it sounds like a Beck's type thing, but no.
[SPEAKER_20]: No.
[SPEAKER_20]: I can't imagine this being actually better than the original remix.
[SPEAKER_20]: Of course, I don't remember that remix of it, so, um, I get the one.
[SPEAKER_20]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: I actually dig the synths in that song quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: I see that as kind of like maybe a song I would listen to while I'm driving home late at night.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's pretty cool and it's got very much of an 80s vibe going for me.
[SPEAKER_21]: My only complaint is that it's a little quiet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'd like something maybe a little bit more driving.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I actually like the synths.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've become a total synth pop whore lately.
[SPEAKER_21]: And yes, a lot of that has to do with Ultramix too.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that song kind of fits in for me.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I'm giving it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel!
[SPEAKER_04]: I liked it a lot.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, remember, it doesn't matter what we think, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's all up to you guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: But you get a third song to pick from tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: And Loki is being cheap tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's hear what he's going to pick.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you for the introduction.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, this song, as we already heard, it was last week we played it.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is their cover of The Fix.
[SPEAKER_20]: Midi Head with Deeper and Deeper.
[SPEAKER_20]: Or Monolithic, whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, it's Monolithic, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, so here it is, song number three tonight, a cover of The Fix with Monolithic with Deeper and Deeper.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy, we'll be back.
We're gonna take the call and get deeper, and deeper, and deeper We're gonna take the call and get deeper, and deeper, and deeper
I get deeper, and deeper The more I see, the more I fall The late night, the girl takes the call I get deeper, and deeper I see the edge, I look up The place to hide, I'm gonna take the call I see the edge, I look up
Thank you for watching!
And I see the edge, I look, I fall And I get deeper, and deeper The more I see, the more I fall Nobody's eyes, you better take the call I get deeper
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number three in tonight's cage match, Monolithic doing a cover of The Fix there, deeper and deeper.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's go deep into our... I can't make a reference.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, what did you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked everything about the song except for the guy's voice.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, it gets... Well, damn, the music gets a 10, the voice gets a 1.
[SPEAKER_21]: So... Loki says it gets an 11.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seven.
[SPEAKER_21]: Seven, alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Only because of the voice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, I thought it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'll give it a nine.
[SPEAKER_21]: A nine from Bradley.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_20]: It gets a ten.
[SPEAKER_20]: And, if you like this, go to midihead.com, buy his albums, and then tell him that Orange Lounge Radio sent you.
[SPEAKER_20]: You'll get access to this wonderful song, as well as many other remixes he's done.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've been listening to that song quite a bit on my new iPod lately, so I have to admit, it's actually a really good song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just hope we don't, he doesn't turn into the new Echo Image on this station, seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, but actually it's a great song, it's a great cover, and I like it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nine, Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like it a lot, good cover, and good artist, so you know what, nine and a half.
[SPEAKER_19]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: An explicit who just walked in doesn't get to vote because he didn't hear that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going to place your vote momentarily.
[SPEAKER_21]: But first, here is a recap of the three songs you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number one you can vote for tonight, Gwen Stefani, What You Waiting For.
[SPEAKER_21]: Song number two you can vote for tonight is Fisher Spooner with Emerge.
[SPEAKER_21]: And song number three you can vote for tonight is Monolithic doing a cover of The Fix, Deeper and Deeper.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, place vote now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we will see what happens.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, moving right along.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've been perusing some of the message forums out there lately, DDR Freak namely being one of them.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought there was this very interesting thread over there in Random Chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know how they do a lot of really crazy stuff over in Random Chat?
[SPEAKER_21]: You know the Random Chat stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_21]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_21]: Being a mod over there and everything?
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: What's this random that you talk about?
[SPEAKER_21]: We don't know anything about random on this show.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just out of curiosity, this is total tangent, but since I'm thinking DarkSakura here and how much she loves to lock topics over there, what would you say would be the most favorite topic you've gotten to lock on random chat?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, please lock this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had a please lock this before.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi, please lock this, alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's an interesting topic going on there in random chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's called, do you actually play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_21]: And I thought it was kind of interesting just seeing how many people actually don't play DDR anymore.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I kind of was going to go around the room a little bit and see, do you play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_21]: And if not, why are you doing this show?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll start.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do I play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_21]: A little bit, not as much nearly as I used to.
[SPEAKER_21]: I play a little bit of Ultramix 2 at home.
[SPEAKER_21]: Most of my DDR playing is Controller Controller.
[SPEAKER_21]: The reason why I don't play DDR that much anymore is because the quality of arcades in this area went downhill significantly.
[SPEAKER_21]: Konami of Japan can suck it for not putting out a new mix in a long time.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that has a lot to do with the reason why I haven't played DDR in a long time.
[SPEAKER_21]: The home version is the only thing keeping it alive to me, but I just can't motivate my fat ass to pull out the ignition pad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Especially when the ignition pad, as good of a dance pad as it is, it's still not the arcade.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to play DDR in the arcade, and there's no
[SPEAKER_21]: I played DDR when I was in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you play it regularly besides that?
[SPEAKER_05]: When I'm somewhere that has a machine, I'll play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got more reason to play now than I play dock at RVGL.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll set out a little bit of money and go play some DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: I played like one game of DDR when I went to go play dock at Derby Owner's Club over at Roseville Golf Land, but here's the problem, I fucking failed Breakdown!
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, you know, it's a 9-footer, it's a more difficult song at the end of the scale, but you have to remember, I'm somebody who was playing DDR religiously for quite some time, and, you know, I... I just... It just makes me sad how much stamina I've lost, you know?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arkadian, do you actually play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_18]: Not really, mainly because my foot's been hurting, and I haven't had that much money lately.
[SPEAKER_18]: Now I might be able to go once my foot feels 100%, or 90% at least.
[SPEAKER_18]: Maybe more in the future, because it's been so long and I need to get off my fat ass, and I sit around too much.
[SPEAKER_18]: And so on.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, do you play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR and Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_20]: Addict!
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, I do.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm Step Mania every once in a while.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, yes, to answer your question earlier about Xbox and stuff and if I was ever going to play it, no, because I'm going to actually set up my Step Mania cabinet to be playing the stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: In fact, that's why I bought crap today to cut the other control panel for the actual select arrows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's why...
[SPEAKER_20]: I was going to do that today.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm hopefully going to build that this week because I bought a while back a new IPAC thing to hook it all up and I have to see if it's going to get fried as easy as the other one.
[SPEAKER_20]: So it's all contingent on that, whether I get to play it some more.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't play in the arcade because the arcade's too far away, takes too much of my time, cuts into my Final Fantasy XI time, and the arcade's broken all the time.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm
[SPEAKER_20]: That and I'm way fucking out of shape.
[SPEAKER_20]: I go and play like a seven footer on doubles and I'm ready to die.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, whatever happened to me.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_20]: It never used to be this hard.
[SPEAKER_20]: But once I get back in shape, yeah, I'd play a lot more.
[SPEAKER_20]: I just need to finish my arcade cabinets before I move out of here, so that's priority one.
[SPEAKER_21]: You don't play a whole lot of DDR in the arcade or at home anymore, yet you're very gung-ho about this cabinet and everything.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_21]: Is it just a love for the basic concept of the game?
[SPEAKER_20]: I like building stuff, have you noticed?
[SPEAKER_20]: Stuff that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_20]: Like the portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_20]: The portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_21]: Also, I noticed you tend to build things halfway through and don't finish them, such as these lovely metal pads that have been sitting over here for the past... Can we play Xbox or PS2 games with them right now?
[SPEAKER_20]: We can if I hooked up the other, the, um, iPack thing, because all I have to do is switch out the old iPack and it plugs right in and it works.
[SPEAKER_20]: But the thing is, the thing is I haven't bought the adapter for the Xbox or the PS2 yet because it was hooking up directly to my computer.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, I could.
[SPEAKER_20]: I could if I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_20]: It just would take a while because I'd have to wire everything.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it's just that those things... I would be curious how thick the layer of dust is on those metal pads that are sitting right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Can I go wipe my finger on it and see how much dust is on them?
[SPEAKER_21]: Here you go, Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: They also buy the air intake, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Look at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a little radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh yeah, okay, I have an idea.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let me wipe the dust off of my little, my computer desk here, because I get quite a bit used to it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, look, it's gray.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let me wipe the dust off of every, there's dust everywhere in here.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's not a surprise that there's dust on those.
[SPEAKER_20]: That and they're right next to the air intake, which I'm sure is not good for the air conditioner one bit, but that's alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: No wonder it smells like wood in this house all the time, this strange mix of metal and everything.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, uh, explicit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Welcome to the show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_21]: I noticed you just ran in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Put down the DS for a minute.
[SPEAKER_21]: Quit chatting with Angel on Pickup Chat for a minute.
[SPEAKER_21]: That mic's been giving us... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_21]: They are like, what, eight feet?
[SPEAKER_20]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_20]: This is what... I think they're exchanging special pictures.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is what's wrong, people.
[SPEAKER_20]: You need to talk.
[SPEAKER_20]: Talky-talky.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like, you know, the people IMing each other when they're sitting in a cafe.
[SPEAKER_20]: Talk.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're writing penis back and forth to each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Rob, that's you last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_21]: You gotta hold the mic at the bottom, because it's going out tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: That mic's on its last legs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I can hear you now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you play DDR?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, since there's been tournaments and stuff, and some new people want me to come back again, I guess I'll play again.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, even though the DDR scene is dying in a way, because there hasn't been any releases for the arcades and stuff, which is totally understandable.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just the new people, the community, the new members are just trying to get, bring it back again in a way.
[SPEAKER_20]: You give me $100,000, I'll bring back DDR.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_11]: The only way that you can bring back DDR is by fixing the Stamina cabinet, damn it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck that cabinet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Give me $100,000.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hell, give me just $20,000 and I'll bring it back.
[SPEAKER_21]: Don't you think that, now, call me crazy, because it's not supposed to be DDR, quote-unquote, but don't you think In The Groove was sort of a way to try to bring DDR back?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I always got the impression of, was that In The Groove was, even though it's not DDR... Well, the thing about In The Groove is that not many cabinets have been sold around the U.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: just yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: And very few songs are in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's mainly just testing the waters until In The Groove 2 comes out and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: And it also depends on what step makers are they going to hire and what songs they're going to put in it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell, they put Ultramix, like, Ultramix in the DDR cam and I play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I already, the first week after Ultramix 2 is out, I put the call out on the show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I said, we need to hound the shit out of Konami of Hawaii and however it has to happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't care if some arcade division went under or what the shit happened.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't care how it has to happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: It just needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hawaii needs to make a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't care who's gotta be blown, who's gotta be paid the money.
[SPEAKER_21]: Make it happen!
[SPEAKER_11]: You know what's hella funny, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: The hell of companies are saying that the whole arcade business is dying unless you're trying to do this card system like Tekken 5 and Midnight Tuner or Initial D. Yeah, but the lines for Tekken 5?
[SPEAKER_21]: Insane.
[SPEAKER_21]: Honestly.
[SPEAKER_21]: You can't say Tekken 5 is not... I mean, despite how you feel about the Tekken series, it's, you know, the biggest crowd I've seen in an arcade in a long time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have my card.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, that's just like people saying, oh, well, you know, internet's killing the telephones.
[SPEAKER_20]: People still use the telephones just like people use the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, people still use the telephone and I talk to them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways, but the whole thing is to convert, you know, Ultramix to an arcade system is like fucking easy.
[SPEAKER_20]: Minimal programming, licensing of songs.
[SPEAKER_20]: Build the hardware.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hardware is fucking easy to build.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's just an excuse.
[SPEAKER_20]: But it's just they don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because they don't want to distribute it.
[SPEAKER_20]: And that's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_11]: The reason why I pump it up is like making more and more money just building new machines and stuff
[SPEAKER_21]: Allow me to be the first to offer sex to anyone at Konami of Hawaii if you can make yourselves a new DDR game.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: Not the Konami of Japan does a bad job.
[SPEAKER_21]: So if they want to do a new mix, I'm perfectly fine with that as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: I will extend my sex offer to Konami of Tokyo as well, K-Set.
[SPEAKER_21]: So just make me a new DDR and I will put out.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's that simple.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anybody else care to offer their sexual favors?
[SPEAKER_20]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_21]: Because it's cheaper to license the songs of Japan, obviously.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's gonna look a little weird, but like, I made this machine over here in Japan, it's called a DDR Extreme USA.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it's not meant to be played in the United States, just... They could call it DDR Shit Mix, and I'd still play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry, Shitake.
[SPEAKER_21]: They could call it DDR Shitake Mix, I would still play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shitake, that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel, you still play DDR at all?
[SPEAKER_21]: You're probably more into DDR than anyone I know right now, so I have to ask you this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, I'm probably going to break down and get a dual-platform ignition because I want to play on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm looking into getting both of those this week, Ultramix 2 and the new pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Magus is dying anyway, so I might as well just replace it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we can play doubles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: Speaking of ignition, which is better, ignition or cobalt flux?
[SPEAKER_21]: I couldn't tell you because I haven't really played enough cobalt flux.
[SPEAKER_21]: I saw it a little bit at E3, but I wasn't familiar enough with it.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're both the same fucking pad.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's the same damn thing with a different logo on it.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_20]: You can't get much different.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, our medal is different than your medal.
[SPEAKER_11]: What about the quality and how many times could it be stepped?
[SPEAKER_20]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're the fucking same.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's call a pledge that not even a rhino could beat down the pad.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_20]: Do they have a rhino to test this?
[SPEAKER_20]: Did they take it to Africa and go, Hey rhino, step on the pad!
[SPEAKER_20]: How do you like it?
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, I'm sorry, but I can say, yeah, guess what?
[SPEAKER_20]: Jupiter has nothing on this pad!
[SPEAKER_20]: This pad can fuck up Jupiter!
[SPEAKER_20]: Seriously, they're just pulling the shit out of their ass, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: A rhino can't fuck this up!
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_20]: Bigfoot recommends, you know, red octane, so...
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck that.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_20]: Really, to be honest, when it comes down to pads, don't buy off the internet.
[SPEAKER_20]: Buy stuff that you can see in a store.
[SPEAKER_20]: Buy it like fries and stuff where you can actually see these pads.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because the shit you get off the internet, because I have bought metal pads off the internet, and I stepped on them and they bent.
[SPEAKER_20]: They bent downwards.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I was like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_20]: It was retarded.
[SPEAKER_20]: Pads are not meant to be folded in half.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow, talk about how they say SUVs can bust them on their advertisements.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, our chat room over at www.orangeloungeradio.com, clicking on chat, uh, interesting point, there already is a DDR shit mix, and it's the Don't Fall Off mix, the DDR Extreme bootleg.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know the one that would speed up?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, actually, there's two of them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, I know about the speed up.
[SPEAKER_21]: The one that'll speed up, DDR Extreme Plus, thank you.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's the DDR, yeah, the one in Country Club Lane, speed up, ooh, let's speed up Max 300 and let's see if we can beat it at 360 BPM.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_11]: or hear cartoon heroes in a very high-pitched voice.
[SPEAKER_21]: What is the deal with Cartoon Heroes?
[SPEAKER_21]: Why do so many people freaking love that song and are quick to label a mix as utter shit if that song isn't in it?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't understand what is so great about the song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is it a good song?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, it's a great song.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was a little better when Aqua did it.
[SPEAKER_21]: But it's a good song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is it fun to play?
[SPEAKER_21]: Kinda.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, I'll die when I play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: But why do so many people freaking obsess over Cartoon Heroes?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, do you know how many people threw a fit when that song wasn't in Extreme USA?
[SPEAKER_19]: I can answer that.
[SPEAKER_20]: Let's look back in DDR history and view what we call the songs that ruin mixes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Starting with third mix, Afronova.
[SPEAKER_20]: Who could love this wonderful African chant as you jump around like a complete nut?
[SPEAKER_20]: Fourth mix, Kick the Can, with its repetitive steps over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's another contributing factor.
1, 2, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're forgetting though, my edit to Kick the Can, aka Big Cans, was awesome and made that song redeemable.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, and as I would continue on to the fifth mix, Hot Limits.
[SPEAKER_20]: The song that just, you don't understand what they're saying, but you know it's very long.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways, DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'd say probably that would be Exotic Ethnic.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was pretty repetitive in DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh no, Flash in the Night.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, that was another one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Flash in the Night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold on, your mic's still cutting out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hold it at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_21]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hold it at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, try it, try it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Put it close to your mouth.
[SPEAKER_11]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's the same reason why it's Cartoon Heroes got whored out, the same reason why So Deep is getting whored off with, like, DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because it's like Hard As Hell 9.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would say, I would say the song that ruined DDR Max, even though I love this song, Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_20]: Cowgirl, yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Max 2, Cigaroo, and who could not forget the song that had everyone dancing, Blow My Whistle, Bitch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_21]: Blow My Whistle Bitch definitely ruined Max 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so, make your point, please.
[SPEAKER_20]: My point is, I don't have a point.
[SPEAKER_20]: The point is that there's always going to be a song that people, that's catchy, and is annoying catchy.
[SPEAKER_20]: And to be honest, I hate cartoon heroes, and I know there's 50 bands out there that all sound like them.
[SPEAKER_20]: In fact, I hear different artists and I'm like, is that, you know, Aqua?
[SPEAKER_20]: No, it's not Aqua.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's Toybox or it's, you know, insert band here.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know, Captain Jack.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, they sound all the fucking same.
[SPEAKER_20]: They have like the same singer that sings super high pitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that it's a man who's been, you know... I think she's on smack.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's on helium.
[SPEAKER_20]: She's fucking taking speed.
[SPEAKER_20]: She's on crack.
[SPEAKER_20]: Crystal meth.
[SPEAKER_20]: She's just
[SPEAKER_20]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay, so anyways, yeah, there's always going to be that annoying song.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, there's always an annoying song that's annoying as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the shit is this?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's annoying when it was originally... Have you seen the video for this?
[SPEAKER_20]: The video for this is fucking annoying, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: Honestly, it's just like...
[SPEAKER_21]: You're confusing the original, there was no video to that, but you're confusing the original Aqua song, which is a little, it's a little bit slower, even though it sounds very similar, it's a little bit slower.
[SPEAKER_21]: Pretty much, okay, take the original Cartoon Heroes by Aqua and play it on DDR Extreme Plus with the plus 20% modifier and that's what you get.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's awful.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways, yeah, they should have Extreme++, which, like, you know, speeds it up by 100% or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: 100%, okay, max 600.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_21]: 1, 2, 3, 4, max 300.
[SPEAKER_21]: Then we have songs that ruin the remix scene, but we'll do that another day.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_21]: Speaking of songs that ruin DDR, I wanted to have an old school flashback and start it off with an old favorite song of mine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Love this song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie was dying to hear some second mix songs that are actually good songs, so we're going to put those in.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we're going to play those songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: But we have to start it off with a song I've been threatening all night long.
[SPEAKER_21]: It is the most old school of old school DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_21]: Please take a minute, despite how you feel about this song, this one goes out to the one and only...
[SPEAKER_20]: God bless his soul, he's not listening to us right now because he's out there.
[SPEAKER_20]: Kyle Snyder.
[SPEAKER_20]: God bless Kyle Snyder, seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: But honestly, this, despite how you feel about this song, respect for a moment, please.
[SPEAKER_21]: We'll be back here on Orange Lodge Radio.
Ay-yi-yi, ay-yi-yi, ay-yi-yi.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob, boob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Y-I-I-I-I, you keep a focus through the green, green door I love you boy, it's your time You're very hard, you look like a young fella Take me overnight Boom, boom, boom, boom, something like a boom, boom Boom, boom, boom, boom, back to the water
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back, hi, on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are such nerds.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was sitting there chatting on my DS with everyone else during the break.
[SPEAKER_21]: We have four DSs in this house right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that we have five, but I'm not breaking mine out.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_21]: You got your DS here too, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_21]: We could just have a DS chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was trying to put some pictures there on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wrote penis, really dark, so you guys could see it, and then put it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who's calling me during the show?
[SPEAKER_21]: These people should know better.
[SPEAKER_21]: Especially this person.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shame.
[SPEAKER_20]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm just waiting for the emulator to work with Bluetooth, and then we'll get a wireless router so we can upload them all to a streaming chat room.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's the dream.
[SPEAKER_21]: And, oh god, for the person who requested Butterfly Pikachu Mix in the chat, no!
[SPEAKER_21]: Heck no.
[SPEAKER_21]: Although I do have that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I do have that.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I'm not going to fire them.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, who wants to hear who won the cage match tonight?
[SPEAKER_21]: The winning song of tonight's cage match actually surprised me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: It only won by two votes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not one vote, but two votes.
[SPEAKER_21]: It all came down to two votes.
[SPEAKER_21]: The winning song of tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Believe it or not, it won.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm actually surprised.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought Monolithic had it sealed.
[SPEAKER_20]: Because she said it was going to be retired and they won another retired one.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's basically it.
[SPEAKER_21]: So Gwen Stefani is officially retired.
[SPEAKER_21]: It'll spend one more week in the spotlight.
[SPEAKER_21]: And then three brand new songs for you to listen to next week.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_20]: As is her career.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was going to take another call over Skype, but I know that our chatters are kind of shy and probably wouldn't want to call in, so how about we get into the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think now's a good time, especially after that victory, to get into the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Does that sound like a plan for you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, and why is it, Miss Jamie, that we have to do the FUs of the Week every single week on this show?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because everything sucks.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big F you goes toward the stinky person on the plane who cut a big fart sitting in front of me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Another F you goes toward just general backwards ass shit, having no free time, and my weird grammatical errors, and the four bottles of Guinness I had last night, and that's really about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want a big F you to my mom for saying that her chronic bronchitis is not aggravated by cigarette smoke.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, you sure you're done?
[SPEAKER_21]: Are you sure?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_21]: You sure?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Loki, your turn.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, Folsom, on multiple occasions.
[SPEAKER_20]: Number one being, um, the lights.
[SPEAKER_20]: Literally, the lights, the stoplights around here are so short.
[SPEAKER_20]: I came to a stoplight.
[SPEAKER_20]: I saw it turn from green to red to yellow, um, you know, all the colors and everything in less than a second.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_20]: There was not even enough time for one car to go through the light.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_20]: Then, then, um, fuck you too, um, a giant marathon is out front of our fucking house!
[SPEAKER_20]: Giant marathon!
[SPEAKER_20]: Ah, shut up, you don't live around here.
[SPEAKER_20]: Doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_20]: Um, you didn't have to hear at five in the fucking morning, wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-
[SPEAKER_20]: broadcasted over a giant loudspeaker out front.
[SPEAKER_20]: It was bad enough that they took up four of our parking spaces up close to our apartment with goddamn porta-potties.
[SPEAKER_20]: Four porta-potties, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: Four porta-potties.
[SPEAKER_20]: Meanwhile, there's 50 porta-potties along the street.
[SPEAKER_20]: Why do you need four more strategically placed in those parking spaces?
[SPEAKER_20]: Along with some stupid food, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, I'm no genius here, but since the fucking, you know, damn road is closed...
[SPEAKER_20]: I'd say there's a pretty good chance you can probably put that booth right there next to all the goddamn fucking porta-potties.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wow, wouldn't that make sense?
[SPEAKER_20]: But no, so we have to make noise for three hours.
[SPEAKER_20]: Three hours in the morning.
[SPEAKER_20]: See, I was expecting not to hear the marathon, because last time I slept through it, but, you know, I got woken up, and my first, you know, things that came to my mind was, this is fucking ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_20]: And we went outside, and there's tons of runners, and trust me, if I'm outside... KCRA3 is protecting you with our live pinpoint doppler radar.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't fucking care about your pinpoint doppler radar!
[SPEAKER_21]: I was trying to find a link to the chatroom...
[SPEAKER_21]: I was trying to find a link about the marathon.
[SPEAKER_21]: There was a story on a local news station I was going to send it to the... That's actually kind of funny now that I think about it.
[SPEAKER_21]: F.U.
[SPEAKER_21]: Channel 3.
[SPEAKER_20]: So anyway, yeah, that really sucks.
[SPEAKER_20]: Other than that, a premature... Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_20]: A premature fuck you to...
[SPEAKER_20]: My car that has to go in on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it's going to suck because I know they're going to try to screw me out of my fucking warranty.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, you know, I won't let them because I know it's not my brakes.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's their fucking calipers that are broken.
[SPEAKER_20]: But I have to take off work on Tuesday to go to my grandma's funeral.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I have to take off work on, or I mean Tuesday for funeral, Thursday for my car.
[SPEAKER_20]: So it's going to be kind of a weird week.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, uh...
[SPEAKER_20]: Yeah, I'm going to call in sick on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm not going to tell them.
[SPEAKER_20]: And finally, just fucking retarded people that play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_20]: I've never seen more unintelligent people in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_20]: People that misspell something and then misspell.
[SPEAKER_20]: Like, for instance...
[SPEAKER_20]: Please help me out, spell P-L-I first, and then they're all, oh, I'm sorry, I misspelled that.
[SPEAKER_20]: P-L-I-S.
[SPEAKER_20]: Please.
[SPEAKER_20]: Pliss.
[SPEAKER_20]: Pliss help me out.
[SPEAKER_21]: Welcome to Ragnarok, chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: My god.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would say Pliss learn how to spell.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways, I just hate people and their bad grammar.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, honestly, I can understand shorthand, you know, using R and U as actual words.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm done.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to that marathon that was going on outside the house this morning.
[SPEAKER_21]: Seriously, you can go to any Sacramento-based website and read about this marathon.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a huge event that happens every year.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think that's great if you want to do a marathon and what have you.
[SPEAKER_21]: But freaking shut up or start the thing after...
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, there's a noise ordinance in the city that says do not make noise until after 8 a.m.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, freaking turn your loudspeakers off until 8 a.m.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or, you know, it doesn't make sense to me.
[SPEAKER_21]: We live right behind a huge lake that is emptiness.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's nothing at the lake.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nobody goes to the lake in the wintertime.
[SPEAKER_21]: Start the marathon just like 300 feet away at the lake, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Honestly, it's a marathon.
[SPEAKER_21]: They can run a little further.
[SPEAKER_20]: But Rob, it's 9-11, and, you know, terrorists.
[SPEAKER_20]: But here's the thing I don't understand, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: I can understand, okay, I would have not had a problem if the guy is just like, you know, okay, we're going to start the race at da-da-da-da time, you know, this kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: And then at the time, you know, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, go, you know, like he did.
[SPEAKER_20]: But no, he had the, and the, blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
[SPEAKER_20]: He just talked for three hours straight.
[SPEAKER_20]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like, you know, I understand you have, you know, the PA and stuff to, you know, get a hold of, you know, attention of these people, but you don't need to fucking talk, like, all the time!
[SPEAKER_20]: Just say, okay, well, you know, announce, you know, 15 minutes before the race starts, you know, so you can get in your marks, you know, and then do the countdown, and that's it!
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, and then there's a fucking siren after that!
[SPEAKER_20]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_20]: Like, cause you didn't, you didn't see, oh, why are all those people running?
[SPEAKER_20]: One more thing I forgot to add, sorry, I'm stealing your thing.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, the police department here, because they were parked...
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I get this F you, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: I get the F you to the police department because frickin' I called them at 6.30 in the morning saying, there is a marathon going on outside this house, I'm sure you're aware, but they are being way too loud.
[SPEAKER_21]: And she's like, sorry sir, there's nothing I can do about that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I said, are you aware that there's a city ordinance that says that you can't make noise before 8 a.m.?
[SPEAKER_21]: If you have an issue with that, you're going to have to call City Hall and request to the permits department.
[SPEAKER_21]: So now I'm going to have to look like a big grinchy asshole when the fact of the matter is I'm probably not even going to live here next year.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I am not going to let this shit slide.
[SPEAKER_21]: I am pissed that they woke me up at 6.30 on a freaking Sunday when I was out drinking the night before.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ass!
[SPEAKER_20]: Sorry, Loki, you had a thought.
[SPEAKER_20]: My thought was because this police officer parked his car in the middle of the fucking lane, on the street, no reason, just sitting there with his flashers on, not blocking traffic because there was an accident, or he pulled someone over, or he was fiddling around with god knows what, he was parked in the middle of the fucking road!
[SPEAKER_20]: For no reason!
[SPEAKER_20]: So I went around him.
[SPEAKER_20]: On the inside.
[SPEAKER_20]: Except if there was a dead person there, I would have run him over.
[SPEAKER_21]: to be continued I am going to call and complain on Monday just you wait and I know the neighbors upstairs I'm proud of you I am taking lessons from Jamie I'm going to have her proofread my angry letter I'll do it too I'll make that stuff fit in it awesome you should sign it even though you don't live here alright let's go around and get some other folks in studio get their FUs of the week we'll start off with Angel um
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, just F you to, uh, yeah, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually don't really have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh, F you to my instructor because he's mad.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, he's actually letting us out on the 8th or something like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, uh, we still gotta come back to the finals, so I don't know what's up with that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcadian42, your FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_18]: Alright, make sure, you hear me, can you?
[SPEAKER_18]: I can hear you.
[SPEAKER_18]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, fuck you to my skin, I don't know about the winter, it just makes my skin start getting all dry, and I just drink lots of water, but it still doesn't help.
[SPEAKER_18]: But, uh, anyway.
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, yeah, and, uh, Loki was talking about, uh, stupid, uh, traffic lights, there's one near my work that's stupid, that's, like, misprogrammed, that's, like,
[SPEAKER_18]: Changes in 5 seconds, after like 5 seconds from green to yellow.
[SPEAKER_18]: And some, like recently, they fucked up the timing so that this crossroad isn't getting all that much traffic.
[SPEAKER_18]: It's like, you sit there for a minute before it goes back to green.
[SPEAKER_18]: That's annoying.
[SPEAKER_18]: Uh, and, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_18]: I get a laziness and so it's still hurting me from playing DDR or something.
[SPEAKER_18]: Laziness.
[SPEAKER_18]: Yeah, whatever.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Explicit.
[SPEAKER_21]: And just so you know, I told the chat room they have to keep it short, so you do too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, the FU's already announced what the marathon is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah, the marathon's, of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: Waking people, waking me up early in the morning.
[SPEAKER_11]: The fact that it got me 30 minutes late to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: And speaking of the marathon, I want to give an FU to some... I want to give an FU to some little, some teenager...
[SPEAKER_11]: I have something to say about that but I'll wait till later.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, you can say it now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everybody knows that girls and gays have no place in DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was not going to say that by just saying.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, two-thirds of this show is comprised of girls and gays, so I would watch a little mouth there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'm just saying, it's just DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's nothing special about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some people take it way too seriously in the forums.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright, is that it?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, FU2, upcoming finals coming up soon.
[SPEAKER_11]: FU2 for not being able to spend money for freaking Christmas because I have to spend some money on bills and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that's about it for now.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right, let's get to the chatroom FUs.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're mad at me because I told them they had to keep it short tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: They don't like that.
[SPEAKER_21]: But seriously, we've got like 20 people that send FUs in tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: We need to go ahead and read one, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, Jamie has one she wants to read first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'm actually on AAM right now, and I'm not telling anybody what name I'm on.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a FU from Vogue Obscurity.
[SPEAKER_05]: A big FU to our roommate M for eating all of our food and not buying anything and shipping ramps.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good sushi, Mike.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dark Knight would like to give a gigantic FU to me getting sick and working at the same time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Somebody shoot me please.
[SPEAKER_21]: And one more FU for my dumbness when I took my placement test during the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Talk about brain farts, man.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sigurd says, first FU goes to the show for not talking about drawn together nearly enough.
[SPEAKER_21]: Screw you.
[SPEAKER_21]: FU to Illusion for turning down offers of sex for his vote.
[SPEAKER_21]: And FU to Hot Topic for not having any drawn together shirts, even though they don't exist yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, think about it this way.
[SPEAKER_21]: If Illusion had changed his vote from Gwen to Monolithic, then it would have been a tie, and Jamie probably would have went with Monolithic when she broke the tie.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, just think about that one.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I wouldn't have.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, okay, well, hey.
[SPEAKER_21]: Flareon A says, F you to Nintendo for not allowing Game Boy and Game Boy Color games to be played on the DS.
[SPEAKER_21]: What the fuck?
[SPEAKER_21]: This just goes along with Nintendo's method of getting you to buy the same thing 50 million times.
[SPEAKER_21]: MPQ says, F you to Microsoft for not letting me install Japanese IME.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm having that same problem, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to Suncoast for ripping me off and charging me... What?
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_21]: Explicit what?
[SPEAKER_11]: You have to download a different patch, not the Global IME from Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, maybe that's what's going on.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, don't rely on the Global IME for that.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to Suncoast for ripping me off and charging me $30 a disc for Azumanga Daioh.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope I said that right.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to the Ty... What?
[SPEAKER_21]: What was that?
[SPEAKER_07]: You said it right, Azumanga Daioh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey, I pronounced something right.
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you know?
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to the Tyco Drumsticks for being uncomfortable and hurting my hands.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to people who call it singles and doubles on DDR.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not tennis.
[SPEAKER_21]: Lastly, fuck everyone who has access to 2DX.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's been singles and doubles since the first one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it might be the way in which you say it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think I might get what it is.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think I get the tennis comparison.
[SPEAKER_21]: Did I get the fuck everyone who has access to 2DX?
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Those are from MPQ.
[SPEAKER_21]: Poto says, F you to World of Warcraft, eating up every second of my life.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jaded2004 says F you to everyone who hates SmileDK Rychan says F you to myself for being emotionally stupid last night F you to egos killing the gaming star Hey, didn't I say that one?
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to tomorrow not being Thursday Aw, big hug Rychan, big hug Blarg says F you to
[SPEAKER_21]: Egalitarians?
[SPEAKER_21]: Egalitarians.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can pronounce words.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just have to sound it out in my mind.
[SPEAKER_21]: Misty says, first and foremost, F you to the cage match.
[SPEAKER_21]: Secondly, F you to chicken tenders and French toast sticks.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because I think I'm just pissed about that because I was working those parts of the kitchen at the time.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope I didn't close a new window.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hope I didn't miss somebody's F you.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry if I did.
[SPEAKER_21]: Snowcat says, F you to having a birthday in December and to people who think it's better to combine presents.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bastards.
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Ranma S says, Giant FU to my job for cutting my hours again.
[SPEAKER_21]: You bastards!
[SPEAKER_21]: I gotta eat too, you know.
[SPEAKER_21]: Another FU to the retard tech that I work with.
[SPEAKER_21]: You are a fucking tool.
[SPEAKER_21]: I swear, if you did get a job through Affirmative Action, I'm putting in my two weeks.
[SPEAKER_21]: FU short version.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, well, I read the long version.
[SPEAKER_21]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Legend of Zaku says, F you to not having a girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to all the drama that I have to put up with in the DDR Freak New York forums, thus resulting in the locking of the forums for a short time and the near split that was about to happen.
[SPEAKER_21]: And F you to the Chinese language for being so fucking hard to speak and write.
[SPEAKER_21]: I could say something about the New York forum thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: No comment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, I'll comment because I have no status on Freak, so it's fine for me to comment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Um...
[SPEAKER_21]: You guys need to learn how to respect authority!
[SPEAKER_21]: No, I'm not saying you in particular, but, I mean, it seems like when somebody says, don't do this, like, a million people want to do it, and then you wonder why people get angry!
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_20]: Films off the internet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm gonna get shit for that, but I don't care.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkTetsuya says, a continued FU to Comcast.
[SPEAKER_21]: I recently got to see the nuclear train wreck that is the new screensavers.
[SPEAKER_21]: I can tell the show's going down the toilet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, Rob, you said nuclear.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's a joke.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to Xbox Live on Ultramix 2 being so glitchy that we had to start the tournament over five times because it kept quitting and being glitchy.
[SPEAKER_21]: F you to the douchebags in my English class that don't have the brain capacity to talk about anything other than sports for more than five seconds at a time.
[SPEAKER_21]: And F you to Sigurd for cheating on me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Man, what a whore.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my.
[SPEAKER_21]: VxJasonXV, who says I should just call him Jason, but I don't, says F you to data entry, it makes us lazy people cry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Funny that I call myself lazy, although I'm writing a program to parse data for me automatically instead of taking less time to just do it myself.
[SPEAKER_21]: And F you to irony.
[SPEAKER_21]: And that's going to do it for the F yous of the week.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thanks for playing, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_20]: One last one.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck you, KFC, for getting rid of your sweet and sour sauce.
[SPEAKER_21]: Why would KFC get rid of sweet and sour sauce?
[SPEAKER_21]: Did PETA make them do that or something?
[SPEAKER_20]: They just got rid of their sweet and sour sauce!
[SPEAKER_20]: I got, uh, popcorn chicken, like, last week from there, and I was like, okay, I want some sweet- extra sweet and sour sauce, and I was like, oh, we don't have sweet and sour sauce.
[SPEAKER_20]: What?!
[SPEAKER_20]: What is this craziness?!
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't get it!
[SPEAKER_20]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_20]: Why- why would you- that was, like, the best sauce they had!
[SPEAKER_20]: Now they have ranch!
[SPEAKER_20]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_20]: Ranch!
[SPEAKER_20]: Ranch and mustard!
[SPEAKER_20]: Honey mustard!
[SPEAKER_20]: I want my fucking sweet and sour sauce.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's like classic.
[SPEAKER_20]: McDonald's has their sweet and sour sauce.
[SPEAKER_20]: Fuck, I eat the sweet and sour sauce by itself.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, I don't understand why you can't just give me the nice sweet and sour sauce you had.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'd buy up the reserves.
[SPEAKER_20]: I would.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think it's time to go to our break, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_21]: When we come back from this break, I think we'll do a little bit of Ask Orange Lounge and we'll open up the Skype line again for those of you guys who want to get through and comment.
[SPEAKER_21]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_21]: So send in your questions for Ask Orange Lounge over private message to Sky in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: In this break, I think we'll do some songs from 2DX.
[SPEAKER_21]: Just some 2DX potpourri.
[SPEAKER_21]: Enjoy.
... ... ...
Thanks for watching!
DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: We put your thing down, flip it, and reverse it.
[SPEAKER_21]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our chat room has gone crazy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I was making some jokes during the break there, and now everybody's talking about my pants.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I feel bad because there's a guy in there that really just needs a hug right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the talk about my pants and my name in various Bomani games is eclipsing that conversation.
[SPEAKER_21]: So, I feel bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, back to the dick and fart jokes we were talking about here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_21]: Actually, I wanted to bring something up that Explosive was talking about during his FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_21]: I felt kind of bad for this guy over on The Freak who had posted something in the NorCal forums.
[SPEAKER_21]: Are there any other gay people that play DDR?
[SPEAKER_21]: And people just kind of, like, jumped down this guy's throat going, It doesn't matter!
[SPEAKER_21]: Why are you posting this shit?
[SPEAKER_21]: It shouldn't matter!
[SPEAKER_21]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't mind that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_21]: More pants chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_21]: No, it doesn't.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I kind of feel bad for the guy because when you are gay, sometimes it is hard to meet people in the same way that straight people kind of meet each other.
[SPEAKER_21]: And especially if you're the kind of person that's had an upbringing where you've had to be very
[SPEAKER_21]: Hey girl, you wanna go out with me?
[SPEAKER_11]: But seriously, man, just, if you're gay, just talk to people, man.
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't matter if you're gay or not.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I just think, now, where I think the guy may have made a mistake is maybe DDR Freak just isn't, maybe the place, people want to talk DDR and DDR Freak, they don't want to talk about, you know, but I think he was just looking for gay people who are into DDR, so I PM'd him some links, because there's actually a live general community that's like gay DDR players, there's gay gamers, get it, gamers communities and stuff like that, so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, yeah, it's okay to post on the NorCal and stuff, but I mean, you see that all the time in DJR chit-chat and stuff and general discussion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you see, like, hundreds of topics like that, and...
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, yeah, and I agree.
[SPEAKER_21]: Now, it's almost, almost, it's very similar to the girls that play DDR topic, because for whatever reason, now, there's a difference, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's a difference.
[SPEAKER_21]: When it's a guy posting, are there any girls that play DDR?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's just, you know, somebody who's sitting there downloading Violent Hypergirls freestyle videos.
[SPEAKER_08]: Love you, Aaron.
[SPEAKER_21]: Love you, Aaron.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, uh...
[SPEAKER_21]: But when it's a girl posting, are there other girls that play DDR?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, then, you know, you're just kind of like, okay, well, maybe, you know, it's kind of too bad that there aren't a lot of girls that, you know, go out to the arcade.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I think DDR has been bringing more.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think there's been more and more, but just in the past.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's more and more now.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's more and more now, but especially when I first started playing, there wasn't a whole lot that I would see at the arcades.
[SPEAKER_21]: Back in the days before DDR, when I would play pinball, I maybe once or twice saw a girl at the arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: I only saw one girl back then, but now I see, like, a bunch of girls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I'm not sure if it's because of the FU tournament I helped organize in Sacramento or...
[SPEAKER_11]: or just the whole tournament issues nowadays that people want to get involved with.
[SPEAKER_20]: When I see girls posting that on the DDR Freak forums, I think, Ooh, lesbians!
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I think.
[SPEAKER_11]: Freak.
[SPEAKER_11]: Little girl, girl on girl mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: Jamie, do you have anything you want to add to this horrible discussion?
[SPEAKER_07]: Your pants are hot.
Shhh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Shove it.
[SPEAKER_20]: I know this is very late.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's another FU.
[SPEAKER_20]: FU to splitting my pants open this morning.
[SPEAKER_20]: That sucks.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was reaching for something and all of a sudden I hear this rip and there was my crotch exposed.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, speaking of rip.
[SPEAKER_20]: You know what that means, right?
[SPEAKER_20]: You're fat.
[SPEAKER_20]: Know what it means?
[SPEAKER_20]: It's that I was laying on my pants and trying to stretch at the same time.
[SPEAKER_20]: It does not mean I'm fat, you dumbass.
[SPEAKER_21]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you have something you want to say?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I'm not going to comment on Loki on that one.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well then fine, you're fat too.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, don't look fat.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just showed you my thugs, don't look fat.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're going to make me straight, God.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, you know there's a camera right there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, look at my thugs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, sorry if it scares people for that.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm changing the subject.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's ask Orange Lounge some stupid question What will we find out this week on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_21]: One thing we won't find out because he already said But Loki split his pants today, therefore he must be fat You know, the butcher's knife is still clean It's one of the only dishes that's not dirty yet
[SPEAKER_21]: Seegard has a question starting it off.
[SPEAKER_21]: This will make you feel better, Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: Who is your favorite drawn together character and why?
[SPEAKER_21]: Mine is Xander for obvious reasons.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mine is Nolan because I have a life and don't watch TV.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh my god, that's such a tough question.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh man.
[SPEAKER_20]: I would have to say Ling Ling.
[SPEAKER_20]: I love Ling Ling and just how funny and Japanese it is.
[SPEAKER_20]: And just like, it's more of like two characters.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's Spanky and Ling Ling.
[SPEAKER_20]: They're interactive, you know, interactions.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's the best part, you know.
[SPEAKER_20]: But Ling Ling's hilarious and... Are you looking forward to Christmas?
[SPEAKER_20]: Well, too bad there's no singles!
[SPEAKER_21]: But see, it was Xander who said that.
[SPEAKER_21]: I would say my second favorite, though, would be Foxy Love.
[SPEAKER_21]: I love Foxy Love.
Bleh.
[SPEAKER_20]: Bleh.
[SPEAKER_18]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Next question from MPQ.
[SPEAKER_21]: How many people care about the song Cartoon Heroes?
[SPEAKER_21]: It seems to me that people actually want the steps rather than the song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you think it would work if they took the steps and then put them on a 170 beat per minute Konami original or something?
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the one thing I can kind of see about Cartoon Heroes, why so many people want that song.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is it the steps?
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I don't think it would work on any other song.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, it would just be weird.
[SPEAKER_21]: But see, you're cutting out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's saying something about the fact that if it was a 7-footer, not as many people would play it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I somewhat disagree.
[SPEAKER_21]: I think there's people that play it because they play Speed Over Beethoven as well.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, that whole type of thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or we could say if the song was... Yeah, if it goes 140 BPM, then no one would play it at all.
[SPEAKER_11]: Think of the songs that are over here instead of BPM being overplayed.
[SPEAKER_21]: This is my thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: And this is the same thing when people ask, why aren't there enough 10-footers in DDR?
[SPEAKER_21]: Can you really play 10-footers on a homepad?
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, if you can and you're passing them, good for you.
[SPEAKER_21]: But you are in a minority.
[SPEAKER_21]: Let's face it, you are in the minority.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you can pass those kinds of songs on a homepad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do you think all songs must be 10-footer?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, let's go.
[SPEAKER_11]: Every freaking song.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why you can make edits.
[SPEAKER_11]: if you don't like the steps.
[SPEAKER_11]: Simple question.
[SPEAKER_11]: Or just play in the groove and just hammer the machine so much so your feet dies and shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, if there's one thing I'm not doing at home, it's hand plants.
[SPEAKER_21]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_11]: No fucking comment.
[SPEAKER_20]: Hand plants are so, like, 98.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hand plants are so ancient civilization.
[SPEAKER_11]: We don't go around kung, kung, kung.
[SPEAKER_11]: You don't need any more time to fight rape.
[SPEAKER_21]: Dark Knight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Everyone must be at the computer or on the webcam because all I see is Bradley.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our webcam kind of needs a new angle, I think, because obviously a lot of us kind of hide back here.
[SPEAKER_11]: He needs a spotlight.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we're angels kind of hiding back here.
[SPEAKER_21]: She's sitting on the ground next to Loki and I. And I see that Angel has candy, so I'm going to steal something.
[SPEAKER_11]: What the hell are you thinking?
[SPEAKER_11]: Wait, what?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it's in the forums.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's Matrix Walk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_20]: I don't want to bring up another FU, I just... Fucking Natalie Portman for not getting naked.
[SPEAKER_20]: I fucking hate that.
[SPEAKER_20]: You don't go see a movie... Okay, it's a fucking chick flick.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, granted, there are some very funny scenes in there, like the whole, um, uh, what was it, internet, um, like, net porn type thing sequence that they had to classical music.
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, that was funny.
[SPEAKER_20]: I grant, that was the best part in the whole movie.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, Natalie Portman was not fucking naked!
[SPEAKER_20]: They advertised this movie as her being naked!
[SPEAKER_20]: And she was not naked!
[SPEAKER_20]: Why?
[SPEAKER_20]: Why, why?
[SPEAKER_20]: So, she falls in the same category now as the Olsen twins.
[SPEAKER_20]: Whereas, she needs to do porn.
[SPEAKER_20]: I have the perfect answer and you will agree with me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Iron Chef America.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh God!
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we need more real Iron Chef.
[SPEAKER_05]: Iron Chef needs to come back on the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: The original.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: We need Michiba to come out of retirement.
[SPEAKER_05]: And kick all their asses.
[SPEAKER_21]: I absolutely agree.
[SPEAKER_21]: Iron Chef America.
[SPEAKER_21]: Bobby Flay is a fucking faggot.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hate him.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was gonna say, I was gonna say, don't insult faggots, please
[SPEAKER_21]: Legend of Zaku says, okay, my 2DX skills are what some would say subpar.
[SPEAKER_21]: How does one make the conversion from single-handed seven-key play to double-handed play so that when I go out to play 2DX again, I don't end up sucking?
[SPEAKER_21]: I think training mode on the home versions is really good, but you said you don't have training mode, so you're kind of screwed, buddy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I hate to say it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Honestly, you're just going to have to practice, practice, practice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcadian, you play a lot of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_21]: Do you have any advice you could give to our buddy Zaku, if we can hear you on that mic?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, practice.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the only thing you really do.
[SPEAKER_21]: There really is nothing else you can do.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no trick.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no wrist exercise or anything you can do.
[SPEAKER_21]: You've just got to practice.
[SPEAKER_21]: Play as many different songs and different levels as you can.
[SPEAKER_00]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: Play songs you don't usually play.
[SPEAKER_21]: Every time you go to play 2DX, make your last song something you've never played before that's about the same skill level, same star level.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the only way you're going to get better.
[SPEAKER_18]: Play things that are harder than you can do.
[SPEAKER_18]: I played the Anothers and everything when I first started out.
[SPEAKER_18]: Even though I couldn't even get near close to passing, I just...
[SPEAKER_21]: See them and try them out Sooner or later you can pass this part of your stuff Alright, let's move on Blarg says, who would you rather have sex with?
[SPEAKER_21]: God An 80 year old in an 8 year old's body Or an 8 year old in an 80 year old's body That's the point where I go to Goldies You know, actually I don't have to worry about it Yeah, you wouldn't have sex with a lady anyway
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless it was Margaret Cho, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would with Margaret Cho.
[SPEAKER_21]: Would you rather have sex with an 8-year-old in an 80-year-old's body or an 80-year-old in an 8-year-old's body?
[SPEAKER_03]: Margaret Cho.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well... I'd choose D. This is totally the Loki side of me.
[SPEAKER_21]: But if the 80-year-old was inside the 8-year-old's body, she'd be experienced and tight, so...
[SPEAKER_20]: No, but you have to understand.
[SPEAKER_20]: You have to understand the logistics of it, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: Would you rather play ball in a field that has short grass or a field that's just like turned to dust, okay?
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, you're going to have an unexperienced old chick.
[SPEAKER_20]: That's just nasty.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_20]: But, if you think about it,
[SPEAKER_20]: Not only are you robbing the cradle, but you're fucking getting some older action at the same time.
[SPEAKER_20]: So it's like, it's wrong.
[SPEAKER_21]: Topic change, real quick.
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Ranma S says, my question.
[SPEAKER_21]: As I was rudely interrupted earlier tonight, I missed half the show, but I could have sworn I heard Oduro Ponpokolin.
[SPEAKER_21]: Did I really hear that, and where can I find that song?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, you did hear Oduro Ponpokolin, and it is actually the version, let me play a little clip of that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oduro Ponpokolin
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, you did hear that.
[SPEAKER_21]: And DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_21]: DDR Festival is one of the songs in there.
[SPEAKER_21]: So pick up the Festival soundtrack, I guess, if there is one.
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think there is one yet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Or you can message Loki.
[SPEAKER_21]: He'll let you know where to find it.
[SPEAKER_20]: You have to find out DDR UK.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's very hard to find, though.
[SPEAKER_21]: Ranma S also says Sky.
[SPEAKER_21]: Similar stuff happens in the cosplay community.
[SPEAKER_21]: Points to my post in the chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: I missed it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry, buddy.
[SPEAKER_21]: You gotta send it over private message or I might miss it.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: What do you guys think about SongPack 7?
[SPEAKER_21]: Worth buying?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, because I think you should support DDR, and it's just five bucks.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, that's like, you know, lunch at Burger King.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: And the new remix is pretty kickass, and then you can play Era against me online, and Era's a good song.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you honestly are just not into the remix, we played it for you guys later tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: If you're just not feeling the I Feel remix...
[SPEAKER_21]: Then I guess maybe there isn't a whole lot for you to gain from this But I would say, you know what, buy it and just support DDR Because the more people that buy songpacks Yeah, this is what you get for coming late There's a new I Feel remix There's another FU, FU for being late Alright Okay, let's see Illusion says Jesus came to me and said he loved me so I kissed him I would like to ask your opinion if that was too forward
[SPEAKER_20]: Now, does that make him gay or Jesus gay?
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, maybe it was Jesus.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, you know, maybe it wasn't the Jesus.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe it was some guy named Jesus, you know?
[SPEAKER_20]: And if he returned back to Earth, I think we have more things to worry about than your kiss.
[SPEAKER_21]: You know, I think Jesus would have just said, thank you, and then ran away.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, he would forgive you for being a dirty homo sinner.
[SPEAKER_20]: You would have inevitably undone humanity because Jesus would then go to hell for being gay and a sinner.
[SPEAKER_20]: And yeah, Earth would end and humanity would go away.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_21]: Well, we don't have any more questions from our chat.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, no, I think we just got another one.
[SPEAKER_21]: But I am going to open up the Skype line here over on www.orangehunterradio.com.
[SPEAKER_21]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura says...
[SPEAKER_21]: I've been trying to dig up info on KR, Konami version, the Karaoke Revolution Konami version, but I only saw the small snippet on Konami's site.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is that all the info that's out there?
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, I have only been hearing about this secondhand, kind of, through Navi, the Poppin' Music Whore.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's been kind of following this.
[SPEAKER_21]: From what I understand...
[SPEAKER_21]: There is going to be a Karaoke Revolution Bomani version.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not in the US, okay?
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a Japanese mix.
[SPEAKER_21]: And I guess it's just going to be something that is happening.
[SPEAKER_21]: We don't know a whole lot about that, but there was questionnaires that happened already.
[SPEAKER_21]: And folks could fill out those questionnaires.
[SPEAKER_21]: But that's all we know right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: So there's nothing else we know that's going on with the Bomani edition as far as I know.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's all about Naha Naha Gachakun battle.
[SPEAKER_20]: That needs to be on there in duet mode.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm eating gummy bears right now.
[SPEAKER_20]: The fun thing you can do about these, you can bite them in half and lick one end of it and stick it to stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: And it will stick there for a long time.
[SPEAKER_20]: And if you stick it to someone's back window and they don't notice it, when they try to peel it off, it's all slimy because of all the moist air outside.
[SPEAKER_20]: It's really fun to do.
[SPEAKER_20]: So bite a gummy bear in half, stick it to your friend.
[SPEAKER_20]: How is that for random?
[SPEAKER_21]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_21]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess it's time to start wrapping up this show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: The show's just about... Oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel reminded me of something.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not so subtly.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, this is something I wanted to bring.
[SPEAKER_21]: I wanted to bring this up in the first hour of the show, and I totally forgot.
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel went and got a Happy Meal at McDonald's today.
[SPEAKER_21]: There's no shame in a Happy Meal at the Happy Meals.
[SPEAKER_00]: I saw Sonic and I'm like, hmm, maybe it's a figurine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's a Sonic Happy Meal.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess they teamed up with Sonic the Hedgehog to do these Sonic Happy Meals at McDonald's right now.
[SPEAKER_21]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_21]: She got a free little game with hers.
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, these are the kind of games like Mr. Game & Watch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Tiger Toys!
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, the Tiger Toys.
[SPEAKER_21]: You remember these?
[SPEAKER_21]: These used to be the things we would get for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_21]: These shitty little, like, watch games that we would get for Christmas as a kid.
[SPEAKER_21]: And now they're coming in freaking Happy Meals, and it's a little Sonic one.
[SPEAKER_21]: And it's basically a ghetto version of the bonus stage from Sonic 2.
[SPEAKER_21]: My God, this is a Happy Meal toy.
[SPEAKER_21]: I remember when we used to get shitty little wind-up toys and little plushy things and fucking Beanie Babies with Happy Meals.
[SPEAKER_21]: And now we get freaking video games with Sonic.
[SPEAKER_21]: And when did Sonic start making a comeback in the U.S.?
[SPEAKER_21]: That's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: I guess I've just been asleep.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_21]: He's got the cartoon.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, so I've just been asleep.
[SPEAKER_21]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_21]: I mean, Sonic's cool and all, so I'm glad that they're doing the Happy Meal thing.
[SPEAKER_21]: But, man, you get a freaking...
[SPEAKER_21]: Game?
[SPEAKER_21]: Like, this is the kind of stuff we would open up on Christmas Day and be excited about, and now you get it in a freaking Happy Meal.
[SPEAKER_21]: What's up with that?
[SPEAKER_21]: Is there something you wanted to add to that, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_21]: You're a Sonic fan.
[SPEAKER_21]: Is this cool?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I just like to thread.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: I understand how cool the free iPods are, but don't start a thread about it!
[SPEAKER_03]: God, people...
[SPEAKER_20]: They're giving them away for free.
[SPEAKER_20]: Does that tell you anything about how crappy they are?
[SPEAKER_20]: They're free!
[SPEAKER_20]: They can toss them away!
[SPEAKER_20]: Sad.
[SPEAKER_21]: I love my iPod.
[SPEAKER_21]: You shut your mouth.
[SPEAKER_21]: We gotta wrap up the show, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_21]: Next week on the show, more randomness.
[SPEAKER_21]: In two weeks, I'm gonna be going to AI, Arcade Infinity.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm making an LA trip.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm hoping!
[SPEAKER_21]: I may not get to go for sure, but that's kind of what I'm trying to do is go to Arcade Infinity probably next Thursday.
[SPEAKER_21]: Not this coming Thursday, but next Thursday.
[SPEAKER_21]: So I hope to see some of you guys there.
[SPEAKER_21]: Our stalker fans.
[SPEAKER_21]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_21]: And my goal is to get a whole bunch of EMUs cards and get them way on the show to those less fortunate who can't get them.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we'll see what happens with that.
[SPEAKER_21]: Anyway, next week on the show, more of the same stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm going to try and line up an interview for next week's show.
[SPEAKER_21]: I want to interview somebody again.
[SPEAKER_21]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, this week's going to be a crazy week, and my work's not going to be too happy with me taking off another day on Thursday, but... What the hell with them?
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_20]: Actually, the... Ah, fuck, that sucks!
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm supposed to get my check on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, well, I'll have to wait.
[SPEAKER_20]: We get our bonuses next week, so that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_20]: But I have to buy gifts, and I think Nelly wants diamonds again, and, you know... Fucking women and their expensive gifts.
[SPEAKER_20]: Anyways... Yeah, that's all.
[SPEAKER_20]: Nick!
[SPEAKER_21]: Angel, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brock's Candy Company needs to be sued.
[SPEAKER_21]: For?
[SPEAKER_04]: Making these things damn good.
[SPEAKER_04]: God.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maple nut goodies.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're really good.
[SPEAKER_21]: They're very good.
[SPEAKER_21]: I've been snacking on it all night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcadia, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_18]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_18]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_18]: I only had one piece of sushi last night.
[SPEAKER_18]: I need more!
[SPEAKER_18]: More sushi!
[SPEAKER_21]: I don't think Anita's listening anymore, but you need to go bang down her door.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't really need her.
[SPEAKER_18]: Unless she wants to make some more, that'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sushi from somewhere.
[SPEAKER_18]: Sushi's wonderful.
[SPEAKER_19]: We need, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie!
[SPEAKER_18]: Sushi night.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_21]: You're off Atkins now, so we need a sushi night.
[SPEAKER_19]: Or sushi lunch.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sushi lunch would be better.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'm still not eating sugars at night.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm teaching, so it may be difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Weekend.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh, yeah, I think that works.
[SPEAKER_21]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_19]: One more thought.
One more thought.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was thinking the other day.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is very important, so everyone pay attention.
[SPEAKER_20]: We haven't done a QZAR night in a while.
[SPEAKER_20]: We need to do one again.
[SPEAKER_20]: So I'll
[SPEAKER_20]: Check on the forums, or not the forums, but check on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_20]: There will be a new QZernite, and we will reign supreme again!
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_21]: Explicit, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, if I wanted to get to work early, I should have just ran every fucking marathon runner over, GTA style.
[SPEAKER_21]: All right.
[SPEAKER_21]: My final thought is thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_21]: And tune in to our spinoff shows, damn you, because we need more people to listen to that because they're cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: And we're almost to the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_21]: There might be big changes coming to Orange Lounge Radio in 2005, which reminds me, we need to have a staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_21]: I know we don't ever have staff meetings, but we need to have a staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Maybe that can be the sushi lunch, even though Loki doesn't eat sushi.
[SPEAKER_05]: We can go to a multiple place.
[SPEAKER_21]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: We can go to a place that has teriyaki, too.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_21]: We need to have a staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_21]: Staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_21]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate my allergies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate your allergies too.
[SPEAKER_03]: My allergies hit you back, so yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_21]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_21]: Final word of the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'll give to Angel, why not?
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it, Brox.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_16]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_16]: And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hanukkah is the festival of lights Instead of one day of presents, we get eight crazy nights But when you feel like the only kid in town without a Christmas tree Here's a new list of people who are Jewish
[SPEAKER_08]: Just like you and me!
[SPEAKER_08]: A known writer drinks Manischewitz wine Then spins a dreidel with Ralph Lauren and Calvin Klein Guess who gives and receives loads of Hanukkah toys?
[SPEAKER_08]: the girls from Baruch Assault and all three beastie boys Lenny Kravitz is half Jewish Courtney Lovitz half Jew put them together what a funky badass show
[SPEAKER_08]: Jessica Biel, Yasmin Blade from Baywatch is Jewish, and yes, her boobs are real.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello, Natty Yamaka, Shy Monica, Two-time Oscar winner Dustin Hoff Monica, Celebrate Monica.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Jay Simpson, still not a Jew.
[SPEAKER_08]: But guess who is the guy who does the voice for Scooby-Doo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Rob Dylan was born a Jew, then he wasn't, but now he's back Mary Tyler Moore's husband is Jewish, cause we're pretty good in the sack Guess who got barbed spit on the PTA tour?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not talking about Tiger Woods, I'm talking about Mr. Happy Gilmore
[SPEAKER_08]: So many Jews are in the show business.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bruce Springsteen isn't Jewish, but my mother thinks he is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tell the world of Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's time to celebrate Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not for now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shanukkah, the sea is silent in Hanukkah.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.