Come on, let's go!
Live as if you're the winner
[SPEAKER_11]: We're glad as long as we're gonna be
[SPEAKER_20]: The following live program is a special presentation of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
Oh, God.
Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_22]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_21]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
We are live!
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is episode number 123 for this December the 19th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: Believe it or not, making this the last show before Christmas, if you can believe it or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_05]: You might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_05]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know her better, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm still bleeding out of my thumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're bleeding?
[SPEAKER_11]: Out of my thumb.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be an ER edition tonight.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, get the antibiotics!
[SPEAKER_05]: Have you ever seen that real emergency trauma show, but the one with pets?
[SPEAKER_15]: Do I ever watch TV?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I figured you might watch that.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you have time for Iron Chef, you have time for this.
[SPEAKER_15]: I download my Iron Chef, and I'm pissed off about Supernova.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're all a little pissed off about Supernova, but I have the answer.
[SPEAKER_05]: When we get back, we'll talk about that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us tonight, Tech Massa, Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Not!
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki is at a holiday gathering tonight for his family, so he may come in a little bit later, but...
[SPEAKER_05]: We all know he may not be here.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's got no pressure to come back at any particular time.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember when Loki used to be here every single night for like two years, religiously?
[SPEAKER_05]: And I mean every single night.
[SPEAKER_15]: He was here for the second episode and I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: I remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us tonight, we do have a special guest able to fill in for the absence of a third co-host.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, I will not be as angsty as him, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe for once, this is what it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're listening to the kindler, gentler Orange Songs Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Holiday Cheery Edition.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh wait, Jamie's still here, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is gonna be weird, because tonight I'm outnumbered by women.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're still gamers, so what's your point?
[SPEAKER_00]: Girls play games?
[SPEAKER_15]: I did nothing but play games for the past three days in a row, okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: And it was all Phantasy Star Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is a good segue into how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get into that all a little bit more in a little bit, but first we're going to take a quick break featuring the mandatory song you know we have to play tonight, but we're only going to play it once this week, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because too many of you bitched last week, but because it is Christmas week here, we have to play it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You already know.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you don't know what song I'm talking about, you obviously haven't been playing DDR very long.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're here to help you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Noob!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do I smell a noobie?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back after this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, join our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangesonstrator.com Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Night is nightfall
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: The chat room was demanding more Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, here you go.
and more.
Thanks for watching!
It's got to be forever, the raindrops blowing, the wind is dancing
[SPEAKER_11]: It would be a much better fight With you, with me If you hadn't let me I'd be fine on my own, baby Never felt so lonely Then you came along So now what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm strong out, addicted to you My body aches, now that you're gone My supplies fell through And you let me give me everything
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 123 on your radio right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I apologize to you guys if you're hearing a little bit of a buzz in the background tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of our cords, I think, is a little bit stripped, so we've got to get it replaced, and I think that stripping is causing the buzz.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll look into getting that replaced before the new year.
[SPEAKER_05]: But for tonight, you're going to have to deal with it, so I apologize.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so here we are.
[SPEAKER_05]: Almost at the end of 2004.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just when I was finally remembering to write 04 on my checks instead of 03, the damn year's almost over, and now I'm going to have to start writing 05, or I'm really going to be screwed.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, what's first?
[SPEAKER_05]: Presence, or how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: Presence!
[SPEAKER_05]: Presence first?
[SPEAKER_05]: You mean we're going to make an exception?
[SPEAKER_05]: Presence!
[SPEAKER_05]: The rule that we always do?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, presents are, you know... Okay, now...
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I know, Loki ran away.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get him back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki came home, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki came home during the break, so I don't know if he's going to be involved in this show tonight or if he's going to be kind of in and out or whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: But he's here, and he's trying to get our webcam up and running as well over on OrangeLaunchRadio.com, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_15]: He says it's up and running.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's not on the website yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got to turn on the switch on the website.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also joining us tonight, we have Arcadian42 came in during the break.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know it's 6.30, buddy, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we have a mic for Arcadian?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there another mic over there?
[SPEAKER_14]: There should be another mic over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: There should be.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: We get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Under the rubble.
[SPEAKER_05]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's under the big Christmas present montage there we have all of Loki's presents.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, I'd just like to point out I have not started my shopping yet.
[SPEAKER_05]: So even though we are going to be doing a little bit of gifts tonight, it just makes Christmas last longer if I don't give my gifts until next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what you're calling it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, well, I'm not going to break my Christmas tradition of doing all my shopping on Christmas Eve.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop the day after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or that.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's even better, honestly.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's why I've been telling everyone to get me gift cards.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, gift cards are awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I can take advantage of them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't I get you a gift card last year?
[SPEAKER_15]: I think you did.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think you're probably going to get another one this year because they're the easiest presents to buy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: I went the day after Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a good gift to get.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, presents.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then, Jamie, you better go first.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's this first present you have here?
[SPEAKER_15]: This is something from Angel.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think it's like a couple of 40s.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's about...
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a bigger than a bread box.
[SPEAKER_15]: Lengthwise, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie has to guess her present in 20 questions or less or we're going to smash it in front of everybody.
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'll guess after I open it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's beer.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, while Jamie is opening her gift,
[SPEAKER_05]: We have a request from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: At some point tonight... Oh, what'd you get, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: It's a Coco mug set with teddy bears on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Aw, hot Coco.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's precious.
[SPEAKER_05]: And so Angel's standing there going, see, Jamie needs a little more cute once in a while.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's very cute.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ooh, Irish cream.
[SPEAKER_15]: It makes me happy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Our chat room over at Orangetownradio.com, clicking on chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're requesting that at some point tonight, in his best Christmas voice, that Loki says, God bless us, everyone!
[SPEAKER_05]: In his best Tiny Tim voice.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's when hell freezes over.
[SPEAKER_05]: At some point tonight, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all they want for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sure you can do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I'm going next.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to open... Angel got me two things.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which one should I open first, Angel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I'm going to do this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which happens to be the same size as the one that Jamie got me.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm going to scream if it's the same thing I got you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Open Jamie's first.
[SPEAKER_05]: So you can still give this to somebody while it's still wrapped, just in case, right Angel?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then I'm going to open Jamie's first at Angel's request.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope it's a severed head.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a little flat for a severed head.
[SPEAKER_25]: Maybe you put it in a blender.
[SPEAKER_15]: Parade head.
[SPEAKER_25]: You like tape, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, I suck at gift wrapping, so bite me.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is the worst paper ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, is this a Final Fantasy XI soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: What a cool... Oh, that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you know I'm an addict and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that the same thing you got, Angel?
It is?
[SPEAKER_15]: I have been looking at that for three months.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I knew three months ago that's what I was going to buy for you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, poor Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you...
[SPEAKER_05]: I guess I'm easy to shop for, yet at the same time very difficult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, thank you both.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a very, very nice thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going to be able to do something with that, right, Angel?
Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: She says sure.
[SPEAKER_13]: He has no idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to open this.
[SPEAKER_05]: A present from Angel, and it's in a, like, trapezoid-style box.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I can see is limited guarantee.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I need that, don't I?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a Jenny Craig gift pack.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's a case for the DS.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good, because I need one of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ah, because I travel so damn much.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a traveling case for the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, sure!
[SPEAKER_05]: She was totally fucking with me
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, I was just looking at this yesterday and I almost bought it.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is so funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Ping Pals for the DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a whole DS.
[SPEAKER_05]: It looks like a Pokemon-style game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I couldn't figure it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, what is this game about?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a mix between Pokemon and... What am I trying to say?
[SPEAKER_13]: Tamagotchi, kind of.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wanted to check this out, so that's good.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give a hug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel hug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though I have headphones on, so I can't really move.
[SPEAKER_05]: Long distance hug.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can you feel the love here on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so excited.
[SPEAKER_05]: I love Final Fantasy XI music too.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_15]: I figured that that would be something you'd really dig.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, okay, Loki has seven in his present now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, I just want to say, this is like my favorite artwork in all of Final Fantasy XI, by the way, is that world map that's drawn all artistic style.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Amano.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I could get a huge poster of that.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's Amano's art.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's so sexy.
[SPEAKER_15]: He did all, because I used to use one of those wallpapers when I, for the short time I played.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to put this up on the webcam.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll put all the presents up on the webcam at some point during the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: www.orangelingerator.com Loki's turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, Loki, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki is opening a present from Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was a bitch to wrap.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a Grim Reaper slash toy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, Jamie has given Loki death for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_15]: I tried to get a cupcake to put with him so I could give you death cake, but I didn't have time.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would have been killer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't he cute?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a happy little holiday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and another one for Loki from Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see what this is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is it another Iraqi suicide baby?
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a
[SPEAKER_05]: It's an amazing pooping reindeer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nellie's infatuated with the pooping reindeer, apparently.
[SPEAKER_05]: And you can eat the poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you going to give Nellie the poop?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, she can have the poop.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to put this all on the webcam so you guys can see during the next break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll get to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or actually, I'll walk over there right now while Jamie... Don't give me Happy Jones Soda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that all the gifts?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, there'll be more gifts next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, we're going to just find a way to get it to you anyway, DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a whole week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go back to how we start off every show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We got a little sidetracked, but presents are a good reason to sidetrack.
[SPEAKER_15]: I like presents.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to start off tonight's show playing a little bit of How Was Your Week, How Was Your Day?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, my week was all, I was just feeling really stressed out and crappy all week.
[SPEAKER_15]: I went to my last day of class on Monday.
[SPEAKER_15]: I found out that I made a B in my business law class.
[SPEAKER_15]: I made a 390 out of 400 in my Excel class, so I have a very solid A in that class.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, yeah, I made like a hundred on my final and they, uh, full points on my final project too.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, I'm all happy and excited about that.
[SPEAKER_15]: That means I have like a 3.2 something GPA for the semester.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um...
[SPEAKER_15]: I paid 300 and something dollars for my next classes, which kind of sucked.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I was really, really stressed out all week and really exhausted.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then finally, Thursday, I just collapsed at work.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was all, you know, totally lacking in energy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I ended up going home after half a day.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I tried, because I was just really sick.
[SPEAKER_15]: and then I felt better the next day so I got up to go back to work and only managed to stay three hours before I had to come home again and I did nothing then but sleep and play Phantasy Star online for the past three days nothing but that so yeah, I'm back to playing PSO I'm not an addict because I don't really want to play anymore for some time I basically went, I made it to level 41 in three days
[SPEAKER_15]: We're trying to get me to Ultimate so I have 40 more levels to go.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, that's really all I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: We went to this place called Crickets on Auburn yesterday.
[SPEAKER_15]: That my friends were up and down was going to be like the best breakfast place ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it was just ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: My French toast was just egg and milk on bread.
[SPEAKER_15]: And like I saw them put plates on top of full plates of food.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_15]: And my potatoes were cold.
[SPEAKER_15]: They were nice there, but it was just kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I wouldn't recommend anybody go there.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm not going there again.
[SPEAKER_15]: But it made my day really grumpy yesterday.
[SPEAKER_15]: I was really grumpy yesterday.
[SPEAKER_15]: Until I had a breakfast burrito, and that made it all better.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I played Phantasy Star Online for about six hours.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's all I did.
[SPEAKER_15]: PSO and sleep.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds very similar to a lot of my weekends.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds very similar to a lot of my weekends, but with a different game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Eggnog is so good.
[SPEAKER_15]: Baskin Robbins Eggnog Ice Cream.
[SPEAKER_05]: And brand name, even.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they have pumpkin pie ice cream, too.
[SPEAKER_15]: This guy has a bony ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you just make the Christmas reindeer poop on your girlfriend's head?
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to put that thing on the cam.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go put that on... Make it poop in her mouth.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Make it poop in her mouth.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's hot.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR Angel, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_13]: Good, I had finals on Wednesday, and, um, tried to start my shopping in the middle of the week, but that thing didn't exactly go so well, so I guess I started on, what, Friday?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, Friday, I believe it was Friday, or Saturday or something.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, um, I got sucked into the world in which, um, well, at least three of the people in here are hooked into.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, Final Fantasy XI, yay me.
[SPEAKER_13]: I got my hat!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_05]: Even I haven't done that fucking Santa hat quest yet.
[SPEAKER_15]: Insert word here.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's okay, I had a bajillion Santa hats on RO.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they doing those Christmas wrappy things again?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, they're doing the Christmas present ones.
[SPEAKER_15]: But I've been trying to get a Christmas present so I can get the heart of Opa Opa.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I have, what Julie gave me as part of my Christmas present on PSO is I have an Opa Opa mag.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to tell you about the nerdiest thing you've ever heard in a little bit about an online game and Christmas events.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I've got to say, the Christmas event in Final Fantasy XI this year, not as good as last year's.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last year's was awesome.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was kind of fun on RO going around beating up Santa Claus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, sorry Angel to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not much, just, you know, the Santa hat thing was like the last thing I wanted to say.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, the funniest thing part of this week, and it happened yesterday.
[SPEAKER_13]: Miklatov, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sigurd, totally ran past me in Winders.
[SPEAKER_13]: He didn't even know it was me, and I had to page him.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, hey!
[SPEAKER_13]: He's like, hi!
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, yeah, you just ran past me.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's like, I did?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm like, yeah, you did.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyway, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, in Final Fantasy XI, sometimes if you're in a crowded area, the characters don't load all the same.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, if you go into Lower Juno, I don't know if you've been there yet, but there's so many people there that it takes a while for everybody to load.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I spent five minutes chasing him.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then he kind of got the hint.
[SPEAKER_13]: He's like, oh.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go over to Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_05]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you must have had a busy day.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had one more thing that happened.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did we cut you off earlier?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, but I had one more thing that happened.
[SPEAKER_25]: Is that your DS?
[SPEAKER_25]: This is my DS.
[SPEAKER_25]: How many freaking people have to bring their DSs to the show?
[SPEAKER_25]: I always keep mine in my laptop case.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_25]: So I can play it at work.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: I ordered my Christmas present from Dan today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which is?
[SPEAKER_15]: Beatmania 2DXA style, and the Parappa clapping game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you know, do you know I just, we're going to talk about this a little later, but you could have ordered another game on PlayAsia, which just started taking orders.
[SPEAKER_15]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll talk about it in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, today I went to my dad's house and we had food.
[SPEAKER_24]: and um what else did I do this week oh I went and saw Lemony Sick it's a series of unfortunate events and that was awesome and I play a lot of Final Fantasy and Christmas Shopping and yeah that's pretty much all I did just Christmas crap trying to get it done and then I got
[SPEAKER_24]: Mr. Bradley, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_24]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_24]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_24]: Did work and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Got 8th style like the week before, and didn't play it again until Friday and Saturday, and some today.
[SPEAKER_06]: And did alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually passed V for the first time ever.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Though I don't know if it's easier timing or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: I almost passed Nebula Grasper, but the first time I played it, and it killed me the rest of the time.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, uh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: and a Christmas party at work on Friday.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nothing did not much today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Congratulations on beating V. I still can't do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too tough.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's too hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: But of course, I haven't played 2DX seriously in a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I really, really need to get 8-style, and I will one of these days.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I spent part of the week in L.A., which is why there was no Outside the Box this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was actually in L.A.
[SPEAKER_05]: the second half of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was on a business trip.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I must say, I had a really just awesome time, but it was really busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: We just went everywhere, and we were just busy nonstop.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I actually got homework in the class, which was kind of weird, considering it was training, but that's what happens when you're on salary.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then Saturday, I was hoping to go to the SVGL3 tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I didn't end up going because I was just so damn tired and I had to do errands with my parents and all this other stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I didn't end up going.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sorry, Angel, because I know you wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But she seems okay with it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm sorry to everybody out there who was hoping to, or I should say I was hoping to run into it at Spiegel 3.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I just got beat out by wanting to sit at home and just recuperate, so that's exactly what I did.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I played a lot of Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: In fact, what ended up happening is that Saturday, here's that nerdy thing I was talking to you about.
[SPEAKER_05]: My link shell in Final Fantasy XI, you know that's the group that you belong to, we all met up and we had a level one foot race, which means we took a level one character and took them to the most difficult areas of the game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in the lead.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was in the lead, so I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said he was in the lead, so he got taken out.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we had, get this, a Final Fantasy XI gift exchange once we all got to Juno.
[SPEAKER_05]: We all had a secret person we were supposed to buy gifts for, so we had a secret Santa in Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got a plus one silver hairpin and a dagger.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is the nerdiest thing, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't get anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I know you did, and I think I know who has you too, but it's just that our little shellmaster, or I shouldn't say shellmaster, but event organizer, because Loki's the shellmaster, but our event organizer needs to get up off her ass and get the rest of the gifts distributed to those that weren't here, so that's what'll happen.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's my nerdy Final Fantasy XI story.
[SPEAKER_05]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody else have anything they want to add about their week, their day?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got new contacts.
[SPEAKER_05]: New contacts!
[SPEAKER_05]: Are they a different color?
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't look like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they're not tinted because they're not IQB2s now.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've got some different kind that helps correct for astigmatism or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So is everything a little clearer now?
[SPEAKER_05]: How many fingers am I holding up?
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it back to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got it back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, we're such great radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is great.
[SPEAKER_05]: What have we done tonight that's been great radio bits?
[SPEAKER_05]: How many fingers am I holding up?
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a great radio bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Poop in my mouth, that's a really good radio bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's a really great radio event.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's play radio charades.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is why they laugh at our faces at E3 and go, Internet radio for games?
[SPEAKER_05]: You losers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm going to poop in your mouth at E3, alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: I see how you like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we have some big Bobani news this week.
[SPEAKER_05]: NightStyle
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
and many more.
Thanks for watching!
DarkSakura!
DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_23]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, and we've been playing PictoChat during the break because we're such dorks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really have a better explanation other than that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you've been keeping an eye on our webcam, www.orangeloungeradio.com, I did put up a picture of the pooping reindeer during the break there, as well as a little glimpse of PictoChat.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wait, what'd you find out, Ellie?
[SPEAKER_25]: How do you shove the poop back in their ass?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why don't you go back to Loki's room and see what else you can shove up there?
[SPEAKER_05]: Go to hell.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, as we alluded to before we went to the break there,
[SPEAKER_05]: We do have Beatmania 2DX Nightstyle somewhat announced for release and I say somewhat announced because basically all they really have to go off of right now I should say all we really have to go off of right now is a website that Konami of Japan has.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually Konami Broadcasting and they have this page which appears to be listing some of their new releases and on March 24th of 2005 they have listed Beatmania 2DX Nightstyle which means Nightstyle looks like
[SPEAKER_05]: That's all we need is confirmation that 9th style will be coming out at home for sure, which is really good because basically we've had, what, 7th style, 8th style, and now 9th style all within... I mean, we had to go, like, a long time, like, probably, what, a year and a half with no new 2DX releases at least, and then suddenly 7th style, 8th style, 9th style, and probably 10th style are all going to come out back-to-back-to-back.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, well, not back-to-back, literally, but, you know, within a pretty good distance of each other, so this is pretty exciting, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you guys excited about this news?
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think about it?
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to come stand on a mic, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think of this news, Angel?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I like it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie is back to present her opinion.
[SPEAKER_15]: As long as it doesn't have the shit timing problems.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, as long as it's not that problem, then it's cool.
[SPEAKER_15]: It'd be an improvement over the arcade.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, basically... Sorry, we're having a little bit of sound issues here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Those same problems I was talking about when the show started with the stripped... Stripped wires causing us to have a little bit of issue here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to get that cord replaced for next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sorry, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, I think I see exactly where the problem is, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Play nice!
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, obviously... 2DX and the arcade had a little bit of...
[SPEAKER_05]: I think the question on everybody's mind is, is it going to be fixed for the home release, or would they keep it arcade accurate so that people who practice at home can take it to the arcade, or what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Any thoughts from a technical perspective, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I know you probably don't even care about this game, but I just thought I'd get your opinion anyway.
[SPEAKER_24]: That would be an accurate assumption.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, then tell me what you think.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, it's a new game, yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: I have a pretzel.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, the timing problems in Night Style are enough to make you despise this game, Jamie, or what's the deal?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, after seeing how bad the timing problems were, I swore I'd never play Night Style, and I haven't.
[SPEAKER_05]: But do you think you're going to make an exception for the home release?
[SPEAKER_15]: If the home release doesn't have the timing problems, then I'll buy it.
Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I just know I'm looking forward to with Nightstyle the new songs because Nightstyle has probably one of my favorite song lists of any
[SPEAKER_05]: 2DX Style, really, I think it had my most favorite song list since at least 6th style, probably, maybe since 5th, I don't know, but 9th style had just so many great songs on it that I love, and I can't wait to play it at home, because I really only played 9th style in the arcade, myself personally, I think I only played 9th style in the arcade like one time, two times, I think two times is the most times I played 9th style in the arcade, and really when I went and played 10th style, I pretty much only played 9th style songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was kind of one of those losers that just played those.
[SPEAKER_25]: I played Gradius.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, that's a 10-style song, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not a 9-style song.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just couldn't play on that 10-style machine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm excited because since we had so many consumer songs and... Don't mess with the sound right now because we're... Wait for a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We had so many new songs on consumer-style aid that it's going to be interesting to see if we get as many on 9-style as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys hoping to see a lot of new consumer tracks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or you just want it to be arcade accurate?
[SPEAKER_05]: Bring back a lot of old songs?
[SPEAKER_05]: Or what?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any feelings on that?
[SPEAKER_15]: I want it to have no timing problems.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want it to play like 8th style.
[SPEAKER_05]: You don't care what the hell's in it, as long as it's...
[SPEAKER_15]: As long as it has no timing problems.
[SPEAKER_05]: As long as it has no timing problems.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because I want to play Lion Suki.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to see more of the ghetto fabulous dancers, like in that one song, the 8th style consumer song that has... I miss the 4th style booty dancers.
[SPEAKER_05]: To bring those back?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Geary Geary Daddy dancers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who are the ones that look like the fembots in the one video in... Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't remember the name of the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody will get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm just happy that my 8th style is going to be here at the end of the week.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I can play dancer.
[SPEAKER_05]: So as you were saying before, you went ahead and you ordered your 8th style.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I got a little private message in the chat room over here saying DarkLionXVI says that actually over on PlayAsia right now, you can pre-order 9th style if you're so inclined.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not going to pre-order it until I know that the issues are fixed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't Be Afraid Myself is what they're saying it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like Love Something was the name of the song.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't Be Afraid Myself had the girls dancing in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the one, yeah, that's the one that's like the, I don't know, the pop video.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm talking about the one that had the... They were dancing in a damn locker room shower.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I'm not, that's not the one I'm thinking of.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm thinking of the one where they're all dressed up in the hippie stuff and they were driving through Tokyo and stuff or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why can't I think of the name of that song?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm looking it up right now because I'm so pissed I can't think of what that song is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Love Box!
[SPEAKER_05]: Love Box.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the song I was trying to think of.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got a pretty dirty title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, Nelly's snickering over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He said box.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, so most folks are going to be pretty excited about Night Style.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, as soon as we know more information about the game, we will be presenting it to you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's funny, looking in the chatroom, they're going, Lovebox, Lovebox, fucking Lovebox, god damn.
[SPEAKER_05]: You have to remember, guys, you're on a buffer.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're about 30, 45 seconds behind everything, so... Losers.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, I guess what we'll do is we're going to take another quick break because it looks like we're working on some sound issues in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to do a quick break, some more 2DX9 style songs since we're so excited about this.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we come back, maybe we'll take some calls over the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Also, at some point tonight, we've got to do a new list list.
[SPEAKER_05]: We have to have a cage match tonight at some point.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we'll listen to Jamie Belch some more.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's your fault.
[SPEAKER_15]: You gave me the soda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you're right.
[SPEAKER_15]: This is the best stuff in the world.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's all my fault.
[SPEAKER_15]: Sugar-free junk soda.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll be back after this, you guys.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be right back after some more music here on Orange Lounge Radio.
and more.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio With the Ping Pong Balls We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio And it looks like we actually fixed some of the sound We replaced a cord So Loki was kind enough to do a little switcheroo there during the break Swapped a cord out So hopefully that'll minimize those sound issues we've been having I notice the buzz is still there a little bit But it doesn't sound as bad in my monitor here So we'll see
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank God!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hooray for Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: This is why we call him the Techmaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the chatroom during that break, they were complaining, or I shouldn't say complaining, but they were talking about some of the different Night Style songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do you have a favorite Night Style song?
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though the timing pushes you off, is there a favorite Night Style song you have?
[SPEAKER_15]: All of the Taku songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, uh, what, Distress and, uh, Lower World?
[SPEAKER_05]: Distress, I'd have to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Lower World.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell am I thinking?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd have to say, actually, Distress is the best.
[SPEAKER_15]: And, of course, I'd do, like, Lionski.
[SPEAKER_05]: My favorite song in 9th style is Power Dream, because I love ping pong.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's another one that I liked, but I don't remember the name of it, because I didn't really keep up too much with 9th style.
[SPEAKER_05]: And of course, Bad Boy Bass.
[SPEAKER_15]: Everyone is something, I don't remember the song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: What we're going to do now is we're actually going to talk to somebody over the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody actually called and said they had something they wanted to talk to us about, so we're going to go ahead and pick up the Skype line here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just told them to give us a call here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, and who is this?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Sherlock, how are you?
[SPEAKER_19]: How are you doing today?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm good!
[SPEAKER_05]: For those of you folks who don't know, Sherlock, one of the moderators over on DDR Freak, which by the way, DDR Freak, kind enough to replay Orange Lounge Radio Friday nights.
[SPEAKER_15]: And he has the best hat ever.
[SPEAKER_05]: That hat is sexy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've seen pictures of the hat and I think I saw the hat from a distance at E3.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was kind of like going to a rock concert.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like, you know, I think I can kind of make it out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I can kind of make out that person.
[SPEAKER_19]: You can almost see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can almost see it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what's on your mind, Sherlock?
[SPEAKER_19]: I found something online that kind of confused me a bit, but it also made me just spin my head, and it really just threw me for a turn.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's DDR-related.
[SPEAKER_19]: and uh... A lot of DDR things kind of make me question myself sometimes, but... Yeah, I mean, you know, everyone keeps talking about, you know, is DDR dead?
[SPEAKER_19]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_19]: You know, the whole April Fool's thing, you know, put everyone in for a turn.
[SPEAKER_19]: But, something came up that really confused me.
[SPEAKER_19]: If...
[SPEAKER_19]: If you guys go to the Konami Arcade website for DDR Extreme, it's konami.co.jp slash am slash ddr underscore new.
[SPEAKER_19]: Brings you up to the DDR website for DDR Extreme.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, run that by me one more time.
[SPEAKER_19]: konami.co.jp slash am slash ddr slash ddr new slash ddr new Alright?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, it's the Extreme webpage.
[SPEAKER_19]: And if you look at it, the logo up top has a little Santa Claus logo in it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Now, what I'm trying to figure out is why they decided to update a two-year-old webpage with a little Santa Claus logo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, Loki's tapping me, he says it's, what?
[SPEAKER_24]: That's fucking old, that's from like last time.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was back when they were talking about the original DDR stream coming out.
[SPEAKER_24]: And that Santa Claus has been there all the time.
[SPEAKER_19]: No, it hasn't.
[SPEAKER_19]: Not that I remember.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's been there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've never seen that there before.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, now, but I do remember that Extreme came out at Christmas time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do remember that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Extreme came out Christmas Day in 2002, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to say.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's been there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki swears up and down it's been there the whole time.
[SPEAKER_19]: It hasn't been.
[SPEAKER_19]: No.
[SPEAKER_19]: Why would they keep it there over summer?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I mean, but isn't, yeah, this is the journal of Naoki Madea and stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why would they bother to update this?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: You, well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: I wish I could say.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not the same, and I'll tell you why.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Because the image name is ddrex2.gif.
[SPEAKER_19]: And then, well, if you view the image.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you take out the 2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, if you take out the 2, there's the original logo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_05]: So... Well, but when did the journal... Okay, Loki's getting frustrated.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because that was like one of the last journals that they did on there, and they changed the logo for the last journal.
[SPEAKER_05]: DDR EX... The EX1 or whatever is for the previous journals in that series there, because there's multiple pages for that journal, so...
[SPEAKER_19]: I know there is, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_19]: Old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Old.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not anything new.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, quit ruining Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jesus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Give the boy hope for this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is wrong with you, you Grinch?
[SPEAKER_24]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you want to go ahead and do that.
[SPEAKER_24]: If you look at that picture through a center graph, there's a secret code in there.
[SPEAKER_24]: It takes you to a secret website that's all about the background information of DDR EX2.
[SPEAKER_19]: Really?
[SPEAKER_24]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's your conspiracy theory for the year.
[SPEAKER_19]: Is it purple?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not purple.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's fuchsia!
[SPEAKER_19]: Are you going to argue with me about colors now?
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on, it was purple.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody knows that it's going to be DDR fuchsia.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's the new... It's like 2DX Red, DDR fuchsia, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: Trust me on this.
[SPEAKER_19]: I've got to know!
[SPEAKER_19]: Okay, I found the code!
[SPEAKER_19]: Can we color a little bit less homosexual?
[SPEAKER_19]: Come on!
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey, please!
[SPEAKER_24]: Fine, if you really want to know what the color is, it's super fuchsia, but you know, I'm not one to judge their title, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't get it.
No, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because the homosexual one would be fabulous fuchsia.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope so too I hope he is, but I unfortunately don't think he is in this case
[SPEAKER_19]: I haven't heard anyone else say otherwise, so Loki's the first one to say something wrong.
[SPEAKER_05]: When he says it, he says it loud.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't let that scare you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, well thanks for the tip, Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_05]: How are you doing otherwise?
[SPEAKER_19]: Life's had its ups and downs.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's DDR in New York?
[SPEAKER_05]: We don't hear a whole lot about what's going on in New York.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh God, don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_19]: We had to lock the forums like two weeks back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not talking about the interweb drama.
[SPEAKER_05]: The interweb?
[SPEAKER_05]: How's the scene going?
[SPEAKER_19]: The scene itself?
[SPEAKER_19]: Not much better, I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's a bummer.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go out there with some defibrillators and breathe some life into DDR a little bit.
[SPEAKER_19]: It's not changing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing's changed around here at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sherlock, go spread the Santa rumor all around.
[SPEAKER_05]: They'll all buy it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you do that.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, thanks for calling, Sherlock.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_19]: You too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Later.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_24]: What?
[SPEAKER_24]: I said you heard it here first, DDR Fuchsia.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, DDR Fuchsia Well, I'm glad Sherlock decided to call the show Even if he may be chasing a ghost Not unlike one of our co-hosts here on the show No, he's just chasing nothing Sorry It's been there, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's been there forever Ever and ever
[SPEAKER_05]: You still look grinch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to do a little bit of a follow-up to something we were talking about last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, this has to do with something you brought up, and it's the girl...
[SPEAKER_05]: The Little Girl That Killed The Other Little Girl, and now has the internet obsession going on about her?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I have a banner for it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I just, I was going to bring that up.
[SPEAKER_05]: The hell possessed you to go and make a banner and imagine, for those that didn't catch last week's show, just a little catch up.
[SPEAKER_25]: I'll put a link to it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, give us this Cliff Notes version.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's going on here?
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened and why is there an internet obsession about it?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, there was a girl who killed one of her classmates.
[SPEAKER_15]: In the class picture, this little girl was wearing a University of Nevada sweatshirt.
[SPEAKER_15]: It just says Nevada all the way across, and it's a blue sweatshirt.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there's all indications that they were friends and everything.
[SPEAKER_15]: Anyway, it started this whole big internet obsession.
[SPEAKER_15]: And keep in mind, they're doing her as a character, not as she herself.
[SPEAKER_15]: And because she was 12 years old, they couldn't prosecute her.
[SPEAKER_15]: Because the age of criminal responsibility in Japan is 14.
[SPEAKER_15]: Which was actually lowered to 14 because of another child murder.
[SPEAKER_15]: And there's like tons of fan art now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tons and tons of fan art.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I took one of the pictures and made a banner out of it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what I like, you know how when people that want to be fashionable with their banners online, they have the banner and then they have the matching little avatar that goes with it, the little box that sits under the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: What I liked about what Jamie did, not only does she have this going on on DDR Freak, but she has it going on on the Orange Lodge Radio forums as well as probably every other forum out there right now that she frequents.
[SPEAKER_05]: She's got the little banner that has the little Nevada girl on it and it says DarkSakura and then the little avatar is a little box cutter.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's actually from the same picture because I wanted to get the whole thing of her holding the box cutter but the size didn't reduce the way I liked it to.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I said just her holding the box cutter and I'm going to post it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: You post it in chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or, you can check it out for yourself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just go to the Orange Lounge Radio forums and there should be a post from Jamie in there.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to give a cheap advertisement in there somewhere for people to visit our dying forums.
[SPEAKER_15]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: I want the quote thread to evolve.
[SPEAKER_05]: In order for the quote thread to come back, people have to actually use our chat room, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_25]: Angel is mouthing that right along with me like I was at the Rocky Horror Picture Show or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's just mouthing it along.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sad that you quit, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_15]: How about for Christmas you pay for me to play again?
I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, how about that gift card?
[SPEAKER_05]: How about that pooping reindeer?
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, I actually did have half of the temptation to reinstall it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Temptation's good.
[SPEAKER_15]: And then I thought, why?
[SPEAKER_15]: I won't have time.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know, once the school year starts again, once the semester starts.
[SPEAKER_05]: When you get really addicted like me, you make time.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's what I have the gem for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, snap.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's my addiction, is exercise.
[SPEAKER_05]: My addiction is feeling fit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I like endorphins.
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to take me to the gym sometime, because I want to see what this is all about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sometime.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's have ourselves a cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, the way the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match works, we play three songs for you guys, and you guys pick your favorite song.
[SPEAKER_05]: The winning song goes into rotation all week long on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Each host picks a song, and you get to hear a clip of last week's winner, as well as two brand new songs.
[SPEAKER_05]: Last week in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match, it came down to The Wire.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was incredibly insane.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a three-way tie.
[SPEAKER_05]: A three-way tie, and it was three new songs because we had to retire a song last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: So DDR Angel ended up breaking the tie, and a lot of folks in the chat room are very passionate about their dislike for this song.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it's going to have a hard time holding on tonight, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe people will see something in the song tonight that they didn't see before.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know, but here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Song number one you can vote for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the artist called J-Punch and the song is called Bitch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I hate myself
[SPEAKER_11]: And I tried You're a bitch, you're a
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, that was song number one in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bitch by J-Punch.
[SPEAKER_05]: And looks like the chat room is about ready to take their handguns to that song.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're bitching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, they're bitching.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're so funny, Jamie!
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see what's going to try and knock this bitch out of here tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll start it off with DarkSakura's pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I picked an overclocked mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is good because we were talking about overclocked a little bit last week and how Loki is going to submit his remix any day now, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, no I'm not actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, what caused this change?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: What caused the change?
[SPEAKER_24]: It doesn't, it's not, no, it's not the type of remix to be on that site.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry, that's it, period.
[SPEAKER_24]: No discussion, it's not going up there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He is not going to compromise his art.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, back to what we were talking about here.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just realized there's a lot of crap on Overclocked, though.
[SPEAKER_15]: A lot of really crappy remixes.
[SPEAKER_15]: But not this song, right?
[SPEAKER_15]: No.
[SPEAKER_15]: This one's a remix from Raiden 2, which is one of my favorite shooter games of all time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Actually, my favorite in the series is Raiden DX, but Raiden 2 was the first one that had these electric things.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's like this big purple line that shoots out and latches onto people and zooms around them, and I was like, that was the coolest weapon in a shooting game ever.
[SPEAKER_15]: Next to the Fist in Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I had to download that.
[SPEAKER_15]: And it actually turned out to be a pretty cool one.
[SPEAKER_15]: So I don't remember the name that they named it, but it's something from Raiden 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give you a hint.
[SPEAKER_05]: The artist is Tefnek, and the song is called the Raiden 2 Airborne Overclock Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_15]: Raiden.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oops, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Raiden.
[SPEAKER_05]: I keep thinking Mortal Kombat since Raiden or Fatal Fury for that same spelling.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tefnek Raiden 2 Airborne OC Remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, song number two in tonight's cage match was Teth Neck, Raiden II, Airborne.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a remix coming to you from Overclocked.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see if that song overclocked or underclocked with the judges here in the room.
[SPEAKER_05]: What do you think, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I liked it, obviously, or else I wouldn't have picked it, so it gets a nine for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I've heard it before, actually.
[SPEAKER_24]: It gets an eight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked it, I'll give it an 8
[SPEAKER_05]: I thought the song was, it was very fluffy, flying on the clouds type thing, I don't know if it's the song I'd go like, yeah, rock on, this song, but it's cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's definitely video game ambience type music, so I'd give it like a, nah, an 8, why not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now we can hear you, Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, where would you give that one?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give it an 8.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, and 8 from Arcadian as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, though, it's not up to us.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's up to you guys in the chat room at www.orangelandre.com and chat.
[SPEAKER_05]: You guys get the final say.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, it's your turn.
[SPEAKER_05]: What song did you pick for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to give them a second try.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is Monolithic with House of Joy off of their newest CD, Diving Descenders.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, one more time, giving them a try here in the cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monolithic, House of Joy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, that was song number three in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monolithic with House of Joy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and see if that was House of Joy or House of Pain to people.
[SPEAKER_15]: House of Pain was cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting off with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_15]: That guy, okay, I'm sorry, if you're going to be a professional, learn how to hold a fucking key.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: I know.
[SPEAKER_15]: He falls, this guy falls into the same category as Politary.
[SPEAKER_15]: Cannot hold a key.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, the music was good, but the guy's voice sucked ass, so I'll split the difference and give it a six.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, let's go around to the other side.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, Loki.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: It gets a 10 because I've been playing this song for over a month.
[SPEAKER_24]: And if it's that good for me to listen to, then it gets a 10.
[SPEAKER_24]: And he does hold a key, he holds goth key.
[SPEAKER_24]: And that's goth key, I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: The voice doesn't really bother me.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I like the music a lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's give it a 9 from me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like his stuff a lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: And let's see what we thought, Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was okay, I'll give it 6.5.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: So remember, it's not up to us, it's up to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: So let's review the songs you can vote for in tonight's cage match.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting off with song number one, last week's winner, Bitch by J-Punch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and song number two in tonight's cage match was Raiden 2, Airborne, Overclocked Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: And song number three in tonight's cage match was Monolithic, House of Joy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, guys, you know the drill.
[SPEAKER_05]: Place vote now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Joining us late during the cage match, as he always likes to join us, say hello to Explicit, real name Jonas.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_05]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_17]: Doing fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just came back from the SVGL3 tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not just now, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yesterday.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, if you just got back now, you were there a little late.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what ended yesterday, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Dude, I was there.
[SPEAKER_17]: I had to compete.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got a note.
[SPEAKER_05]: None of us went.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was really hoping to go, but I got lazy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And because of my trip, I got really badly burned out.
[SPEAKER_05]: But nobody noticed I was gone.
[SPEAKER_17]: But at the same time, just keep in mind that the hype wasn't really worth all that hype.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you talk about the hype, what do you mean?
[SPEAKER_17]: You know how everybody says, oh, it's SVGL, the biggest tournament in history.
[SPEAKER_17]: You got SVGL.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think, when was the first SVGL?
[SPEAKER_17]: Do you remember?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: First SVGL was, I don't know, a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know SVGL 2 was 2002, in April, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_17]: And SVGL is December 2004, the third installment.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it was the last in a long line of events then.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, supposedly the biggest tournament ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Depending on how people's opinions are.
[SPEAKER_17]: But all I gotta say is the big, well I'll explain later if you have any questions Not so far, I'm curious kind of what happened, how did the day go?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well it was a very very long day, the PA took, PA really I think started at 11.45 for the qualifiers I think the PA ended at 6 o'clock itself, it took that long
[SPEAKER_17]: because there was some controversy with the pads.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people were complaining.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, what is this controversy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I've heard about it over on DDR Freak, on the forums.
[SPEAKER_17]: They said, because they switched, I think they switched the pads from 4th Plus or into Groove, whatever they switched the cabinet to for the Extreme.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they said that one player's side is not working or I'm not really sure what's going on there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Someone said that this guy was a sore loser or...
[SPEAKER_17]: The pads were really not working, depending on what you guys' opinions or different playstyles.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't really opinionize on that, but it delayed a shitload of time.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unnecessary.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unfortunately, I've noticed this is kind of a trend in a lot of tournaments lately, where somebody's complaining about the pad, and then they have to do these extensive tests on it to see if they're working or not.
[SPEAKER_05]: My advice to future people who are going to be throwing tournaments...
[SPEAKER_05]: to have some kind of conflict resolution thing in the tournament rules that says, if there's a question, this is the procedure, and whatever the outcome of that procedure is, end of story.
[SPEAKER_05]: No arguing.
[SPEAKER_17]: I really learned a lot with the SVGL3 tournament organizing, even though many have actually said that it was very badly organized.
[SPEAKER_17]: Regardless if it's true or not, I would say it's badly organized because of the
[SPEAKER_17]: Time restraints.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think 2DX took way too long, even though there was like 5 people who competed for 2DX.
[SPEAKER_04]: The only 5 people?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, 2DX for it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm assuming 5 or 8, but it took way too long for its own type.
[SPEAKER_17]: Usually that's too fast for 8 people.
[SPEAKER_17]: But if it was like 32, it would take long, obviously.
[SPEAKER_17]: But yeah, around that much competed.
[SPEAKER_17]: It wasn't that many people.
[SPEAKER_17]: And freestyle started hella late.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not to mention the lack of room for people to actually compete on.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was too crowded inside.
[SPEAKER_17]: People had to sit down for the camera.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was all stuffed near the machines that have a lot of sound.
[SPEAKER_04]: Spiegel is a very interesting place to have a tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do they have the machine inside?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: How in the hell were you able to see anything?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, like I said, it wasn't really worth the hype.
[SPEAKER_17]: I see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because the management itself is also involved.
[SPEAKER_17]: They refuse to do certain things and certain expectations to...
[SPEAKER_17]: to us competitors.
[SPEAKER_17]: One is, yeah, of course, not everybody is satisfied, but at least come to a point where everybody agrees in a way.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know Team Seattle was there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_17]: SoCal was there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some of the Sacramento people were there, like Toadie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I was kind of hoping he'd come tonight because I wanted to talk to him about it because he competed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, and I competed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ugh.
[SPEAKER_05]: What was that arc for?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because the rules kind of got altered in a way, I wasn't really sure if that was the rules because there was a qualifier list in SVGL3 I'm assuming, many people have thought it was going to be practicing one of the following songs like Highs Off You, Superstar, etc, etc, etc But I chose one of the, all of the things called Extratuned Some people may have fucked up on it, well I fucked up on it For some reason, it's not one of my greats in the beginning
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people were okay with that, but some people were not really happy with the rules there.
[SPEAKER_17]: But then again, it's a competition.
[SPEAKER_17]: You don't want to start drama.
[SPEAKER_17]: Do the drama during the forums, but not during the tournaments.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's where the forums come in the after to see what they can do better.
[SPEAKER_17]: Even though 50% of the control is basically on SVGL's part.
[SPEAKER_05]: So how did freestyle go?
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard freestyle was really good, that there were a lot of really high-level people.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I can't really opinionize that.
[SPEAKER_17]: There were some ups and downs with freestyle.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, the ups was it was a good competition, great competition, great competitors competed.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like Tequila from Omaha came all the way from there to the Bay just to compete.
[SPEAKER_17]: Turned out very good, and some of the performances showed a lot of hard work.
[SPEAKER_17]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: In a way, especially with finals, why the hell are you going to place a fucking tournament right after college finals?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, because they don't want to do it on Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, you could find a problem with almost any week that you could possibly pick, I think.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, because I thought SVGL was supposed to be held during the summer, which was a predicted thing, but Christmas?
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, right before Christmas, it's finals, people are stressing out over it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Freestyle section, they can't do a routine because because freestyle in my opinion was too limited for that whole day because right after finals you have to work on a routine it's a big pain in the ass especially when I had finals like two or some people had finals like two like two of them on Friday and they had to work immediate without sleep just to make sure it looks good but the biggest problem with the the environment of the freestyle is that they didn't put outside
[SPEAKER_17]: Give a lot of air conditioning And of course the place itself wasn't even air conditioned And the second of all, very limited space You got people crowding all over the pad So people wanted to do a lot of movement outside the pad But they were limited because they got people around Blocking their... Even my routine got fucked over How so?
[SPEAKER_17]: Because it required at least 3 to 5 feet of open space on my right side When I was competing
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, was it supposedly going to happen that there was going to be the machine outside?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that ever said that was possible?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, SPGL2 had... Yeah, but I can see where in the winter there might be rain concerns, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, because then imagine if it had rained and they tried to put the machine outside, it would have been even more cramped.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I mean, the weather itself was not to a point where it was about to rain.
[SPEAKER_17]: Besides, I already checked the weather and SVGL beforehand so I know what the hell's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Even though, of course, the weather is not really 100% accurate.
[SPEAKER_17]: But at the same time... But here's another problem with the situation with the freestyle conditions.
[SPEAKER_17]: You got extreme near the 4th Plus machine.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you're either going to probably be hearing extreme songs and 4th Plus at the same time conflicting with your concentration on the routine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, ouch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you might be hearing like... They didn't turn one off or anything?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, for some reason the extreme was a little louder than, um, friggin', um... Fourth Plus?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, and you got the 2DX written almost nearby, too.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was In The Groove involved, too?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, the In The Groove machine got switched with Fourth Plus.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gotcha, okay, gotcha.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you got... Yeah, regardless, I still have not played In The Groove, so I can't really opinionize with these steps on In The Groove.
[SPEAKER_05]: That would have been interesting, though, if that was, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's controversial.
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't really say anything because I've never tested the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_17]: And of course, everything's a matter of opinion.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm kind of surprised nobody took that opportunity, though, to do something with in the groove.
[SPEAKER_05]: Kind of, I don't know, like having to pick the West Coast.
[SPEAKER_17]: They only have two cabinets.
[SPEAKER_17]: And of course, like, you got SVGL, CVGL, RV, not RVGL, well, sort of the way RVGL, MGL.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're all golfers.
[SPEAKER_17]: They have to share machines with each other in a way.
[SPEAKER_17]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Especially in the barrier, which is very... Of course, you know, like, MGL got the Pump It Up Exceed from SVGL and probably in the groove from SVGL.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not really sure if that's true or not.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or if both places have this in the groove.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: 2DX... Oh, did you want to hear about the results?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, what happened with the 2DX turning?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I really didn't really...
[SPEAKER_17]: See what's with 2DX, but I've heard that a lot of people complaining about how 2DX Red was off-sync as shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, it's like, think of it as night style.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not sure if it's not... That's what the fucking game is, they gotta get used to it.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're off-sync.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I'm not sure if it's that, or if it's the hardware, I'm not sure, cause...
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people were complaining with that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I really couldn't complain.
[SPEAKER_17]: Either I had the worst accuracy or on 2DX, because I played myself, and I got a good attack the whole song.
[SPEAKER_05]: And this is on a red, was it on a red?
[SPEAKER_05]: Red.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, the new red Deliver Style.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Drool, get a boner.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I'm not sure if it's really, but since RVGL's getting one, I'm not sure if that's going to be, if it's the hardware problems that people are saying or the software problems itself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: Only time will tell what's the truth if it's off.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is there any questions with the FBGL tournament?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing I haven't gotten on there and read myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just kind of feel bad that I wasn't really able to go to the tournament because I really wanted to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: But then at the same time, it sounded like it was really crowded as hell and not a lot of standing room.
[SPEAKER_17]: And if I wasn't entering, maybe... Well, there was some drama involved as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's the drama?
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell us about drama.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll get to the FBs on that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to know now.
[SPEAKER_03]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, how old is DDR Bot?
[SPEAKER_17]: He's 11 years old.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, basically, he's resorting to an 11-year-old's immaturity to pick on the 11-year-old.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just curious, all right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, well, yeah, you got that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Birds of a feather.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course you got the complaints of the pads, whether or not it's SVGL sport or if it's the people being so loser.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who started it?
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't get involved.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people drooling over DDR Player's girlfriend.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to ask the hard-hitting questions of this program, alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to know, who started this shit?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cast the first stone?
[SPEAKER_05]: Who's the drama starter?
[SPEAKER_17]: Who is their fan in the flames?
[SPEAKER_17]: I can't really... I don't really know exactly, but it has something to do with SoCal and Team Seattle.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is a long going back and forth that's happened for a long, long time so that's again, not a surprise, alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Err, I'm not sure what happened but they said it was JSP versus some girl in Team Seattle, JSP won that one but for some reason he dropped out of the race.
[SPEAKER_17]: For either attraction or sexually attractive reasons or
[SPEAKER_05]: Was it Tanya, the girl that's always on, because I know she was going, the girl that was the get up move girl?
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_24]: If I remember correctly reading this.
[SPEAKER_24]: I read this briefly, I think.
[SPEAKER_24]: It was the chick that was the one that was on MTV promoting DDR.
[SPEAKER_24]: I didn't know there was anyone on MTV promoting DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't even know about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, actually, Tanya was on the, what is it, the 20 games of the year thing or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah, I've heard about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: They shot stuff around Seattle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, okay, so...
[SPEAKER_17]: I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, for the winners of PEA, one of the first places, of course, Team Seattle.
[SPEAKER_17]: Second was Fidox, who actually came to the FU tournament and the August.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, good deal.
[SPEAKER_17]: So that was very good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Third place, I don't remember third place, but I know the top two.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, back to drama.
[SPEAKER_05]: Was there any good freestyle drama?
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, the limited room of space.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course, I already told you about the freestyle drama.
[SPEAKER_17]: The limited amount of room of space.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to know, I have to know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anybody get served?
[SPEAKER_17]: In what way?
[SPEAKER_05]: Did anybody do their routine and go, you got served?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody got served?
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because people were just waiting for freestyle to start.
[SPEAKER_17]: It took too long for everybody else to fucking...
[SPEAKER_17]: Get freestyle prepared.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think it started at 8.30.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was too late.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everybody's tired.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I could have gone to Spiggle if I knew it was going to go that way.
[SPEAKER_17]: But at the same time, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, the condition, it was too... It was just too hot inside and limited space.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can't really do anything.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like pointing your fingers upwards, just not moving your whole body and taking advantage of the whole freestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, were there any fistfights?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, there were no... Shouting matches?
[SPEAKER_17]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_05]: Knives drawn?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I heard... Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, I was just reading the forum.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people are saying, damn Fab Five.
[SPEAKER_17]: It does have something to do with throwing a football at an 11-year-old's head.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, Fab Five?
[SPEAKER_05]: Carson and Tom and Gann and all them were there?
[SPEAKER_05]: They're my idols, man.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not sure what the hell is going on with this drama and shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, you know, this drama exists and...
[SPEAKER_05]: And people are serving other people and it's just, you know, servolution.
[SPEAKER_17]: Then you got boyfriend-girlfriend conflicts with other men or other women, whatever the hell you say it's.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, this should be interesting because one of the, I think one of the NorCal people,
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll say, where is this?
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-uh, uh-uh, okay, uh-uh, no, uh-uh, uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_03]: He is not sleeping with my boyfriend, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, now, uh-uh, it's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I'm going to serve you right now, okay?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: How was that?
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, what's funny is that... That was my, like, Texas slash ghetto.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was my Texas ghetto.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't understand this drama, but this is one of the funniest questions I've ever... One of the funniest questions...
[SPEAKER_17]: I've been asked to me, why is this hot Asian girl going out with old Joe Dirt?
[SPEAKER_17]: And I think this one guy actually liked this... Did anyone actually see the movie Joe Dirt?
[SPEAKER_24]: There's a hot chick dating Joe Dirt, I mean...
[SPEAKER_24]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that was a response I got from one of the people, saying, ooh, this girl is hot.
[SPEAKER_17]: See, I know something like this is gonna happen, so... Oh my god, he tricked the Asian!
[SPEAKER_24]: He must be super genius!
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, and I did actually talk to some gay guy.
[SPEAKER_17]: An actual gay person.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh my god, they exist?
[SPEAKER_00]: Wait, you actually saw a gay person?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, I've actually talked to a gay person in a tournament.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's like you, Robb.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh dear.
[SPEAKER_24]: He's like you, Ron, but gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait, what, what, what, Loki?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not gay, I just... Whoa, whoa, whoa, I thought you... You just pull in on the radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, this is just my radio personality, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, pussy, I'm all about the pussy, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tips, yeah, that's all I want right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big, big, big... I can't do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gayer than Judy Garland.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't hold it anymore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, perhaps you and that gay guy would have a good match.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if he plays DDR, he's probably under 18, so not a good idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, he's over 18, but I'm not sure if he plays DDR or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: An actual, living, breathing gay person?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just curious.
Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, therefore, because I'm gay and this other person's gay, we have to have sex, obviously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did they capture him in nets?
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, okay, because if one of the gays is running around, then, you know...
[SPEAKER_24]: You don't want that stuff spreading.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, he does act gay.
[SPEAKER_17]: He actually says he was gay.
[SPEAKER_24]: He's like, as he's bent over some dude, yeah, I'm gay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, that's all right.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm glad you could finally meet a gay person.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's for you, Skye.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go and talk about, because the chat room is getting restless.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're going... How long have they been having this conversation?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, Loki, I want to go to break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yeah, where's SVGL?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's near MGL.
[SPEAKER_17]: Problem solved.
[SPEAKER_05]: SVGL is in the Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's in southern Bay Area.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, it's a 20-minute drive or...
[SPEAKER_05]: If you know where MGL is, it's basically... If you don't know where it is, it's near San Jose, California, basically.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's simple.
[SPEAKER_05]: The easy... Because remember, we're an international program.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just drive three simple steps to drive to Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_17]: Go to I-80, then go to 680, then exit where you'll see... El Camino, Real.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's SVGL, talking about MGL.
[SPEAKER_17]: SVGL takes a little longer to get to, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there's gay people there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just start, you know what, just get in your car and start driving towards the Madonna music and you'll end up in Spiegel soon enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'll see the giant rainbow sign in the air.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know they're all tagged.
[SPEAKER_15]: And they've got like, you know those tags like pierced on their ears.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright you bitches, let's hear who won tonight's cage match, shall we?
[SPEAKER_05]: We need to take a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to go to a break right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though I couldn't find half the songs you wanted to hear in the next break, I did find one.
[SPEAKER_25]: You found Panorama?
[SPEAKER_05]: I did find Panorama.
[SPEAKER_25]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: All that you wish for is to have you Fly and keep on
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Mel B of RTF.
[SPEAKER_01]: And for an extra $1.99 a minute, my girlfriend Mel B can join us on all the fun together.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, if you're a broke ass like I am, why don't you come to one place that costs absolutely nothing to go to and still the fun is just as great.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Orange Lounge Radio, Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kick it with me and you just might realize the best things in life are free.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, we are back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mel won that freestyle thing with tequila, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Was that it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that how it went?
[SPEAKER_05]: The Freestyle over at Sigl.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mel and Tequila?
[SPEAKER_05]: Mel and Tequila, yeah, they won it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job, boys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yep, did a very, very good job.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's all worth Tequila's drive and Mel's... He drove from... No, I'm not sure, but I think it's by flight.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to say, that's a hell of a drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: By flight.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you said you had some stuff you wanted to talk about tonight with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, now I want to talk to you because I noticed that you were doing something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, of course, I want to distract you from that other thing you were doing.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to join our chatroom, www.orangeloungeradio.com Come complain about the cage match picks with everybody else there in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_05]: Again, we also have mini-programming that goes on during the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monday nights, Diversion, the Orange Lounge Radio Remix show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tuesday nights, Pump Up the Volume with the one and only DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_25]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Thursday nights, Outside the Box with me,
[SPEAKER_05]: Who?
[SPEAKER_05]: Me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Myself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob and I. Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and Friday night over on DDR Freak Radio, relive the magic of Orange Challenge Radio Sunday nights as DDR Freak Radio rebroadcasts our Sunday night program at 6 o'clock Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, what's up?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, um, sim stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, basically...
[SPEAKER_24]: DDR Maniacs has been down for a while now, so no new theme stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways, there was a couple turnouts going on that I don't care about, but anyways.
[SPEAKER_24]: The first one that should be mentioned, well, I guess that would be the first one.
[SPEAKER_24]: Turnimix 5+, which is called the re-Turnimix, which I didn't really read the rules, but it sounds like it's just taking old songs from the Turnimix 1 through 5 and redoing them.
[SPEAKER_05]: Big deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so that's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can find all the information you want.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so it's basically like the flashback episode of your favorite sitcom.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the same old shit with a different laugh track.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_24]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then there's DDR OSC 3+, the original Stepfile Contest.
[SPEAKER_24]: This is remixed, basically.
[SPEAKER_24]: The rules for this is it has to be a song, a remix of a song that's been used in DDR Tourney Mix, a remix of a song that's been used in OSC, or an overclocked remix that hasn't been used in either one, or an original...
[SPEAKER_24]: Remix of a song that's in a non-music game, you know, base game.
[SPEAKER_24]: So, no DDR remixes, but, you know, remixes of other crap is okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the due date for this is the 28th.
[SPEAKER_24]: All your information can be found on the MyStyle.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's links to the OSC homepage and all that wonderful crap.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, um, other than that, still stuff's being worked on for the, you know, the Sinfile releases.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, one of the things I thought was funny that I'd like to mention was we've had our very first, very first, um,
[SPEAKER_05]: Circus de Soleil
[SPEAKER_24]: and then Cirque du Soleil.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, my mistake.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, anyways, they actually came after Bomani Stealth for having, I guess, some of their music on their site, which should be surprising because any of their music actually being out there on the internet, why the fuck anyone want to listen to it level and make a remix or a, not remix, a sim file for that?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: What I want to know is how the fuck did someone find that?
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways, so they got the Seasoned Assist for that thing, but everything else is going as planned.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I just thought that was funny that that would be on there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Other than that, really nothing else going on.
[SPEAKER_24]: So just those two little tournaments there that we really don't have that much to notice for, and well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: A comment in our chatroom I'd like some discussion on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tournamix is shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Disgust.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just really don't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nobody gives a shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't look at those as a good indicator.
[SPEAKER_24]: There really aren't that many quality sim files out there anymore.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's the problem, the pool is way too diluted.
[SPEAKER_04]: As you just said, I didn't follow any of that shit you just said, basically.
[SPEAKER_05]: All I heard was blah blah blah, another contest on blah blah blah, another site.
[SPEAKER_05]: With blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what the fuck, it's a contest based off of other contests, that's kind of weird to me, sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, so basically you've got what, you've got tournaments, and then you have the EI tournament, and then you have this, and then that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everybody's got a freaking tournament going on right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like how like two years ago when Extreme was kind of new.
[SPEAKER_05]: Every other week, there was a DDR tournament somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, I remember in NorCal, every week for a couple months, there was a tournament somewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was just like, people did not have the time to come up with freestyle routines.
[SPEAKER_05]: They didn't care anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, I see the same thing happening here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here's my problem.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, and this is the biggest problem that I have with everything.
[SPEAKER_24]: Once FoodMix came out, that set the new standards for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing can achieve it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just nothing has come close.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing will come close until FoodMix releases something else.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that's it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry, but there's no Simphile creator out there that can even match that, or even come close to matching that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even without the yippy hippy background movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you were to take the background movies out, would you still feel the same?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I think background movies is a little much to ask some Joe Schmo in their basement to create.
[SPEAKER_05]: How the hell the Food Mix guys did it, hey, you know what, I don't know, they just had way too much free time.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're very talented, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, that's really what... Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_04]: The songs are great, and the steps are great.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not arguing that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just saying, they've got it all.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, even if you were to remove the videos, would you still say that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even so, the artwork in the background is still phenomenal, and they created their own songs that didn't sound like shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: That was also really good.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the interface, the whole theme was awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just everything about that was awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, as I see in the chat room, you know, how about the judging?
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, I've been saying it since, what, Tournament Mix, I don't know, 2, 3, 1, I don't know, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've been saying they cannot have these sim files labeled by who made them, because you'll never get fair judging for it.
[SPEAKER_24]: What do they do every time they fucking label who they're from?
[SPEAKER_24]: Then they're not voting on SimFile, they're voting for who their favorite person is.
[SPEAKER_05]: And everybody goes straight to download DM Ashura's file, and they go straight to download Moogle Hunter's file, and don't get me wrong, I love Moogle Hunter, he's a local guy, I love him.
[SPEAKER_05]: And what else, they go straight to download Bomani Ruler, Jesus Christ, and they go straight to download whatever, the big people in the SimScenes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And they win!
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait, actually, you can't say that about Moogle Hunter on Terminix 4?
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_24]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, they're not.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: It gets gone to shit, basically.
[SPEAKER_17]: People just, like, not care, and they just, oh, let's download a song, and let's get a high score of it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, I download personally.
[SPEAKER_24]: I go on, you know, by my style, almost daily.
[SPEAKER_24]: I look on there in their sim files, you know, selection area, and I look and see what remixes are on there, and I listen to every single Max remix on there, every single one that's been made.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, I know that's wrong, but I do it, you know, because you know what, there are... Next person to take a Max song and mix it with a Pops A or Pops B song, like Max, I don't know, Max, Mr. Wonderful or whatever, I hope you get laughed off the internet, seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mr. Maxiful or whatever, I hope you get laughed off the internet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, someone did make... I think someone did do It's Rennie Max.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not really sure that's true.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways, anyways, I was gonna... Kill me!
[SPEAKER_24]: I was gonna say, now, now, now.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, now I know people.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now, there are good files out there and good songs out there.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's why you have to listen to them all.
[SPEAKER_24]: Because...
[SPEAKER_24]: it might be something good.
[SPEAKER_24]: However, 99% of the time, it's not.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's just someone, you know, posting absolute crap on there.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, see, that's what's kind of cool about Bomayusels, they have a little rating system thing, and you can also, you know, put comments about the file, like, this is a piece of shit, you know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Constructive comments.
[SPEAKER_17]: But, uh... Well, actually, I wouldn't say about constructive comments, because, you know, people posting, oh, you stole this, you stole that crap, and then it gets deleted afterwards by a mod.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyways, whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: So basically, yeah, there's just not a lot of good shit out there anymore.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry, FoodMix and Diverse Systems have basically cornered the market in sim files and remixes.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, sorry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, and that's all that's going on in the sim scene right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just a variety of tournaments.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what, here's an idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to make your tournament stand out above all the other remixed tournaments, how about throwing some decent prizes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Get some entry fees and some real good prizes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get some folks to donate some good stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really, what's the best prize you've ever seen for one of these tournaments?
[SPEAKER_17]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Case in point.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_05]: When do you see the really, really good freestyle routines?
[SPEAKER_05]: When there's a $1,000 pot on the line.
[SPEAKER_05]: When do you see the really shit routines?
[SPEAKER_05]: When it's going to be a pat on the back and a certificate.
[SPEAKER_05]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_05]: You the winner.
[SPEAKER_05]: You winner of tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just a little quick note here.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'd like to mention, Gold Wave is not a remixing program.
[SPEAKER_24]: Do not use it as a remixing program.
[SPEAKER_24]: It is not meant for remixing.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's meant for audio editing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Audio editing does not include remixing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Please, do not use it to remix stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speeding up a song or putting a filter over it does not constitute a remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please do not make it a remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Please do not reverse a song and call it a remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not a remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: People, please stop.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, on that note, I think we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: And chopping up a song very crudely and in, I might add, Gold Wave, is also not a remix.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think what we're going to do is we're going to go to a break.
[SPEAKER_05]: And why don't we do, because we haven't played any of this in a while, why don't we do some music from FoonMix?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sound good?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds foony.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sounds foonerific.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll play some FoonMix music.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then we come back, the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because what a good way to follow up some FoonMix music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll be back after this with more Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Enjoy.
Oh, wait a minute.
What is this?
It's making me think about my life.
Feel the touch of love.
[SPEAKER_18]: He's the roof operator Hypnotized by the look in your eyes Hit the coast
See you.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_23]: Warning, Orange Lounge Radio's Bombani Music and More program might be dangerous for you to listen to in the kitchen.
[SPEAKER_23]: We have reported incidents where exposed listening to this program in the kitchen has caused people to bust out a Sharpie pen, draw arrows on the tiles, and start stomping away.
[SPEAKER_23]: A friendly public service announcement from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to try to do a list list in a little while.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think the topic tonight, so you guys can start thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, should I hold off on it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll hold off on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Some of you guys that were in chat earlier tonight already know what the list list is all about for tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, you know, start thinking about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I am going to do the one that you guys were talking about beforehand.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said that would be a good list list topic.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: But first, we have to get ranty.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, because it just would not be an episode of Orange Lounge Radio if we did not have a little bit... What in the hell is that noise?
[SPEAKER_05]: You need to talk about what that's all about, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is that thing?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's my gavel meter.
[SPEAKER_05]: What the hell is that?
[SPEAKER_24]: It records, or it displays EM fields, like dangerous stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: For instance, Jamie's laptop, pretty safe.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, that's about like .6 milligauss, or 6 milligausses.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or, yeah, I think it's .6, that's right, because this is 0 to 1.
[SPEAKER_24]: But, for instance, like my TV, it's off the scale, so basically I'm getting cancerous rays as I sit there with the TV on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, it's a cancer meter.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's basically what it is.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it's also for ghost hunting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, I like how you just added that in here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and it's also for ghost hunting.
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, this is bad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Here is justice.
[SPEAKER_15]: My first F.U.
[SPEAKER_15]: goes toward people who decide to weave in and out of lanes in the fog.
[SPEAKER_15]: That's really stupid and that's how accidents happen.
[SPEAKER_15]: But then again, I suppose the Darwinism will soon work on that moron.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another one goes to people who drive too slow in the fog because then all the rest of us are backed up by the people who are speeding running into my ass.
[SPEAKER_15]: And of course, driving off without stopping or anything, so...
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, F.U.
[SPEAKER_15]: goes to the top of my trunk inside because I gouged out a big piece of my thumb just shy of the tendon and it bled and bled and bled and I got one of those band-aids on it that's supposed to trap the fluids underneath so that you'll heal faster using your own antibodies and it looks like a big purple bubble.
[SPEAKER_15]: It's really disgusting.
[SPEAKER_15]: and F.U.
[SPEAKER_15]: toward the financial situation where I can't afford to get the special edition 2DX8 style, but I have Parappa coming, so it's all good.
[SPEAKER_15]: And F.U.
[SPEAKER_15]: toward how expensive Dan's present was.
[SPEAKER_15]: Since he doesn't listen to the show, I have no problem saying that I bought Dan the Ultimate Matrix box set
[SPEAKER_15]: and it was $70 although I think they marked it down by $10 at Target.
[SPEAKER_15]: I paid $59.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, I was about that at Target.
[SPEAKER_15]: They lowered the price.
[SPEAKER_15]: But still, when I first looked at it and saw a $70 price tag I was freaking out but I bought it for them anyway.
[SPEAKER_15]: Another F you goes toward just the sick that I had for the past three days.
[SPEAKER_15]: It was the type of illness that just saps all of your energy.
[SPEAKER_15]: And I did nothing but eat lobster burritos and ice cream for three days, sat on the floor and played Phantasy Star Online and slept.
[SPEAKER_15]: Those are the only three things I did for the past three days.
[SPEAKER_15]: Today's the first day I felt like getting out and moving around.
[SPEAKER_15]: And that's really it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, let's move on to Loki!
[SPEAKER_24]: Um... The only thing I can remember is the stupid bitch that tried to pass me in the right lane today.
[SPEAKER_24]: Cause, you know, it was merging over, and there's a lane that you're not supposed to pass in.
[SPEAKER_24]: And so she tries to, you know, accelerate up to me, and she almost hits my car.
[SPEAKER_24]: And so I honk at her, and she doesn't look at me because she knows she's stupid.
[SPEAKER_24]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_24]: and the slow driver I was behind on the way to my dad's house today because he's driving down a one lane road fucking slow because there's a little fog in the distance and he can only see, you know, 999 miles and not, you know, the full thousand, so damn and, um what else, oh, and I feel like I just noticed right now that wonderful device that talks to the dead is all fucked up because it was in
[SPEAKER_24]: My backpack type thing and cut all the wires broken and god knows where the germanium is.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now I gotta fix it so that sucks.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then fuck you to my work for making me have to cook more shit because I want to have another potluck because now they want to start becoming like a team or something which I guess involves numerous potlucks.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't like potlucks, fucking bastards, just because they want to eat pigs.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, and then also, fuck you, that stupid orc that killed my, uh, Malala's manslave character.
[SPEAKER_24]: And that sucked, because poor Taru was just like, looked like a cookie.
[SPEAKER_24]: ADDICT!
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh yeah, I think you were there too.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't know, I don't really have much to complain about.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh yeah, my boss for not giving me my review yet, and I know I'm not going to get a raise, even though I've been there for five years.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm not getting paid shit, so that sucks.
[SPEAKER_24]: And then, uh, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: I just hate Christmas.
[SPEAKER_24]: Fuck you to Christmas, because, you know, I don't want to buy people gifts.
[SPEAKER_24]: You're a Grinch.
[SPEAKER_24]: I buy people gifts all year round, and I don't really give a shit about the birthday of Jesus or whatever it's supposed to be for.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know, I'm sure Immaculate Conception...
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay, that's what I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mary was a fucking whore, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: She just does not want to admit it.
[SPEAKER_24]: They're not putting it in the books, okay?
[SPEAKER_24]: But you know that...
[SPEAKER_24]: She had her way.
[SPEAKER_24]: She had her way around Bethlehem there.
[SPEAKER_24]: Little slut.
[SPEAKER_24]: Anyway, um... Well, now that we're all going to hell, anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, yeah, if I give my printer for being out of ink and I have to buy more ink because the fucking cartridges are, like, tiny, you print, like, one page and it's like, Out of ink!
[SPEAKER_24]: You're out of ink!
[SPEAKER_24]: Ah, shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: I might as well buy a new printer, because it comes with the ink when you buy a new printer, and it's just about as expensive as replacing the ink, so why not?
[SPEAKER_24]: Alright, I'm done.
[SPEAKER_05]: An F you to the fog, because fog is scary, and I don't like driving in it, and I think people are always going to run into me, and it's scary.
[SPEAKER_05]: An F you to the fact that the bar sucked last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did not have really a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you know, I had fun with the person that I went with, but I just wasn't feeling it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, F you to bars in general.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think I'm going to stop going.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except for karaoke, because I love karaoke.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I don't really have a whole lot else.
[SPEAKER_05]: An F you to not really getting any sleep in the past few days, and the fact that I'm not going to get any more in the next few, because I've got a lot of stuff going on at work next week, and I just want to cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's it for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go on to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: As I try not to strangle Rob with the mic cord.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, yeah, just F you to circumstances, because... Well, not for me personally, but for other people that I... Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: But I don't like said person either.
[SPEAKER_13]: So never mind.
[SPEAKER_13]: and yeah, nothing else because it's Christmas week and I'm not as angsty as I was last week, so too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Arcadian42, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, let's see, uh, fuck you to Feel Uncounted Law at the moment.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I just feel tired tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, fuck you to... You're getting it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Am I getting?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I don't know if I'm getting anything, but I just had colds and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe I've just been... Okay, uh... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not really too much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll give a preliminary fuck you to the Sacramento Quark, because they're probably going to make me pay the full damn fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope they'll reduce it for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Out of the goodness of their hearts.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have no hearts!
[SPEAKER_06]: But, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Explicit!
[SPEAKER_17]: I've already said most of my Effie is from the SVGL tournament.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, an Effie goes to the Fog.
[SPEAKER_17]: God damn, I couldn't even see what the hell is driving.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god, thank god I didn't go to SVGL because I would have cried like a little girl in the Fog because I hate Fog.
[SPEAKER_04]: I really, really hate Fog.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fog is sexy.
[SPEAKER_17]: F you to my friend Patrick for giving me the wrong directions.
[SPEAKER_17]: We almost got lost a few times.
[SPEAKER_17]: Heading to SVGL and heading back again to Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_17]: Either that or just giving F you to Yahoo Maps for messing up the directions.
[SPEAKER_17]: F you to my friend for misplanning the time management just heading to SVGL.
[SPEAKER_17]: We were supposed to be there like around 11.15 as planned, but I had planned earlier, but he wanted me to do certain things.
[SPEAKER_17]: Therefore causing us to be there around like 11.35, almost being late to the whole tournament.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I hate to say this, but F you to my friend Sean for, not Shane, for...
[SPEAKER_17]: Being to MSBGL very late, instead he went to Milpitas Golf Land, playing in the groove for 30 minutes, when you know there's a big tournament that a friend of ours, who was actually at his car, who hella wanted to compete in this first big tournament, and trying to shine at his first tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we have an actual... You know that's kind of smart, to go play in the groove at Milpitas, because you know everybody's a Sunnyvale?
[SPEAKER_24]: No, hella is not a word.
[SPEAKER_24]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: I just needed to point out that somehow or another I managed to spend $111.11 at the grocery store today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for that bit of utter randomness.
[SPEAKER_05]: Back to explicit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, an FU goes to having four freaking finals the whole week, not getting me enough sleep.
[SPEAKER_17]: Damn, finals sucks, but at least it's over with and at least I passed all my fucking classes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank God for that.
[SPEAKER_17]: and FU2 people who actually spent $23,000 on a fucking Yu-Gi-Oh card.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: That is ridiculously stupid.
[SPEAKER_17]: Spending $23,000 on a freaking card, which is going to be released later on as an actual comment.
[SPEAKER_24]: Everyone knows that, you know, Pokemon's where it's at.
[SPEAKER_17]: A card collector with lots of liquid assets to throw away at any whim?
[SPEAKER_24]: A person who burns money in his fireplace.
[SPEAKER_24]: A person who wipes his ass with dollar bills.
[SPEAKER_24]: A person who uses napkins.
[SPEAKER_24]: Or actually, dollar bills as napkins.
[SPEAKER_24]: A person who eats money.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, and F you goes to the scar I have on my leg during the SVGL3 tournament.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was non-stop bleeding the whole time.
[SPEAKER_24]: Wow, really, and you didn't die?
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't die, so I'm still alive.
[SPEAKER_17]: Not poisoned and stuff and all.
[SPEAKER_17]: And FU goes to the rest of the drama on SVGL3, of course.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, I screwed up on the fucking tournament, regardless of the TAT issues or not.
[SPEAKER_17]: And FU goes to Amp, the drink Amp, for not keeping me awake the whole time.
[SPEAKER_17]: It says it's supposed to keep me awake just like balls does.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, those assholes were lying to you.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm sorry there's no substitute for balls.
[SPEAKER_24]: Some good balls down your throat is just perfect.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, because someone said, amp is better.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_17]: I nearly fell asleep in the wheel and almost got into an accident.
[SPEAKER_24]: God damn that stimulant for not keeping me away.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, that's how bad our freaking amp is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, the Amp2DX is good for being hella- either the songs being hella off-sync or just me being off-sync as shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Scoring like 90% good is not cool, especially for songs that you nearly- That's cool for me.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's like playing D2R with a full grade attack, which I nearly done.
[SPEAKER_17]: And finally... And... Oh, no, I'm coming!
[SPEAKER_17]: Wrap it up!
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yeah, of course, FU for not sleeping, of course.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU for actually cleaning up for fucking Christmas.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know Christmas is at our house, and that's why I'm taking it this week, but I shouldn't have been cleaning up the whole week.
[SPEAKER_17]: I had finals, for goddamn sakes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear to God, you're going to have your own spin-off show where you just sit there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You and Dark Child.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to give you guys your own show.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's going to be on at 3 in the morning.
[SPEAKER_05]: so you can get this all out of your system.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now wrap it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: That has to be continued.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, no, never to be continued.
[SPEAKER_24]: Over.
[SPEAKER_24]: Done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you in the booth or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: What is this sound effect?
[SPEAKER_24]: Why hasn't he tried out for like the real world?
[SPEAKER_24]: I hate my roommates because they annoy me so.
[SPEAKER_24]: Let me count the ways.
[SPEAKER_24]: Damn those cameras!
[SPEAKER_24]: Let's fucking break the cameras and blow up the house.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, like I said, to be continued.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's no ending of the FU, bruh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, Sheriff.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who needs friends?
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S says, You know what you sound like right now?
[SPEAKER_05]: You sound like our old microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is Matt, coming to you from two years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S says, F you to the idiots on my job for stealing broken iPods.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you that fucking stupid?
[SPEAKER_05]: Another F you to the RIAA MPAA for taking down supernova.org.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rot in hell, you bastards.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it's funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: Wait!
[SPEAKER_05]: If you actually go to supernova.org and check out the site, it says that they shut down due to bandwidth issues, not because of the RIA or MPAA.
[SPEAKER_05]: However, bi-torrent.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's not B-U-I, but B-I, like bisexual, bi-torrent.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And thank me later.
[SPEAKER_24]: And all I have to say is... There's something else probably going to come out that's going to replace BitTorrent anyways.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm coming out of the booth!
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm just using Torrent Reactor right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, back to the FUs.
[SPEAKER_05]: And an FU, continuing DJ Ranma S, and an FU to the customer that tried to kick my ass for buying the very last mini PS2 in my store.
[SPEAKER_05]: Suck on a cold!
[SPEAKER_24]: Stop buying smaller products!
[SPEAKER_24]: Goddammit, Sony's trying to do to you what they did, or what Nintendo did with the Game Boy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Just release the same shit, smaller and less, uh...
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm gonna shove that tube up your ass that you're using for the sound effects.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sherlock has an FU.
[SPEAKER_05]: An FU to the Syracuse DDR scene for being a bunch of hypocritical shit-talkers.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're the reason why I hate going to the local arcades.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Jazz says, F you to Fog.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to drive via road reflectors last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: DarkSakura sends a message and it says, I want to offer a fuck you to that Sky guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: He really pisses me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_05]: Screw you, hippie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jaded2004 says, F you to my windows for making it cold in here because it's 12 degrees outside.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, it's time to move to the Bahamas.
[SPEAKER_24]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't see it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: Can I see that tube for a minute?
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I want to do the sound effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: Come on, let me do the sound effect.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is God talking.
[SPEAKER_00]: Loki, you need to be punished.
[SPEAKER_24]: He has rock jerbs on it now.
[SPEAKER_24]: I Frenched it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rychan says, F you to the manic depressants that seem to find me and being the person I am, listening to their whining and act like their friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to my awesome week coming to an end on my birthday.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to myself for crying so much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rychan needs an Orange Lounge hug.
Hug!
[SPEAKER_05]: and F you to my ignition pads finally biting the dust.
[SPEAKER_05]: I loved you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nine months of accomplishments.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cry face.
[SPEAKER_05]: Illusion says F you to this crazy lady that was honking at us and flipping us off as we headed home from Knott's Berry Farm last night.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, hold on.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have two issues with that.
[SPEAKER_05]: A, when you're in SoCal, that's the way everybody drives down there.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're all fucking nuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And B, what the hell were you doing at Knott's Berry Farm?
[SPEAKER_24]: Dude, that place rocks.
[SPEAKER_24]: You can make your own candles.
[SPEAKER_05]: Knott's Berry Farm.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about now, but five years ago, man, the laughing stock of theme parks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know about you, but how can they have a theme park based around jelly?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jelly Land.
[SPEAKER_05]: With Snoopy and his jelly bandits.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like an overrated, like...
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't even know what.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, illusion continues.
[SPEAKER_05]: F you to myself for being too greedy to want to pay my own hard-earned money on other people.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, yeah, emphasis on hard.
[SPEAKER_05]: And F you to televangelism.
[SPEAKER_05]: And lastly...
[SPEAKER_05]: Podo says, F you to imbalanced paladins in the World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm tired of killing the thing three times.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, don't play World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_05]: And another F you to Loki for that Virgin Mary comment.
[SPEAKER_05]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: But do F you to not say, and I quote, JK, but do F you to not saying Merry Christmas, everyone.
[SPEAKER_24]: Christmas?
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_05]: No more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Chris Mass?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_24]: Christ Mass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Illusion says Knott's Berry Farm is only ten bucks now.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_05]: Do they pay you ten dollars to go there?
[SPEAKER_05]: So if an enema is ten dollars.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you guys want to do some listless tonight?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, we need some folks to participate in Listless tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, you're going to do it, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure enough.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you're going to do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I'm going to do it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, are you going to do it?
[SPEAKER_05]: And why don't you two share?
[SPEAKER_05]: The couch gets to share.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: I changed my mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian gets to do it by himself.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jonas, you don't get to do it because you were late.
[SPEAKER_05]: But if you want to do it late, or if you want to do it... Jonas is late.
[SPEAKER_05]: Is he pregnant?
[SPEAKER_05]: If you want to help Arcadian, you can.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: The way Listless works... Okay, we haven't done Listless in a long time, but the way Listless works, because you know how we have this obsession in our society where we have to create the top list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we have to have the top three of all... Actually, can I have the tube?
[SPEAKER_05]: Can I have the tube for a minute?
[SPEAKER_05]: It's the top three of all time.
[SPEAKER_24]: Beatmania2DX
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumor is that someday, somehow, they're going to bring it over to the USA.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they can't really call it Beatmania 2DX, because there was no Beatmania DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, you can't really call it Hip Hop Mania either, because that's gay.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, we have to come up with a new name for Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: So tonight, we're going to come up with the top three names for Beatmania 2DX in America of all time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Your head does not have the water for properties of the tube!
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, remember guys, top three names for Beatmania 2DX's American release of all time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, of course, to humor those people that are going to get out there and go, you know, Orange Lounge Radio, you fags.
[SPEAKER_05]: What they should do is just call it Beat Mania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Speaking of that... I understand that.
[SPEAKER_15]: Speaking of that... My stipulation though is that nobody can pick Beat Mania 2DX as the title.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that's a given.
[SPEAKER_05]: And nobody can say Hip Hop Mania 2 either.
[SPEAKER_05]: Be more creative.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, hold on.
[SPEAKER_17]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually hear people call Beat Mania 2DX Beat Mania 2Dicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beat Me With Two Dicks?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is that what you just said?
[SPEAKER_05]: Beat Mania 2Dicks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beat You With Two Dicks?
[SPEAKER_05]: I can have that arranged.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not by me, of course.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, so just humor us a little bit, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're coming up with new names, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: In the meantime, we're going to go to a break featuring some tracks from Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, who knew that I would want to choose this kind of song?
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to hear the Safari?
[SPEAKER_05]: You want to hear a Safari?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll do the Safari, because the Safari's been in like every 2DX.
[SPEAKER_25]: Alright, we'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
Gaming Radio, so uncensored.
[SPEAKER_05]: and even Tom Brokaw could get a job with us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello everybody and welcome back to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're about to get this listless segment underway.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember that we are trying to find the top three names that they could call Beatmania 2DX if they released it in the US.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because you can't call it 2DX because there was no one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course, then you could argue that Hip Hop Mania would be the name.
[SPEAKER_05]: But that's gay, so we're not going to call it that either.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we're going to find a new name for it here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or for anybody that plays Final Fantasy XI with me, it's SoTeets.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yes, DarkSakura, you need, it's right, well, you threw it on the floor.
[SPEAKER_05]: Somebody did.
[SPEAKER_15]: Um, Rob?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Addict!
[SPEAKER_15]: Then again, I'm over here chatting with two people about PSO.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, you're like, oh, I'm going to go home and I'm going to play PSO all night.
[SPEAKER_15]: No, I'm going to go eat my shake.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, let's see.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was going to try to find some game show music here, but I don't know if I have anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dammit!
[SPEAKER_05]: We need Price is Right music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I kind of have Price is Right music.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I do have an idea what we could do.
[SPEAKER_15]: We need Plinko music.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't have... There is no Plinko music.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_15]: We need the yodeling one.
[SPEAKER_15]: You know which one that is where he goes up the mountain?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I got a better idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to do this one.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's not that it's a... Okay, seriously, stop.
[SPEAKER_24]: That's right, everybody.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's time to play Listless.
[SPEAKER_24]: Tonight's celebrities for Listless will be determining our list of the top three names for Beatmania 2DX in America of all time.
[SPEAKER_25]: Say hello to DarkSakura!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh shit, my clothes are done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say hello to Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to DDR Angel!
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Say hello to Arcadia42!
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, wow, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: And say hello to Barker'sBeautyExplicit!
[SPEAKER_06]: Motherfucker!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: And now, introducing...
[SPEAKER_05]: Sky!
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here I am.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not that I use two voices or anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go around and see what everybody came up with, and I'm going to write them down here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Remember, chat room, you guys have the final say.
[SPEAKER_05]: And in great reality radio fare, there's an elimination round where we're going to take out some of the ones that we deem to be crappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's hear it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, number three.
[SPEAKER_15]: I can't believe it's not BB and GDX.
[SPEAKER_24]: I can't believe it's not B-Mania 2DX!
[SPEAKER_05]: Why that name?
[SPEAKER_05]: Any reason why?
[SPEAKER_15]: Because it's not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_05]: You're number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Toast!
[SPEAKER_05]: Any reason why you're calling it Super Toast?
[SPEAKER_24]: Because it's better than normal toast.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, DDR Angel, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_05]: She needs more time.
[SPEAKER_05]: You got a number three at least?
[SPEAKER_05]: You got one?
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, Jamie can scream at it now.
[SPEAKER_05]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: You could.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, I don't know if Rob's going to laugh when you say it already.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just say it already.
[SPEAKER_13]: Spinning Tatoo Master.
[SPEAKER_25]: Spinning what?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, that's not right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Spinning Tatoo Mania.
[SPEAKER_15]: Spinning Tarou Mania!
[SPEAKER_15]: Why would I laugh at a Final Fantasy XI joke?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: My number three pick, because I was thinking that they want to actually sell copies of this game, so they'd have to borrow from another franchise.
[SPEAKER_05]: So my number three pick for a name would be Rumble Roses 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumble Roses 2!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, uh, Arcadian42 and Xplizit, what number 3 name did you come up with?
[SPEAKER_05]: We're gonna do it separately.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can do it separately, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, you're number 3, Arcadian.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, uh, play it to these stupid Americans.
[SPEAKER_25]: It's gonna be, it's like keys and stuff!
[SPEAKER_25]: It's like keys and stuff!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, explicit, your number three pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: My number three pick would be Beatbox Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Beatbox Revolution!
[SPEAKER_05]: Any reason why?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's gross sounding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I explained it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, let's go on to our number two picks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Starting off with Jamie.
[SPEAKER_25]: Button Smashing Game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Button Smashing Game!
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would go with... He puts a lot of work into this, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's gonna be, um, how about just Turntable Mania?
[SPEAKER_05]: Turntable Mania!
[SPEAKER_05]: God, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I gotta think of a better one.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Angel, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_13]: This one sucks, too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_13]: DJ Spin Master.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Spin Master!
[SPEAKER_05]: My number two pick, again, going with the theme of they actually want to sell copies of this game in the US, would be MTV Presents Britney Mania 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: Brit Mania, for short.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to Arcadian 42.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something a bit more normal.
[SPEAKER_06]: Feel the Beat Mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Feel the Beat Mania!
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretend you're a real DJ, but not...
[SPEAKER_25]: Pretend you're a real DJ, but not!
Is it but not or but you're not?
[SPEAKER_15]: I had that, but not really.
[SPEAKER_23]: Pretend you're a real DJ, but not really!
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, you're number one.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had to think long and hard on this, okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's Super Monkey Wombat Cheese Burrito.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Monkey Wombat Cheese Burrito Any particular reason why you want to call a video game with falling bars Super Monkey Wombat Cheese Burrito?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because it fits.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're an idiot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, Angel.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, if he's an idiot, my next one's not that much better, but I thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: From a total noob's perspective Oh shit, there's too much to do!
[SPEAKER_13]: The game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh shit!
[SPEAKER_00]: There's too much to do!
[SPEAKER_00]: The game!
[SPEAKER_05]: My number one pick...
[SPEAKER_05]: My number one pick, I think, really encompasses what the game is really all about.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I've been playing Bomani for a long, long time, and I've been looking at the forums and everything, and I think I've captured the name that really shows what this game is all about.
[SPEAKER_05]: So my number one pick, Elitist Elitist Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elitist Elitist Revolution!
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadian 42, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to be Ringo.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's not me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Turntablist King.
[SPEAKER_06]: Turntablist King!
[SPEAKER_05]: Any reason why?
[SPEAKER_06]: Cuz.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, cuz, I like that.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Jonas, aka Explicit, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: DJ Chasm, the international finger-banging music game.
[SPEAKER_00]: DJ Chasm, the international finger-banging music game.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, boy, we have a whole lot on this list here, and six of them are going to come off this list right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me read the list here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe it's not Beatmania 2DX, Super Toast, Spinning Taru Mania, Rumble Roses 2, It's Like Keys and Stuff, Beatbox Revolution, Button Smashing Game, Turntable Mania, DJ Spinmaster, MTV Presents, Britney Mania 2005, Feel the Beat Mania, Mix It Up, Pretend You're a Real DJ But Not Really, Super Monkey Wombat Cheese Burrito, Oh Shit There's Too Much To Do, The Game, Elitist Elitist Revolution, Turntablist King,
[SPEAKER_05]: and DJ Gazm, the international finger-banging music game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie, one of these sadly has to come off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: What's coming off?
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Toast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Toast is toast.
[SPEAKER_05]: Loki, which one of these is coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_24]: Sadly, Beatbox Revolution because there is a beatboxing game coming out and that's not beatboxing.
[SPEAKER_24]: And that's another reason I'm there.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Angel, which one of these has to come off the list?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like Keys and Stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like Keys and Stuff off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to eliminate, sadly, sorry Angel, but Spinning Tarou Mania's got to come off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: As much as I love Final Fantasy XI, even 2DX isn't that good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, Arcadian42, what's coming off the list?
[SPEAKER_05]: That Britney whatever thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like so over.
[SPEAKER_05]: MTV presents Britney Mania 2005 because, in the words of Arcadian 42, it's so over.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Britney is so last year, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, like totally.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to get on the forums and tell those Orange Lines Radio people that Britney is so 2003, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: Jonas, you're the last one to get to eliminate something off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate to say this, but I'll have to say Rumble Roses 2.
[SPEAKER_05]: You bastard!
[SPEAKER_05]: That was the best name on there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rumble Roses 2 is off the list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to paste the list in the chat room and you guys can send a private message with your vote right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: So send a private message with your vote.
[SPEAKER_05]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let me get the music for this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe it's not Beatmania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_05]: Button smashing game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Turntable mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Spinmaster.
[SPEAKER_05]: Feel the beat mania.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mix it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: Pretend you're a real DJ, but not really.
[SPEAKER_05]: Super Monkey Wombat Cheese Burrito, oh shit there's too much to do, the game, Elitist Elitist Revolution, Turntablist King, and DJ Gasm, the international finger banging music game, place your vote right now by sending a private message to Sky with your vote, and the winners will be announced very soon, we have to go to one quick break, it looks like we're running over a little bit guys tonight, I apologize, hopefully nobody cares right, nobody cares if we run a little bit over tonight,
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go to a quick music break.
[SPEAKER_05]: We're going to do a 2DX song, but we'll do a long song.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's one of my very favorite 2DX songs of all time, and I want to play this so you guys can deal.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's whored out everywhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: Everywhere people play this song.
[SPEAKER_05]: And when we come back from this song, we're going to announce the winner, so please hurry up, get your votes in now, so we're going to announce the winner, and we're going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be back here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't go away yet, because we're going to tell you what's coming up next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, you can leave to the laundry room, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm just telling the listeners, alright?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we'll be back.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_00]: Hiho, Kermit the E-Fog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_11]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we are back to wrap it up here on Orange Lounge Radio, but I know you are dying to know what won tonight's list list.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are you ready for this, guys?
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's time to announce...
[SPEAKER_00]: The top three lists of all time!
[SPEAKER_02]: Names that we would call Beatmania 2DX here in America.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was a very close vote tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very, very, very, very close vote tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But in the end, three of them came out victorious.
[SPEAKER_00]: In third place, DJ GASM, the International Finger Banging Music Game.
[SPEAKER_00]: In second place, oh shit, there's too much to do, The Game.
[SPEAKER_00]: And in first place, drumroll please, Elitist Elitist Revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you everybody for playing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Listless is not a Mark Goodson production.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so I guess that's going to wrap it up for the show, you guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think that sums it up for me there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Elitist, elitist revolution.
[SPEAKER_05]: And on that note, our show is over.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, yeah, 9.30 already?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, it's already.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's past 9.30.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's 9.34 over there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we've got to get this wrapped up.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, so we've got to go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you, everybody, for tuning in tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next week, more presents.
[SPEAKER_05]: More of Jamie's Laundry next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, maybe.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: And a new end of the year special.
[SPEAKER_05]: And that means, of course, we've got to do this again.
[SPEAKER_05]: We've got to do a list list for the best Bomani song of the year.
[SPEAKER_05]: So that's going to be a big one.
[SPEAKER_05]: So more information to come on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hope you guys can join us for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: And much more to come next week on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: More information on Night Style if we get it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Jamie wants to give her final thought right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, Jamie, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wish I were home so I could change into my freshly washed pajama bottoms.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're comfy and soft and smell like gain.
[SPEAKER_05]: Drive around in your pajama bottoms.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's what I do.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, she's holding it to her face like a gas mask.
[SPEAKER_05]: I exquisite your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Can't hear you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I seriously can't hear you, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't hear him.
[SPEAKER_05]: Get him the other mic.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quick, quick.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, he has to walk over here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck SPGL3 Drama, enjoy the holidays, so HO!
[SPEAKER_17]: HO!
[SPEAKER_05]: You like them hoes, don't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Merry Christmas, and a happy fucking New Year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Merry Christmas.
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Arcadium, DDR Angel, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ting!
[SPEAKER_05]: Arcadium42, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_05]: Cross your fingers, we'll have to play the whole damn fine.
[SPEAKER_24]: I gotta buy me one of those bootleg Nintendo things in the mall because they're still selling them even though they got in trouble for that shit.
[SPEAKER_24]: Then I gotta look at my cabinet because my cabinet's lonely and needs more interfaces.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my final thought for tonight, everybody, is bootay.
[SPEAKER_24]: My final thought is Super Monkey Wombat Cheese Burrito.
[SPEAKER_05]: Which didn't get a single vote, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_24]: It will have a special place in my heart.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, that'll be the time you're getting your 12th bypass.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have to have that surgically removed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright guys, thanks for staying a little bit long with us tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing too bad.
[SPEAKER_05]: But thank you very much everybody for tuning in and listening and supporting Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: We really do appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't forget, we are on 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
[SPEAKER_05]: OrangeLawnsRadio.com Big changes coming to the station in 2005.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yep, 2005 when we'll quit.
[SPEAKER_24]: No more.
[SPEAKER_24]: You guys do realize that we're quitting, you know.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's coming to the new year.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quit making all these threats.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final word of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll give it to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_05]: Final word of the show, please.
Boop.
[SPEAKER_23]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live.
[SPEAKER_23]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production.
[SPEAKER_23]: For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: The first thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me Is finding a Christmas tree The second thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me Rigging up the lights And finding a Christmas tree
[SPEAKER_11]: A third thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me Hangovers, rigging up the lights, and finding a Christmas tree A fourth thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me Sending Christmas cards, hangovers, rigging up the lights, and finding a Christmas tree A fifth thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me
[SPEAKER_11]: Five months of pills Sending Christmas cards Hangovers Wrecking up the lights And finding a Christmas tree The sixth thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me Facing my in-laws Five months of pills I hate those Christmas cards Hangovers Wrecking up these lights And finding a Christmas tree
[SPEAKER_11]: The seventh thing at Christmas that's such a pain to me Is still Misha Donnie Facing my in-laws Five months of bills Vending Christmas cards Oh, jeez!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm trying to rig up these lights!
[SPEAKER_11]: And finding a Christmas tree
[SPEAKER_11]: The eighth thing at Christmas, that's such a pain to me Our great farmer, the Christmas Charity, what do you mean you were in Lourdes?
[SPEAKER_11]: Five months of bills Making up these cards You just give me a beer, huh?
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we have no extension cards Finding a Christmas tree The ninth thing at Christmas, that's such a pain to me
[SPEAKER_11]: Finding parking spaces Daddy, I want some candy Donations Facing the field Five months of bills Writing up those Christmas cards Hangovers Now why the hell are they blinking?
[SPEAKER_11]: And finding a Christmas tree
[SPEAKER_11]: The tip they get Christmas, that's such a pain to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: Battery's not included.
[SPEAKER_11]: No parking spaces.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bobby doesn't!
[SPEAKER_11]: Get a job, you bum!
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, facing me, you lost.
[SPEAKER_11]: Five months of bills.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yo-ho, sending Christmas cards.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, jeez, look at this.
[SPEAKER_11]: One light goes out, they all go out!
[SPEAKER_11]: And finding a Christmas tree.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't even know half these people.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, who's got the charity paper?
[SPEAKER_11]: Get a flashlight, I'd love to!
[SPEAKER_11]: The 12th thing at Christmas, that's such a thing to me Singing Christmas carols, sale TV specials Batteries not included, no parking
[SPEAKER_11]: Charity!
[SPEAKER_11]: Gotta make them dinner!
[SPEAKER_11]: Five months of dinner!
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm not sending them this year, that's it!
[SPEAKER_11]: Shucks, up you!
[SPEAKER_11]: Fine, you're so smart, you'll rig up their life!
[SPEAKER_11]: And find it a Christmas tree!
[SPEAKER_23]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_05]: Orange Lounge Radio, the post-show, or the afterbirth, as we so lovingly called it for these past two and a half years, where we talk about all that other stuff that we didn't get to quite on the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can't believe we've been doing it this long.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, it's seriously time to quit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah, fuck me.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_05]: Quitter, quitter.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll be doing this right.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, I got a fortune cookie today.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was really weird.
[SPEAKER_05]: It said something about, like, something you are focusing on, and I was thinking about Orange Lounge Radio when I read it.
[SPEAKER_05]: It said something you are focusing on, it will grow a lot in this next year.
[SPEAKER_05]: It'll be very interesting to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although we have a really boring webcam.
[SPEAKER_05]: We seriously need to start pointing that somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, we need to get a goldfish or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, when you were reading that fortune, I was thinking of my penis, so...
[SPEAKER_05]: I had so much food today.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Panda Express and I ate like a three combo.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you break the webcam?
[SPEAKER_05]: Way to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm so awesome.
[SPEAKER_05]: That wasn't Jamie, that was me.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're belchy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am going home, bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: You're going home?
[SPEAKER_05]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to go home to my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, you're going to E3s next year, right?
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: If we end up deciding to go to The Price is Right, will you go?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because hearing Come On Down made me think of, you know, when I went to The Price is Right a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was so much fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: And Loki, you're going to go too?
[SPEAKER_05]: I have to go before he dies.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, what if I'm a contestant?
[SPEAKER_05]: We all have to wear... Oh my god, if you were a contestant on that show, I'd pee myself because you'd be so shy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'd pee if I died.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd be like, yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god!
[SPEAKER_15]: I wouldn't be one of those screamy, happy, clappy people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, hi, you girls are ugly!
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd be like, wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: I suppose I'd pick this.
[SPEAKER_05]: You'd have an orgasm and you'd know it.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_15]: Don't touch me.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh my god, you're orange.
[SPEAKER_05]: I want to go, and we all should wear matching shirts.
[SPEAKER_05]: and we can hype it up on the station and have it be the big Orange Lounge Radio television debut.
[SPEAKER_15]: I did internet radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, hype it up.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Orange Lounge Radio television debut.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_15]: Except when one of us walks behind the G4 camera.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a good night, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anybody else want to add anything?
[SPEAKER_05]: You're dying to see The Price is Right live in person, aren't you?
[SPEAKER_05]: I've watched that show since I was five.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh really?
[SPEAKER_05]: What was on it last week?
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_09]: Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: The most difficult thing I've ever tried to do is to clear the mind.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright everybody, that's going to do it for our post show here on