[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_00]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_09]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is episode number 121 for this
[SPEAKER_12]: December the 5th of 2004.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're tuned in to the B-Money Scene's most longest running radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_12]: My name is Rob Roberts, you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_12]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_12]: In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, back from her vacation.
[SPEAKER_12]: Say hello to DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, they wanted to keep me.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, you can't let them keep you.
[SPEAKER_13]: They all had grits.
[SPEAKER_05]: I ate at the Waffle House!
[SPEAKER_05]: And I had my hash browns smothered, covered, chunked, and diced.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: All she's missing is her accent.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll talk more about the trip a little later on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also with us, as always, say hello to our tech massa who's setting up the webcam right now, Loki!
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's try that again.
[SPEAKER_01]: Say hello to our tech master, Loki!
[SPEAKER_12]: Joining us tonight are some very special guests.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the usual crowd.
[SPEAKER_12]: Say hello to DDR Angel.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's a very happy hello, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: And also say hello to Arcadian42.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I want to talk about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because we just had an 80s pre-show and it kind of ties into that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That little thing you're playing right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, we got a whole lot of interesting stuff to talk about tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, I'm lying.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's really not a whole lot going on, but we're going to try to film three hours best we can anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know I want to talk about 8 Style tonight, Pop Music 10, because I got to play both those this week for the first time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, How's Your Week, How's Your Day, Cage Match, all that fun stuff when we come back after this break featuring...
[SPEAKER_12]: Music from DDR Third Mix, because Third Mix was cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to join us in our chat room, there's quite a little crowd there already.
[SPEAKER_12]: Head on over to www.orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_12]: After this, boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_09]: Some of the new programming coming to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Jamie, I have a suggestion about some of the music in our Bomani Music and More program.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_06]: No subject will ever be taboo.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I was thinking maybe we should move Pump Up the Volume from Tuesday Nights.
[SPEAKER_13]: Except, of course, a subject that was just under discussion.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, well, what would you think if maybe we cut back on some of the tack music we play on the station?
[SPEAKER_06]: I collect your fucking head.
[SPEAKER_13]: Just like this fucker here.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, why did you do that to Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: The hot thing on episode 69 was just a joke!
[SPEAKER_13]: Now if any of you sons of bitches got anything else to say, now's the fucking time!
[SPEAKER_09]: Orange Lounge Radio, where everybody has a say.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: The lovely and wonderful Jamie there in that promo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, sort of.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ash played by Lucy Liu.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: You remember that a long time ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: This was like probably the first year of Orange Lounge Radio, which it's sad that that could be considered retro, but it really is.
[SPEAKER_12]: You remember way back during the first year of this program when somebody had talked about, I want to say it was Dark Tetsuya was somehow involved with this, brought up the casting of the Orange Lounge movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: And they took votes in the chat room and they said that you should be played by Lucy Liu.
[SPEAKER_05]: How ironic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Which is, yeah, how ironic.
[SPEAKER_12]: A little too ironic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially considering you're not Asian at all.
[SPEAKER_05]: No.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_05]: I finally got something new when I went to Alabama.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be like me being played by Denzel Washington.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, Alabama?
[SPEAKER_05]: I got, um, I believe it was, I thought you were taller.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, this is a good segue.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've got to get into how was your week, how was your day, because I've got to figure out about what this is all about.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, Jamie, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: My couple of weeks were pretty decent.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very, very, very, very, very busy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's see, with my trip to Alabama, I got there, my mom got us lost and away from New Orleans.
[SPEAKER_05]: We ended up heading up toward Hattiesburg.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's something stuck in this thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, we ended up going up to Hattiesburg.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then right when mom realized where we were we had to go around a different way so we headed home.
[SPEAKER_05]: Got there, I didn't get in bed until 6 in the morning central.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means I had been up an official 24 hours because I woke up at 4 pacific in the morning.
[SPEAKER_12]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: My ass crashed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Next day was Thanksgiving but we didn't do Thanksgiving stuff, we just slept.
[SPEAKER_05]: I did some hanging out, you know, it was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_05]: Then on Friday I went to Dothan, saw my daddy, my Uncle Dale.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Uncle Dale and my daddy are having their second childhoods.
[SPEAKER_05]: My Uncle Dale has a... A.K.A.
[SPEAKER_12]: midlife crisis.
[SPEAKER_05]: 2004 Mustang GT.
[SPEAKER_05]: My daddy has a Camaro.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, my daddy is cute on the internet, because they have this old 500 megahertz kind of crappy thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my daddy is so cute playing on it, because he just hunts and texts with little keys, and it's so cute.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my daddy sends me everything in 72-point font and email.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's adorable.
[SPEAKER_12]: I used to be that way on AOL Instant Messenger.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would type to everybody in huge 72-point font, and they'd be like, knock it off!
[SPEAKER_12]: But I figured my chats are very important, and I want to make sure they're not missed.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, so Saturday, we had our official Thanksgiving at my uncle's house, and we had fried turkey.
[SPEAKER_05]: Mmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: What about deep fried turkey?
[SPEAKER_13]: Deep fried turkey.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know how dangerous that shit is to make?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, but it's so yummy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, my uncle had a very nice deep fryer with a lid and everything.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it was very gummy because it makes all of the meat just super juicy.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it had all kinds of things that I'm not supposed to eat.
[SPEAKER_05]: On the way to Dothan, though, I had boiled peanuts.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I passed by two movie galleries and saluted them for you, Loki.
[SPEAKER_05]: Like, you know, the single finger salute.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then that night, I went to Ground Zero.
[SPEAKER_05]: which is a comic book store with gaming tables.
[SPEAKER_05]: There were lots of people playing Yu-Gi-Oh and I felt really nerdy.
[SPEAKER_05]: But downstairs there was an arcade there.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a very strange name for an arcade in light of recent events.
[SPEAKER_12]: Isn't it great?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But there was...
[SPEAKER_05]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_05]: I met Dork.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I met quite a few people.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, I met the... I'm supposing that he's in charge of the machines there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He goes by Pyramus Online.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very, very cool guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to a... I went to a Bomani party!
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: You went to a Bomani party?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just randomly got invited to a Bomani party down there?
[SPEAKER_05]: They were all heading over, so I went over and played 8th Style on a widescreen TV, and that was rad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, you just...
[SPEAKER_12]: You went over to strangers' houses to play video games?
[SPEAKER_05]: We actually lived about a block away from where my ex-roommates lived.
[SPEAKER_05]: So it was very close.
[SPEAKER_05]: and I went over, of course, to hang out with my mama's son and my papa's son and K-Kitty and Bobby and we had a pretty good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: We watched movies.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw the end of The Day After Tomorrow and no offense, but that movie sucks.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't think... That's my very professional opinion.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know a lot of people who are going to disagree with you there.
[SPEAKER_05]: My mom loves the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: They love the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really want to put down anyone else's opinion of it, but my opinion of it is crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I learned the fine art of DVD duplication.
[SPEAKER_05]: and so I was able to deliver a copy of Kill Bill Volume 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Launchator does not advocate piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes it does.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I got, actually you know there's that show Kindred the Embraced that came on based off of the White Wolf Universe and I have all the episodes they ever made of that because I think that the actor died.
[SPEAKER_05]: The main guy who's playing the prince.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I have all of that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still have it on my, if anyone brings me DVDs you'll get copies.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um... Orange Sounds Radio does not advocate piracy.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's actually, they're not... I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're not licensed right now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I want to find out more about this Bomani party, because basically you went over to a stranger's house.
[SPEAKER_13]: I sang, Rob.
[SPEAKER_13]: People that stalk us on the internet, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Are these people our listeners?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, okay, so message to our listeners, stalking us works.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, uh... I was hanging out with a lot of... A lot of the people, though, were people from DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, no, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, I mean, you got...
[SPEAKER_12]: You've got the moderatorship on DDR Freak, so a lot of people know who you are over there.
[SPEAKER_12]: The show's getting pretty big over there, thanks to the syndication on Friday nights over there on Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was just a bunch of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I met a lot of good people.
[SPEAKER_05]: We basically were just playing 8th style.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now, we brought out Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now you don't sing karaoke.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't, but I got the line from Adventures in Babysitting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nobody leaves without singing the blues.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's all it took?
[SPEAKER_13]: They didn't have to feed you Guinness or anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: I was begged.
[SPEAKER_13]: They didn't make you drink Guinness or anything?
[SPEAKER_13]: You just did it perfectly sober?
[SPEAKER_13]: I just figured it was going to be about another year before I'm back.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you knew that there were no recording devices present, so... So I sang Bizarre Love Triangle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no, that's a good song.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, see, you missed some karaoke action here on the show last week.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I didn't miss it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I actually, I was really... Loki's still pissed at me over it, by the way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I actually was going to be trying to tune in on my laptop, but I had promised my mama-son I was going to take her to see The Grudge, which after having, since I was glad I saw Ju-on first, very glad I saw it first, because then, it was neat noting the differences in the movie, I'm not going to spoil it for anyone who hasn't, and actually, the thing that pissed me off is that I don't know the reason why they think they have to explain every single last fucking detail to a US audience.
[SPEAKER_05]: When it's the not knowing that is the messed up part of the movie.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even so, I thought it was very good.
[SPEAKER_05]: And even better, especially since it was done by the original director.
[SPEAKER_05]: So, um, we did that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went to Steak and Shake.
[SPEAKER_05]: Steak and Shake is the best place ever.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_05]: Steak and Shake.
[SPEAKER_12]: Only in the South, which you have a place called Steak and Shake.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's these thick hamburgers, really good.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's like a little diner type place.
[SPEAKER_05]: But you can get these humongous milkshakes and they make a half and half.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's literally split down the middle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Half one side is one flavor, half the other is the other.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I actually mixed it up and had banana eggnog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, God, it was good.
[SPEAKER_05]: That was orgasm in a glass.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, it didn't taste like tuna.
[SPEAKER_05]: It tasted like banana and eggnog.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: I got to meet lots of good people.
[SPEAKER_05]: I had a really good time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Monday, my brother was being an ass the whole time.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm not too proud of my brother Matthew.
[SPEAKER_05]: I talked to my brother Phillip while I was there.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's supposed to be down for Christmas, I think.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's getting married.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, he's already married.
[SPEAKER_05]: This is my brother who's a marine, and his wife's a marine, and they're actually going to Texas to have a humongous big Mexican wedding.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm going to go.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because this is going to be a big party.
[SPEAKER_12]: Will there be margaritas involved?
[SPEAKER_05]: Likely.
[SPEAKER_05]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, people that know me pretty well know that I'm actually not a big tequila fan.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll drink margaritas because you can barely taste the tequila, but I cannot stand straight up tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, you had that cheap shit here.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I still don't like tequila.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can give me Cuervo.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_12]: I still don't like it.
[SPEAKER_05]: I can do shots of tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it's nasty.
[SPEAKER_05]: I like the Blue Agave tequila.
[SPEAKER_05]: The stuff that Anita had way back at the Nasty House.
[SPEAKER_05]: But it was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_05]: I went back to New Orleans on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hung out with my mommy.
[SPEAKER_05]: I fussed at my mom.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: and then Jamie Fuss had the most long, boring flight back.
[SPEAKER_05]: I hung out at the Dallas airport for nearly two hours.
[SPEAKER_12]: Airports aren't so bad now, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: They have Wi-Fi there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, they got Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just chilling on my laptop.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not just that, but everything there is to do.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're practically shopping malls as well, although I would never buy anything there, but it's fun to look.
[SPEAKER_12]: Airports aren't that bad anymore.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, some of them are.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I was having a pretty good time, I mean.
[SPEAKER_05]: And then I got on a plane.
[SPEAKER_05]: I read the entirety of Ramsey's The Damned on the plane.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just, I have to say, safely, the Dust and Rice book, because all the rest of her stuff since, it's kind of crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's been gay porn.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, but it's also some crappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really crappy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Woman needs to get her groove back.
[SPEAKER_05]: Not rest on her name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although I did read the first novel of her Sleeping Beauty book.
[SPEAKER_05]: Very interesting, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, that was my trip.
[SPEAKER_05]: The rest of the time I finished homework, put up with stupid crap.
[SPEAKER_12]: You talking about that Bomani party makes me nostalgic.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember when we used to do that stuff?
[SPEAKER_12]: At the old studio, which was a really great house for having parties.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'd have the Bomani parties.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to do that shit again.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, we kinda had a Bomani party last night.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, it wasn't like a hardcore Bomani party, but I'm sure we'll get to that as we go on through How's Your Week, How's Your Day.
[SPEAKER_05]: You remember the stuff I would bring with me?
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: People would say Bomani party, and I'm like, aw, shit.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember you brought your Dreamcast pads to one party.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was insane.
[SPEAKER_05]: I said, okay, this is what DDR was like in the old days before we had this vivid nonsense.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember when one of our old guests used to be on the show a bit, Somi Magus, when he put on his girlfriend's top and was playing Par Par Paradise.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the picture made some rounds on the internet after that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I remember Loki would haul his computer and his Delight Delight reduplication and his pads he'd made for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm nostalgic.
[SPEAKER_05]: I would carry around the Drum Mania, Keyboard Mania, 2DX Controller, the bunch of games.
[SPEAKER_05]: All the old beat manias, my ASCII pad.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you think that when this DDR thing is dead, which, you know, could happen any day now, do you think that these Bomani parties are still going to be going on?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, we'll just go back to porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll just have to go back to the orgies, you're right.
[SPEAKER_12]: How silly of me to ask.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know, we'd have to get that copy of Ally McFeel again.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, anything else you want to share about your week and your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: Moving right along, alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, it had a cameo by Ron Jeremy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh my god, I was looking up, um, there's a site online that's like, uh, these, uh, just paper dolls online, and I was trying to make, uh, a new avatar for myself on, uh, my live journal, and I accidentally came across the real doll site.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh god.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's very, very icky.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a request for a new DDR Freak avatar.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because the gay pimp one you made me is really cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have a request for a new one.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want a Xander from Drawn Together.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just to make Seeker jealous.
[SPEAKER_05]: From what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Drawn Together, that show on Comedy Central.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh girl, you are so far behind.
[SPEAKER_05]: I do not have anything but basic channels.
[SPEAKER_05]: The local channels.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're missing out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a funny show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I hardly ever watch TV.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I think the TV is retarded.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't even watch Survivor or The Apprentice or any of that reality bullshit anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: Drawn Together is the only show I watch.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, and look at Hell Freeze Over.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: You want to talk about Hell Freezing Over?
[SPEAKER_12]: I came this close to joining a gym on Friday.
[SPEAKER_05]: For, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: For the people who didn't have that visual, Rob held his fingers the length of, um, never mind.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because we're not going to talk about that.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_05]: No, because we don't bring up old drama.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it says that when you said Xander, I started thinking of Buffy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I need to respond to some... I need to respond to some stuff in the chatroom going on right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: First off, Sigurd's telling me he hates me because of the Xander thing, and he says his is better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: And somebody else... Where was it?
[SPEAKER_12]: A couple people commented, DDR's not gonna die!
[SPEAKER_12]: Well...
[SPEAKER_12]: I also have an announcement?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I no longer am on the Atkins crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, not crap.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's good for a lot of people.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was not good for me.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I can have sushi again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sushi is wonderful.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, and, and, and, and, and, and.
[SPEAKER_05]: Nothing else.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, Rob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: Damn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_12]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_05]: Angel, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_04]: School was school and... Oh, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Saturday was nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just wanted to waste the week away until Saturday came, because, well, I had a birthday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually hanging out with everyone was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we had played lots of Fumani, Eight Style, and Poppin' Ten.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I got to see those for the first time, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: And the best thing of all was obviously hanging around with people that I don't usually get to hang around with, so that was good.
[SPEAKER_04]: and just enjoying my birthday weekend so far, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, Bradley, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_11]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, this week was work, of course.
[SPEAKER_10]: And an interesting thing happened at work.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was a person... My kind of work is sort of a training.
[SPEAKER_10]: They train people to do stuff.
[SPEAKER_10]: So one of the students came back.
[SPEAKER_10]: He had some questions for her because he didn't do a test.
[SPEAKER_10]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_10]: The manager had to take him outside and talk for like an hour, try to calm him down, and then he came back on Friday, and his wife told him to bring along some candy just to give to us, or something like that, and he comes back and, okay, he's like, hell, here's this candy, and then he comes, and then he starts launching this big thing about discrimination!
[SPEAKER_10]: He discriminates against me!
[SPEAKER_10]: He doesn't like me!
[SPEAKER_10]: And for some reason, some bullshit like that, and so...
[SPEAKER_10]: Me and the receptionist are in the room and he's like, something kind of weird shit like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good thing the boss came in a minute later and started talking to him so we could sneak out.
[SPEAKER_10]: I went out in the hall for about an hour while they discussed something over and over again.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is the kind of guy who says the same thing like ten fucking times to try to make some sort of point that
[SPEAKER_10]: Were they getting paid for this?
[SPEAKER_10]: To talk?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it's a business, so... I always found that humorous when, you know, there's big fights going on and we have to sit down and have a discussion, but we're all getting paid for it, type thing, and we just wasted three hours of productivity to talk out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not that I ever get into disagreements with people, but, you know, I had to sit in on them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I didn't have anything to do with it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just went out and stood in the hall because I didn't want to get involved.
[SPEAKER_12]: And you got paid for it, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, so it was a nice one hour break just to not do anything.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just wait until it cooled down.
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh, okay, and on Monday I got Katamari Damashii, and that was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, every time something... It's like, it's like how when everybody says friends, you think of NBC, or when somebody says 90210, with Katamari it's... Shut up, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, actually I think of that, I think of that song too.
[SPEAKER_10]: and played that most every day this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, I did play this every day this week, except for today, because I got up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last night was the party for Angel and Anita, or DD Archipelagic, for their birthdays, and that was a lot of fun, because Navi brought over 8th Style and Poppin' Music.
[SPEAKER_12]: God bless the town's Poppin' Music whore.
[SPEAKER_10]: I got to play on those Arcade Style controllers.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and...
[SPEAKER_10]: and that was fun which I didn't do all that great on 8th style because basically he had this he had it up on a stand and then the the TV was down like a two or three feet and several feet away so and I haven't played on like an arcade style controller in a long time and of course there was the just played like the hard news songs like oh god like oh what the hell is this called Nebula Grasper Nebula Grasper is a fucking impossible
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, at least for a first try, it's like, what?
[SPEAKER_10]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_10]: All over the place.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I always love non-Bamani peoples, like the people who don't really play 2DX and DDR and stuff, I always love their reaction to stuff like that, because there were a few people at the party last night who don't really play DDR or 2DX, and they were just kind of watching Navi playing, and he was just crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: He was playing like Nebula Grasper or another or something, and everybody was just kind of like, that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is so crazy.
[SPEAKER_06]: Man, that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, actually I played pop music for the first time ever, because it's the first time I've actually been to anything where it's been brought out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I actually passed like a, I think I passed 22 on 9 button.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: And today we got up late, so it didn't do all that much.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mr. Loki, how was your week, how was your day?
[SPEAKER_11]: Today did not start out too good due to certain events that have taken place outside of our apartment complex in the street.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was not fun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, we'll get into that later, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_11]: And then yesterday, it was okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Went and...
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_11]: I can't remember Thursday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Thursday was okay, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: Most of the week I've been just playing Final Fantasy XI, leveling my summoner to 20, which I just finished right before the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_11]: What else have I been doing?
[SPEAKER_11]: I've played a little bit of Grand Theft Auto, finally passed this mission that I couldn't beat for a while, and now I have to run errands for some pimp.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um... Went and saw Closer, I'll get into that later.
[SPEAKER_11]: And, um... Eh, that's about all.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's been, like, kind of a week just crashing into the ground.
[SPEAKER_12]: That sucks about your grandma, I'm sorry to hear it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Eh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have you used your machine to try and contact her yet?
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I have not, you asshole.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you ever open your portal to hell?
[SPEAKER_12]: I was gonna say, you went on a ghostbusting trip yesterday, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_11]: Hunting.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ghost hunting, not busting.
[SPEAKER_11]: We just, we went, walked around Knights Ferry, which is basically this old abandoned, it's not really an abandoned mining town, it's just an old, um, mining town, it's got like a bunch of dilapidated, it's not really a mining town, I guess, they have an old, um, mill there that's kind of been, um, it's just the ruins of it, so we just walked around there, and they also have a very long, um, they have a 115 meter, um,
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: My example was something that's more trauma there than, you know, old.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, because necessarily just visiting any old place is not going to work.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need to have something where, oh yeah, 50 people murdered there, you know, that kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: Just something, you know, traumatic, like a sane asylum or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, no luck with any of that stuff around here, so.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_11]: So yeah, that's what I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't this place the insane asylum?
[SPEAKER_11]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: I have to haunt this place first.
[SPEAKER_11]: I haven't quite gotten around to that yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Soon enough, you know, I've been, like, I have my priorities.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, I was going to work on the cabin today, and then I just got tired.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those fuckers this morning.
[SPEAKER_12]: And by tired, he means looking for a party in Final Fantasy XI so he can get his summoner to level 20.
[SPEAKER_12]: At it!
[SPEAKER_11]: No, I was tired from other things, but yes, I just got bored of that too.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the other things in the morning made me tired because I'm exhausted right now from having to wake up early yesterday and having to wake up early today.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, my turn, my week and my day.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got to play 8th Style and Pop Music 10 twice this week, actually, because I hung out with Navi on Monday.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll talk about those games a little bit later, because, you know, I want to talk about my mommy stuff a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Navi and I, after playing some of that, we got to go to the mall, and I was going to help him do some Christmas shopping over at Arden Fair, which is a big mall in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a huge mall.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so we ended up walking out of there.
[SPEAKER_12]: He didn't end up buying anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: He just kind of looked around at some different places.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I fucking bought an iPod at the Apple store.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I wanted one, really.
[SPEAKER_13]: I wanted one really badly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm still two away from my free one.
[SPEAKER_11]: Why don't you just buy a fucking iMac, you know?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just join the cult.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've thought about it, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Good, it's a big flaming piece of shit that doesn't do anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: You make Apple users cry.
[SPEAKER_05]: Unless you're into graphics.
[SPEAKER_12]: or Media, which, you know, this show happens to be.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because all the pros are on Macs.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe we wouldn't have the freaking buzz on a Mac.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_11]: We wouldn't have any of the software either.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, besides that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Virtual PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: Besides this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I have to emulate a good PC.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just wanted an iPod actually because the stereo in my car broke a while back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, it was Sigurd's Echo Image CD that broke my CD player in the car actually because it ate it and wouldn't give it back one day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Once it heard Echo Image, it could hear no other music.
[SPEAKER_12]: Basically, it's how it all boiled down.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, it won't eject CDs anymore and now it won't even play the CD that's in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So,
[SPEAKER_12]: Luckily, though, it has an auxiliary port in it, so I can plug anything I want in there, so I'm just like, fuck it, I'm gonna get an iPod, and I'll just use that as my car stereo.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's worked out really well, except for the fact that if you think I'm bad when I'm talking on my cell phone and trying to drive, you should see me when I'm trying to find the song on my iPod I want to hear and drive at the same time.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's beautiful.
[SPEAKER_05]: and you know what they can pass all the laws they want to say I can't talk on my cell phone and drive but I don't see them making any law anytime soon that says I can't play on my iPod and try to drive at the same time so look out I believe the law is operation of electronic devices while driving so your iPod's included god damn it extraneous like CD like laptops peripheral devices
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, Sigurd in our chatroom right now over at OrangeLaunchRadio.com, he says that that day where my echo image, or his echo image CD got eaten by my car stereo player, he said that that day kind of pissed him off.
[SPEAKER_12]: Except for the Classic Gaming Expo and the little girl that was hitting all the buttons on the restrooms that she rocked.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that reminds me, I actually found the picture of Jamie doing that at Classic Gaming Expo.
[SPEAKER_13]: I had my heads in the air.
[SPEAKER_13]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_13]: We paid you $10 to do it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I spent it on Pac-Land for the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, we bought some game for you, basically, for you to imitate a little girl.
[SPEAKER_12]: I found the picture.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to send it to Sigurd.
[SPEAKER_05]: By the way, we're going to the Classic Gaming Expo again this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even though... It's a bowling game.
[SPEAKER_05]: Even though last year was kind of... The only reason that last year's was eh was because they had that thing a few days before.
[SPEAKER_05]: The Classic Gaming Expo this year is going to be in Burlingame.
[SPEAKER_05]: That means trips to network video.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the store that sells the airsoft guns.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, and I guess that was pretty much my week of my day.
[SPEAKER_12]: I spent a lot of time playing Final Fantasy XI as well because basically I got stood up Friday night, so I decided to wither away my sorrows inside a nice game of Final Fantasy XI, so...
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_12]: The freaking game took us three hours to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: The last time I played Cranium it only took two.
[SPEAKER_12]: Turbo Cranium ended up taking longer.
[SPEAKER_12]: What in the hell is up with that?
[SPEAKER_12]: And no, it's not because we kept taking breaks.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just was a long-ass game.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was no shorter.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nobody's gonna get this joke but you, Rob, but you can be my puppet master any time.
[SPEAKER_12]: How foul.
[SPEAKER_12]: I ended up having to leave around midnight because I was kind of afraid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, A, I was tired, and B, I was afraid I wasn't going to be able to park when I got back here if I waited any longer.
[SPEAKER_12]: But how was the rest of the night?
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We ended up playing Hear Me Out for the majority of the night.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, we played Poppin' 10 also, but yeah, that other game was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, a DD Alcoholic made sushi from scratch.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was really good, but it was kind of interesting because she used wieners in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, she used hot dogs instead of fish.
[SPEAKER_12]: She put, like, hot dogs in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it was actually really good.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was kind of weird.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just thought it was neat.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was very resourceful.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was a good idea.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to take a break.
[SPEAKER_12]: When we come back from this break, we're going to talk a little bit more about 2DX8 style.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to talk a little more about Pop Music 10.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to play the new remix of I Feel for you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: We played it on Thursday night, but I know nobody listens to Outside the Box on Thursday night, but more of you guys listened tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're going to play the new I Feel mix from Service Pack 7 from Ultramix 2, because a lot of people don't want to hear that.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're going to play that for you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: and plenty more when we come back from this break.
[SPEAKER_12]: In this break, though, some music from DDR Festival.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because we haven't really gotten to hear much music from DDR Festival yet, but we have some songs for you guys.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to hear Superstar, Diamonds, and Cutie Honey on this break.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's honestly, I didn't bother to buy Festival, I just, I didn't think there was enough in it for me, because I had Extreme, and I have an Xbox, so, and I had Ultramix One, which are a lot of songs came from, but Festival certainly has some quirky little songs in it, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting, that's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although I love Superstar, I, it's almost worth buying the mix for that, but not really, because that's like 80 bucks.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: 2DX8Style.
[SPEAKER_12]: Got a chance to check it out over at Navi, Pop Music Horror.
[SPEAKER_12]: He has it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got to check it out earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: And man, do I suck at 2DX now.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, me too.
[SPEAKER_12]: I haven't played 2DX seriously in quite a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: I didn't really get into 7Style.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played it one time.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot of this has to do with the fact that my controller is broken, and I'd rather buy myself a lot of other useless crap, like iPods and things like that, than buy a new 2DX controller.
[SPEAKER_12]: and I seriously think that's the reason that I haven't been playing a whole lot of 2DX.
[SPEAKER_12]: The 8th style is pretty sweet, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_12]: It has a lot of great new songs in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: For those of you guys that listen to this show regularly, you already know how I feel about Everyday Lovely Day, like I love that song.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then of course it has a bunch of 2DX Red songs in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, not a bunch, but three, which I consider to be a bunch for, you know, preview, because usually it's only like one or two.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then some of the new consumer videos are pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, Step Into the New World.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't really like that song a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: The song kind of, meh.
[SPEAKER_12]: But the video's pretty great, like, with the anime and everything and the guy running down the street.
[SPEAKER_12]: And he uses this computer animation technique that's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, it turns these 2D settings into 3D.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kind of like Parappa, the rapper.
[SPEAKER_12]: It looks like that, except not drawn.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess that makes no sense whatsoever, I don't care.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then also another video I love is Lovebox.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if you guys got to see this video at all, but Lovebox is the one that has, I think it's Meg and one of her cohorts or something, I don't know, an uncredited person.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're dressed up as these like Austin Powers dance chicks, kind of.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, they're all dressed in these, uh, like, 60s hippie, like, things you'd see on Laugh-In.
[SPEAKER_12]: You remember that old show Laugh-In?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, when the people would be dancing?
[SPEAKER_12]: It was kind of like that, and they're just driving around the city and singing, and they're wearing, like, glow bracelets and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's really great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Love Fox.
[SPEAKER_12]: I highly recommend this one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although the song kind of sucks, but the video's great.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, you guys have gotten to play 8-Style a little bit, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you guys think of 2DX 8-Style?
[SPEAKER_05]: I was stuck in Let Me Go with Bella.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I remember that song was so great.
[SPEAKER_05]: And the scene kept falling out of my lap.
[SPEAKER_05]: I miss arcades.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um, were you playing on a regular, like, little controller?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, now he has one of those arcade-style controllers, so you don't have to put it in your lap.
[SPEAKER_12]: But they're kind of loud, like, they're really, those arcade-style ones are really loud.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, you could hear that thing probably outside, like, a mile away, clack, clack, clack, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_12]: And sometimes it kind of overpowers the music, but it plays beautifully.
[SPEAKER_12]: It plays so beautifully.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arcadian, what do you think of 2DX8Style?
[SPEAKER_10]: Looks pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is this something you think you might have to break down and purchase?
[SPEAKER_10]: I already have purchased it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, have you?
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't gotten it yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_10]: You probably mentioned it, I forgot.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I mentioned it like two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I forgot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any particularly favorite consumer songs that you like in 8Style?
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't heard him enough to truly say yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played a new 7-star, I think it was Don't Be Afraid Myself, was one of the, like, it's the J-pop one, it's got a really, it's actually got a pretty That song was great!
[SPEAKER_12]: That's got a pretty cool video to it.
[SPEAKER_05]: Didn't it have a video in the bathroom?
[SPEAKER_05]: In the shower?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was like they were dancing in, like, a locker room shower.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I think that might have been it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I could only kind of half-see the video because I can't play the song.
[SPEAKER_12]: That song was cool!
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, the song is cool, but man, I fucked up that song so bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, it really shows, like, how out of it on 2DX I am because I can't sight-read anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was able to play Attitude and Stardream and all these songs I used to play all the time on 8thStyle.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was able to play those just fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: But man, throw something new at me and the rhythms and everything didn't make any sense to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was so sad.
[SPEAKER_12]: I cry for my 2DX skills.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Dancer.
[SPEAKER_12]: 8thStyle was worth it just to be able to play Dancer again.
[SPEAKER_12]: Although, is it just me or is something kind of weird at the end of the video?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like it freezes kind of at the end of the video.
[SPEAKER_12]: I remember it kind of faded out in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe I'm just crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: But a lot of 8-style machines had broken videos in the first place, so it was probably the first time a lot of people got to actually play 2DX with the videos.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know, pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Angel, what were your thoughts on 2DX 8-style?
[SPEAKER_04]: Lovage, Orange, Attitude, and A. That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because, you know, I used to watch you guys play that all the time, and I was always all envious, and I still am, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: A is technically a 7th style song, but it does make a repeat in 8th style.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's interesting, they took some of the most noteworthy 7th style songs, like A and Stoic, and they ended up repeating on 8th style after all.
[SPEAKER_12]: So now I'm kind of like, do I really need to get 7th style?
[SPEAKER_12]: But then I remembered, yes, I want to whore Beauty of Silence in the privacy of my own home, is basically what it boils down to.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just like, remember the old arcade days?
[SPEAKER_12]: Frickin' everybody whored Beauty of Silence.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, almost everybody.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know I was a big part of that, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, player's best would be 5-1-1, because all the noobs would play 5-1-1.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then, like, Beauty is Silenced.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, moving on, Poppin' Music 10 was another game I got to check out earlier this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pretty cool, I have to admit, I think I kind of like the way 9 is set up a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought the unlock system in 9 was a lot cooler, because 10 has this wacky roulette thing, and Navi had the timing down perfect, though, so that he was managing to unlock quite a bit of stuff on the roulette wheel, but it was kind of yawn to me, because the Gambler's E thing in 9 was
[SPEAKER_12]: I was a little disappointed by that
[SPEAKER_12]: The middle one, wherever it's ranked, like a 30 or something.
[SPEAKER_12]: 29, 30, I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody needs to get me $1,000 for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_12]: So that way I can buy an ASC for 2DX, an ASC for pop music, and then import 8th style and as many pop music as they can before I'm bankrupt.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you guys want to get me $1,000 for Christmas, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you play Poppin' 10 at all at that party that you went to, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't have Poppin' 10.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I thought maybe... I brought Poppin' 9 with me, but we ended up not playing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, what did you think of Poppin' Music 10, Angel?
[SPEAKER_04]: It was pretty, and watching Navi play is just insane.
[SPEAKER_04]: He plays faster than anyone else I've seen, you know, but I just ended up watching it because I knew a lot of people wanted to play Pop Intense, so I just kind of left it at that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Plus we were busy with Cranium anyway, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, by the way, if anybody wants to call us, we just opened up the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to figure out what that's all about, head on over to www.orangelondradio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we want to take some phone calls asking you guys that have gotten a chance to play 8th Style or Pop Music 10, what you guys think of it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have to say that the final verdict on 10, I kind of...
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, obviously I need to play it more, and obviously I still want it, but I still think I kind of like 9 just a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just think 9 had some, it was just set up a little better, and just kind of had some better songs, but 10's really good, don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would still buy 10 in a heartbeat, but I just think I like 9 a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arcadian, you got to play a little bit of Poppin' 10, what'd you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Real fast.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Sounds Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey there, Sky, Siggy here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi Siggy, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I finally figured out what you were talking about last week with the 2DX8 style.
[SPEAKER_12]: You remember how you said there was something in it that looked like extreme US?
[SPEAKER_12]: And a lot of people in the chat room went, what the fuck is he talking about?
[SPEAKER_12]: That kind of thing, remember that?
[SPEAKER_12]: I got what you meant now.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was the menu in the beginning, kind of had that round wheel thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's the menu.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, you got your copy of 8th Style, yes?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_12]: And how have you been enjoying it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was one of the lucky ones who got the 2DX Red e-amusement card, because after November 18th, they don't have it anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, is there anything special about the card, or is it just the fact that, hey, I got a card?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I wanted to use the 2DX red e-amusement card at AI, because they have the e-amusement card readers.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what I heard.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, I'm actually going to be able to go to Arcade Infinity next week, I'm hoping.
[SPEAKER_02]: The e-amusement card over there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Recently, I double-aided a V-35.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, V35 is one of those songs I used to be really good at, but then I just suck it up now.
[SPEAKER_12]: What is that you're holding up there?
[SPEAKER_12]: A Namco?
[SPEAKER_05]: My Tekken 5 character data card.
[SPEAKER_12]: Get on topic!
[SPEAKER_12]: No, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have you gotten to play Pop Music 10 at all?
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last time I played a Pop Music was Pop Music 9 back in San Francisco.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, but isn't Pop Music 9 great?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think so, anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: Uh, so, anything else you wanna share about 2DX8Style, your experiences you're having with it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, um, there's a, there's a thing, uh, about the, uh, getting the, the hidden songs, uh, 2DX, 2DX Red songs, you don't have to, you don't have to, uh, about, about the easy thing, it's, it's, it turns out to be false.
[SPEAKER_12]: What, what do you mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can't, you can't play, you can't play, uh, easy songs by, by unlocking, uh, by unlocking Tayo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: by using an easy option.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you can't play an easy to unlock those songs?
[SPEAKER_02]: You can.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you can?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, shit, that makes it easy, doesn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: And what is the requirement again to start unlocking some of these 2DX Red songs?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I actually don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: Play at least about 100 songs to unlock Spiral Galaxy and Taiyou.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_12]: 100 songs?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, yeah, just mostly light sevens or, you know, light seven to seven key songs.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not afraid of playing seven key.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got to play some more to get better at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's... Play more light seven.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just, you know, just for the heck of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just for the heck.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would play... Now, see, light seven would be the kind of thing I would play to whore my VJ Army account up if I had one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hypothetically, if I had one.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd be all, look at all these triple A's I got.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, it was on light seven.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, man...
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm good, because I know that there's people out there that do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, but that's okay, you know, light sevens are songs too, you have every right, but you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's another for random plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to play at least a hundred songs to unlock random plus.
[SPEAKER_02]: And what exactly does random plus do again for those that... Random plus is where the turntable is now included in the shuffle.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay, I gotcha.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that would be so hard if you got some scales that, oh god, that's crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Especially, you know, especially Wargame.
[SPEAKER_02]: I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can only imagine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, Wargame on 7-key was never a big problem for me.
[SPEAKER_12]: For some reason, Scratching, I'm like, I'm okay with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Checking you out was the second 7-star I ever beat, and now I understand it's an 8-star.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, like, I beat an 8-star, like, when I was beating my first 7-star.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is so crazy to me.
[SPEAKER_12]: But, for some reason, Scratching has never bothered me.
[SPEAKER_02]: After you play 100 songs with random, just hold the whole key 2 and then wait for the random to go red.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's how it works?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's how it works.
[SPEAKER_12]: So those of you guys that are feeling a little crazy and want to play some random with the turntable, there you have it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: What would you say would be your favorite new video in 2DXA style?
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't seen all of them because I'm really busy playing...
[SPEAKER_02]: Playing the seven key songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I say, I like Nebula Grasper a lot.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nebula Grasper's got a pretty good video to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's one of those futuristic, typical kind of things.
[SPEAKER_12]: It kind of reminded me of Hyperboundary Yate a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because, you know, that was an LED song too, and it had all the futuristic graphics with it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kind of reminded me of that a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I bought a 2DX Red, so I really like Spiral Galaxy as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, were you able to get the V-Rare when you got... Oh, no, no, I didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a regular one I ordered.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, anything else you want to share about 2DX ASO?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, nothing much else.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we'll talk to you later then, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a good one, Siggy.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like getting phone calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: People say in our chat room right now is that they're talking about 2DX too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it is the news that's going on right now, you know, you guys, but fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to talk about a little bit of DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to try and get the I Feel, the new remix for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki's going to get that taken care of during the next break, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Then I guess we're going to go to a break so we can get that song.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to hear some music from DDR Festival, some more music.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll do the second mix break in a bit, but I want to get the festival stuff taken care of first.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I did threaten the chat room with some Butterfly, and I know that's first mix, but I want to get that in there too, at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we'll see what you can do.
[SPEAKER_12]: But in this break, a different version of Udorup.
[SPEAKER_12]: I can't even say this.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know the Captain Jack song from fifth mix?
[SPEAKER_12]: Udorup, pom-pom-pom, or whatever, pom-pom-pom.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need you I need you I need you
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, that wasn't too bad.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, so we'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're going to check out these songs, and we'll be back, and we're going to talk a little bit more about Ultramix 2, some of the news there, and play that new song from Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: And, of course, the Cage Match, FU's of the Week, all that good stuff coming up.
[SPEAKER_12]: And in the chat room, they're saying, look, since you're so white, Sky, just say Dancine Pomponcolin.
[SPEAKER_12]: And even that I can't say right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just, I wasn't cut out for radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Crazy.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, we are going to be playing the new I Feel remix.
[SPEAKER_12]: We ripped it during the break there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, our tech massa, is working on it right now, trying to get it all perfect.
[SPEAKER_12]: I said we should just rip it out of edit mode, but apparently if you try to rip it in edit mode, it cuts off the very beginning little speech thing, because it starts off with, like, it sounds like one of those speaking spells or something saying it.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Loki was like, no, we can't have that!
[SPEAKER_12]: So he made us go back and do it in edit mode, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_05]: That's Pump Up the Volume where I just go crazy and play whatever.
[SPEAKER_05]: Although if you're in our chat room, you can make a request.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if I think that it doesn't totally suck ass, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then Wednesday night.
[SPEAKER_12]: as the oldie and moldy Orange Lounge radio show where basically we play a show from two years ago for your listening amusement.
[SPEAKER_12]: Listen to how much we used to suck.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you think we suck now, like we really sucked then.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then Thursday nights, outside the box at 7 o'clock, myself, Rice Princess, and LankyStyle talking about the latest and greatest in video gaming.
[SPEAKER_12]: This last week was a pretty good show.
[SPEAKER_12]: You missed a good time if you missed this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: We had a good time.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then Friday nights,
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not on this station, but it's over on The Freak on DDR Freak Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Rewinds, in case you missed a previous episode of Orange Lounge Radio, you can catch it over there, up to date.
[SPEAKER_12]: Actually, the show they're going to be playing this Friday is last week's show, which was the one where we had the Middyhead interview.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you guys missed the interview with Middyhead, awesome guy, awesome interview.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have to check it out, so go listen to Freak on Friday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, the karaoke cage match, by the way, was on last Friday, and of course, Loki won.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was there any surprise in anyone's mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've got to plug the LiveJournal community because we haven't plugged that in a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you guys have a LiveJournal, which I know a lot of you do in this day and age, we're starting to move into a LiveJournally-centered internet, head on over to our LiveJournal community.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just username OrangeLounge on LiveJournal.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if you join it, you get some of the latest announcements on what's going on in the station.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sometimes we propose ideas for changes to the station on our LiveJournal and we get your feedback there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's just a nice little community.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a way for you to meet other listeners of OrangeLounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Crazy people like us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_12]: DDR Ultramix 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's been a game we've been talking about a hell of a lot lately, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_12]: But SongPack... I keep calling it Service Pack.
[SPEAKER_12]: SongPack 7 came out this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Finally...
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot of us were expecting that SongPack 7 was going to be out when the game came out, but for whatever reason there was a delay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sounds like there might have been some kind of bug that prevented things.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot of people bitchin' and moanin' because SongPack 7 has a lot of old songs in it.
[SPEAKER_12]: We were talking about this a little bit last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: But SongPack 7 has End of the Century and Lost in Eurita and Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_12]: A lot of old classic DDR songs.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I guess played out to a lot of people as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: Era as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you get some tack finally in DDR Ultimate Mix 2.
[SPEAKER_12]: But a lot of these songs, since they're old, they're kind of played out.
[SPEAKER_12]: So they're getting a lot of kind of negative feedback from folks out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Even though, I don't know, I think it's kind of neat because A, you get them 60 frames a second.
[SPEAKER_12]: B, you can play them on Xbox Live now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not that I'm a huge fan of any of the songs really.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like Era, don't get me wrong, I love Era.
[SPEAKER_12]: Um...
[SPEAKER_12]: But then there's this new remix of I Feel, the Junk Circuit mix, which is pretty interesting because Junk Circuit is another artist that's over on a different drum.
[SPEAKER_12]: The background for this song has the website address.
[SPEAKER_12]: You may have noticed a lot of the different drum songs, like the Jesper Kidd, a lot of the new songs in Ultramix 2 have websites in their backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_12]: So it's kind of interesting that we're getting those in some of the song packs as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: But...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think in visiting Junk Circuit's website, I think there's actually a lot in common between Junk Circuit and Nuropa, who does the song Standing Still in Time, because they have the same website contact email.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're telling us in the chatroom to stop talking about the song and play the damn thing already.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll get to it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to copy it over right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki's put the finishing touches on it, so we'll go ahead and play that for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: But really first, Loki, what did you think of this remix?
[SPEAKER_11]: I do like this one a little bit better too, but I kind of like the old one as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: I gotta admit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: What do I know?
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: I gotta copy it over.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess there was a big tournament on Ultramix 2 tonight, online.
[SPEAKER_12]: There was a lot of people talking about it over on DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_12]: I missed it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It wasn't something... I knew I'd get my ass kicked, so I didn't want to participate, but I guess it went pretty well from what I hear.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, I'll stop talking and start playing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Launch Radio presents the brand new I Feel remix.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the Junk Circuit mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: Enjoy, guys.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you feel it?
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_12]: Who did that again?
[SPEAKER_12]: That was Junk Circuit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, I like the original better.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think a lot of us can agree that the original is a little bit better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Nothing ever tops the original.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like when you remake old movies.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, Loki says it does top the original.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I disagree!
[SPEAKER_12]: Nothing tops the Kiryamoga.
[SPEAKER_12]: What'd you think of that, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_10]: I liked it, except I think that the... I feel that little... Hold the bottom of the mic here.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's breaking up a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: The cord's loose.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're ghetto here.
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't have good equipment.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, now you're cutting out completely.
[SPEAKER_12]: There you are.
[SPEAKER_12]: Am I here?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, you're here.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now you're gone again!
[SPEAKER_12]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_12]: We need to buy a new mic, I think.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something's going on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Steal this one real fast.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yo, that one's dying.
[SPEAKER_12]: I cried for that microphone.
[SPEAKER_12]: There we go, try that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: Except for, I think, that little computer I feel it voices is a bad touch.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they left it out, it would make it better.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jazz in our chatroom agrees with you.
[SPEAKER_12]: He says the whole, can you feel it, samples just sounds fucking cheesy, is what he says.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Jamie's yelling from the laundry room that she agrees.
[SPEAKER_12]: So overall, I like it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I think it's pretty good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think the, can you feel it, is a little weird, but it, I don't know, it's different.
[SPEAKER_12]: I give him points for trying.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a good remix.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a fun song to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: The steps are kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It took something good and added a bunch of extraneous crap to it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is there any DDR remix that you've liked so far?
[SPEAKER_05]: I liked the What's-His-Face one that you interviewed last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: MidiHead?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: That one was good.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, What's-His-Face.
[SPEAKER_12]: I wasn't here!
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a little sticky announcement thingy where you can ask me to hit a question.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you missed getting your question last week, because we took some questions from our listeners, but if you missed your chance to ask me to hit a question, they are taking question submissions right now.
[SPEAKER_12]: So go check that out if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you think of that remix, Angel?
[SPEAKER_12]: You like everything, so I know you're going to have something good to say about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I liked the first one from Silent Hill when we first did that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then when the other one came out, I liked that one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do you think my answer is going to be this time?
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Ten?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're such a Bobani whore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: You called her a whore.
[SPEAKER_12]: You make it sound like it's the first time.
[SPEAKER_12]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to take some calls on the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to give us a call, head on over to www.OrangeLaunchRadio.com and click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of curious about some of your guys' feedback on Ultra Mix 2, specifically Song Pack 7, if you've had a chance to check it out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any online experiences you might have had on Ultramix 2, and even if you want to talk about a DDR Festival, because we haven't talked a whole lot about DDR Festival, and that's just because none of us in Sacramento, I don't think a single person in Sacramento that I know of anyway has bought the game, so we don't know what to say about it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And to add to that, if you'd like to talk about Drawn Together as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, that's not...
[SPEAKER_12]: I have an opinion.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_12]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you ever get a chance to play Ultramix 2, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you guys pick that up at your place yet?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to get it?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's fun!
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_13]: You should.
[SPEAKER_05]: The house has been rearranged in Halo 2 land position.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have no room to put any dance pads or anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Look at this place!
[SPEAKER_13]: Hello, you can sit on our camp.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have infinitely more room.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan's got the...
[SPEAKER_05]: Normally in my living room we have the TV on one wall, the couch on one wall, and the loveseat back on the far wall.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well now the loveseat and couch are back to back with just enough room to have a place to put your legs and an Xbox between TVs.
[SPEAKER_05]: It is currently in LAN mode.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you guys hosting a bunch of Halo 2 parties or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: Dan did on his birthday on Monday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, his birthday was Monday, huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Happy birthday, Dan.
[SPEAKER_05]: I wasn't here for that.
[SPEAKER_05]: He told me I should feel guilty.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, now that's not true.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I don't think anybody's calling us on the Skype line, so what can we do?
[SPEAKER_12]: Damn it, they suck!
[SPEAKER_12]: Except now they're talking about drawn together in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_12]: You freaking ass, Loki.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jerk.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, now you keep telling me that you're going to start playing Ultramix 2 because I notice that every time I've been playing it, you're like, yeah, I need to play that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I need to play that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you actually going to be playing?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, we're finally getting a call.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're going to reprieve for now, but as soon as this call is done, we're going to ask you about that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_03]: Legend of Zaku here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Zaku.
[SPEAKER_12]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have that much to share because, you know, as I said, you know, I'm a college student.
[SPEAKER_03]: Then get off the phone!
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have a PS2 or an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_03]: I might get one this Christmas, but I'm kind of iffy on which one should I get.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Bomani-wise, that is.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you don't have a PS2 or an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you're asking the age-old question, which system should I get?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, but with regards to not only, you know, games, but also Bomani as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm adding a little kick to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And you have nothing to add about Drawn Together.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something that's going to remind you of the arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something that's going to bring the arcade experience to the home.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something where there's a lot of different songs available.
[SPEAKER_12]: Something with iToy support if you want to get your hands involved.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go for the PS2.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to get something where you can play online and you want to play against other people that live around, go for the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_12]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: You being the starving college student, that means you're going to have to pay for the Xbox, Xbox Live, and then five bucks a song pack.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but also with the PS2 I might have to mod it
[SPEAKER_03]: I have to mod if I'm going to play 2DX or any of those lovely Pomani games besides DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that's very true, and that's going to cost you money as well, I mean, if you want to play the Japanese game.
[SPEAKER_12]: And that's the other thing, if you plan on modding your PS2, which, you know, can have mixed results, I guess I hear now it's pretty easy to mod it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I live in the city.
[SPEAKER_12]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Chinatown's not that far, and I can always get it modded there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you can get a modded PS2.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you're interested in 2DX or Poppin' or any of that stuff, you're definitely going to want to get the PS2.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the other thing to consider, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have PS3 and Xbox 2 likely to be out in stores before next Christmas.
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't know for sure, but if I were a betting man, I would say those things are going to be in stores next Christmas, which means the systems that are out there now, their prices will be halved, or they'll be $100 or less.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I probably already took notice of that, and I think 9th style, if it does come out next year for PS2, I don't know if it's going to jump into the next console, it'll just be the last PS2 2DX game.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of hoping that there is a 9th style and a 10th style pretty back-to-back.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of hoping that those games come out pretty quickly.
[SPEAKER_03]: PS2, or just one for PS2 and the next for PS3?
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope they both...
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's given that PS3 will play PS2 games, so they ought to just both come out for PS2.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, seeing as, you know, I already noticed that 2DX games come out, you know, there's always 2DX games coming out for PS2 every single year.
[SPEAKER_03]: And basically, from what I'm speculating, from what I'm predicting, Night Style might come out in May next year or something, or near the summer.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nobody really knows.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just taking a guess here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, taking a shot.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm just taking an educated guess from...
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, alright, I think pretty much I... Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Then again, 9th style would make a lot of sense on PlayStation 3 because then they could fuck up the timing by putting it on a new system, just like the arcade ones.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if I get a PS2 for Bomani, I'm going to have to pay money for the 2DX controller, poppin' music, so it's going to be equally the same if I'm going to have to try going after both.
[SPEAKER_03]: because one will have more peripherals and the other will have more services and things to buy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, also to even confuse things even more, there's also the Phantom console that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: How is that confusing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Who gives a shit about the Phantom?
[SPEAKER_12]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly, exactly.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hey, I've got pictures of them on orangeonradio.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: And I hear rumors of a...
[SPEAKER_11]: Engage2, that's shaped like a banana.
[SPEAKER_05]: I have rumors.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've heard rumors about foul women.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm about to have after this show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're looking for a system for Bomani, don't get a GameCube.
[SPEAKER_12]: GameCube?
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hell no.
[SPEAKER_12]: GameCube's not worth the money.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the best.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, don't you be knocking the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a beautiful system.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not knocking the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's cheap, but I mean... Don't make me come out there and cut you, because I will.
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: You're going to travel 3,000 miles?
[SPEAKER_03]: To cut you?
[SPEAKER_12]: To cut you, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you even know where in New York do I live?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll send my minions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then, do you want a cookie for that, Scott?
[SPEAKER_03]: We can track your IP!
[SPEAKER_12]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Live365 has it all on record, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match
[SPEAKER_12]: I've been perusing some of the message forums out there lately, DDR Freak namely being one of them.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought there was this very interesting thread over there in Random Chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know how they do a lot of really crazy stuff over in Random Chat?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know the Random Chat stuff, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_12]: Being a mod over there and everything?
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: What's this random that you talk about?
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't know anything about random on this show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just out of curiosity, this is total tangent, but since I'm thinking DarkSakura here and how much she loves to lock topics over there, what would you say would be the most favorite topic you've gotten to lock on random chat?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, please lock this.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've had a please lock this before.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's an interesting topic going on there in random chats called, do you actually play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_12]: And I thought it was kind of interesting just seeing how many people actually don't play DDR anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I kind of was going to go around the room a little bit and see, do you play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_12]: And if not, why are you doing this show?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll start.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do I play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_12]: A little bit, not as much nearly as I used to.
[SPEAKER_12]: I play a little bit of Ultramix 2 at home.
[SPEAKER_12]: Most of my DDR playing is controller controller.
[SPEAKER_12]: The reason why I don't play DDR that much anymore is because the quality of arcades in this area went downhill significantly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kenami of Japan can suck it for not putting out a new mix in a long time.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that has a lot to do with the reason why I haven't played DDR in a long time.
[SPEAKER_12]: The home version is the only thing keeping it alive to me, but I just can't motivate my fat ass to pull out the ignition pad.
[SPEAKER_12]: As good of a dance pad as it is, it's still not the arcade.
[SPEAKER_12]: I want to play DDR in the arcade, and there's no good arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: And yes, I realize there was that Stepmania thing, but to me, it's still only 90%.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the damn thing broke in a week anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: And it's still not everything that DDR is.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's still got issues.
[SPEAKER_12]: And in the groove, it's okay, but...
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, just, you know, ego killed the video game star, I guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, do you play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_13]: I played DDR when I was in Alabama.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you play it regularly besides that?
[SPEAKER_05]: When I'm somewhere that has a machine, I'll play.
[SPEAKER_05]: I've got more reason to play now than I go play dock at RVGL.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because I'll still have a little bit of money and go play some DDR.
[SPEAKER_12]: I played like one game of DDR when I went to go play Doc at Derby Owner's Club over at Roseville Golf Land, but here's the problem, I fucking failed Breakdown!
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, you know, it's a 9-footer, it's a more difficult song at the end of the scale, but you have to remember, I'm somebody who was playing DDR religiously for quite some time, and, you know, I... I just... It just makes me sad how much stamina I've lost, you know?
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Arcadian, do you actually play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really, just mainly because my foot's been hurting, and because I haven't had that much money lately.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now I might be able to go once my foot feels 100%, or 90% at least.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe more in the future, because it's been so long and I need to get off my fat ass when I sit around too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, do you play DDR anymore?
[SPEAKER_12]: DDR and Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, yes I do, I'm Step Mania every once in a while, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Um, but yes, to answer your question earlier, um, about you, you know, Xbox and stuff and if I was ever going to play it, no, because I'm going to actually set up my Step Mania cabinet to be playing some stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, that's why I bought crap today to cut the other, um, control panel for the actual, you know, select arrows and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's why, um, I was going to do that today.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm hopefully going to build that this week because I bought...
[SPEAKER_11]: A while back, a new IPAC thing to hook it all up, and I have to see if it's going to get fried as easy as the other one.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, it's all contingent on that, whether I get to play it some more.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't play in the arcade, because the arcade's too far away, takes too much of my time, cuts into my Final Fantasy XI time, and the arcade's broken all the time.
[SPEAKER_11]: Not in a way fucking out of shape.
[SPEAKER_11]: I go and play like a seven footer on doubles and I'm ready to die.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, whatever happened to me.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's what I want to know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It never used to be this hard.
[SPEAKER_11]: But once I get back in shape, yeah, I'd play a lot more.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just need to finish my arcade cabinets before I move out of here, so that's priority one.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't play a whole lot of DDR in the arcade or at home anymore, yet you're very gung-ho about this cabinet and everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why do you think that is?
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it just a love for the basic concept of the game?
[SPEAKER_12]: I like building stuff, have you noticed?
[SPEAKER_12]: Stuff that doesn't work.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like the portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_11]: The portal to hell.
[SPEAKER_12]: Also, I noticed you tend to build things halfway through and don't finish them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Such as these lovely metal pads that have been sitting over here for the past... Can we play Xbox or PS2 games with them right now?
[SPEAKER_11]: We can if I hooked up the other... the, um... iPad thing, because all I have to do is switch out the old iPad and it plugs right in and it works.
[SPEAKER_11]: But the thing is...
[SPEAKER_11]: The thing is, I haven't bought the adapter for the Xbox or the PS2 yet because it was hooking up directly to my computer.
[SPEAKER_11]: But yes, I could.
[SPEAKER_11]: I could if I wanted to.
[SPEAKER_11]: It just would take a while because I'd have to wire everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's just that those things, I would be curious how thick the layer of dust is on those metal pads that are sitting right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Can I go wipe my finger on it and see how much dust is on them?
[SPEAKER_12]: Here you go, Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: They also buy the air intake, just so you know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah, okay, I have an idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me wipe the dust off of my little, my computer desk here, because I get quite a bit used to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, like it's gray.
[SPEAKER_11]: Let me wipe the dust off of every, there's dust everywhere in here.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not a surprise that there's dust on those.
[SPEAKER_11]: That and they're right next to the air intake, which I'm sure is not good for the air conditioner one bit, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_12]: No wonder it smells like wood in this house all the time.
[SPEAKER_12]: This strange mix of metal and everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, uh, Explicit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Welcome to the show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: I noticed you just ran in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Put down the DS for a minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quit chatting with Angel on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take a chat for a minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: That mic's been giving us... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: They are like, what, eight feet?
[SPEAKER_13]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_13]: This is what... I think they're exchanging special pictures.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is wrong, people.
[SPEAKER_11]: You need to talk.
[SPEAKER_11]: Talky Talky, just like, you know, the people IMing each other when they're sitting in a cafe.
[SPEAKER_12]: Talk.
[SPEAKER_12]: They're riding a penis back and forth to each other.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, Rob, that's you last night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: You gotta hold the mic at the bottom, because it's going out tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: That mic's on its last legs.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yes, I can hear you now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you play DDR?
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, just as an internment and stuff, and if some new people want me to come back again, I guess I'll play again.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, even though the DDR scene is dying in a way, because there hasn't been any releases for the arcades and stuff, it's totally understandable.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's just the new people, the community, the new members are just trying to bring it back again in a way.
[SPEAKER_11]: You give me $100,000, I'll bring back DDR.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm telling you.
[SPEAKER_14]: The only way that you can bring back DDR is by fixing the Sanmenia cabinet, dammit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I like that cabinet.
[SPEAKER_11]: You give me $100,000...
[SPEAKER_11]: Hell, give me just $20,000 and I'll bring it back.
[SPEAKER_12]: Don't you think that, now call me crazy because it's not supposed to be DDR, quote unquote, don't you think In The Groove was sort of a way to try to bring DDR back?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's why I always got the impression that In The Groove was, even though it's not DDR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, the thing about In The Groove is that not many cabinets have been sold around the U.S.
[SPEAKER_14]: just yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: And very few songs are in it, mainly just testing the waters until the Groove 2 comes out and stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it also depends on who, what set makers are they gonna hire and what songs they're gonna put in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hell, if they put Ultra Mix, like Ultra Mix in the DDR Cam and I play it...
[SPEAKER_12]: The first week after Ultramix 2 is out, I put the call out on this show.
[SPEAKER_12]: I said, we need to hound the shit out of Konami of Hawaii and however it has to happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care if some arcade division went under or what the shit happened.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care how it has to happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: It just needs to happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hawaii needs to make a new arcade mix.
[SPEAKER_12]: End of story.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't care who's got to be blown, who's got to be paid the money.
[SPEAKER_12]: Make it happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know what's hella funny, though?
[SPEAKER_14]: That hella companies are saying that the whole arcade business is dying.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have no cards.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, that's just like people saying, oh, well, you know, internet's killing the telephones.
[SPEAKER_11]: People still use the telephones, just like people use the internet.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, people still use the telephone, and I talk to them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyway, but the whole thing is, is the convert, you know, Ultramix to an arcade system is like fucking easy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Minimal programming, licensing of songs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Build the hardware.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hardware's fucking easy to build.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's just an excuse, but I just don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because they don't want to distribute it, and that's a bitch.
[SPEAKER_14]: The reason why I pump it up is by making more and more money just building new machines and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Allow me to be the first to offer sex to anyone at Konami of Hawaii if you can make yourselves a new DDR game.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Not that Konami of Japan does a bad job.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if they want to do a new mix, I'm perfectly fine with that as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: I will extend my sex offer to Konami of Tokyo as well, K-Set.
[SPEAKER_12]: So just make me a new DDR and I will put out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's that simple.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anybody else care to offer their sexual favors?
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, this is what's pissing me off.
[SPEAKER_04]: They're like, oh, this is too expensive to license songs here in America.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's why we can't do it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Do all in-house music.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have, like, what, five different series to pull from?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do what you've been doing for years.
[SPEAKER_12]: License the song in Japan and then let the machines come over here.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's what they've been doing for years.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because it's cheaper to license the songs in Japan, obviously.
[SPEAKER_11]: I look a little weird, but like, I made this machine over here in Japan, it's called a DDR Stream USA, but it's not meant to be played in the United States, just... They could call it DDR Shit Mix, and I'd still play it.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry, Shitake.
[SPEAKER_12]: They could call it DDR Shitake Mix, I would still play it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shitake, that's all.
[SPEAKER_12]: Angel, you still play DDR at all?
[SPEAKER_12]: You're probably more into DDR than anyone I know right now, so I have to ask you this.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, in fact, I'm probably going to break down and get a dual platform Ignition because I want to play on Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, I'm looking into getting both of those this week, Ultramix 2 and the new pad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because Magus isn't dying anyway, so might as well just replace it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then we can play doubles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Speaking of doubles, which is better, Ignition or Carameldansen?
[SPEAKER_12]: I couldn't tell you because I haven't really played enough Cobalt Flux.
[SPEAKER_12]: I saw it a little bit at E3, but it wasn't familiar enough with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're both the same fucking pad!
[SPEAKER_11]: It's the same damn thing with a different logo on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: You can't get much different.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, our metal is different than your metal!
[SPEAKER_11]: What about the quality?
[SPEAKER_14]: What about the quality and how many times could it be stepped?
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're the fucking same.
[SPEAKER_14]: The gold flood said not even a rhino could beat down the pad.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh yeah!
[SPEAKER_11]: Do they have a rhino to test this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Did they take it to Africa and go, hey rhino, step on the pad!
[SPEAKER_11]: How do you like it?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I can say, yeah, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Jupiter has nothing on this pad.
[SPEAKER_11]: This pad can fuck up Jupiter.
[SPEAKER_11]: Seriously, they're just pulling shit out of their ass, okay?
[SPEAKER_11]: A rhino can't fuck this up.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_11]: Bigfoot recommends, you know, red octane, so fuck that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: Really, to be honest, when it comes down to pads, don't buy off the internet.
[SPEAKER_11]: Buy stuff that you can see at a store.
[SPEAKER_11]: Buy it like fries and stuff where you can actually see these pads.
[SPEAKER_11]: Because the shit you get off the internet, because I have bought metal pads off the internet, and I stepped on them and they bent.
[SPEAKER_11]: They bent downwards.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I was like, what the fuck?
[SPEAKER_11]: It was retarded.
[SPEAKER_11]: Pads are not meant to be folded in half.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, talk about how they say SEVs can't bust them on their advertisements.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our chatroom over at www.orangeloungeradio.com, clicking on chat.
[SPEAKER_12]: Interesting point, there already is a DDR shit mix, and it's the Don't Fall Off mix, the DDR Extreme bootleg.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know the one that would speed up?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, I see there's two of them.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know about the speed up.
[SPEAKER_12]: DDR Extreme Plus, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the one in Country Club Lane, speed up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, let's speed up Max 300 and see if we can beat it at 360 BPM.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: or hear cartoon heroes in a very high-pitched voice.
[SPEAKER_12]: What is the deal with Cartoon Heroes?
[SPEAKER_12]: Why do so many people freaking love that song and are quick to label a mix as utter shit if that song isn't in it?
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't understand what is so great about the song.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it a good song?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, it's a great song.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was a little better when Aqua did it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's a good song.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is it fun to play?
[SPEAKER_12]: Kinda, I mean, I'll die when I play it.
[SPEAKER_12]: But why do so many people freaking obsess over Cartoon Heroes?
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, do you know how many people threw a fit when that song was in Extreme USA?
[SPEAKER_11]: Let's look back in DDR history and view what we call the songs that ruin mixes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Starting with...
[SPEAKER_11]: Third mix, Afronova.
[SPEAKER_11]: Who could love this wonderful African shent as you jump around like a complete nut?
[SPEAKER_11]: Fourth mix, Kick the Can, with its repetitive steps over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's another contributing factor.
1, 2, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're forgetting, though, my edit to Kick the Can, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_12]: Big Cans, was awesome and made that song redeemable.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, as I would continue on, the fifth mix, Hot Limits.
[SPEAKER_11]: The song that's just, you don't understand what they're saying, but you know it's very long.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, DDR Max, I'd say probably that would be Exotic Ethnic.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was pretty repetitive in DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh no, Flash in the Night.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, that was another one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Flash in the Night.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on, your mic's still cutting out a little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold it at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to bring out the...
[SPEAKER_12]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold it at the bottom.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, try it, try it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Put it close to the bottom.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: The same reason why Cartoon Heroes got poured out is the same reason why So Deep is getting poured off with DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it's like hard as hell 9.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would say the song that ruined DDR Max, even though I love this song, Cowgirl.
[SPEAKER_12]: Cowgirl, yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Max 2, Cigarro, and who could not forget the song that had everyone dancing...
[SPEAKER_14]: I hate cartoon heroes and I know there's