Orange Lounge Radio
Who's the host?
Dark Sakura
Sky and the Low Crew
Tonight, April 3rd, 2011
Two high profile games are outright canceled
The 3DS breaks records in its first week
And is the Xbox Live Indie Game Store being manipulated?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of the show
Where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
It is episode number 408
For this April 3rd, 2011
My name is Rob Roberts
I'll be joining you over the next few hours
With my co-host, the one and only
Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers
Fwee
How are you?
I'm actually full
Full?
I made a delicious
Full of crap?
Uh uh, no that's Shermie
I had a delicious meal that I cooked myself
Alright
By myself
Now bake me a pie
I don't know how to bake
Anything that I've ever baked
Except for my failure cake that I told you about last night
Has been a disaster
And can you tell the listeners what a failure cake is briefly
Failure cake
Before we get into video game time
Was me making chocolate pancakes
And then getting bored with the rest of the batter
Because I didn't want any more pancakes
So I poured the chocolate batter into a cake pan
And then put some giant chocolate chips on it
And then baked the whole thing
And it tasted delicious
I don't know about you guys, I'd still eat that
Even though it's a cake of failure
It was delicious, delicious fail
Alright
A host not full of fail
Say hello to the one and only tech master, Loki
Hello, how's it going?
I am good, how are you, Loki?
I am doing fine
Alright, except we are
Why are we not hearing you very well tonight?
I don't know
Why aren't you hearing me tonight?
I think we're hearing you, you're just really quiet
I'm really quiet?
Yeah, you're good now
Sorry
I think we have to keep you kind of low
Because when the Nintendo topics come up
Oh yeah
You'll get a little louder!
I'm not louder, I'm more opinionated
You're passionate
I am passionate, come on
It's like, I don't know
It's just stupid people doing stupid things
Alright, we've got a lot of interesting news stories tonight
Kind of along those lines
We'll get to those in just a little bit
But first let's say hello to a guest here in studio tonight
Back again this week
Say hello to Salacious Pop
What up
How you doing Salacious Pop?
Good
Good, how has life been treating you lately?
Um, been really busy
Yeah?
What's been going on?
Preparing for a move
Yeah?
You moving?
Yeah
You moving in with Jamie?
She's really lonely this week
Yeah
Alright
It's the vault, I'm just going to stay in the vault
Awesome
I don't even get to play anything, I just get to look at stuff
It's awesome
Now, we missed April Fools this year
Because the show tonight is on the third
But you were mentioning a really good April Fools joke
You thought we should have done
Well I can't talk about it or else I can't do it next year
Oh yeah, we got to do it next year I guess
Okay, it's really good y'all
It was basically like
OLR Episode 3 coming like from the vault of 1982
Where with the news stories you're like
Yeah, I'm really looking forward to that ET game on the Atari 2600
It's going to be great
The only thing about that is it's kind of close to what YouTube did
So it'll be better next year
Yeah
Next year y'all forget
It's a little too close to Flugelhorn feline
Which by the way was the best April Fools joke on the web
Just so you know
Alright, anyhow
Well, by the way, Rob, it's not a rumor
Now, see, oh
Okay, before we went live tonight
See, now I have to talk about all this because you brought it up
Bobby was abbreviated tonight
So we went live a little bit early
Just kind of BSing with the live listeners and doing some music
And one of the topics that came up before the show was
The Wachowski Brothers and they did The Matrix
And there's these rumors or something going around
That one of them had a sex change
Larry is now Lana
But now, see, the chat room, Tiger Closener chat room
Which by the way, hi chat room, chat.orangelsauce.com
Saying that's not true
It's on IMDB
Is it?
Yeah
Credited on IMDB
I thought some producer said it wasn't true, IDK
Well, I mean, you know
Alright, there you go
Well, if it's on IMDB, I guess it's true
You know what?
The Matrix 2 and 3 still sucked
Boy or girl directing
Yes
Alright, let's talk about video games
Of course, we do that here on the show
Chat.orangelsauceradio.com
If you're listening to us live on this Sunday night at All Games Radio
We do tape live at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at allgames.com
So join us in our chat room
To get to the chat room, chat.orangelsauceradio.com
Have I plugged all the websites?
I believe so
Twitter, OLR, Facebook, Orangelsauce Radio, etc, etc
Now we can talk about games
Hi Dark Sakura, how was your gaming week?
Hi
I played a lot of Dragon Age 2
I borrowed it from my friend's husband
Well, he's my friend too
But I borrowed his game
And it's really fun
And I'm kind of hooked
And I played some WoW
And some Final Fantasy 3
And then I looked at games at Fry's with U2
Yes
That was it
We went shopping last night and not for shoes
I didn't buy anything
I know, it's kind of sad to go to a huge electronics store like Fry's
Which, I don't think they have those everywhere
I think just on the west coast
So Fry's is just like, it's an uber electronics store
I think they're spread around
Yeah, there might be a few in other places
But yeah, it's an uber electronics store
Huge games section, huge computer section
We went in there, looked around
Didn't buy anything
It's kind of sad
Their PSP section amazed me
They do have a lot
That still exists
Well, there's still a lot of good stuff coming on the PSP
The UMD's
Yeah, the UMD's were what impressed me too
That they're still really supporting them
$10 for most of them
Because they got them really cheap, I'm sure
I guess so, I don't know
You know, there's only one company still supporting UMD
And that's Sony
Of course
I don't remember the last movie
I want to say 2012 was one of the last movies to come out for it
Zira, they are kick-ass
Whatever came out last
No, I know I was looking and I was like
Oh, Charlie's Angels Full Throttle is only $4
And they have like 40 copies of it sitting on the shelf
That's kind of the sad thing is that sometimes Fry's just way over stocks
A certain game or something
I'll tell you what else they had just hundreds
I'm not even lying
Hundreds of copies of just trying to get rid of them
Castlevania Lords of Shadow
Because it sucks
The new God of War-y Castlevania
Because they're fucking cutthroat with their goddamn vendors
Every time the vendors come out and stuff
And we get to talking about different customers
They're talking about visiting Fry's
They fucking hate visiting Fry's
Because Fry's, they're just cutthroat
They want everything
And it's just, it's ridiculous
They're like, I hate fucking going and visiting Fry's
SolarFlare's in our chatroom at chat.org.com saying
I've lived on the west coast for over 20 years and have never seen a Fry's
Maybe they don't have them in Oregon
I don't think they do, Oregon or Washington
I'm not sure where SolarFlare's is
But I think they're mostly like
I know there's a few in the bay, some in SoCal
There are some in Texas, I know that
I think they dip into Arizona and the southwest a little bit
So I think they go south and west, not north and west, sadly
So, alright, anyhow
Uh, Loki
Wait, wait, I want to go back to Dark Soccer and talk more about Dragon Age 2
Because I haven't played the game
So you're enjoying Dragon Age 2?
Yes, it has Eve Miles doing a voice
For anyone who does not know, she was Gwen on Torchwood
Now you didn't really play the first game, right?
No
And you're doing okay with the second game?
Yeah, just fine
What is it that you like so much about it?
Lesbians
Have you...
Did you draw that?
Not really
Have you actually gotten to the part where they, you know
Well, right now Meryl the elf
Is gushing over my character
Which is kind of cute and funny
Because my character is all like face tats
And red eyeshadows, she's really fierce looking
And she's a rogue
And, uh
But they've already had, like, love chat
And then there's this one guy who was hitting on my character
I was like, no you're gross
But he was apparently from an earlier game
He's the one that you give him a cat called Sir Pouncealot
I guess
He was talking about his cat
And then there's Isabella
Who's, according to Tiara
She's a slut
She can sleep with her a bunch
And then she's like, oh, it's just sex
So, I'm like, I haven't gotten to any fun part though
I mean, I've done a lot of
I really like this game, but it's not fun
No
It's kind of what I just heard, it's just me
I've done a lot of killing
Which is great
And I've got it in extra gore mode
So, like, they're covered in blood
When you're done with a fight
And they're battered on their face
And then I was like, that's awesome
Okay, gore and lesbians, got it
This game really isn't fun
I'm just here for the pussy
And gore
It actually is really fun
I'm still in the first act
Okay, you're like in the grind or something, right?
Yeah
Trying to grind out that pussy
Well, some elven cooch
Say no more
What's the battle system like?
It's like you run down
The stairs, oh no, there's people there
And one of your party comments
About how there shouldn't be people on the street after dark
And then you have to kill them
And there's blood everywhere
And you occasionally
No, they're like highwaymen
And you can go outside of the town
To certain areas
And you'll find piles of bones
And you can dig through them for loot
I see
It's really great though
And, okay, I guess
So now you're talking about touching bones
In your quest for pussy
My quest for pussy
No, it's
There's also, you know, you can go through people's stuff
And right now I'm actually trying to build up my character
So I can get the lock picking
So I can open locked
Trunks and stuff and steal people's stuff
And
What else was I doing?
There's just, I'm doing
A lot of the side quests too
So I can level up before I get to the
The big thing
But there's somewhere else that I need
To go to get some dude named Fenris
Who was, I think, in one of the last games
Now it's gonna be a three way
Well, no, I don't
Okay, Meryl
Is my fangirlism because
I adore Eve Miles
She's very cool
And Welsh accents to me are hot
Really hot
Alright
And I don't
The elves that live outside
Are all Welsh
The elves and humans that live in the town
Are all British
And dwarves are American
Is what I'm getting so far
Whereas, you know, don't we usually
Have dwarves being Scottish?
Well, if you play WoW a lot, yeah, dwarves are Scottish
Or, you know, Lord of the Rings
Well, no, he sounded vaguely
He didn't, he sounded Welsh
Alright, well, you think you'll play Dragon Age 2
Through to completion?
Yeah. Alright, that's good
It's always good to finish. I'll take pictures
Of the lesbian scene. Alright, please do
Alright, let's move on over to Loki
Loki, how was your gaming week? Um, it was okay
I played Motorstorm Apocalypse
Through rookie mode now
And I think most of the way through
Pro mode
Although, it's like, all the races have been
Somewhat difficult up until now
And it's just like
And now it's really, really hard
So, I'm actually stuck on one
Race right now
But, really enjoying it still
Storyline's still really cheesy
But, still
Pretty fun game
And then, I've been playing
On my 3DS
Really only pilot wings right now
And I haven't really played any of the
Like, I don't know
The missions or whatever you have to do
Different challenges
Mainly the free-flying
Which is kind of annoying a little bit
Because you can only fly around for like
A few minutes at a time
Which is so
Stupid
It's like 3 minutes at a time
Fun!
Well, I mean, you do only have a limited amount of fuel, right?
Well, okay
If you want to go by that route
Then why can't I have it
Where I refuel, or
Gas is expensive, you know
Or, like, when I'm using the rocket belt
I never get low on fuel
I could hold that fuel
You know, the throttle down the whole way
And it just never would run out of fuel
But, um
I'm basically collecting these markers
Or whatever they're in the game
And I have 74 of 75 of them
So, I'm still trying to find the last one
But, it's just like
You know, the Wuhu Island thing
It's like
Oh, hey, look at this
This is from Wii Sports Resort
Oh, this is the part where you can, uh
Here's the bowling alley, here's all this stuff from the game
I'm like, okay, well none of this has to do with
Flying
Can you, like, crash through the roof of the bowling alley?
No, you can't
How boring!
You can fly through tunnels and stuff
You know, it's kind of cool jogging around
I guess in Wii Sports Resort or something
Well, actually, no it wouldn't be
Because you'd be jogging in place and that's really boring
But, um, I could see
If you're into jogging in place, what the appeal
Might be, um
But, it's just
It seems really lazy to me
I mean, they could have just easily created
A new island, it's not that damn
Detailed at all, I mean
Somebody could easily create an island within
A day
I mean, there's no animations
Whatsoever going around, there's no
Cars moving around, no people running around
It's just all
Not doing anything
It seems to be like a dark pilot wings
Where you can, like, rocket belt into the bowling alley
And steal a baby and, like, run away with it
Or, you know
Yeah, see, once again
And this is unfortunate
This goes back to Nintendo
What they do with new games
Or, I should say, games that they put out again
They basically take them
They don't add any features to it
And they strip it down to what the bare essentials
That they need to do another release for
It's just like all the Animal Crossing games
And here's the problem
People like us keep buying them
And so it teaches them
Actually, you're the only one that's bought a 3DS in this room
No, I'm talking about Animal Crossing
Oh, okay
No, I'm just saying, uh, it's people like us
That keep buying those crappy games
And it just gives them the impression
Okay, so we don't really do anything
People just still buy our games
It's just like the whole Tron thing
What's different this year?
We put a 12 on the box
I mean, it's okay
It's somewhat fun
I haven't played through everything yet
But, you know, you're looking at
What was on the original Super Nintendo
Version, it's just
I'm sorry, it's even less content than that
I mean, you really couldn't
You know, bother to
Put the extra content in there
They don't even remove the landing pads
And stuff like that, they're in the different missions and stuff
They're in the free mode, they're just all sitting there
Still, because they didn't bother to
Even say, okay, well, during this mode
This isn't here, or whatever
It's just, it's always there
Let me get you some questions from our chat room
At chat.orangesonshooter.com
Robert M. is asking, Loki, Loki, can you shoot in pilot wings?
No balloon popping, at least?
There's a few levels in the mission mode
Where you can do that
Shooting or balloon popping? Or both?
Both
Let's see, TigerClaw is asking, what they should have done
Is recreated that helicopter mission from the first pilot wings
Most people never even saw those missions
The first pilot wings was hard
Well, they've got some stuff that's
Undocumented
Or whatever, it's not on the box
Where they have the squirrel suit
Or whatever, you could do skydiving in there
Wait, the squirrel suit?
Yeah, like a flying squirrel suit
It's not really a squirrel suit
It's like, have you seen those
Skydiving things that they've got the webbing
Between your arm and your body
And the leg and your body
So it provides more drag so you can fly around
When we're talking about a flying squirrel
I'm thinking of Rocky from the Rocky and Bowling Cool show
No, it's not like some stupid Mario
Thing where you're in a tanooki suit
Or some crap like that
I'm literally imagining a
Skydiving squirrel
That trick never works
I'd pay to play that
But it's just
I don't know
It's a fun game
I guess, it's what I've been playing
Just because I just wanted to play
Through some of that
I've played Ridge Racer a ton
Street Fighter, it's alright
I saw a question about the battery life
Earlier in chat
And that's a bitch I've heard
The battery life isn't really that great
On these things
I haven't really had a problem with it
Because I keep charging it all the time
I've never had it run out on me
But then again, I also
Don't leave it in sleep mode
Because I figured that the battery would go dead
And I kind of want to play the game
That's the thing, they have all these things that rely on sleep mode
And I know that doesn't suck
As much battery as playing a game would
But, you know, if it's
Running out of battery that fast
Why rely on sleep mode for all this stuff?
Let me go to another
Question from chat, and I think this is a good one
Savalas in our chat room is asking
At chat.org.com
Loki, do you have buyer's remorse with buying the
Nintendo 3DS now that we're a week in?
No, not really
I mean, I got the few games that I wanted to get
And that's it, and that's what I'm gonna plan on
Getting until
You know, whenever the next best game comes out
I mean, there's the
Dream Trigger game that I'm thinking about getting
Whenever the hell that comes out, and
That's pretty much it, I mean
Everything else is gonna be fourth quarter, so
I'm perfectly fine with what I have right now
That's why I didn't purposely go
And just buy all the stuff that came out launched
Because a lot of it's crap
And a lot of it, you know, even the reviewers go
This is basically the game that
Came up before, but now it's in 3D
And it doesn't really utilize 3D that much
And you're gonna get a lot of that stuff
Because people don't know how to utilize it
Or they're gonna try to cash in real quick
Especially putting out a budget game
Because all the games are $40
So a $20 game stands out because, hey, that's much cheaper
But
You get what you pay for? Exactly, yeah
Alright
And then what else did I play? Oh, Game Dev Story
But still playing a little bit of that
That's kind of mindless because
My team is so good at developing
Stuff that
I mean, we beat out everybody in the awards
And all that stuff, it's kind of fun
Even the fictional company
That's the game publisher
Of the actual game
Their
Toilet system is not
Doing well compared to
Compared to my glory hole system
Yes, that's what it's called, the glory hole
Kay
Everybody loves the glory hole
Alright
And then Cry Theft Auto
That's what I played this week
Alright, let me go over to SalaciousPop
How was your gaming week? It was alright
Pretty slow
Played some Pac-Man Championship Edition DX
Some Super Street Fighter IV
A lot of the
Mortal Kombat
PS3 demo
And I finally got to play Marvel vs. Capcom 3
What did you think of MVC 3?
I really liked what I saw of it
Definitely want to get it at some point
It has the sort of hybrid
Four button controls that
The Dreamcast used for
Marvel vs. Capcom 2
And then I guess also Tatsunoko vs. Capcom
For the Wii uses something similar
And I didn't realize that it played like that
So when I was using a six button
Fight pad
I wasn't quite landing the combos
That I thought I was because I realized
Oh, well not all the buttons are mapped the way I thought they were
There's no low, medium, strong
Punch, low, medium, strong kick
They're kind of combined
Some of them
So yeah, I loved it
Was there a particular character you really enjoyed?
I don't
Really care for her
In the context that she appears
In the Marvel universe
The female Wolverine
Clone, X-23 I think her name is
She was fun to use
Cool
Anything else you want to share about your game a week?
Um
The fatalities in the
Mortal Kombat demo
Are really gory but they're all kind of stupid
And they're all kind of the same
You think? Yeah
See, here's my whole thing
You know I hate the Saw movies and all that stuff
And I talk about this on the show
But yet I giggle so much at Mortal Kombat
And all the fatalities
And some of them are really bad
Like the Melina one, what does Melina do?
She walks up to you like she's going to kiss you
And then she
Sucks you up and spits you out
No it's not like you think that's what's going to happen
But she like rips off your face
She throws her thighs at you
So they're out of your rib cage
So you're all spiked
And then she makes like this
I guess Melina's always horny or whatever
She's always moaning and cooing
So it looks like she's going to kiss you
And then she rips your head off at the jawline
So that your chin and jaw
Is still attached and your body falls over
Then she eats your tongue
Out of the head that she has in her hand
She doesn't just eat it, she goes
Like it's sushi
She's got Baraka face
And then so she eats your tongue out of your
Sort of severed head and then she just chucks it to the ground
Like a football, like eh
And then she jumps on the camera
And like kind of tries to dry hump it
Right? Well that's if you're
That's her non, like if you don't do a fatality
You just let them fall down
And then she like smears blood on her boobs
Because again she's always horny
Like I don't know what her problem is
I bet yet the whole time I see this
For the first time I'm giggling maniacally
And like Alan's like what's wrong with you
And as soon as, I know I don't really appreciate
The whole TNA fighter game thing at all
Because as soon as I saw her buck naked outfit
I'm like she's going to get a yeast infection
In that onesie
She has a naked outfit?
She's not really naked
She's wearing floss
And the best part
Is that this new Mortal Kombat
Game, the blood kind of seems to stay
On the characters and it stays like
In kind of natural looking ways
So after she's fighting or whatever, her boobs will be like
Covered in blood and she's like rubbing her boobs
It's all like, it's really
Disgusting but funny
It's just a PS3 demo
It's not the game yet
Because the demo has four characters in it
And the fatality for Scorpion
If you look it up in the off menu
Is wrong
The fatality for Scorpion was just backwards
That was funny
Actually wait, hold on
You know what I should do here
Is I should actually just pull this up real quick
It is a three hour show, we have time to do some fun things here
Describe Scorpion's fatality for us real quick
Because that was pretty funny too
He takes his katana
And he slices your head off
And then again at the waist
But he does it so fast
Obviously it's going through you but you're still upright
And then he kicks
Your stomach
So your middle piece flies back
So then your legs fall
And your head goes up in the air and then he cuts your head
In half like a cantaloupe
Well I love the
Fruit ninja reference there
Okay, here you go Dark Soccer, you ready?
Here you go, enjoy!
See she's all sexy walking
And then give me a kiss boy
Sike
See and then she's all like rubbing her boobs
She's all mmm I just ate that guy's tongue
That's the best fatality ever
There you go
See, I gotta admit
I gave the demo an unfavorable review a couple weeks ago
It is growing on me a little bit
It's growing on me just a little bit
I think having seen some more of the fatalities
And getting to do
Like kind of getting more comfortable with the fighting system
Because you know they took out the whole weapon thing
And all that's gone now
So it's a little bit back to old school
And you know kind of getting used to that again
It's growing on me, I think I will get the full version
So I can do more fatalities
And Salacious Pop can be very disappointed with me
And I have one other thing to add to my gaming week
So when I was
After I downloaded the Mortal Kombat demo for PS3
I noticed there was a new Castlevania
And there have been so many Castlevania releases in the last two years
I was just like oh I'll get this whatever it is
And it's the one that just came out within the last month
What's it, we were just talking about it
What's the name, it's Castlevania
Lords of Shadow
Yeah, I played maybe ten minutes of it
And I was like okay well this is just them
Trying to be God of War
And for some reason
I don't want to say that it hurt to look at
Like it didn't give me a headache
But just running around
Something was off about the graphics visually
It was hard to look at, I don't know
But I was like okay this is God of War, Castlevania
And I just deleted it
It originally wasn't a Castlevania game
Oh yeah that's right it wasn't supposed to be a Castlevania game originally
It's a new IP when we can just slap Castlevania on it
There you go
sj100matt is in our chat room talking about the Mortal Kombat demo
And the fatality is saying
Rob you should show your mom the game
Rob that's gross, Rob
Actually that's a great idea for a future
OLR YouTube
She looks cold, she needs a jacket
We will get right on that
That sounds like a great future OLR YouTube
Is Rob's mom plays Mortal Kombat
It'll be fine, good times
Alright let's see my gaming week
There was some stuff that Salacious Pop did
But there was some different things
One night randomly we were having You Don't Know Jack
Which has kind of become this strange Friday tradition
All of a sudden which I'm kind of liking
Friday night playing You Don't Know Jack and drinking wine
I think you need stronger booze
But yeah the booze in You Don't Know Jack is good
Wine keeps it classy
Yes wine keeps it very classy
With the fart jokes in You Don't Know Jack
Which is always hilarious
But then we just started playing old school games
And when I say old school I mean like
Old school on the Xbox Live Arcade
And some things they don't even sell anymore
We were playing Smash TV
We were playing the Mortal Kombat 3 Ultimate
The arcade one that's on
Or was on Xbox Live that's not there anymore
So we were kind of having fun just playing some of those old games
And it's neat because you can kind of see how far along
The Xbox Live Arcade really has come
I mean it really was just a bunch of ports in the beginning
And some of them weren't done very well
Looking back, now going back and playing
The Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 I'm kind of like
Well where's the move list in the game?
Or where's you know anything
It's just literally the ROM
Just dumped and sold on Xbox Live Arcade
So they have come a ways
A little bit since then
And you know I think back to some of the episodes
We were doing back then and I seem to remember
We were complaining about that a lot
That a lot of the releases were just ROMs being dumped
On Xbox Live Arcade and I think Microsoft tried to fix that
After the first year or two
They said okay no more of that
That's a feature
Well excuse me princess
Not entirely the arcade
No I get what you're saying though
Yeah well remember we were playing Mortal Kombat 3
And for some reason
I could remember Kabal combos
Kabal was the character I used to use in Mortal Kombat all the time
And I remember how to make him do the spinny thing
And then punch punch uppercut
Little laser purple pew pew beam
I could do all that still
Yet when it came to fatality time I couldn't remember how to do it
So I'm like well let me pause and go to the move list
Let's just pause and reconfigure the buttons
Or quit
So we had to go on GameFAQs to get the fatality
But then we were like too lazy to do it
Let's just play something else
Let's play Smash GV
I will say one new game I played this week
I played a free game that's now available on the Playstation 3
Called Free Realms
Free Realms is a free MMO
That is available on the Playstation 3
And that's what they're calling it
It's a what?
A freemium MMO
And you download this 25 meg file
And first I was like oh shit this thing's small
This is a small game
Alright so I launch the game
Only to wait and download 700 more megabytes
So I'm like fine
It's Playstation home
So I'll go in the other room and play WoW and then come back in an hour
So finally I get in there and it's like choose your character
And you can do little character customizations
You chose this character
And I don't need to download that character
No that was the last time I downloaded
But you can either be a male or female
And you can be a human or you can be a fairy
So of course I rolled a man fairy
Because I figured nobody was going to be playing those in the game
So it would be kind of funny
And don't you dare be making jokes
Because I'll beat you
Alright so anyway
I rolled the character
You can do a custom name
But if you do a custom name then it has to go to be approved
So you have to choose a name from this slot machine thing
They have all these pre-approved names
A first name like a middle name and a last name
I think my name ended up being like Rob like Forest Tree or something
I don't remember something really dumb
So I went in there whatever
And then it's just okay
Now you're in free realms have fun
No tutorial no setup
No nothing just
Okay here you are
No tutorial? What is this?
A paid game?
So I was like okay well I kind of figured it out I think
Like I went around and figured out how to start mining
And I was like okay I'm going to mine
So the mining game is kind of like
I don't know it's like
Bejeweled but not really
Imagine if the point of Bejeweled was not to swap tiles
But instead you drew lines
That matched all the colors that were in a row
And you had to do like three or more
There's a game like that on Gaia
That's the mining game
It sounds like puzzle quest 2 when you have to pick lock a chest
Or bash open a door there's a sort of
Jewel game
It's different
I guess they just put out puzzle pirates on consoles
I mean seriously
That's an old school game I miss that game
That was actually a really rad MMO I want to go back and check that out
Anyway this is about free realms you be quiet
So I did that and whatever
So I was doing the quests
And I noticed that in the quests
If you did not want to try to find
The NPC that's the next step of the quest
You could just hit R2
And your character would just auto fly there
I fly because I'm a fairy
You just auto fly there or whatever
And okay so I made it really easy
So I kind of figured it out
This MMO is really for kids
It's a kids MMO
How many people were wandering around like
LOL want to buy gold or whatever
Nobody was really talking
You could see other real people
Yeah I guess
Do you have a player or do you have pre-determined things
That you have to say because it is
I don't know I didn't try to chat
I don't want to talk to these people
I just want to figure out what the game is
So I gathered
It is a bunch of minigames
Thrown together to make an MMO
I don't know if you saw
There's something called penguin defense
I love penguins it's like a tower defense game
And then there's basically every
Facebook-y puzzle game
99 cent iPhone game is somewhere in here
Which is one of the crafting types
I don't know if you saw but the guy
That you know I guess is
The head of
The team that made this game or whatever
Is like saying well our game is actually
Really really similar to
Minecraft I'm like
What? No it was nothing like Minecraft
Really? But apparently like the house building
Or some crap in there is
Similar to Minecraft but not
You can customize your house but it
Struck me a little more Animal Crossing than it is in Minecraft
It's not Minecraft he's just stupid
Well and here's the other thing folks
Once I got to like the 4th
Level of mining it was like
Do you want to play more mining?
Become a member today of free realm
So that was it
So essentially this MMO is just all these
Little minigames but you can play all the minigames
Up to level 4 and then it's like
Oh you gotta be a member
So it's sodium 1? Yeah basically
So I'm sorry that's not a
Free MMO
A demo of a pay MMO
This is another
Instance of a game company using deceptive
Terms to market their product
Because a lot of people are probably going to check this out because it's a free MMO
And I'm here to tell you it is not a free MMO
It is a demo
Of an MMO and I know what their defense
Would be is that well
Once you capital you can still
Be in the world and you can still talk to
People and you can still customize your fairy
And to their defense
And I hate going to their defense but
Their defense is actually
A pretty cheap MMO
$35 for a lifetime membership
But once again
Why would you want to do that?
Pay 99 cents and get the same games
On the iPhone it's really the same deal
$35 for a lifetime membership but there's no reason
To believe the longevity would be
More than 2 years before they shut the servers
Down because no one's going to play it
Here's the thing
I will give it this credit
I thought it was kind of dopey
Maybe twice and I was like okay I think I've done
Everything there is to do in this game
I see it more like a kids MMO
I think that's where they've obviously
Taken a lot of safety precautions
A lot of it's kind of watered down
I think this is something more for kids
But here is where they screwed it royally
There's no tutorial
There's nothing to kind of help you
Understand what you're supposed to do in this game
And I think a lot of kids
Would get really frustrated with it
I think this would really have to be
I think there's a very specific age range
It's probably like 10 to 13 year old girls
I think would enjoy Free Realms
And maybe some boys but I don't know
It just strikes me as more of a girly game
Because there's not a lot of violence
And yes I'm being totally sexist right now
But that's really it
It's more of a tween game
Like I could see the Jonas Brothers
And Justin Bieber showing up here
That's what Free Realms struck me as
So that was it
That was Free Realms
It's free so I guess if you want to check it out
Go for it but I think you'll get bored of it
You just totally made me think of a good porn star name
What's that?
Justine Beaver
Probably already
There probably is one
Because I thought you said Justin Beaver
And I knew you said Bieber
But then it made me think of how I was calling him Justine
And then Justine Beaver
Going to our chatroom at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
Robert M in our chat says
I assume Free Realms is the same on the PC
As far as the Freemium model
I think so
Yes
Okay
I wasn't really motivated to go check
You'll have to excuse me
I think this is not necessarily
Granted it's a way
I think it's going to get a lot of exposure to people
That might not normally try it
Because it's integrated with the PlayStation Network
And it's technically free to start playing it
But it can also be used as kind of data for them
Because they're working on a new EverQuest
They're working on some other
I forget what else
There's another IP that they're working on
A sequel for
That's also an MMO
But it'll work on this to see what works
What doesn't work
And it's a good way
Imagine if EverQuest came out the next one
As a free to play type of game
Or something like that
That might have a lot of appeal
Here's the other kind of interesting thing
I just want to throw out there
As long as we're talking about MMOs on consoles
Because there really haven't been a lot of successful ones
DC Universe to be determined
Obviously that one's kind of still new
Home
Despite all the smack
I'm talking about Free Realms
I felt there was more to do in Free Realms
Than there was to do in Home
I kind of felt like the effort that was spent
Making Free Realms
Would have been better spent
Putting minigames into Home
Or making Home
Have more of a game element to it
I get that Home
I guess is supposed to be a little more about multimedia
And I don't know
Maybe more about the chatting and so forth
Whatever
I kind of felt like
There was at least some point to Free Realms
Even if it was one I did not care to delve into further
Than Home
Where you log in and it's kind of like
If there's not a new world to go explore for five minutes
You're kind of like LOL bored by
You know?
So I don't know
It strikes me as odd that
And I realize it's a different development team
Sony's a huge company
And Free Realms already existed in some regard on the PC
So I mean
It just seems weird to me that Home
After all these years
Still I don't see the point of logging in
To Home regularly
There's nothing for me to really check every day
I don't know
Anyhow
That was my gaming week
Talked a lot about Free Realms
And some of the other minigames
Are there plans or something like that in Free Realms?
I think they have guilds
But I wouldn't know the first thing
Can you invite the people to your house?
Your guild members to your house?
Honestly Loki I didn't play that far
You probably can
And that's more people that can come to your house
And fucking Home!
Awesome!
Way to go Sony!
Bravo!
I am confident in saying though
That if there are TVs in Free Realms
You can't put videos or pictures on them
Just like Home
I'm pretty confident in saying that
So
That still doesn't matter
If no one can see them
Only so many people can come to your house
Sorry sorry
If we have any more people in this house
It's gonna violate the fire code
And the marshal's gonna come down here
We don't want any of that stuff
You know what I mean?
Just
Don't want to mess with that
Alright let's move on
We're gonna get into some actual video game news here
Of course our chatroom
chat.orangelaunchy.com
If you want to join us live on this Sunday evening
Real quick housekeeping
I may not be here in a couple weeks
So we may have a guest host in a couple weeks
I don't know I've talked to the other hosts about that
I'm not gonna be here in a couple weeks
Which week's that?
Is that the 17th?
Yes
Maybe we're not gonna be here at all that week
Where are you gonna be?
I'm not gonna be anywhere
But my wife's gonna be somewhere
Okay gotcha
She's going to a wedding
Well then I'm gonna safely say we are probably not gonna be here at all on the 17th
Which is in two weeks
Because that is also the night I need to be out
I am going in for Mensa testing though on the 16th
Which is pretty awesome
Mensa testing?
Yes Mensa testing
What?
Okay I have to know more about this
Why are you taking the Mensa test?
It's fun
Did you just sit there and you were just kind of like watching the Food Network
And then suddenly it just dawns on you?
I should take the Mensa test
I don't even remember what it was
Somehow I got directed to the test that's on their website
And I did really well on that
And I've been playing around with their iPhone app
And I was just like eh you know this is all good and all
But I want to actually try the real test
And I mean even just looking at what questions
I mean obviously the questions in the app aren't necessarily the same questions
But they have the similar types of questions
I don't see how it's really a valid IQ test
Because you really only have to be good at answering certain types of questions
And that's it
Only you Loki
This is so typical of you on the show
You're openly questioning why anyone would want to become a Mensa member
Yet you're scheduled to take the test
No I just want it I just want you know hey
Listen I just want to try it just for the hell of it
And you know hey if I if I'm accepted into it
Great that's something else to put on my resume
Whatever it doesn't matter
I want to take the Mensa test
You should
It's 40 bucks
40 bucks you got to go to a there's a guy
That's how much brain age costs right?
There's a guy does it once a month down in Dixon
And you just go down there and you go take the test
It's an hour and a half and that's it
I don't think Rob should take it
Why? Because then I'm gonna fail and I'm gonna cry
Is that why?
If you pass whatever sort of weird totally irrational opinion you ever have in your life
Politically or for anything else
Well I'm a member of Mensa so I think maybe that my opinion
Listen all you got to be
Is a bit more important than yours
All you have to be good at
I mean it's seriously it's mostly math and it's mostly pattern finding
So if you can find patterns and kind of think little you know a little bit out of the box I guess
That's it you'll be fine
And once again I still don't understand how it's really a valid
Whatever though I'll take it I'll take the test
I probably won't you know quality because you have to be in the 98th percentile of the United States
In order to you know be accepted in there
So I'd assume that's probably close to getting everything correctly
Many years ago I went on a date with a guy who was in Mensa and he had the magazine on his table
Like you know it was one of those like you know coffee table discussion pieces
I always thought
Well okay let me put it this way like if you join Mensa and stuff they have a bunch of different functions to get out
Nothing sounded interesting at all
Is there like a Mensa prom?
I don't know about that they have dating though like a dating thing you can date other Mensa members
It's stupid but it'd be cool to put on like you know to get the little you know award or whatever the hell they have
They're all hey you've been accepted in you know that'd be kind of cool but you know beyond
Do I really want to be like a functioning member? Fuck that
I want to be a member of that society
Well now are you gonna get excommunicated from Mensa if any of the members here at this program?
Eh no
Well I've had um I've used to get letters all the time to go take the test
I never wanted to do it because I thought it was stupid and pretentious
All these fucking smart people I'm just sitting here going
If you can bring your Mensa card to like Coldstone and get a buck off it's like yeah hell yeah
Free side of pancakes at Denny's because fucking Mensa card hell yeah
Smart people got it going on
Yeah is Mensa like AAA will they come change my tire?
I think it's like AAA
I don't know so we'll see we'll see what ends up happening there
I probably won't pass it I mean because there's there's a certain type of question from from playing the game
There's a certain type of question that stumps me usually
It's because it's a lot of it and they only do certain types
It's a few rows of numbers and at the very end there's you know there's four rows of four
And you're supposed to figure out what the pattern is between all of them
And a lot of it has to do okay well it's this number times this number with the digits reversed added together
You know minus this times this and you're supposed to figure it out basically you have a minute of questions
So you have to figure out this really ridiculous you know pattern in that time
And a lot of times I'm unable to do it really quickly
Although I've gone back though and actually looked at some of these and go okay so that's how they're doing it
And you find you know I don't know if it's breaking the test or anything
And you find there's certain patterns to the way they ask questions and stuff
And okay I got to look for these types of things up there it is and way you go
So I don't know it's it just sounds interesting a challenge or something I don't know
Well I'm busy this month but if you if you go next month let me know I'll go
Yeah it's on the 16th this month
Wow that's a horrible day I can't do that day
Okay
Maybe next month all right Randy's in our chat room at chat.orangelandraday.com
And says sky at the Mensa test this is like brain age right this is me at the Mensa test
Red, yellow, blue
It's really
Blue
A big
Bro
It's really a big IQ test
Yeah
That's all it is
I know I wasn't gifted and talented when I was a kid that counts for something right
Right
Yeah
I can get a dollar off at Coldstone right all right
Akuma JP in our chat room says just show them your boobs and that's it pass
I don't I don't know if that would work
Yeah
I don't think that's how it works all right anyhow let's move on actually get into some gaming news tonight
All right
Mensa talk was way better than talking about the Twitter and the Facebook and all that
I can just picture our mailbag now though filling up with emails you don't understand Mensa you're very rude
No I understand it completely I'm just you know I want to become a member but I want to become a
You just want a gold star next to your name
Okay I want to become a non-participating member of Mensa is that is that too much to ask
I just want to be on the roster I don't necessarily want to go to the meetings I don't want to attend some Mensa conference
Don't care I don't care about talking about political issues I just want the damn you know badge or whatever
Just put it on your resume
Exactly
All right how about gaming news video games hello
All right well I guess I should be sad about this but uh Mega Man universe has been canceled
That's right it's the game that was basically kind of a remade Mega Man 2 with some customizable characters
And user created levels and really didn't look that great in my opinion but some people were really gung-ho about it
It's canceled too bad so sad their decision I guess was caused by various circumstances that's such a detailed explanation
And of course they're saying that maybe that has to do with the departure of the Mega Man creator and you know the universe lead designer Kenji Inafune
So I don't know it it just looked like Mega Man powered up just you know on PC or whatever Xbox Live Arcade now with like ooh it's character Mega Man you know
Interesting idea but I mean they could
It looked interesting to me so of course I'm a little bit disappointed that it got canceled but at the same time if the game really did suck then they did the right thing
You know and it's tough to say that because you know I'm excited about the prospect of a new Mega Man game but even I have to admit it was a little weird when they had that trailer with Ryu in it
And like you know suddenly the other Capcom characters are in Mega Man universe it's like what the fuck is this game
No it would have been cool though if they had all that stuff but see here's my problem is it's basically remade Mega Man they had remade Mega Man 2 levels
If it's Mega Man universe it should be all the fucking games all of the levels all of the bosses you know something like that where you can have your customized character but you're fighting
You know how I don't even know how many you know boss characters it would be but just like you know almost a hundred you know different characters
Well remember when we only knew the title and nothing else that's what most people were speculating it was is that oh Mega Man universe is finally gonna be that clusterfuck game
Yeah it would be really awesome like okay well let's see what you know this weapon does to this character from a different game you know and stuff like that
I mean it actually if I remember correctly I think Mega Man 2 did have that kind of in when you're going through the Wily stages where they have the old you know one characters and you have to figure out what weapons did what
I don't believe the one character's ever showed up in two it's the two characters showed up in three you had to replay the stages in the corner stages in three I remember that it's weird
Got it okay I was close anyways but yeah something like that it's just they're not gonna do that because because he just it's like giving away too much I guess
Oh well too bad not coming out but we're still getting Mega Man Legends 3 right yeah it's still be supposed to be coming out of that 3DS at some point
One reason to own a 3DS I suppose I am very looking forward to that Legends was awesome
Alright well some news going on with the Xbox there is a new dashboard apparently on the way and there's a preview that was being rolled out
Major Nelson had put out the call on his blog that there is going to be another Xbox 360 I guess beta test if you will they call it a preview program it's basically a beta test
Where you know they did this a little while ago with the new experience I think they did it again with the new Netflix and all that
Yeah I did it last time when they have that and I didn't do it this time for a couple reasons well mainly because I hated having to update my system all the damn time
Because it would be like oh you got another update oh you got another update and you know all these updates rolling out a few times a day and it was annoying
And seriously not worth my getting a copy of Halo Reach even if it is in this new format and I am kind of curious to see what the new format is
I don't know it's just not really worth it
Well what's also interesting about this beta test program everybody is getting a free copy of Halo Reach with it so you know there is definitely something in it for folks here
And the reason why it's coming with Halo Reach is because there is a new disk format that's basically being beta tested with this whole thing
And that you know a lot of people are kind of assuming oh well this is to basically prevent copy you know don't copy that floppy and the piracy all that stuff this is there to update that
And that is probably true that's a big part of this as well but apparently there is something else going on
This is from a website called Digital Foundry apparently saying that the new disk format that Microsoft is going to put in this new Xbox update
It's going to give an extra gigabyte of the disk back so they are basically creating a new gig of space on the disk
I don't know if that's like maybe using the outside layer or maybe some type of copy protection they were using
They had a video partition or something like that or a certain partition that was in there
Actually it was kind of weird I think it was either the security partition or like the video partition
Here it is there was over a gigabyte dedicated to a DVD video partition that also contained anti-piracy security sectors
So that is going to be drastically reduced or admitted completely so it will free up more space on the disk
What this will mean in the immediate future I don't know but it does mean an extra gig can be packed in
That would only seem to really affect I mean I don't know like a lot of RPGs that go beyond a disk have just gone multi-disk
Like Lost Odyssey had fucking four disks
Yeah but there is certain games that maybe because it is really expensive to put out multi-disk games
For games that are getting close to that and they have to compress all their stuff or they have to cut out things because there is not room on a single disk
Or whatever it is that they are trying to put out this way it gives them at least an extra gig of space to work with
And not every company fills up at this completely so it would make sense and really they could get rid of that stupid video partition
Because who cares? Okay so I pop this in my DVD player because I am an idiot and it comes up with some Xbox logo
That doesn't say that this is
Oh is that what happens? I have never thought to put an Xbox 360 disk in a regular DVD player
So it is that video partition and so it will go oh this is an Xbox disk you have to play it in your Xbox 360
Well how about you just don't do that and then all it will do is it can't re-disk
Or just have a picture
Hey idiot this is for an Xbox 360, bye
It could just be a static picture
Well it pretty much is a picture I am surprised that it takes a gigabyte of space for that
I mean it seems like an awful lot for just a little picture
SSJ100Matt in our chatroom at chat.orangelandradi.com is asking so will these free copies of Halo Reach go towards its overall sales numbers
Think maybe throwing back a little bit to when they were giving Guitar Hero Van Halen free with Guitar Hero 5 remember that
Yes but it doesn't really matter at this point anyways because I mean the sales of it has probably dropped quite a bit
SolarFlare in our chatroom says it will still be behind Blu-Ray though, interesting point
You know that is one thing that holds the Xbox 360 back a little bit you know we do have a lot of companies that want to port their games to both systems
So I bet there's a lot of games out there on the PS3 that aren't really realizing their full potential of Blu-Ray
And this will not just help the 360 games expand but I think it will help the PS3 ports expand too right
No I mean a little bit maybe but I don't really think it's going to make a huge difference because if those companies are holding back their ports just because of space issues
Or if they're porting it to multiple systems using the same assets then it's not a huge deal I don't think
If they really wanted to they could just uncompress everything for the Blu-Ray but with Blu-Ray the whole problem was that it's slow
Especially that data on the inside is really slow compared to the stuff on the edge of the disk
So it's just I don't know I don't think it's going to make a huge difference there's not a lot of games that utilize all the space on there as well
Let me close on this question here for this story, SolarFlare in our chatroom asks are they trying to make time to having to break out the next gen console
You know we have noticed a lot of in this generation of games and you know part of it you can blame on the recession
Part of it is this whole 10 year cycle or whatever they're talking about but you have noticed that especially the 360 has had its life extended
A couple times here with Kinect and now maybe this is another step to try and breathe another year or two into it
It probably is just to help the developers out a little bit because you know there's space issues with you know what's on the disk
And it's it's just probably something they looked at and go do we really need this no okay let's get rid of it then we can free up all the space for our developers
I'm sure they would dig that so you know that's probably what it's all about
Alright well let's move on with some more news I think DarkSakura has some more Xbox news for us
I do if I don't drop my mic this actually has to do with the live indie games issue on Xbox live about the ratings
You know we had said that we had a feeling of the ratings were kind of fixed you know that they might have been manipulated
And it turns out that it actually might be the XNA creators club excuse me actually tweeted that and I quote
We are investigating a possible misuse of ratings on XBLG titles will announce more information here as it develops
So basically it's been coming to people's attention that ratings have gone from you know really high to just dropping drastically
And so they're fairly certain that there's manipulation behind it
So is the most so if the fraud is true is it being used to bolster the ratings of games that maybe are terrible or to lower stuff that competitors don't get by
It wasn't necessarily that they were being well they were being manipulated but it wasn't by the whim of a certain publisher
Basically it was that one lacrosse game that was on there they tweeted their fellows hey give us a five star rating
Well the people that are fans of the game also took it upon themselves to rate the other games one star that were in the area
So they you know inadvertently created like you know ratings fixing almost but it's just because there's no real system in place to where you have to purchase the game in order to rate it
And that kind of stuff
Oh yeah I guess that's true
So you can just rate it regardless
Yeah it seems to be highly unfair that someone should be able to rate something that they haven't played so
Yeah because I thought that you you know spent your one to three bucks or your two to four hundred whatever microsoft space bucks
I'm like wow this is terrible and then you can give it two stars after you've at least played the demo or bought it but I guess not
Yeah
You can just do what you want
Well they're looking into it apparently so maybe they'll realize that was one big oversight
To be honest doesn't iTunes have that same problem I mean I could go in and rate podcasts to one that I've never listened to
Well not with the apps I think that you're given I think you can only rate them after you've used them
Perhaps
I know that if you delete an app it asks you to rate it
Yeah
So
Which by the way you should leave Orange Knobs Radio a five star review on iTunes
Do it
Yes we actually had a couple nice ones this past week so thank you guys for doing that really appreciate it
That kind of stuff does help because when we get more five star reviews on iTunes it kind of like bumps you up in the listing and you know just helps us get more exposure
Add more people to our chat room and make it a bigger party on Sunday nights
We need to be as exposed as Malina's boobs
If not more so
Yeah
That's right alright moving on Loki
Oh by the way the people doing this total dicks I forgot to say that earlier
Another cancellation story this isn't a big surprise because this has been delayed forever and I remember playing it back a couple
God how many E3's ago was that that I actually played this but Sony online entertainment has confirmed that they have cancelled the agency
It will not be coming out
You know it was delayed forever it was a spy MMO kind of a cool little game but oh well
Man I'm just keeping sad trombone open in a window tonight because there's a lot of just cancellation news
Kind of alluding to what I was talking about before when we were talking about Free Realms they're also saying that the company is discontinuing production of the title to focus on developing resources on delivering two new MMOs based on its renowned PlanetSide and EverQuest properties
Which while also maintaining its current portfolio of online games so you know maybe a new free to play you know EverQuest because
I'm surprised just a straight up port of the first EverQuest game hasn't shown up on PS3 yet
Because there's still shit tons of people playing old school EverQuest there's what like 20 something expansions it's crazy
But you know people invested a lot in that game
It's the same reason that it's so important what Blizzard does next with their next MMO because you know this titan thing or whatever it is they're doing
They have to be very careful because they don't want to cannibalize wow but they might you know it's weird
I got an email a couple weeks ago from Ultima Online which I think I demoed way back in the day
So you know yeah new loyalty mount for like as if you have a concurrent subscription like City of Heroes does that for how long you've been paying for the game
For Ultima Online when did that come out?
I was one of the first MMOs period
It was probably like 99 it was a long time ago
Yeah it was like 12 or 13 year loyalty mount
Okay yeah so if they're still around then so is the EverQuest people yeah
Boy oh boy that is and yeah I think it's when you invest so much time into something it's hard to walk away from it
And for me that's a lot of wow it's hard for me I was really interested in DC Universe but I've been having a hard time saying I'm gonna really invest this time in DC Universe
Because all my friends are on wow this is tough
Just type a slash played and see
Oh cry all right Spassinator in our chat room says the agency being canceled how the flying fuck can anyone not see that coming
Well I don't know I don't know if I would say I saw it coming I did notice it was an awfully long development cycle
But MMOs on consoles have just become so unpredictable like and most of the news is really bad
And I don't like what are they doing wrong why why do consoles just seem to not be able to get MMOs
The lone exception being probably DC Universe maybe Final Fantasy 11 but that game is a little old now
So what is it about consoles that MMOs just aren't fucking working
I think that games on consoles are more serialized that they have a beginning and an end even if it's a God of War or an RPG that takes 80 hours to beat
You get to the ending you play it again you get the alternate ending and you're done and you move on to the next title
Console games is all about how much I want to say like it like it's an assembly line of just how many games you can churn through in a certain amount of time
But you know you you buy certain amount of games in a year and you want to get through them all
Whereas an MMO is really open-ended you never get to the end of wow
And that's sort of the culture or the attitude that piece that more is more appropriate for PCs if that makes sense
I'm with you to a point but then I ask what about Halo where it thrives on it's at least you know the older games especially to thrived on online
Which didn't really have a beginning in the end maybe maybe a match had a beginning and an end I don't know
Well yeah those are broken up into matches
Because I guess sports are somehow different and Halo is kind of like a sport IDK
Yeah I don't know Game Guru in our chat room flat out says because it is not wow
I don't know you know as much you know I'm a big supporter of wow although I don't always agree with everything Blizzard does
But you know I think there's room for more than one you know a game like DC Universe I don't think it's a failure
I don't know how that game has been selling I think it's been doing okay
But right now okay in the console universe is better than anything else right now
Than nokay?
Yeah than nokay
Eve Online is still kicking doesn't have wow's numbers but it's definitely got its market share
There's people still doing Perfect World
Final Fantasy 11 still has supporters
Guild Wars
Shit Ultima Online and EverQuest still have lots of people to play
Lineage 2 still a fucking huge game
That's really big in Korea
Yeah just not here in the US
So let's see going to our chat room again Brad from Pod Culture says wouldn't Phantasy Star Online count kinda
Well I thought it was cool that Sega actually let people transfer their characters to private servers
That was cool and so it was like well we have to close it but I know there's still people doing it
And there was Phantasy Star Universe was going on
Yeah true but Phantasy Star Universe I don't think was ever
I know people who are still playing it
Really? I just wouldn't think
Although by people I mean Julie
One person
Phantasy Star Online back in the Dreamcast especially and don't get me wrong I love Phantasy Star Online my god
It really just kinda like set the tone I think in a way for MMOs and I think a lot of MMOs wouldn't exist today if it wasn't for PSO
I love PSO
I don't know like in a way PSO isn't even really an MMO to me
No it's more like you run these rooms okay you're done
Yeah
You hang out with your friends making weird emoticons
And then you dance
PSO always felt a lot like Diablo to me for some weird reason
The whole random dungeon crawling
I actually I really started liking PSO when I started playing online
I'm sorry on the computer
You know what I think really hurt PSO you know what really really hurt that franchise more than anything I think
PSU
No I would say it was before that I would say it was the GameCube game
Because Nintendo just aborted online support
Literally told Sega sure we'll help you out with this you know MMO thing and put out this broadband adapter or anything and then Nintendo just basically said ah fuck it
LOLJK
No here's what I think was even worse the Dreamcast version in the US no online play
You had to do this little thing to manipulate it to get it to play online
Because it wouldn't support the broadband adapter
Yeah I imported that or I did something where
Yeah I could play the Dreamcast one online
I had the ethernet
I had the modem though
Well no we had that too it was it was like it was something that you had to manipulate in the menu
The DNS I think or that your IP you had to put in something to force it to go out through the ethernet
Yeah
You had to do something to it to get it to work
I don't remember having that problem I just remember it working ah whatever it's been so long
Well I guess and also going back to the agency thematically a spy MMO I don't know something about MMOs is you have to even in fantasy star online you're not killing literal dragons
But it's whimsical fantasy sci-fi you know no one wants to get together with their five friends and smuggle microfiche
Matrix online ended anything that I've noticed well the city of heroes is still going Star Trek online is still going strong
I love Star Trek online in fact I need to pay for a month but
Yeah I don't I don't think MMO has to be swords and dragons and mystical stuff
It has to be fantasy
Yeah it's just I think the other that's a tried and true method that's an established formula that's a formula that's working right now
That's WoW's formula in a way I think
But now they have goblins with motorcycles
I think we haven't really seen the other type but then again Eve online is not is a space game DC Universe not really dragons
Star Trek online totally different thing but Star Trek's a whole separate fandom too you know like
Well and the fact that they're getting so much right in Star Trek online they're really playing to continuity fans and sort of getting
I mean I hated enterprise but they are incorporating the better parts of enterprise into the game
And it's got something for the fans that's the big thing is that the people that are playing Star Trek online are Star Trek fans
Alright let's move on from MMO chat we're running a little long because of MMO chat let's do some other quick stories here
I got a story about GameStop and GameStop apparently has bought absorbed some more companies
They bought spawn labs and they've also bought a company called impulse now what the hell did these things do
Okay spawn labs they did this high def box set that apparently I guess it sounds to me a lot like the whole online system
It's kind of similar to that so that's you know one thing they've absorbed and then they also got impulse
Which apparently is going to have three parts to it which is the client the impulse client which you can use to download games
The reactor which is like DRM management and copy protection and all of that
Letting the developers do achievement friends list and all the kind of like steam xbox
Sounds like a steam clone
And then impulse publisher which is real time reporting and management tools
GameStop has bought these companies so in a way I sort of see this as them thinking ahead a little bit
Because these companies have more to do with online distribution and something that isn't so much the stores
You know they did not buy stores in this acquisition well they did but it's a different type you know
So I have a feeling they are thinking ahead as to this whole how do we counter digital distribution
They're absorbing more and more into their collective
A little bit yes but you know it doesn't mean all the mall stores are going to shut down next week
But I don't know this digital distribution thing if I was kind of in this GameStop industry I'd be a little freaked out right now
Well maybe not right this second but you know five years from now this could be
Just makes me think of Blockbuster and Netflix when Netflix first came out
Is this you know Johnny come lately by mail oh who's going to use that
Blockbuster hopped on that bandwagon but they did it too late but I think they hopped on it early enough to save them past Hollywood's demise
Right so I feel like GameStop you know and again I don't mean to like panic people or whatever this is years away
You know these things happening but GameStop buying this I think they're trying to kind of put themselves in a position
Where they are like Blockbuster got in on it early that's what this seems like to me
They're setting up a safety net
Yeah
That we know because if I don't have any details because I really don't think I know any more store managers
But from what I've noticed I'll go into a GameStop you know and it'll be dead empty
There'll be no one in there and I think that it's just first of all a sign of the economy and another thing
And this this is actually I'm not going to go into it because it's a little bit more on the cycle psychology level
But I think that people are becoming more isolated wanting to do more things from home
Not wanting to go out amongst people you know what I mean
That that's why online services have become so popular you know people need to get out of the house
See I have to play devil's advocate here though a little bit the one by his house in South San Francisco always packed
The one in that mall what is that mall called?
Well yeah but that's in the mall
ceremony
I'm talking about strip mall places
Oh okay
They're dead
I don't really go to a lot of those yeah
Well Dan will randomly let's go buy this store number because he knows all the store numbers
Uh-huh
I'll be like okay well which one's that oh it's the one over here then why didn't you just say that was the one over there
So
Let's see go into our chat I'm going to chat on orangeontraday.com
SolarFlare says they're going to have to do some good stuff to compete with steam
I think that's what part of all this is is to really align themselves in a way where they can
Maybe they'll start doing this thing in the store where you know buy the copy in the store and get some type of digital download thing
The free costume or you know something extra maybe that's kind of where they're going
We'll see
All right moving on dark soccer what do you got for us
Well we have some news out of Japan
Oh which is where video games come from
Oh and it's a new Super Mario Brothers Wii arcade cabinet that's being developed by Capcom
Yeah it's Super Mario Brothers Wii Coin World
It's a four player game where you earn medals by participating in mini games so kind of
It's Mario Party
Kind of Mario Party-ish I say ish
Not too much running and jumping
And it actually is on Capcom of Japan's website there's a trailer and everything
And I'm just like why is Capcom doing it but then again Capcom is
Nintendo hasn't ever really been much in the arcade scene except for the play choice
Oh that was years ago though
Arcades are not even the same thing now
In fact I more think this is news worthy as oh arcade games are still popular somewhere in the world
But I think it's actually neat that they've got that relationship with Capcom to do it
Because Capcom does put out good quality
Who did the Mario Kart sit down driver game that's at
Namco because you can play as Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man in that
All right yes I thought
So yeah Namco did that
So yeah it's not totally unheard of that's a good example
It's not totally unheard of that other companies might get to do Nintendo stuff in the arcade
One of my favorite and most underrated arcade machines ever F-Zero
Which is a fucking amazing game
Actually the arcade machine's biggest problem was it only had six freaking tracks in it
And you could unlock them all at home
There's one of the guys that's in the Playstation hacking scene or whatever
He's kind of gotten out of it now but know what his thing is now
He's dumping the stuff for the Triforce system
Nice
Yeah of course the Triforce system was the F-Zero game
Because that was Nintendo, Sega, and Namco
This looks really fun
All on one
It's like you take a different corner and everyone's got different minigames
But it looks really cool
I'll link the website to everyone in the chatroom
You know how that would make millions here in the US
Tickets
Is have it spit tickets
Yeah
Gee I wonder if this will be part of New Super Mario Brothers Wii Dose
Maybe
You never know
Alright let's move on, travel the world, look at some release dates of actual stuff coming to a store near you
We're in April now so now that we've passed the fiscal end of years for a lot of companies
There's not a lot of companies putting out stuff
So here's what we've got
Carnival Games, Monkey See Monkey Do for the Xbox 360 and Kinect
That's coming out this week
Karaoke Revolution Glee volume 2
Coming out game only and with a mic
Sorry I just burped
Sorry
Remington Super Slam Hunting Alaska on the Wii
Starring Sarah Palin
Except not really
And then on the 3DS a week from today
Tom Clancy Splinter Cell 3D
And I believe Raven Grab is travel through time 3D is also coming out at the same time
That's it
Wow
Yeah
Short week
Alright
As will be much of April
Well
SSJ100 Matt says needs more bacon
Let's go to Japan real quick and look at the games coming out there
We have Bullet Soul comes out in Japan this week on the Xbox 360 and Dragon Age Origins Awakening
I imagine it seems like they're behind a little bit
Keep in mind they've got to translate that stuff into Japanese so it is a little bit behind
On the Playstation 3 this week
Nada
Going over to some other systems then
Taking a look at the Wii
Nothing there either
In fact not a lot on the horizon for the Wii
How about the 3DS in Japan?
Well you got a game called Cubic Ninja comes out this week in Japan
It looks like you move little boxes that have ninja looking graphics on them
And you, I don't know, move them around these stages and make them fall down holes
It looks like a puzzle game
Let's say it's a puzzle game, it uses the tilt controls on the 3DS and it is a 3DS game without 3D
Is that coming, oh really
It's coming out over here in June
Just the screenshots that I just so briefly saw
It kind of looked like the yellow blob on the PSP port of the Loco
Loco Loco?
Loco Loco, yeah, looked like that
On the PSP this week, Earth Defense Force 2 portable
That might be an interesting lookie
Awesome
Princess Frontier portable, awesome
And then a game called Are You Alice? comes out this week on the PSP
Hello, are you Alice? No, okay, are you Alice? No, are you Alice?
Regular and limited edition
This looks to be, it's kind of like based off an anime it looks like
Kind of like these chapters, looks like kind of like one of those interactive novel type things
Because there's regular and limited edition
It's a dating sim
Is it really?
I think it is
No, this looks too like
If this is a dating sim, no, the woman would not have a sword in a dating sim
Look at it, it's got all that text
Oh boy, alright
And there's some pretty fun, funny hentai ones out there that involve swords and dragons and tentacles
Coming next year from Quadratic Dream
Are you Jason?
The side story for Heavy Rain
Are you Jason? No, okay
Are you Jason? Have you seen Jason? Do you know Jason?
That's it for Japanese release dates
Well in the UK, Jack and Squat really
On the 5th is Red Faction Battlegrounds for Xbox 360
And the same thing a day later on the 6th for Playstation 3
And also the Dishwasher Vampire Smile on Xbox 360
What the crap is that?
Sounds like the sequel to the Dishwasher, the indie game that ended up being a real arcade release
Oh yeah
Sounds like a sequel
There's people in cages and a dude with a big sword
That is a sequel to the game
I would play that
Alright, just a couple more stories for you guys
And then the classic game of the week
And we have a pretty big one this week
So we'll get to that in just a moment, but first, Loki
I don't know if I can report this story without fear of being sued by Namco
But I'm gonna do it anyways
Namco Bandai has filed for a couple trademarks in the Katamari franchise
Katamari Amore, which is filed under Katamari Amore and Katamari Amore Rolling Whopper
Hopefully nothing to do with Burger King
And I guess hints obviously that they're gonna put out another game in that series
And then of course there's two additional trademark applications for Time Trip and Have a Nice Trip
Not necessarily in the Katamari series, perhaps
But I guess Trip was one of the characters in Enslaved
So maybe it's something to do better
Or maybe, heaven forbid, a new IP altogether
I don't know
Maybe, or it's another Katamari game, who knows
Didn't the guy from Namco or whatever
Yeah, he left to make
Yeah, he made a pretty
The subtext was pretty clear that he was sick of the franchise after the second one
And he just didn't care anymore
They kept making them anyways, or I should say they kept rehashing them
Oh, I'm still playing Noby Noby Boy
Yeah, because that's what he did after Katamari
It's actually fun, people are still doing stuff on Noby Noby Boy
On the phone, and uploading everything to Facebook so that girl will grow
I hope if it's a new Katamari game it is not part of this whole jump the shark that's kind of dominated this last generation of the games
I'm sure we'll have a Katamari game that'll be in 3D that'll be basically the rehash levels again
And it's going to be on the 3DS
I'm sure that's going to happen eventually because
If it's in 3D I'll throw up
Because that's what they do, and whatever
I don't know, I can't really get excited about this stuff because
Even I bought the last Katamari game that was on 360
It was just kind of, eh
The 360 one was bad
The PS3 one's alright
The PS3 one's okay, but the problem with the PS3 one is that it's basically the same stuff from the first two games
Mixed together
It's kind of like
The Katamari game on the PS3 is like the Wilson Phillips greatest hits album
They only fucking had two CDs, right?
So there's not a lot to compile a greatest hits album from
Daft Punk has the greatest hits and I think they only had what, three albums?
Yeah
I guess it's kind of like that then, I don't know
You know, surely you've seen those one hit wonders that have these greatest hits CDs
When I'm discovered and released an album, I'm just gonna call it Greatest Hits
Like your first album will just be called Greatest Hits?
My first album will be Greatest Hits
My second one will be, well these are better than the last ones
You know the DDR band Erotic, which of course
Greatest Tits
Yeah, they had an album called Greatest Tits
I like that name
Moving on, one more story for me for this part of the show
PlayStation Rewards
Remember this?
It was a beta program that happened last year
And the beta is now ending
And this PlayStation Rewards program was supposed to be launching for all the PlayStation folks in the next month
But I guess Sony has decided based on what they've learned throughout the beta test
They do not want to roll this program out to the public yet
So yeah, they're gonna say, well we thank loyal and devoted customers with innovative offerings
But yeah, it's not happening right now
In fact, they're thinking it's been delayed indefinitely
Now the PlayStation Rewards program was supposed to have these quests
And other things that go with it
It was supposed to be quests
Did you get real tangible stuff from this I think?
You could get pro or legendary status from this
And I think you got free PlayStation Pulse
Or move things, I don't know
You get little trinkets from it
Yeah, they've decided to delay this indefinitely so far
So I don't know, maybe they'll come out and say they changed their mind at E3
But a quote from a PlayStation representative
After careful consideration and evaluation following the PlayStation Rewards beta
We have decided not to roll out the program to the public at this time
We remain committed to providing the best overall consumer experience for our users
And we will be refocusing our efforts in the near future to further developing PlayStation Plus
And our other network services
So maybe becoming a PlayStation Plus member is all the reward they want to give you
That's what it sounds like anyway
So if you want rewards, you gotta pay for them
They're like, wait, we can charge people for these rewards
Awesome
Yeah, that's not a reward really, that's a sale
That's buying something
Yeah
Alright, well let's get to the part of the show
And you shouldn't really have to bribe somebody to use the different services on there
That's what I'm saying
Okay, now let's get to the part of the show where we take a stroll down memory lane
And revisit a classic video game from the archives in Dark Sakura
This one's really classic, it's kinda moldy
Yeah, in her quest to find the classic game of the week
That she thinks, hey you ungrateful bastard kids, you need to play this game right away
And get off my lawn
Alright, or mow my lawn if you're gonna stand on it
Yeah, mow my lawn, seriously, it frickin' needs it
Then get off it
Alright, Dark Sakura, what is the classic game of the week?
I think there's only one way to introduce that, and that's to play some of the dialogue off
Alright, let's see what I can do here
I think I have to fast forward a wee bit in this video to get to the dialogue
Here you go
Wow, what a mansion
I hope this is not Chris's blood
Okay, this is Resident Evil
And I actually did put up a sample of the redone dialogue in the GameCube version
That's so much better, so much better
I can probably get to a little bit of that here, let's see
What is this place?
Not quite your ordinary house, that's for sure
Hey, Wesker, where's Chris?
I bought the GameCube for that
Jill, no
You don't wanna go back out there
But we've got to be saying the same stuff
What was that?
Chris?
Anyway
No
I hope this is not Chris's blood
Master of Unlocking
Maybe you, the Master of Unlocking, can use this
Yeah
Let's see, so it was known as Biohazard in Japan
Which actually, I've got a PlayStation version of Biohazard and I have it on Saturn
But this one is put out by Capcom
And it spawned a legacy still going on today
It was developed by Shinji Mikami
And as of May 2009, it sold 40 million copies
So this was one of the early ones into the survival horror series
And you, it had a full motion intro
But they cut part of the intro for the American one
Because there is a scene where Chris pulls out his Zippo
Lights a cigarette and takes a drag
And then there's another scene where this zombie's head falls off and it looks like Michael Jordan
They cut that too
Honestly, it didn't look like Michael Jordan, guys
It didn't, it was stupid
But yeah
So with this one, basically you are S.T.A.R.S. member
Jill Valentine or Chris Redfield
And you are exploring this mansion and unlocking its secrets
And Chris is helped by Claire
Was it Claire? Yeah, it was Claire
And she was young and perky and a medic
Rebecca, that was it, Claire was his sister
It was Rebecca
And Barry helps Jill
He also has the best line in the game
You are almost a Jill sandwich
And I hope this is not Chris's blood
So yeah
It was really, really ahead of its time when it came out
And there's actually other versions out
They did the, I think it was called
I'm trying to find the name of it
They did a redone version of it that was
Like a remix
I believe it was like a remix version
And they had different outfits and the items in the house were in different places
And the graphics were touched up a little bit
And then there was the GameCube version
Which we just heard a little bit of
That was completely redone, better dialogue
I think it still had the same voice cast though
But it's pretty much the original game
Just really, really cleaned up
Some of the story elements
They added a little bit more references to the sequel
And Code of Veronica, I think they fixed some of the continuity issues
But otherwise it was the same game
But even in the very first one they had a reference to Ada
Who was in Resident Evil 2
And she was really cool
And it also has my favorite thing in here
Is the diary
Ugly face so ate him
Itchy, tasty
Yeah, so that's where itchy tasty comes from
So this one, I mean it spawned all kinds of sequels
You know, we had Code Veronica
We had Resident Evil 2 and 3, 4 and 5
Who remembers Dino Crisis?
Dino Crisis is actually pretty neat
It actually just announced Resident Evil Revelations for the 3DS
And that they had Resident Evil Portable
There's all kinds of versions out there
There's mobile games
I even had this on the game.com
I'm reminded of a
I'm not sure if it was the advance
But there was a Resident Evil novel guidance side story
Where it's Leon and Barry on a cruise ship, I think
I think you were right
I don't think it's canon
Because that's some obscure stuff
There were the Umbrella Chronicles, the Dark Side Chronicles
Resident Evil Outbreak
It was a mobile one, you said?
Or handheld?
Handheld
There was Biohazard Eye Survivor
And Resident Evil Assault the Nightmare
You know, actually one of my favorites in the series was Gun Survivor
Which I got to play in the arcade
No, Gun Con was Namco
The accessory
Well, in Japan you could play it with the gun
But in the US it
Oh yeah, because you can't use those here
They're taboo
Which I always thought it would have been perfect to do it on the Dreamcast
Maybe Gun Con in the US
But you couldn't play Gun Survivor, you just navigated through
But I thought that with the D-pad that was on the gun
You should have been able to control with that
Although the arcade version was really cool because you
Walked by pressing forward with the gun
And you could back up with the gun, it was really fun
But the first Gun Survivor one I think was Code Veronica
Or was it the second one?
I think that was the second one
But that's the one I played
And there was also Resident Evil Operation Raccoon City
That was another one
It's supposed to be coming out on Playstation 3, Xbox 360, and on Windows
And Resident Evil 6 is also coming out
So yeah, all kinds of stuff going on
And then there's movies, which the movies don't really have a lot to do with the game
Not anymore really
Just a few things that are in common
And there were all kinds of comics that went out
They did a manhua, which the Code Veronica one was actually really good
I liked it
All kinds of cool stuff
So yeah, Resident Evil
Worst voice acting ever in the first one
But it's laughable, it's fantastic
And I think Resident Evil of the 3D generation of consoles
The Playstation 1 was the first game
That really spawned an entirely new genre
Which was survival horror
And we have Resident Evil to thank for Silent Hill
And that whole franchise
I think Silent Hill took a different turn in survival horror
Well yeah, but just the whole dark
You against monsters
The whole scary thing
I think Resident Evil sort of laid down the foundation
I don't know, I always thought Friday the 13th
On the Nintendo spawn
No way, no way
It was Nightmare on Elm Street
Or maybe it was the Metal Gear
Which I think was always kind of
I don't know, it's not necessarily survival horror
It's survival tactics
Survival, tactical, dodging
Well that's always stealth
Yeah, that'd be stealth action
Whatever, shut up
But did any of those games have zombie dogs?
They did not
Okay then, zombie dogs
So is that it? That's it
Classic game of the week, Resident Evil
Oh, there's actually one more thing
Make it quick
That was a beta
Of Resident Evil 2
That had a different character named
Elza Walker and Leon
And she was like a motorcycle chick
Wearing the red and white leathers
And they actually ended up scrapping it
When it was about 60% done
I'm trying to get my hands on one of those
I think my N64 box, the console system
When the N64 first came out
You know how they have
On the side of the box
The game, like if you buy this console
Here are the games that are coming out
I have one that has a Resident Evil 1.5
Or 2, because it was supposed to be an N64 game
It was supposed to be Resident Evil 2
Yeah, that's on that and it never came out
I guess for that system
Because I said the backgrounds weren't interesting enough
But it had a lot of the same mechanics
From the first one
But they saved a few things to what eventually became the second one
And lost a kind of cool looking character
Sad face
That's it
Well that's it for your classic game of the week
We'll see what she picks next week
But for now we're going to take a quick break guys
We will be back in just a little bit
With more of Orange Lounge Radio
Don't go anywhere though guys
We've got plenty more coming up in tonight's Part B
We're going to talk about the 3DS
A little more about the launch
A lawsuit against EA
And a game called Xenoblade and its localization
We're going to come back to the Ultima topic
Because there's some really interesting news
So that could be very interesting
We're going to talk about all that right after this
When we come back with more of Orange Lounge Radio
Welcome back everybody
To more of Orange Lounge Radio
Live on this Sunday
April the 3rd of 2011
With a 408th episode of our show
Let's talk quickly about our side projects that we do
If you like OLR
You might also like these shows
Dark Zakra
Comic Insanity
We go live on Tuesday
You can download the podcast at
Infamous.net
That's N-F-A-M-O-U-S dot net
And you can also find us on iTunes
It's a comic book podcast done with
You've heard her on the show Tiara, Mara & Marvel
And Dan Shadow
And we are very very fun
Listen to us
Very fun
Also pretty fun
The best little Hoard House in Azeroth
It's a little side project
Xtfer and I have all about the world
Of Warcraft
www.hoardhouse.com for more information
That's H-O-R-D-E-H-O-U-S-E
Up to 20 episodes this week
We hit 30
Nice you're old
Oh wait we're on 408 of this show
I know right
Quickly going to go to
The rapid fire news
And the tweets and all that stuff
I wanted to ask you
Speaking of Twitter and all that
Some folks saw that you were doing a little bit of fundraising this week
By selling off some of your
Video game collection
Which I know is probably not an easy thing to do
But what was some of the stuff you sold this week
And how did it do?
My most coveted title
That I got rid of was
Magic Knight Rayearth
By Working Designs for the Sega Saturn
It was the last game put out in the US
Months after the Saturn was already
Dead and buried
They put this out
Even more rare I think than Panzer Dragoon Saga
I want to say
It's up there
Panzer Dragoon RPG
I don't know
The two of them are pretty much rivals
For hardest to find
So Rayearth was a top down
Basically it was a Legend of Zelda
A Link to the Past clone
As far as visually how it looked
The RPG
Anime cutscenes
The clamp anime
Beautiful show
They did such a good job with translating it
Especially since they don't talk every time you touch something
Like in a Japanese one
It saved so much memory
It was so much better
So that went for
I've seen it go for over $100
But I got about $80 for it
That's not too bad
I never played it
Never touched it
We've beaten it
Bust a Move
Not the puzzle bobble thing
But it was released in the US as Bust a Groove
The soundtrack
I think in the JP
Edition was a lot better
Paper Mario 64
Ogre Battle 64
And a bunch of Saturn import stuff
Darkstalkers
X-Men vs Street Fighter
I'm going to have a round 2 of stuff
Going up next week
One of which will include
The PS2 edition of Rez
I'm getting rid of that
Because I have it at Rez HD on Xbox 360
And I think some DDR games
You're going to get rid of too right?
Yeah I'm selling my PS1
3rd Mix and Best Hits
Which I think came out after
4th and before 5th
Let me talk to you about Rez
Ok
So check that out, that'll be up soon
The reason I'm getting rid of these
Is because they're in great shape
I know I'm never going to play them again
But actually having them in my hand
I wanted to hook my Saturn up
To play some Vampire Savior
Even though if it wasn't for me selling them
I never would have had the Inkling
To ever touch the game again
Even though it's a great game
So it's just weird how you're attached to something
But you know you'd never play it
Unless you're confronted with getting rid of it
It's just weird how nostalgia works
That's kind of how our vault is
Except we sometimes do get the wild hair
To break out one of the systems and play it
I mean the whole reason we have
So many systems is because nothing quite
Mimics having the controller
In your hand
You can play Vampire Savior with us
I'll hook up the Saturn
Alright, well let's get to some rapid
Fire news before we get into
Doing the tweets tonight
Last call for tweets at twitter.com slash o-l-r
Meanwhile Loki hates to tear you
Away from whatever it is you're doing over there
That involves a lot of numbers
I don't think that's porn
But yeah we gotta do some rapid news
I'm crunching in numbers
Yeah there's some cool announcements
Chopped Lifter HD
It's a remake of the classic game
Supposed to be coming out on the Playstation
Network and PC this fall
And based on some of the screenshots
Here
Looks
A little
Much like the classic game just you know
With the 3D HD visuals
Kinda cool looking
I don't know, hopefully it turns out well
And then
Another remake also in the works
Warlords
The old Atari game is being remade
That one's coming to Xbox Live Arcade
And Playstation Network this summer
You probably can expect that as part of the
Summer of gaming or whatever the hell they call it
On the Xbox Live
They're saying that it's gonna also
I guess have the classic version
As well as an
Evolved version
I guess which was found
Or they had the evolved version
Which was in a previous Xbox Live Arcade release
But this
I guess is gonna be
Something different
Never really played
The original Warlords game so
I don't know, looks neat
And then finally
Minecraft
Goes into beta 1.4
And they added
The wolves, cookies
And some other stuff
Yeah tameable wolves
Cookies, sleeping in a bed
Resets your spawn position
A new logo holding shift while
Climbing will hang onto the ladder
Spiders no longer
Trample crops and
Lots and lots of infrastructure
And statistical
achievements
Alright
Neat, let's
Have you played Minecraft yet?
No I have not either
I watched a funny video today though
Of some girl's Minecraft house
And she was just really funny
Oh my god there's like 400 pounds of bacon right here
And there were like pigs everywhere in front of her house
It was really funny
I haven't played Minecraft
But yet I've played SingStar
And SingStar is adding 40 new songs to the store
This week
Now you can sing along with such karaoke classics
As Cryin' by Aerosmith
Who Let the Dogs Out by The Baja Men
Crocodile Rock by Elton John
Let's see
I'm Good I'm Gone by Leaky Lee
Likey Lee?
I don't even know how to say her name
She's crazier than Bjork
I don't know how you would sing along to that
But you can now
Grace Kelly by Mika
A bunch of songs by the band Razorlight
Oh, Just for Salacious Pop
I know you love the Pussycat Dolls
So you can do Hush Hush now
On SingStar
Also some dance add-ons have been sold as well
And then most interesting in a way
Classical song packs
I'm not sure how exactly you sing
I guess maybe it's old opera style
I don't know but you can do
O Sole Mio by Di Capua
Mozart with Queen of the Night Aria
La Donna y Mobile
by Verdi
I don't know why but yeah
now classic songs are available
I know classical singers
That's a series that's like Boohoo Crazy in Europe
Yeah, it's pretty big over there
There are okay games here
They had the SingStar Queen
and the SingStar Abba
Probably the biggest thing about this is that
the actual music videos, if available, play
behind the song when you're singing it
So that's pretty cool
Can't wait to see the music video for the Mozart stuff
I know, I'm kind of wondering how that's gonna work
I have some generic video in the background there
I don't know
Well, some more information following unfortunately
the tragedy in Japan
It has some folks asking a little bit forward
What's gonna happen to Tokyo Game Show 2011?
Well, now there's no plans to
cancel the Tokyo Game Show just yet
But they are saying it could happen in a reduced state
This was in an interview
that the Tokyo Game Show officials did with Kotaku
They didn't say anything yet
But they did say
Depending on the situation from here on out
It's possible that the show
is reduced
The show is scheduled to take place in September
I'm sure it'll still be a
pretty big thing and they haven't said
it's closed off to the public or any of that yet
But they are treading a little bit
carefully with a lot of uncertainty
still happening in the world
after the really unfortunate
earthquake and subsequent
tsunami and subsequent issues with the reactor
and all that stuff
Hopefully they're able to get all that sorted out
in the 2021 show in September
Speaking of the tragedy in Japan
A real favorite here of
Orange Lounge Radio is spearing up a new
effort to raise money
Akira Yamaoka, who of course was
one of the minds behind Silent Hill
and so forth, he is doing a benefit
album for tsunami survivors
It's called Play for Japan
Kind of a play on words of the
Pray for Japan Twitter hashtag that was going on at the time
It's gonna be a benefit album
and it's gonna have some of these
participants will be involved
Akira Yamaoka, Nobuo Uematsu
who did of course Final Fantasy and a lot of those
Yasunori Mitsuda, Chrono Trigger
hello, need I say more
Bear McCreery, if you don't recognize that
Battlestar Galactica
and which, god that had a great
soundtrack that show
and Woody Jackson who did Red Dead Redemption
so some western influence
as well as from Japan
so that's pretty awesome
Akira Yamaoka also posted a letter at
playforjapan.org
available in several languages
so that's pretty cool, it's supposed to come out in May 2011
on iTunes
so you don't even have to leave the house to do your
little bit to help support
the Japanese relief, I think that's a great idea
Alright, let's move on
Dr. Sakura
Well, we have some
Street Fighter news actually coming out of
the UK
there was
registered for the BBFC
Super Street Fighter 4 Arcade Edition
to be coming out in June
that's the British Board of Film Classification
which also is in charge of
video games for some reason
why can't they do that here?
anyway
Capcom hasn't
necessarily confirmed
but they're putting out that there's
that it could be
download content
or you can buy an expansion, they're still
speculating
also in other news
Music Unlimited, the platform is coming
to PSP, NGP
and Xperia Play
this was actually stated
by the CEO of Sony Network
Entertainment, Sean Layden
saying that it's going to be coming
to the PSP in a matter of weeks
so that will be later on this year
and
this is
as far as I can tell
I think this is a music sharing
program
from what it looks like
but like a legal way of doing it
instead of like you know
LimeWire or whatever the kids use these days
BitTorrent I guess
and then in Rock Band 3
news we have Joy Division download content
which I like Joy Division
but not just them, we have Grand Funk Railroad
the Locomotion and we're an American band
and J Gal's band Freeze Frame
and Joy Division Love Will Tear Us Apart
That's it
Alright, let's go to the Twitter
but first I want to read a comment here from our chatroom
at chat.orangelandtrady.com
Kossin in our chatroom says
I do not want the MPAA
in charge of video game ratings
those guys are idiots
yeah actually that's a really good point, those guys are idiots
you know the way they rate some of those movies
is unbelievable
I like the idea of a unified system
between movies and
video games but don't fucking put the MPAA
in charge of that, dismantle the MPAA
and put a new board in charge
that would be a wonderful idea
so a good point from that person in our chatroom
Let's go to the Twitter
twitter.com
slash o-l-r is where you can send us
tweets every week
we read your tweets here on the show and we'll respond to them
Fun ET Man sent us a tweet
saying I wonder if you will talk about this
and sent us to an article on
thelostlevels.org
this is a website that likes to kind of find
old prototypes and things that have
changed in games, they've done some
stories on Zelda or whatever
well this article happens to be on the game
Bio Force Ape
and I guess this is a game that was kind of recently
finally dumped into a ROM
here's the deal, this game never actually
came out, it was teased in
Nintendo Power in the early 90's
it was an NES game and in this game
you take control of Bio Force Ape
a genetically altered super chimpanzee
as he tries to make his way through a high-tech
maze to rescue his adopted human family
what? yeah right?
apparently one of the best parts of the game
is when Bio Force Ape takes a wild out of
control ride on one of the speeding platforms
or coal cars
animation is humorous and so on and so on
and yeah so I guess there was
this whole debacle, somebody had
the game, it came out in
2005 that the game was out
there and that there was photographic evidence
taken and I guess
you know obviously the thing was
it had bugs in it and so forth
the guy was urged to
sell the prototype but he was
really scared about the ROM getting out there
more
stuff came out including this
humorous punching of a slime
it's like a monkey made out of
butter, what is that? I don't even know what that is
but then apparently he smashed the
cartridge, he said screw you guys
I'm going home and smashed the cartridge
well apparently the real deal was finally
sold and
dumped and there's actually a whole little
thing available on YouTube
where you can actually kind of see some of this game in progress
it's fast moving for an NES game at the
time, it looks like it has blast processing
it looks like it is made by Sega
no it's not Sega, it's close
it's uh, SETA
SETA made the game
it looks like a Ninja Gaiden ROM hack
or something, a little bit doesn't it
it's very fast moving
see there's a little minecart
it looks kind of cool
go monkey go, go monkey go
alright
let's see moving on to some more
tweets here
SSA100Matt sent us a tweet saying
our old pal YYR has released
a press kit for Snake
361, it's the sequel
to Snake 360
Snake 361 is supposed to be coming out for
the holidays this year
and let's see what is some new stuff
teleporters and traps
so now you get teleporters in the game
of course Snake 360 had the
four player battles, it was very
multiplayer, they really should let this
they really should just let him put it out on Xbox Live
it would be really cool if you could actually play it
through the interwebs, but right now
it's more of a local multiplayer game
and I think he had YouTubes of people playing the game
and having fun, battle mode
will, I mean those teleporters are going to drive you
bonkers in battle mode, so that'll be fun
and there's some 1080p screenshots
available now and some music
is all there, so all the information is
available at snake360.com
Spazinator
tweets us a story, it's a Sony
story here, let me see what this is all about
I've got to load this, it's not loading
God dammit he's trying to rickroll us
you little bastard, I cut it off
before he could, was that real?
yeah it started coming, it said Rick Astley
nope, nope, done with that
so congratulations Spazinator
you have banned yourself from
Twitter for one whole month, we will not be reading
your tweets for one whole month
that's what's going to happen to people that try to
rickroll us, you are banned from Twitter for a month
congratulations, alright
let's move on to Tiger Claw
sends us a couple links here, one of them
is about Burnout Crash
Burnout Crash is coming to the
Xbox 360 and the Playstation 3
I guess EA hasn't
announced a new Burnout game
but Australia actually released
a classification for
Burnout Crash
and I guess surfing some LinkedIn profiles
has found out that this is happening
it's an Xbox 360 and Playstation 3 title
no official announcement yet
seems logical there would be another Burnout game
at some point, hopefully it's a little more like
the older games, I know the Burnout Paradise
or whatever was really well supported
but that franchise
still sells really well, right?
as far as I know, yeah
Paradise was awesome
alright, I mean
come on, you gotta love, it's like
oh, any moment I want to go in the crash mode, ok
crash mode, it was awesome
alright, and
moving on, let's see, Tiger Claw
sends us one more link here, I'll read
the other one he sent us
is coming up later, let's see
Americans average 13 minutes
playing video games on TV
daily
only 13 minutes?
I think that's the people who play for 4 hours at a time
balancing out those that don't play at all
I don't know how that works, but yeah
adults spend an average of 13 minutes
a day using a TV to play video games
that's from Nielsen's state of the media
US TV trends
by ethnicity
I guess, because now it breaks it all down
by ethnic as well
African Americans spend slightly more time
playing video games on TV averaging
16 minutes a day across the population
Hispanics spend an average of 10 minutes a day
you know, they're all
less than 20 minutes
which most people I know that play video games spend
hours and hours, so
this is just this weird law of averages thing
coming into play
Nielsen got paid probably millions of dollars to do that study
that really didn't tell me anything
ironically enough though, you have to admit this is a little bit ironic
according to their little graph here
the smallest ethnicity
or I should say the smallest playtime
by any ethnicity, 9 minutes
Asians, who knew?
there you go
because they have
the tiger mom
I guess, I don't know
let's move on
something a little less racial please
a little less racial?
alright, fine
so we're gonna talk a little bit about
the 3DS, obviously
3DS probably did pretty well
I'd assume
Nintendo's saying it's the best first day
handheld sales
launch ever
so
there's no real numbers yet
but they're saying they did pretty well
and I guess the numbers will be made public on April 14th
when the NPD numbers actually
come out
so it'll be interesting to see how well they did
I'm assuming they sold everything
or at least pretty close to everything within the last
probably week it came out
so
good for them, I suppose
unfortunately though
it wasn't without problems
there are some issues with the 3DS
including some crashes
apparently people have been running into
some software crashes
that require the system
to be shut off and then turned back on
to get it playing right
apparently this was fixed in
the latest firmware
the one you download to get your little 3D video
from OKGO
so that's kind of cool
at least that's been fixed
however something that's not really gonna be able to be fixed
some sort of patching system
is the fact that the hinges once again
are loose or at least some people are
reporting loose hinges which require
you to actually send your system back in to get it repaired
what a slut that 3DS
must be, totally loose I heard
I haven't had that problem with the loose hinge
yet, but I know it was something that
plagued a lot of systems before
especially on the DS Lite
kind of sucks
but thankfully
not a problem for me
well hopefully they'll fix a lot of these
hardware problems in the 3DS Lite
which will come out next year inevitably
or the 3DS XL
or the 3DS I
or the 3DS bigger peen
whatever they're gonna call it that comes out next year
yeah, so
you can bet on that, and then colors of course
there'll be colors
alright, moving on
lawsuit!
somebody is suing EA
there might be some weight to this one though
if you're in law suits or somebody mad about something a little frivolous
this could have some actual weight to it
you know the game John Madden
Football? Well you ought to because
this is the series that became Madden
NFL like what, oh
7, oh 8, oh 9, 11, 10
an annual sequel for like 20 years or something
yeah, every year there's a damn Madden game
well it started as a game called John Madden Football
and it was originally what?
it was on the Commodore 64
the Apple II, it was on DOS systems
all the way back in 1988
it was the first John Madden Football
and you can kind of tell because like in this little like
horrible pixelated screenshot
that was the extent of the Commodore 64 graphics
back in the day, like look how pixelated he is
and also his hair is not totally
grey, I mean clearly that's toupee
but it's not like totally freaking grey
so you know this is a long
old game, well my point with
this here is that Robin
Antonick who created the very
first game, and you see his name there in the programming
there, in Madden
apparently
23 years after this very first game
he is not seeing
any revenue from it
now he has filed suit against
Electronic Arts for tens of millions in royalties
and apparently
he was responsible for the development of
virtually all the groundbreaking technology
at the heart of the game, that's at least
what he claims in his suit
EA has not paid this guy
any royalties since
was the last time he got royalties
interesting, I mean
he did make the original game, it was
kinda his baby, I mean I'm
sure the game has changed many times since
then, something you may not know, John
Madden football did not have actual NFL
teams, they didn't have the NFL license at the time
EA got that years later
so you know you could say
the game's changed a whole fuck ton since
the beginning, so maybe this guy doesn't deserve
anything, well yeah I mean it's
John Madden's namesake
that's the brand, you know
the actual announcer guy
but this person
Robin
sounds like he might have signed a bad contract
when they took the license from
him where he was paid up front for the
concept
of what it is, but I'd have to read more
about what the actual
the complaint that was filed in court
I would need to read that to know
how reasonable this is
yeah, but
it's gonna be interesting, I mean especially
with such a huge franchise to see
kinda what happens with this, but you know
a lot of times, especially back in the day
I mean back in the 80's, you know this was
always a huge thing where programmers
really weren't getting the credit they deserved
I mean that was why Activision was kinda
formed in the first place, it was a bunch of
people really upset that programmers didn't
get more credit in Atari games
the very first Easter egg
in a video game was where
the dude's initials were in Adventure
that was so that the guy could kinda sneak
his credit in there, because Atari never
credited their programmers and game designers
but Activision, remember the names like
David Crane and so forth, these guys would make the games
and get to put their names on them, because a lot of
these Atari games were by like one guy
or two guys
and they're cool guys
ET, worst Atari 2600
game of all time, according to some people
was done by a guy called Howard Scott Warshaw
you know why else he's famous?
He also made Yara's Revenge, made one of the best games
he's one of the worst games, go figure
you should read about how he was
under all that pressure to make ET, it really makes
a lot of sense as to why that game didn't come out so well
Pac-Man was
one guy too that wanted
to put it on a bigger cartridge, but Atari wouldn't let him
because it would cost too much, that's why it sucked
so
that's so bad, it's like the worst port ever
but it's so funny because you play the old school
Pac-Man on the 2600 and it really
is garbage, but then they had a Miss Pac-Man
later, it was great
for an Atari game, it was great
well the reason why is because the
Miss Pac-Man was on like a 4K cart
whereas the Pac-Man was on like half that
maybe a quarter of that, I don't know
so like, the whole drawing one
ghost every frame, why the ghost
flickered so terribly, that was a restriction
of the cartridge, I mean think about it
those programmers had 2K
to design an entire
game, 2K
is how long an SA is, you know, it's
crazy
anyhow
boy, we
should get into classic gaming discussion a lot on this
show, it's pretty good, alright, it's cause we love it
we do, uh, and we're old
um, Dark
Sakura, Wii, what do you mean
Wii, I'm sorry, especially Dark
Sakura, hey, don't make me break
out the vuvuzela
how about I break out another new story
well, Monolith
Soft's putting out the Wii
RPG Xenoblade, and it's being
localized, for
Europe, yay
um,
it's actually going up for
Xenoblade Chronicles, that
um, although the trailer itself is
untranslated
it shows basically all of the imagery
going out, um, Nintendo
of Europe put out a press release
and then removed it
um, but somebody
actually managed to get it out and get the information
out, and it's supposed to, uh, have
English and Japanese voice action
uh, voice, uh, options
so
maybe we'll get it
here too? I'm assuming if they're gonna
spend the time to translate into English that they're
gonna release it in not
more than one region, I mean, they gotta
what if there's like an elevator in the game
and they call it a lift? Americans
might not understand, oh my god, where will they
find that one employee to type
elevator?
Woo, that was a day's work, there
what if somebody in the
game, maybe there's a smoking scene and the guy
says he's gonna go out and have a fag
and that could never go over here in the
US, because like, you know, Glatt will sue
once again, you know, that same employee
on day two could easily type
cigarette
this looks pretty good though, or maybe they're gonna
go out and have a crumpet and people will be like
they don't know what the fuck that is over in the United
States, pants versus trousers, people
will just burst into tears, exactly
my favorite one is the word fanny
it's not just a pack anymore
no, fanny
here is your butt, there, the vag
oh my, is that why
a fanny pack is really in the front?
a friend of mine explained that
to me, of course, well, you know why I always
giggle when I pass the catering place, because
it's called Randy Peters?
because Randy is like horny
oh, I get it, oh
you're a nerd, alright
I wanna get to
some old comments from our chat room, it was on
the last story, but my bad, we
didn't get around to this here
let's see, GameGuru
in response to the whole Madden lawsuit
thing said, all EA has to do is prove
that his code was not used after 1992
or that the contract
with them was only valid until 1992
Spazernator
says, yet Activision no longer gives
credits and manuals anymore, oh the irony
and DarkToaGak follows that up
with what the fuck is a game manual
I thought they did have
credits and game manuals, they're just like all the way in the back
they do, and then EA
EA doesn't have manuals anymore
from what I remember, really, they're all
digital, it's all online now, digital manuals
it's all on the disc, I think you just have to make
the information available
this game looks super pretty by the way
oh, the Xenoblade, yeah, yeah it looks
pretty cool, it doesn't look like a Wii game
that's for sure, alright
just a couple more stories before we get to the mailbag
mailbag.orangelaungeradio.com is where
we invite you guys to email us every week
we talked a little bit about how there was a
PlayStation 1 emulator for Android
and how, you know, that may
interfere with the PlayStation phone
since, you know, anybody could just download ROMs
and play them on there
yeah, except that, you know, Sony decided
hey, you know what, we got this PlayStation
phone coming out, so
ahhhh, let's get it removed
so PSX4Droid
was removed from the Android marketplace
without warning due to
a content policy violation
um, he's
I guess, are, you know, saying
what the hell, he's expecting, he
figured it was from the, you know,
Xperia Play coming out, but also
that it's a little weird seeing as
there's other, um
another emulator already
on there, FPSC
that's still on the marketplace
so he's like, what the hell
um, and he couldn't be more right
that that was pretty much the reason
why they removed it, because the day after
it was removed, PlayStation 1
games started appearing on the Android marketplace
and of course, they were limited to the
Xperia Play
and the initial offerings, of course, were
Cool Borders 2, Destruction
Derby, Jumping Flash
Medieval 2, and Siphon Filter
and, uh,
all those are available for
$6 or $3.99
and, uh, I guess it's the same
price that they're going on the
PlayStation ork right now
um,
it is kind of, uh, funny that I
guess they're saying that, um
I don't
know, I would think
I thought the marketplace for Android was
open, I mean, if you can't get your app
on the Android marketplace, I mean, there's other
marketplaces out there where you can
I don't know
upload it somewhere else and someone can download it from
that website, am I correct, I think?
Because I know they have the Amazon marketplace
now, and obviously that's not on the Android
marketplace
I don't know, iPhone's
all different. They're all, oh yeah, everyone in here
is an iPhone already. Yeah, I know, so sorry
don't mean to be ignorant, but it's how it is
Well, I mean, that sucks
I guess, but, you know, it makes sense because
obviously, you know, if there's a free PlayStation
or even a PlayStation emulator
that you can buy and then download the ROMs
for, that would kind of defeat
the point of having to buy
you know, all
these different games
and, you know, if it is anything
like a normal Android phone
people really want to, since it is
legal to jailbreak your phone
you could jailbreak or root your phone
and download this anyways
and... But really, why play a PlayStation
game on your phone?
Well, why buy a phone that's meant
for playing PlayStation games
if you're not going to play PlayStation games
better yet, why buy a phone
to play PlayStation games? I'm not sure
I don't know, I guess it's really not that different
than the PSP when all is said and done, but I don't know
I know, but... I guess that
when I think playing games on my phone
I think that the horrible
horrible touchscreen
controls on the iPod
iPhone, that only very few
games get right, like, I hate
the whole, like, static button
like, trying to put a layer of button thing
on the screen, expect that to work, because it doesn't
like, games like Mega Man 2 and stuff are just fucking
terrible, you know, and I think of like
how the fuck are you supposed to play a PlayStation game
with that type of setup, but then I forget
oh yeah, these Xperia plays and stuff, they actually have buttons
they're meant, they're like PSPs
but they actually work as phones, so that makes a lot more
sense to me. But
I don't know, I mean, it's not like this thing
plays PSP games
it plays PlayStation 1 games, I mean
really, who's really... Your PSP
will play PlayStation 1 games too. Exactly, I mean
if you really want something to play
PlayStation 1 games on, seriously
go find a generation 1
PSP, oh my god
that would probably be pretty dirt cheap
or go to a
farmer's market
auction thing that has the, you know
I'm thinking like, Denio is here locally, but
PlayStation's everywhere
there are PSPs everywhere, and if you
really... Even the actual PlayStation 1s
I wouldn't, yeah
yeah, PlayStation 1s, but I mean
on the go, I mean PlayStation 1's not very
you know, portable
I mean, you could technically do it
with a battery pack and stuff, but it's
I seem to remember some little screen
they have the screen, no, they do have
the screen, and they're used for hacking
stuff quite a bit, they're definitely
used for portable consoles
more than the actual, you know
PlayStation 1, but I mean seriously
you just buy a PSP and just play your
PlayStation 1 games on there if you really want to do it
and that way you don't get locked into a contract and you don't
need to buy this expensive phone for it
but I mean, people like gaming on the
phone, and here's my
thing, it's like, you know, it's good
that they have these buttons, but are all
the developers really using it? No, they
are not, so, you know, don't expect
to buy this and go all of a sudden, oh hey, now I can
play Mega Man 2 or something like that
really easily
using the buttons, because you're
not going to be able to
I don't know, it's
whatever, I mean
if you want to do this, this is something for you
just, you know, know it's out there now
Misty in our chatroom says, speaking of
iPhones, someone needs to get theirs away from a mic
Jamie
I'm dealing something with Dan
oh, well still, it's
I moved it, look, it's over here
and you know, whenever
anybody hears that doo doo doo tone
like everybody looks at their, any iPhone owner
whenever that, there's some commercial on the radio
that uses that tone and it's terrible
I don't do that because my volume on my
iPod is turned off, and also
my iPod is turned off
like a normal person would
iPhone people
crazy
well, maybe my mommy needs to contact me
in an emergency
my husband's two states away, so
I'm trying to keep in touch with him
no, I understand that, that's no problem, but I'm just saying, you know
yeah, I don't know what you're saying, alright
alright, let's move on to another story about
Ultima, I mentioned earlier in the show
Ultima Online randomly got brought up
well, there are some rumors going around
that Ultima could quite possibly be coming back
but I don't know, this is stretching a little bit guys
here's the deal, Ultima 4
has been available online
through these various websites
Abandonware or Flash
emulators and so forth, GOG maybe
yeah, well no, not even GOG, I'm talking like
illegal means to play
Ultima 4, but you know how like a lot of that
Abandonware, the whole theory behind it is
well, after so many, even though it's like total
BS, after so many years you lose the right
no, companies don't ever lose the rights to them
it's just that they just bank on
people are going to stop caring after
7 or 8 years or whatever the Abandonware sites say
well, I guess these sites were hosting
Ultima 4, and sites have been
giving away that game
since like the late 90's
this game dates all the way back to 1985
there was a version of it on the NES
and that was one of the later releases
Ultima 4 is an old ass game
well, apparently what happened
is that some of these sites that were hosting the game
EA had them take
down, there was like some
cease and desist that went out there
now, some people are thinking
it's tied into this whole
thing that Paul Barnett
who is a creative director
at BioWare and Mythic, he's a very
RPG centered guy, he's been talking about a
secret project which includes
an all new MMO from EA
so could it be that
EA is trying to protect this old IP
all of a sudden because
they're about to announce a new Ultima MMO
at E3, who knows
so of course
as brought up earlier in the show, Ultima Online
has been out since 1997
so it is a 14 year old game
so maybe it's going to get an update
and that could also explain this whole loyalty program thing
coming out of the blue it seems like
maybe like a last hurrah for Ultima Online
before they're about to announce something big
at E3, who knows
and the last time that we heard something
about this happening
was the Sarian games
that had all the Space Quest and King's Quest
for Sierra Online available to play
and then the
the fandom game
I'm blanking on the name
Silver Lining, they got a C&D
and we thought oh it's just you know
Activision being horrible
but no the Telltale
Telltale got the King's Quest
revamp license
and it's like oh well maybe they weren't just being
total assholes, there's actually a relevant reason
for them to do those C&Ds
because that happened just one or two months ago
that gives me reason to believe
this Ultima story can hold water
very good point
well we'll see what happens, I think E3 will be very telling
this could be one of the big things they announce
would there be interest in Ultima?
Ultima was, that was a big Richard Garriott thing too
remember that was like his baby
I didn't actually own my own gaming PC
or a PC period until like
95, 96
so all the Ultima stuff that came before
I personally missed out on all of the Ultima stuff
during the 80s
see I owned 3 and 4 on the NES
I owned both of them on the NES
and they were great games
well they were really hardcore
they were not like Final Fantasy
they were pretty in depth
I think 3 had an amazing soundtrack too
weren't they off a model of Dungeons and Dragons?
Ultima Exodus
was 3
yeah because I tried playing that one
I had it on Ness
like the Cleric or the Druid
there was like a million classes in it
yeah that was Ultima and then there was Ultima Quest of the Avatar
which was a little more
but see those games are really not like their PC counterparts
they were really
I don't want to say dumbed down but they were really changed
for the NES
mine ended up under a lawn mower
not my fault
poor game
I found it in my front yard after
trying to find it and it was under a lawn mower
there was Ultima 5
on the NES as well
and I think Ultima 7 I played on the PC
that was Pagan right?
there was one big one that
7, 8 or 9 I don't know had a lot of hype
to it
well they all had some hype to them
but now Richard Garriott is long gone
he's not dead or anything
but he went off and did Tabula Rasa
which tanked unfortunately for him
that was the whole space MMO
it was not free
it was an NCSoft pay game
I played it once
it was alright but it was more like a shooter type game
and yeah that didn't go over so well
well maybe after that whole debacle
failed maybe he's coming back and doing this
who knows?
could be a variety of things
alright let's get to the mailbag
every week we invite your emails at
mailbag.orangelaungeradio.com
and our soccer is going to dive into the email bag head first
and pull out a couple emails that she thinks are worth
sharing with us tonight
I found some sticky ones
first email
last week you mentioned Sony changing over divisions
for their network services
I oddly got an email regarding this change
but the contents of the email smelled of a phishing scam
the sender appears to be from
playstation underscore network
at playstation dot
enovix dot net
I haven't followed the links in the email
which simply mentions the change
the need to enter into new terms of service
and the link where my Sony online services settings
can be updated
the change has been confirmed as being legitimate
am I simply being paranoid about this email
Robert M
no I think you have a right to question those types of emails
exactly and also I don't think
that they are actually having you agree to those terms
of services through
through that I got an email
I think I just ignored it
because I did get an email but the
minute I went back into the PS3 I played PS3
just a couple days ago I think after the first
because this is when we were playing Mortal Combat
it was Friday right? and it made me
accept the terms of service when I signed in
so that will all happen through your
playstation so don't do anything with
email I was watching Supernatural on
Friday night and it didn't have
me do anything
maybe you weren't connecting
to the interwebs idk
might be
ok next email
note
the following letter has been mirrored posted to the
Sims 3 online forums
and this is also titled by the way
empirical response to the Dragon Age 2 protest letter
dear sirs
in the past week I've been playing a lot of the game
The Sims 3 on my iPad
I like most of the game however there is one element of the game
that absolutely offends me
in the game you can make different meals for yourself
and whoever you happen to be living with
at the point in the game
among the meal options you can choose from
is vegetable soup
this option deeply offends me
as an ardent carnivore I eat meat with every meal
every! I eat meat with breakfast
meat with lunch, meat with afternoon snack, meat with dinner
meat with my late night snack
I eat meat like it's going out of style which after
going to my local whole foods it just might be
the option of eating vegetable soup
offends me as I feel meat should be not
only an option of what to eat at meals
it should be THE option
now why should you listen to me? what does my opinion matter?
my opinion matters because as a ginger
mere asthmatic pudgy impotent male
I represent the majority of gamers
and if I don't fuck it my opinion
is sacrosanct and my mommy
says I'm special
I make this promise, if The Sims 3 is not updated
to take the portion of eating vegetable soup
out of the game I will post an online petition
that will surely be signed by many of the gamers
who identify and agree with me
online petitions are no joke, think of all the things
that have changed because of online petitions
think of it, you're truly redertainment
satire over
this message has been brought to you by the tachymeter
that collection of numbers
on the outside of your
tachometer
that you have no idea what the fuck it's there for
tachymeter is on your car
to show you your rpms, right?
so
yeah, I thought the parody though
was pretty funny, I mean it's
pretty right on
I lulled
so what's the name of the guy from Bioware that did that old
the David
David something
Spader?
no, that's an actor
yeah, he's an actor
there's an online petition
to get him fired because
I guess the same
sex options the NPCs in Dragon
Age 2, whether it be the female
what's her name, the Meryl?
yeah, well the
elf girl Meryl, yeah
and then also the male equivalent which I guess are the easier
options to hit on if you want to do
well I guess the person that put up this
petition is like, oh well this is just
stereotyping
gay and lesbian men and women as
aggressive sex
fiends but I think Meryl
will hit on you no matter what gender you
are okay, but just
and so will, I think
is Varick the dwarf
guy? yeah, I think they're just
set to be attracted to
the main person yeah
but I just thought it was funny that
he had put out that response to that
one idiot guy who wrote in
but there's also just a petition to get him
fired because I guess the gay and lesbian characters are
horny that's butt-tarded
if anyone's horny
it's Isabella I found it
here's the petition, it's on petition
spot.com please don't visit it
it says fire David Gator for
stereotyping gays
at me when I never found any interest
or even flirted with him this sort of thing shows
that gays are unable to be normal people
think nothing about sex
this is the type of garbage that has people
believe gays shouldn't serve in the military
we are human beings that
are the same as everyone else please sign
this petition if you wish that Dragon Age
senior writer David Gator should be fired
and this is by the user
Oakland how about fuck you
because get this if
say we have, I'm just gonna use
Meryl for example and she's
hitting on my female rogue
but in the male scenario she hits on
the male rogue too and you
reject her is that going to make her like
you anymore is it gonna make her a little bit upset with you
it doesn't matter
gender she's still hitting on whoever
alright
so we would like to give a big hearty
OLR fuck you
to the following people who have signed this petition
and posted their names publicly
on the internet for us all to see
after all it was your choice to sign this in a public forum
so we'd like to give a
good hearty fuck you
to Ryan Cukor
John Holmes
Ryan Guerrero
John Jamerson
William Wallace
Matt Gephart
yeah I think some of these are fake
Keegan Murasaki
Joshua Daniel
Bear Wagner
Alexander Rich
Lando Vides
Sally Minamoto
Dylan Carey
some of these are funny
Jordan Coward
Daniel Young
I'm trying to read the people that have pictures
Jonathan Price
Bobby Bowden
let's give a couple more
fuck yous here
courtesy of Orange Lounge Radio to the following users
positions at spot.com
Jose Carlton
Thomas
Anton Sinia
Aidan Woodruff
and let's do
one section here
folks to give fuck yous to
Benjamin Lee
Alex Diaz
Nikita Belkopiatov
Harvey Vdarsky
and
Luca Patterson
a hearty fuck you from Orange Lounge Radio
I just
I don't know I brought that up to say that that
Sims parody letter is awesome and that you can't
please everybody
or someone will always
have a problem with what you're doing
this is people looking for drama where there is none
it's like what is so boring
in your life that you have to make drama to be upset
about seriously
the world is not about you
my favorite though is that there are totally people
trolling that particular like half of the signatures
well there was one that I wanted you to read but it was obviously
a troll one it was like some gay dude
that wants to get
boned every day or something it was I don't know
funny
there you go alright ready for the next
yes
hello olr first off I want to let you know that I'm typing
this on my iphone so if there are any weird
words it's probably autocorrect
ok
a while ago I emailed asking
if either the olr crew or
anyone in the chat room knew of any video game
characters who wear knitted clothing like
riku scarf in final fantasy 10 2
or nora estheim's
sweater in final fantasy 13
I'm still looking for suggestions
but I found another character
final fantasy 3's lunath some purple sweater
under his jacket that's true
sky requested that I send some
pics of past projects I've included some of
my past works the gray afghan I'm working
on now and that green scarf
also doubled as a shawl for this
petite model I'm looking forward
for suggestions on video
game characters knitted attire so let me know you should
totally knit me stuff
can you knit a mobius scarf?
cause I totally want one anyway
on a completely random note the other night I had
a really screwed up dream where the three olr
hosts were included oh I don't know
I'm afraid for some reason we were
in some everglades slash marsh looking
place and me and dark sakura
were in one dune buggy and loki and sky were
in another following us a building
to our left exploded like a balloon filled with
water as we drove by it for some
reason they veered off the path and were following
a higher path that swerved in and out of the main
that we were on
there was a small ditch in the path
and we fell a little and hit a curb
and achieved some air time like we were in
some dukes of hazard chase
all four of us eventually reached our path
which was my parents home
which was bizarre cause they were white and I'm filipino
we started
getting chewed up by mosquitoes which
woke I guess which means
I woke up all itchy for some reason
yeah I know totally random thanks
for humoring me stan
don't eat
before you go to bed
they make you dream
weird shit or don't take night
don't sleep with night quilt
tonight on the
orange lounge radio knitting and crocheting
video game show we're gonna
talk about how to knit
a nice little scarf no I think this stuff is
kinda neat actually
we're there taking this
one step further into the
whole you know
making tangible
goods from video game inspired
stuff and I know dark soccer you're really into
this I'm surprised there aren't more people
that kinda like crochet the whole like
8 bit patterns using the
old sprite graphics to like
make those what are those things the
needle point or whatever this is gonna be a
beret yeah but I'm
talking about like can't you like stitch a
like sprite into those
um you theoretically
could on a crocheted item you just need
the grid but um Becky does
um needle point
and then there's cross stitch
I think in a recent issue
of the official World of Warcraft
magazine they feature a fan
who does handmade plushies
that are very intricate and exquisitely
done she's not allowed to sell
them but because they're so good
they gave her a pictorial in the
magazine so she makes like moonkin plushies
and oh cute she cuts out the
fabric and does it all I want a walrus
person whatever they're called
kolok or whatever
these should be playable
you never know alright
and oh let's see the pictures
oh I closed it hold on
hold on
by the way a quick follow up Tiger Claw linked
us to this in our chat room uh gaygamer.net
actually started a support
David Gator petition which is
available also on petitionspot.com
and whereas the
anti had about 400 signatures
this one is up to
1700 no 16
1642 signatures
check this out there you go
there's one picture
oh wow very intricate
yeah very intricate I can't
knit for shit but I can shirk okay hey you rhymed
oh
sheep
that's so cute
oh
it has little numbers on the sheep that's cute
they're counting sheep I get it
and it is just so fantastic
radio that was amazing radio
let's look at some pictures together guys
and there's a scarf
and a pretty lady wearing it
my chair has decided
that it doesn't want to stay up anymore
oh this is like his model
yeah look at that
and
she kind of looks like she's been crying though don't be sad
this red eye is from the camera Rob
from back here it looks like
she's been crying don't be crying
it needs color correction
photoshop please
alright let's move on
oh here's the last one
that's actually cool kind of like a houndstooth
alright last email
dun dun dun
hi OLR seeing as the mailbag
has been rather light as of late I thought I'd send
an email for the upcoming show
I just wanted to touch on a few subjects but I'll try to
keep this email from going on too long
you failed
wall of words from back here
wall of words
wall of words crits you for 9,000 hit points
hush hush hush
first off
as of the time I typed this on Thursday afternoon
there's no notable free videos on the
PSN video store
if something were to be added between now and when
the OLR airs
or the OLR now
I'll mention it either in chat or via Twitter topics
although there's nothing good
that's free so far I should mention
that the PSN video store does have
a petty decent
I'm sure you meant pretty decent
sale going on for the outright
purchase of
SD versions of miscellaneous comedy
movies such as Airplane, Disaster Movie
Joe Dirt, RV, Team America
several MST3K titles, etc.
as well as three stand-up
comedy specials and select seasons of Super
Jail, Aqua Teen Hunger Force
and the anime series called
Durarara the Complete Series
excuse you
the movies and stand-up specials are normally
$10 while the other stuff is normally
$2 but during the sale they're half
off
touch you
on the subject of video stores I've noticed that the
XBL-Zune video marketplace has been updated
to include a new tab specifically
for free TV shows, sneak previews, etc.
this should be very helpful
that stuff has been gooped
grouped together
in one place
rather than having to hunt around
for it at all
lastly I want to
touch on the PS3 version of Free Realms
which has been released via PSN this past
Tuesday although I haven't put enough time
into it to give a full fair review
of it I'd at least would like to give my
early impressions of it which are mixed
frankly there's a few couple
a few a couple things hurting it
was it a few or a couple?
the game seriously needs a manual be it
a PDF printed one or
in-game which isn't included
some things are easy to figure out while others are
bigger pain in the ass than an appointment with
one's proctologist
while the game is a
freemium title and trophies are supported
you must have a subscription to unlock any trophies
Sony kinda neglected to mention
that early on and the only time they really
said anything was in response to a question
in the comment section to a
post on the Playstation blog
in terms of the
game's overall appearance it can
best be described as if Mr. Rogers
had made a stew out of Barney the
Teletubbies most Nickelodeon cartoons and the Power Rangers
ate said stew then vomited
all over a unicorn a bunny
infested World of Warcraft
whether this is a positive or negative
is purely subjective and impersonal preference
this email has been brought to you
by Nyquil capital N small y big
fucking Q Nyquil Nyquil Nyquil
we love you you giant fucking Q
see Dark Sakura I can quote
Dennis Leary too
that's it
well
I guess somebody kind of agrees with me on
free realms
that it's a horrible
piece of crap game that makes
no sense that you have no
idea what to do not that there's anything wrong with that
no I'm kidding I call it the
sphincter of MMOs it's not the worst game
I've ever played but it's just not good
the sphincter of MMOs it's not
the crap that comes out I don't know if it's the sphincter
but it's definitely like the upper
intestine
well my reason for saying the sphincter
is because it's not the crap
it's just where the crap comes from
okay you win
let's get angsty
do some angry rawr
FUs of the week
my FU goes towards the
repaving of the sidewalk
the street outside of my house
because they're closing the street tomorrow
and Tuesday from
I wanna say 7 in the morning
until 5 in the afternoon
and
I really shouldn't have to leave my house
until like 9 to get to school
because I'm making up time at school
and instead I have to
park my house a block away at
my friend's house so that I could
walk to my car in the morning and then go to school
which is not that far I'm not complaining about walking
but I complain about
walking that I shouldn't have to do
they should do this like
at night
with sound mufflers around them
or they should give us money to be in communities
but I guess we're getting any road out of this whatever
money rocks
Loki!
um
I don't know there's not a whole lot that I'm really mad about
just I guess FU to lack of sleep
because I haven't been getting a lot of sleep
I have to wake up way early in the morning
and
you know one or two days isn't bad
I've been doing it for 8 months straight now
uh
it takes a toll on you it makes you go a little crazy
oh you were already
crazy Loki
I know and just compounded on top of that
um
I don't know I think it's been pretty good for me
I don't really have a lot to say FU to do
so yes FU to ants
oh little bastards
I hate them that's a good one thank you
how about you?
even if it's for really good reasons
like a new job
or you know
just a new beginning or whatever
the process of moving
as an adult is one of the most
annoying bullshitty things a grown
person can do to themselves
you've got to change your address
get the stupid postal
card pack up everything you own
get friends to help you move
even if
it's awesome and nothing goes wrong
moving is bullshit
there you go
moving is hard
it's for grown ups
no it stinks I don't like it
anyhow that's it for the FUs of the week
let's move on to a couple more stories
and then your calls at 1877
game OLR
as if we didn't need more
reasons to believe that there's gonna be
a new Grand Theft Auto announced at E3
uh
well there's been a casting call for
people to
do some character
voice over work and one of those
characters happens to be from the Grand Theft Auto
universe including
the guy's name is James
Pettison
and he was a
guess aside character
at least in San Andreas
where he openly
recounted acts of pedophilia
and in Grand Theft Auto 4
he was arrested by the Indonesian police
after being suspected of child molestation
in Bali
so
yeah now apparently
he's coming back in the next game and
someone's gonna be doing the voice for him
some other characters they name
as well they're pretty generic sounding
Samantha a young female
obsessed with sex parties always dreaming
of being a Hollywood celebrity
um
also let's see here
uh
what else there were some other characters
I thought they were talking about too as well
um a lot of like weird stuff
um
but yeah so probably
new game coming out I would not be surprised
next year so
exciting I love it
and the rumor is
that it's supposed to be going back to Los Santos which
was from San Andreas probably
one of the best Grand Theft Auto games ever
so I think a new
Grand Theft Auto game is kind of a given so
San Andreas was an analog
of LA in that game
Los Santos was
Las Vegas or no? No, Los Santos
was part of San Andreas remember cause there's three
cities in San Andreas it was
Los Santos, San Friere
and Las Venturas
Las Vegas
yeah Vegas, San Francisco
and Los Angeles
yeah
but that game was massive
I have to really go back and play it
get back from my sister
why not wait for the next one?
if you have a gaming PC get it on
Steam for like five bucks and it's a lot better
I have it on PC the last
PC I tried running it on was my old laptop
and that thing is a piece of shit I could probably run it on this
really well
but you know I've got it on
I've got the old
hot coffee disc
from the Playstation 2
my sister's been borrowing it forever
and you know even though she doesn't need to
cause there's a rip on the hard drive of that Playstation 2
she has
so I just need to get back and play it on my
generation 1 Playstation 3 full backwards compatibility
oh yeah
alright
well one more story for you guys before we get to the phone calls
and this is about a man named Phil Fish
and you might not know that game
or you might not know that name but he is making the game
Fez it's an indie game
and it's going to be coming out on Xbox Live Arcade
possibly the PC and the Playstation 3
but probably not the Wii
in an interview with
Destructoid he was quoted saying
quote right now we're only concentrating
on XBLA which makes the most sense
for us at the time
PC and Playstation Network would also make a lot of sense
but in my opinion WiiWare just wouldn't be worth
our time and effort
it's a dismal system that I don't want to deal with
neither as a customer nor a developer
no demos? Fuck off
and that's a quote from this guy
who told the WiiWare system it can go fuck off
now granted this guy
I don't want to say he's a nobody
but his game hasn't really been proven yet
he's one of those garage developers
that Nintendo kind of doesn't want in their house anyway
so I don't know
if this story carries a lot of weight
but I mean the guy did kind of have
the balls to call out Nintendo
but I kind of think it's not going to
really change a goddamn thing in the scope of things
but he really does have a point
why do people keep developing for WiiWare when it's kind of shit?
exactly
and as I posted on Twitter
earlier this week
remember Nintendo was commenting
on how they wanted to make sure
they kept the garage developers out
because in order to make sure
that there's quality products coming out
on WiiWare and DSiWare
and stuff like that
guess what came out on DSiWare this week?
it was a program to take pictures of your friends
and put them in funny Halloween themed
backgrounds
it looked like shit
it looked like something that was on the iOS platform
yay, clip art
Halloween themed?
I'm sorry, monster themed stuff
I'm sorry, the best one on the iPhone
was that heroin
yeah, that was funny
the make your friends fat application
is funny too
it was absolutely terrible
and perfect week to come out
right after they said
oh, we need to make sure quality is on there
that's some quality shit right there
you're so much better
than the iOS platform, what was I thinking
even, you know, contemplating that you would
ever allow something that terrible to be on
your network
oh, Nintendo, you don't need these garage
developers at all, you got your Mario games
that you're rehashing and putting out
whatever, that's fine, they're better off
you know, not going to the WiiWare service
but seriously, I mean, come on
demos, I mean, demos have been around
for fucking years now, and you can't
implement demos on your WiiWare service
or you just don't want to because a lot of this shit
is crap on there, and
it's just terrible games
oh, haha, you downloaded it too late
hahaha, Nintendo just kinda doesn't get
online, I think it's the same story
every week, ok, they don't get online
and they don't have any demos
for Wii games, they don't have any
demos for any, I mean they had
demos one time for a select few
WiiWare games, so it is possible
they, eh, fuck it, we don't give a shit
our customers don't need demos
our quality speaks for itself
it should be a no brainer, I must buy everything
Nintendo
the developers of
Super Meat Boy, which I think is
one of the most successful indie games since
Braid really, the
two studios that were most willing to work with them
was XBLA and Steam
Sony wasn't really interested in the
game, and when they wanted to put out a
WiiWare edition of Super Meat Boy
they were fine with the no demo thing, but just the
restrictions they had to put on the game
really crippled it, they just cancelled the whole thing
because the WiiWare platform and how
big the game has to be was
shitty. I mean, this is a company
that thinks that users
can't understand megabytes, they
have to, you know, put it
down to blocks, yeah, really, how is
you know, five megabytes and
five blocks any fucking different, I mean
other than being really confusing
to the fact that how many, you know
When you have 64 and you take
away two, you're left with
62. Yeah, but then you have to figure
out, okay, I have a two gigabyte memory card
that's in my, you know, 3DS
or in my Wii system, how many
fucking blocks is that?
I don't know.
No one knows. Is the 3DS still speaking
blocks? Yes it does. Oh god.
Yes, it
does, and because
I mean, come on, man, everybody's
using computers nowadays, everybody
megabyte, the term megabyte's been
around forever.
Even if they don't, they have an 8 gig
iPod, they know what 8 gig means,
you know, the terminology
is everywhere now. And even
still though, why is it so hard to, you
know, megabyte? Okay,
well, I don't know what a megabyte
is, but I know that I have this many
on this memory card.
How's that difficult?
It's not, it really isn't, but
for whatever reason, they decided, let's
go ahead and do that again.
It's just like they make a lot of poor
decisions when it comes to different
software and features that they have on
these systems. Whatever, you know what,
Nintendo, you can play this game as long
as you want, and your system will be
successful for a while, and eventually
you're gonna hit that slump again.
You're gonna hit that slump again, and
then you're gonna be in fucking last
place, and oh, all that shit, now you
gotta catch up again. So
ride the wave while you can, but
eventually it's gonna come crashing down.
Alright, well, let's
get to the Skype line. We're gonna open that
on up, 1-877-GAME-OLR,
or our username on Skype is
OrangeLoungeRadio. Give us a call,
and we'll talk topics with you, if there's something
you wanna cover that we've talked about earlier tonight, or
maybe you wanna talk to us about something completely
new. While we wait for some calls,
cause there is a bit of a delay, Loki, do you have any
last minute stories for us tonight? Yeah, I do have one
thing. Sony is looking to dismiss
the other OS lawsuit. Remember,
there was people suing Sony
for removing the other OS
in the Playstation 3. I thought they dismissed that a long time ago.
Well, no they didn't. It was actually going to courts and stuff.
But here's the twist now. Sony wants
access to all those people's hard
drives that filed for the other
OS lawsuits, because they're saying
they may be part of a bigger hacker
conspiracy. Thank you! So basically
they're saying everybody that wanted Linux
on their system, they're a hacker, and they're out to
destroy Sony. Wasn't the government
using it? Oh yeah, but they're hackers, and they're out
to destroy Sony. Why put that in
your system if you think that everybody's
hackers out to destroy Sony?
If Sony made the goddamn
system, why don't they just make some
program that lets them see what's in the system?
I'm sure they could do that remotely, like a whole
Skynet thing, right? It's just terrible, but here's the thing,
I mean, well, if you think about it though,
if they made some sort of program and they had it
where you connected online to see that kind of stuff,
that would update their system, and they
would be unable to have the other OS
in there, cause you can't update your system
anymore if you want to keep that.
But, the real,
well, one reason they wanted to see the hard drives
is to make sure that they actually did have other OS on,
and this is their Playstation 3 hard drives,
not their PCs. They wanted to make sure
they had other OS on there, but
at the same time though, and the judge doesn't understand,
is when you put other OS on there,
it's now a computer, and
you need to go through the protocols
for, you know, discovery for that kind of
stuff where you have to have a third party company, look
at the stuff, not Sony, going through
and having full access to your
hard drive of your now computer.
Alright, let's go to the phones. Hi, you're on Orange
Launch Radio, who's this? Hey, it's Ronma,
what's up everyone? Your
audio, I have to hang up.
There's some terrible, terrible feedback that you've got
going on, and he's probably sitting there going
why did he hang up on us? But you've got some,
I know you all heard that, right?
Yeah, ow. So,
you gotta fix that. Echo 123, buddy.
He works every other week, I wonder what's wrong with
tonight, let's see. Alright, let's try to go.
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
Sledge and Zaku here. Hey Zaku, what's up, buddy?
Nothing much, just
trying to recover for, you know, for a
sleepy Sunday night watching, you know, listening
to your show. But yeah,
just going on the debate of how Nintendo's
basically, like, you know, they're
basically like, they're basically
regressive at this point. I mean,
they're pissing off devs to, you know,
and it goes back to how
too much pride they have, like,
remember how they, like,
covertly, you know,
dissed, you know, the developers
of Angry Birds? Yes, I remember that.
The CEO actually, like,
he actually, you know, he didn't mention
it in a name, but he actually mentioned them
in, you know, within that same
aspect that they're just, like, bringing down
the wages. Kind of like,
you know, it's kind of like those, uh, you ever
seen this episode of South Park where
the, you know, the Goobacks episode
and you see the guy shouting, they took our
job. They took our jobs! It's
pretty much like that. They're complaining about
how, just because it's a
zero-sum game, well,
to them it appears to be a zero-sum game,
that it's just, like,
it's not worth, it doesn't pay to be a
developer anymore. But on the other
hand,
Rovio, what their
strategy is, as long as they get Angry Birds
for a cheap price with a lot more
replay value, then
they've done their job in terms of getting
people to play that game multiple
times. And even if you did
the analytics, if you tracked the number of
people just, like, launching the game and going
through levels, you would see
that it's a pretty, it's a pretty big
number. Even myself.
Think of the shit-tons they're making, not just off the game
itself, but all the license tie-ins
now. I mean, maybe they have a plan on this thing again.
They have a free version on the
Android market that runs on ads alone.
How many impressions, you know,
how many impressions are that,
you know, through AdSense? That's a lot.
That, you know, they make a
crap-ton of money instead of, you know, aside
from selling it for 99 cents,
which it pays for itself after a few plays.
So Nintendo's just threatened by that lower
price point? I mean, Nintendo also, God,
go in any Hot Topic,
and next to, like, one Angry Birds shirt,
you'll see, like, 20 Nintendo
classic franchise
shirts, you know? Everybody has a...
Nintendo lives off nostalgia, man.
But that's the thing, is, like,
Nintendo, on the other hand, can't...
I know they basically are
marketing... They've marketed the Wii
as more of a casual gamer system,
therefore, you know,
setting aside
all the, you know, all the
hardcores that they marketed to in the past.
I mean, that's pretty
much it. As long as you're...
What's happening is that they're getting
outgunned by other, you know,
more easily
available platforms, like an iPhone
or an Android. Something that most
people would have in their pocket,
aside from a DS.
And it's more than capable of running those games.
Alright, anything else on your mind tonight, Zaku?
Um, Back to the
Future of the Game, the first episode, is
pretty much free from their
Telltale Games site.
Pretty awesome so far. Yeah, you having a good time with that?
Although, even contrary to what the others are saying,
it's, like, it's getting better.
Like, I'm hearing the third episode's actually the best
so far. I'm really excited
for their Jurassic Park game. I don't know
what it is, but, like, you know, they had a new trailer
come in. It's like an adventure game where you just, like, click
around to solve puzzles
based on the storyline of the Back
to the Future.
And the guy who basically does
Marty's voice is very close.
Does almost a
spot-on impression of Michael J. Fox.
Nice. You have to actually listen to it, though.
I do. I really need to play the Back
to the Future. I forgot that it was
the free, you know,
time for it now that it's out. Because I remember
the whole stories about the, you know, code
word being in the Blu-ray and everything. So that's cool
that it's out there for free now. So I'll definitely have to check that out.
The first episode's out for free. Right.
They're gonna get you on the other ones, though.
Yeah. Alright. Well, Zaku,
take care, buddy. We'll see you next time.
Alright, bye.
1877 Game OLR.
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio.
Was that it?
You don't have any other stories for us, Loki?
Uh, well, that was the only
new one right now. Let me dig up
some other stuff here real quick.
Because, I don't know, it was kind of annoying
that, uh, I think
Oh, and the other thing, too,
that should be noted with that is they're basically
saying contradictory things
in both cases, and they're on record saying
contradictory things in both cases, so
they're lying somewhere.
Like, they're saying, oh,
well, this other OS stuff, that's all
Sony, Japan's, you know, doing.
They're behind it. And then
in the GeoHats case,
or the GeorgeHats case, they're like,
oh, that's Sony America. They're behind it.
Which is it, Sony?
You're on record saying both, so
you've perjured yourself one way or another.
Alright. We're gonna try this call
again, see if it's better. Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio. Who's this?
It's Ranma. Can you hear me better
now? Yes, and you're not giving that horrible
feedback. I don't know what that was about.
I think it's something with my computer.
I think it's long overdue for a fresh Windows
installation. Maybe Sony is trying to get
inside your computer and see what you're really doing with it.
Either that, maybe because Logitech
is pissed because I dumped their headset
for a better Microsoft one. SonyCat
is watching you masturbate.
I could give two shits about that. Alright.
What's on your mind tonight?
Something a little bit different,
as, if you remember what we talked about
in PM last week,
I upgraded my phone.
I now have an Android phone, and
I'm doing something I thought
I'd never find myself doing. What's that?
Mobile gaming.
Oh my gosh, alright.
Took the plunge and did some mobile gaming.
Now, do you have a phone that has actual
tangible controls, or is it an
all-touchscreen phone, like the iPhone?
Both. I have the
Samsung Epic 4G. Touchscreen,
if I slide it out, I have keyboard
access. Nice.
But so far, the games I've played
is completely in total touchscreen, which is not
so bad, even with the
screen protector on it.
Well, what kind of games have you been playing? Tell us about
some of the better ones.
Well, you can probably assume I have
that game everyone has been talking about,
Angry Birds. Of course.
I'm playing it, and I'm like, I can see
why people are into it. It's like
the new version of Worms
or something like that, you know?
And as
I was going through the marketplace,
I came across this one game that was probably
you probably tickled pink over the name of it.
Uh oh. It's called
Pew Pew. Pew Pew!
What is it?
It has involved kittens with lasers?
No, it's
pretty much Geometry Wars.
Oh, that's kinda cool. On Android.
That's cool. And it has
a couple of controllers on there
so you can control and play, and I've been
playing it, and the controlling is not so bad
on it, and
see, I picked up another game
that I got from Joe of Data called
Unfurry. That's like a block puzzle
game, but it's pretty good.
And as I'm going through the marketplace,
I can understand why
Nintendo said what they said.
I think the GDC about these
games on the 3DS,
because I looked at them like,
yeah, a lot of these games are total
and utter crap. Call me crazy.
If I'm dropping $250
on a gaming comp, I'd like
some quality games, you know?
Right.
You just don't want a bunch of free stuff
that sucks.
That's pretty much it. Now, if they
do something along the lines of
if a bunch of independent
developers put together a bunch of these
minigames together, and put together
some type of collection
for like $20 or something like that,
that probably wouldn't be so bad.
You know, funny enough, there's something like that on Steam, or at least
there was. It was either April Fool's Day or the day after.
There was like 13 independent games
going for like maybe $29
or $39, and one of them
was like Super Meat Boy. There was some big titles
in there. VVV, which I think Act F's
called in about before it was in there.
Yeah, I remember that.
High Profile Indie Games was in this big pack
lately, so sometimes the indie games will
band together for big sales like that.
Definitely.
And I started to notice that,
yeah, I'm playing around with
these games more than my
DS, because my phone is right there.
Pull it out, hit the button, the game
starts. Whereas I gotta pull it out of my
bag, fire it up, pick the game,
and start it up, you know? I guess it's like
convenience. It's a portable system where you don't have
to think about grabbing the system. You just, you always
have it on you.
And definitely, yes.
There you go. Well, congratulations
on jumping into mobile gaming.
Anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
Yeah, something that I think
Jamie would greatly appreciate.
What is that?
DDR Dollar Bill went to Megacon, and he
got me this shirt. It says
on the back,
KOKRK,
King of Kong, Orlando, Florida.
And on the front it says,
Never Surrender, Never,
Billy Mitchell.
And I just noticed
that it's a limited
edition shirt with his signature.
It says, Billy Mitchell
Video Game Player of the Century.
How about Jerkface
of the Century? I like that
even better.
Aw, I'm sure he's a nice guy.
No, he's not actually.
He's a big jerk.
No, I've never talked to the guy.
But he apparently sells really good barbecue sauce?
Hey.
That works. Let me be the judge of that, because I love
my barbecue sauce. Me too.
Alright, Rama, we're gonna let you go, try to fit in one more
call before we end the Skype tonight, so take care, buddy.
Wonderful. Bye.
Alright.
Let's see if we can take one more call
on the Skype line. 1-877-GAME-OLR
or our username on Skype is
OrangeLoungeRadio. Any other
stories?
Yeah, there's a new game, I don't know if you've
ever played the game QWOP.
Remember QWOP?
I have not played QWOP. I've played a lot of crap.
I have.
Anyways, there's a new game called
GURP, and it's a rock climbing game
that requires you to basically
kind of
bend your fingers in
almost a twister type of way
using the shift keys, the mouse buttons,
or shift keys are the mouse buttons, and you have to hit
certain letters
on your keyboard in order to climb,
and you have to avoid this rising water.
And if it's anything like QWOP, it's really
damn hard. Impossible, yeah.
Alright, let's take one more
call here on the Skype line before we call tonight.
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
This is DT.
Hey, DarkTets Studio, what's up, buddy?
Oh, I
think you can probably guess. I know, I was gonna
say, this has got to be about
WonderCon. I know you were really excited
about your trip out to WonderCon, which happened this week.
Tell us about some of the games you saw at
WonderCon.
Oh, man. Well, Nintendo
had a huge boost, and they were showing off
all of the 3DS games they had
that.
Did anything
catch your eyes
over there? It was pretty cool?
Well, I like
that a little bit. Steel Diver.
Uh-huh.
It was pretty cool. Was that the first time you ever got to
touch 3- was that the first time you ever got to get your hands on
a 3DS? Yeah. What'd you think about
3D? What'd you think about it when you, like, first
saw it?
Oh, yeah, it was pretty neat. Yeah, did you
do that whole thing, like, cause I know I do
this the first time. Like, you know, you
know you're about to play a system that's 3D with
no glasses, but then you, like, you know, you're kinda
like, you have that little bit of a doubt where you're like,
oh, this is gonna be stupid. And then, like, you
pick it up and you're like, whoa, you kinda have
that moment of, whoa, it really is 3D.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so.
Batman also had, uh, Kate
Icarus demo. Oh, did they?
Nice. Was it playable
or was it just, like, a trailer?
Yeah, no, it was playable. Oh,
shit, nice. I felt like, uh, unless you ever played
Sin and Punishment. Uh-huh.
Yeah, it kinda
felt like that. Nice. By the way,
Sin and Punishment was- Lion with the analog stick
and the name was the- Sin
and Punishment was another one of those games that
Fry's, that they had, like, 20 extra copies of
that they were trying to get rid of. The, uh, new
one that was out on the Wii. Mm.
It's unfortunate. Anyway, sorry about that,
DT. Yeah, I'm sorry.
But, uh, okay, well, what other,
what other, like, did Capcom have anything? I
know you always try to run over there and look at their booth.
Oh, yeah, well,
most of the stuff they had, those stuff was already
out, but they did have Resident Evil,
which was, well, it's alright, I guess.
Oh, cool.
Mm-hmm.
Um, what else?
Any other games?
Uh, let's
see, they had the, all the
big movie, comic book movie games,
like Thor and Captain America and
Green Lantern. Oh, yeah, god,
there's gonna be a ton of those this summer with all the
comic book movies coming out. Oh, yeah, we have Thor,
Green Lantern, there's an X-Men movie
as well, right, the first class? It's crap.
I know, I so don't wanna see it, I don't care.
Uh, what else is there?
I think there's, um,
I feel like I'm missing some huge ones.
Oh, well, whatever.
What, huge? Comic book movies.
Comic book movies. There's Thor,
there's Captain America, Green Lantern,
Green Lantern, there's the big three.
There's X-Men First Class,
there's the Spider-Man reboot this year, or is that next year?
No, that's not for a while.
And, um,
but they're also, I think, gonna
be rebooting Fantastic Four,
Transformers, if you wanna count that as, uh,
another Superman,
and, uh, Batman.
Oh, yeah, Batman 3 is next year, and that I'm
excited about, but I don't know how the game would be.
Well, I did see your write-up,
uh, is available over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com,
so it looks like you kept a little dear diary
while you were there, and saw stuff.
Now, I have to ask, did you get to see the masquerade at all?
Uh,
a little bit, it's a bunch of costumes
all over. Did you see,
by chance, the, um,
Main Street Electronica Parade?
Oh, no,
I didn't see that.
One of my friends was in that, and that, uh,
she's been on the show before, Victoria, I think,
filled in one week when Jamie wasn't here.
She was one of the gals in the, it was a, uh,
they did the Main Street Electrical Parade, but with
a Tron theme, like the Tron guy was stuck
in the Main Street Electric Parade.
Yeah, it was pretty awesome.
They didn't win! They were robbed!
Of course, I didn't see the winning video, but I'm extremely
biased. Extremely biased.
So, alright, well, DT, I'm glad you had fun
at the show. You know, we will actually have to go
some year. This was just really not a good year
for me to go, but I am hoping we will go
to Find Me this year. That is
something we're trying to do, so we'll see. Alright.
Oh, we're gonna go back next year, so.
Awesome. Well, we'll try to make it next year.
Alright. Alright. Take care and check out
that article at orangelawnsready.com by DT.
Alright, bye guys!
Yep.
I don't know why I said guys. I was saying bye to you guys.
Bye to you guys. I'm gonna go read that article. Alright.
No, it is about time to say bye, guys.
The show's about over.
Thanks, you guys, though, for tuning in to us. We're gonna
close up the Skype line. If you didn't get through tonight,
sorry. Try sending us an
email next time. Mailbag
at orangelawnsready.com is the place where you
can send us an email.
Let me ask Loki one more time if there's any last minute
stories before we wrap it all up. Yeah, there's
a leaked Forza 4 pitch
video that was supposed to be, I think, part of their
E3 presentation, and
basically confirmed everything that
was already leaked out regarding
Forza 4, including the head tracking,
the Kinect
integration, that kind of stuff.
Good stuff.
Head tracking, pretty awesome. They were saying, yes, you'll
be able to use head tracking to look into the corners
when you're driving and stuff. Although, that's a little
awkward for me.
I think because if your TV's in front of you,
you can't really turn your head to the side.
It's gonna be a little weird, yeah.
It'd be cool if the multiple
monitors support or whatever, but
once again, why would you need
head tracking if you have multiple monitors?
But hey,
glad to see they're using head tracking,
so that'll be awesome.
Alright, very cool.
This might be a little hint of what is to come
for the next generation of Kinect, and this could be very,
very good. Yeah. So we'll see.
Alright, well it's that time of the show where we go around
and get everybody's final thought as we wrap
up another week here at Orange Lounge Radio.
SalaciousPop, thanks again for being here.
You did a lot of talking this week. I'm very proud of you.
Alright, so thanks, and do you have
any final thoughts for our listeners?
No.
Alright then, alright.
Let's see, Dark Soccer, I guess I'll go to you next.
Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners tonight?
I want more pinkberry.
And my final thought along
those lines is that the Lychee
pinkberry can go to hell.
Blood orange forever. It's not gross.
It's good. It's not blood orange.
But the mango is amazing.
Eh, whatever. It's not blood orange.
Alright, Loki, your final thoughts tonight?
Um...
I don't know.
I'm down to
my US 3DS system.
I got rid of all the rest.
Aww.
Aww, that's great.
Did the wife catch you?
No.
He was like, why would she?
And then you're gonna come home,
and be like, what?
No, she doesn't listen to the show.
I was talking to her last week.
She listened for just a minute.
It was like...
Just long enough for a baby to hear daddy.
Pretty much, yeah.
She's trying to get him
for two naps tonight.
Last night he woke up
with me, I woke up with him at five.
I usually wake up with him at five in the morning.
Every day.
On the weekends even.
And so he wouldn't go
back down to bed for like about an hour.
He was just trying to get him to go back down.
And he finally slept till
seven forty, but...
I'm actually now able to be
wide awake at five in the morning.
Which works out, because I can work on my PC sometimes.
You know, and able to work on
Grand Theft Auto map edits and stuff like that
really in the morning without being interrupted.
But, uh...
It's tough.
I have to take naps now on the weekends
sometimes, because
there's only so many days you can wake up that early
and not be affected by it.
Well, Rob naps every day and he doesn't even have a kid.
So, don't feel too bad.
Hey, you've earned those naps.
Ring ring, hi pot, it's kettle on the phone.
I wanted to say,
and I know they're not listening obviously,
and I don't think they listen normally,
but congratulations to our friends
Eric and Mel for their brand new baby girl.
Cute baby!
Someone finally had a girl.
I know, it's like a big sausage fest,
but finally
finally getting some girls in here.
Alright.
Alright, well that does it for another week
here at Orange Lounge Radio.
Thank you guys so much for tuning in and supporting independent radio.
You know, all we ask if you like our show,
help us spread the word. We don't have big budget
advertising dollars. Say something nice about us
on a forum. Tell your friends about the show.
Leave us a nice review on iTunes. Anything you can do to help
spread the word of Orange Lounge Radio would be
much appreciated.
And next week, we'll be back to do it all again
one more time, episode 409.
I guess that means we have to do some cleaning next week
because it's 409. Hey, I cleaned that desk.
You did. It better not need cleaning next week.
I'll dirty it up. It isn't, it's
dust free, lemony fresh.
But shirmy tainted.
Well of course, duh.
Alright, that does it. Have a wonderful
week everybody. We'll see you next time here at
Orange Lounge Radio.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio
is an Orange Lounge
production. To join us
for a live show, visit
www.allgames.com
Sunday nights
at 6 pm Pacific time.
The views and opinions expressed
on Orange Lounge Radio do not
necessarily reflect those of the entire
staff of Orange Lounge Radio
or allgames.com.
But we're probably right anyway.
See you next week.