Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts?
DarkSakura
Sky and Lowkey
Tonight, April 24th, 2011
Is EA Sports set to roll out a new paid subscription service?
Child of Eden is delayed on one platform
And could an upcoming paid demo determine the fate of Mega Man Legends 3?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of Orange Lounge Radio
It's the show where every gamer has a voice
We tape live at All Games Radio
www.allgames.com
Every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
My name is Rob Roberts
I'll be joining you over the next few hours with my co-hosts
First up, the one and only
DarkSakura, Jamie Summers
Hi
How are you?
Feeling far better than I did previously
Yes
I can eat now
I'm sorry to hear you were sick and all
What happened?
You just had a
No idea, I think it was just a bug
That's too bad
It had to have been a virus because nobody else got sick
Do you feel refreshed after a week off?
We weren't here last week
And you were really the only one that didn't have anything going
Well, I don't know if you ended up doing something else
But Lowkey's my fault
I got to spend a good night with my boy
Good, good
Little date night
More of a hanging out
How cute
Hey, I think we actually played some more Final Fantasy that night
Oh, your little Final Fantasy megathon or whatever you're doing?
Yeah, whenever we get back to it
We got the level up, the job change
Okay, there you go
Oh, so you're still on one
But you're now probably what, halfway through one
Because that's about the halfway point of the game
Little more maybe
Yeah, cool, cool
Well, I'm not here tonight sadly
Techmaster Lowkey is not here
I don't know, there's something about like
Baby's first Easter
And all this like, I gotta do family stuff
Like, whatever, nice excuse
Alright, no, just kidding, obviously
Understandable
I can't wait until next year when they're all like
We've done all this, who cares
So sadly Lowkey is not here tonight
But filling in for Techmaster Lowkey
Say hello to Salacious Pop
Hello
How are you?
I'm great
Thank you for coming here on kind of a short notice
So, appreciate it
No, I live with you now
So you can just drag me out wherever
Exactly, it's pretty easy
I have to be honest, Salacious Pop
It wasn't the first person I tried to get on here
I know that sounds really horrible
It's not, obviously he's a wonderful guest and so forth
But it's kind of like, you know, you try to bring on
A variety of folks
And unfortunately everybody else I asked
Was like, ah, Easter
And I got Easter stuff going on
Yeah, there's Easter things
It's like a big holiday or something
No, I guess it is for a lot of people
But I always thought Easter was kind of done in the morning
Like, I finished Easter stuff in the morning today
I had family stuff going on
But that was all in the morning, so
I don't know
Well, I mean, I think the real Easter experience is
You get up and you go to church
So, if you're not going to mass, then
Yeah, but
You can make it up as you go along
Mass is like at midnight or something, right?
So, you got plenty of time for OLR still, right?
No, I don't know
Alright, forget it
I'll quit being a heathen or whatever
Anyway, let's introduce the chat room
They're always there
Because really, Jesus died so you could have chocolate
chat.orangelaungeradio.com
Marshmallow Peeps
Eww
A chat.orangelaungeradio.com
You can chat live with us
here on tonight's program
And get your little piece in
Whatever it is you want to say and so forth
We do have a handful of people in chat
Despite the holiday
Of course, it's a little less than usual
And in part, you can blame a week off
Because, I'll tell you what
Hoard House inadvertently had a week off as well
And I'll tell you what, died
Forums died
It's like, if you do a podcast
I'll tell you what, here's the advice
Because we get emails once in a while
You know, how have you guys stuck with doing a podcast
For nine years to today?
Do you have any advice?
You have my advice?
Try never to take weeks off
Unless you absolutely have to
Because, unfortunately, folks will get out of the habit of listening to you
And it's over like that
Alright, anyhow, we're back
Hopefully you will find room for us
In your podcasting and listening schedule again
And we want to talk about video games
Gaming news
We'll start it off as we always do with our gaming week
DarkSakura, how was your gaming week?
I played a bunch of stuff
Well, I played a lot of World of Warcraft
And two new games appeared in my steam account today
The Star Trek DAC
And Darwinia
Which I have installed
Just have not played
Because I had an epic nap today
How could that have happened?
I don't know, Rob
Some Sky person sent it to me
And we had our Final Fantasy go on
It's not like you had a birthday or anything happen during the hiatus
By the way, happy birthday
Thank you
Old lady
Not old lady
Just kidding
I still got it
Well, Tuesday we went to Dave and Buster's for my birthday
Thank you guys for coming
You're welcome
And I had a purple people eater
Which I kind of regretted having
Because that was when my stomach was starting to get really bad
But, um, we, uh
I played some Derby Owners Club
And Tank Tank Tank
And some of that really awesome Terminator gun game
And this weird trivia game
That I really didn't know much of the answers to
Because it was like sports
And pop culture
Like, the type of pop culture that I don't keep up with
And, uh
What else did I play?
Because I played other stuff
I played Droplets
When I had my big bad insomnia attack last night
Except all it really did was make me have to pee
And, uh
Some, uh, Luminesse
What else did I play?
I played something else
Oh, yeah, um, Peggle Extreme
And then watched an entire playthrough of Portal 2
You actually watched the whole thing start to finish, huh?
Yes, I did
Wow
See, I didn't want to ruin it for myself
I did that with the last one, too
Did you really?
That means now I'll have some idea
So how to play a little bit more seamlessly
So that I do not get too motion sick
So, um, do you find that if you kind of play the YouTubes in advance or whatever
That it helps the experience or hurts it?
I think it helps it
I've been trying very hard to dodge spoilers
I have not beaten Portal 2 yet
And I'm really, like, everybody's like
You gotta hear the song
I'm like, doesn't the song have spoilers?
So
Not really
I mean, yeah, it does really give away the ending
But I'm trying really hard to avoid all that, so
You know
Yeah
But I love it
My favorite thing so far is
BIRD KILL IT
So, uh, do you know that it's Noble Garden Week in WoW?
Because you played some WoW, it's Easter
Oh
It's Easter holiday, it's one of the easier ones
I didn't do that, I'll have to do it this week
It's all this week, it just started today
Okay
It's Rob's favorite holiday
Ugh
No, my favorite holiday is coming up next week in WoW
It's Children's Week
And my favorite, I mean, ugh
It's terrible
And it's the one holiday I need for my Violet Drake
Because literally last year I said
Fuck Children's Week, I'm not putting up with this bullshit
Ugh, you gotta do it
And I had to wait an entire year
Anyhow
Well, let's
I found, by the way, a dragon that I want
That's blue and has transparent wings, looks kind of aquatic
It might be one of those hard to get ones
I know, but I want it
Alright
It will be mine
Let's move on with some other video games
Salacious Pop, what'd you play this week?
I've actually played a lot, considering that usually my schedule is simply WoW
Which I'm playing far less of
I played some Toki Tori
Because it was a part of the Steam Potato Bag special
I had already owned Toki Tori
So they just patched in the Potato Portal 2 content
Because I wanted to try and unlock Portal 2 early
Even though I didn't really have the means to buy it
I still haven't really played Portal 2 yet
So Toki Tori Mortal Kombat
Beat the story mode
And did some just regular one person versus PC fighting on that
And some Smash TV
Some Fatal
Going old school, what made you do Smash TV?
Just when we were
I was putting my Xbox Live account on your Xbox
And was trying to sync up all the games that you have on it
So I was just going through some old stuff on there
And yeah, that's it really
What did you think of Mortal Kombat?
I wish the story mode was longer
Because all the endless fighting
If there's even just a little bit of dialogue in between
It'll hold my attention more
Than just doing ladder mode
And getting up to the boss
And starting all over from scratch
But yeah, I liked it
I found a lot of bugs in it
Audio bugs
That hopefully they'll be able to patch and fix
Once a certain system is back online
Which we'll get into I'm sure in a minute
But yeah, it's fun
It's a good
They pretty much looked at what Street Fighter 4 did
And it's like, oh that's awesome
We should do that for our franchise
And it's working for them
It doesn't hurt that they've had a little bit of a break
With Midway having gone under
And somebody else had to pick up the series
So it kind of gave them a little time to think about how to reinvent
Yeah, I think Warner Brothers
I know Warner Brothers published it
Well the Mortal Kombat folks I think broke off
And made this NetherRealm Studios
Is their new little thing
And then Warner Brothers is their publisher
So you know, Mortal Kombat's
Been a viable enough franchise
I don't know how well the last few games in the series have sold
Keep in mind the last game that came out
Was the Mortal Kombat in DC Universe game
I don't know how well that sold
But before that they were
Cranking them out
I think those games have always sold enough
I don't know if they've ever sold big
And it really seems like they're trying to get this new one
In the series to sell big
Because we had what?
We had Deadly Alliance
We had Annihilation
There was another one in the middle there
The one that had the Mortal Kombat mini racing
Kart game was there too
Annihilation was the one that had
Literally everybody
That was kind of the last Mortal Kombat game
But then they're like, oh
How do you save a franchise? You do a reboot
And you know, that's literally what they've done
Literally, like that's the story
Is built around a reboot
Yeah, the story mode
If you play it from start to finish
Does the canon
The official canon of the first three games
And it sets you up for what
Mortal Kombat 4 was, lore wise
At the end of the story mode
Let's go to our chatroom
At chat.orangesonstrader.com for some comments
Tigerclaw in our chatroom says
The MK story mode is long if you take into account
How difficult it was to beat Shao Kahn
The best strategy was to
Teleport, uppercut, repeat that and stay
Far away until time expires
Yeah, I did some lightning ball cheese on him
Just get away, pew pew
I'm gonna pew pew at you
And then he just hopefully doesn't block enough of him to win
Because the thing about story mode is that you have
To play as pretty much every character
Or do you play every character?
Only the human side really
You don't play the outworld
And netherworld people
But you still have to play a pretty good mix of people
Yeah, Sonya, Jax
Most of Raiden's little groupies
Are who you control
And Tigerclaw in our chatroom also fills in here with
Rob, it's like what they did with Star Trek
Due to the events of the beginning
It creates an alternate timeline
I don't think that's very spoilery
I think that's pretty common knowledge
In story mode, I believe people die
I haven't gotten that far in my story mode
But I believe people do die
I don't want to spoil that for you
But there's big twists and events
I believe characters become characters that didn't exist before
Kind of interesting
Back in the 90s when MK2 and MK3 were out
Baraka wasn't in MK3
Because in the canon
He died at the end of 2
They don't show that and obviously you can still play as him
In this new reboot
So they left out some of the deaths
So the official canon is in there
That's cool
Going into my gaming week
Obviously I played Mortal Kombat
Pretty extensively this week as well
I do like how they have
Really brought a lot of the nostalgia
I think you commenting
What Street Fighter 2 did
We should do that
Or Street Fighter 4 did for Street Fighter 2
Is almost exactly what they've done
A lot of that has the nostalgia of the different stages
And I really like how in story mode
The very first part of story mode
Takes place in a stage
That you see in the original Mortal Kombat
With Shang Tsung sitting up on the throne
And all the monks sitting in front of him
That applaud
They literally bring that to life
In this new Mortal Kombat game
And that's pretty cool to watch
That's something I don't really remember happening in Street Fighter
So kind of getting to see all that play out
With, I hate saying next gen graphics
But you know
Or ten years later technology
Updated
Graphics and effects is really cool
Kind of watch all that play out
Did you bring it?
I didn't bring it tonight
I'm sorry I didn't know you wanted to play it
I've been watching all of the fatalities
And the special unlock characters and everything
And I found out where all of the hidden coins are
Yeah there's a little guide online
That we use to get every costume
If you don't
Buy any of the extras
In the crypt and you just do story mode
From start to finish
You have 130,000
Of the MK coins
That's enough to get almost half of the goodies
It's enough to get all the costumes and the fatalities
That's cool because I think that there's like
Another hidden 20,000
Yeah
I'm being corrected by our chat room
Annihilation was the movie
Armageddon was the game
My bad, my bad, sorry guys
Thanks Spaznator
A comment from Randy in our chat room
I felt like the story mode cleared up the events of the franchise
It was definitely more confusing before
Yeah you know Mortal Kombat
Kind of always felt like one of those games
Where they had to kind of write the story
To fit what they wanted to do
And so there were all these weird things going on
But yeah I kind of agree
That what they've done with this little reboot
I mean granted although they're changing some things
It kind of makes a lot of stuff make more sense
All in all as far as for the game itself
And this is interesting because
When I did the demo a couple weeks ago
I think I expressed concern
Like I'm not sure I'm going to like this game
Well just goes to show
Don't ever base your opinion of a game off the demo
Don't ever ever ever do that
Because it was actually really good
And I've been having a good time with it
I think there's such a great variety in characters
That they've brought in
Pretty much every single fighter from 1, 2, and 3
Are in it right
With maybe some very minor like the boss characters
Not all of them are there
When I was going through the list I saw that
Kentaro, Goro
Shiva
I think they all show up in the story
But they had fatalities for him
Oh really?
The big centaur dude with the big horse
I think he was the boss of MK3
He's in it in a cutscene but you don't play as him
And then Quan Chi from before
Was brought in so he's playable
But otherwise the people from 4 aren't in it yet
Yeah although
DLC might change some of that
There's a character that was introduced in Deadly Alliance
Who's actually one of my favorite characters
Kenshi is one of the first download characters
The blind ninja guy
There's a lot of people calling for Tanya to show up
I would love Tanya to be in the game
She's awesome
She wasn't a major character though
She was a bitch
So I'm not expecting her to show up
But it would be cool if she would
And then I was watching the fatalities
For Kratos
Kratos is in the game
He obviously fits right in
I gotta say though
He plays like any other character
Which I think is a compliment
You don't want a character like Kratos
To be gimmicky or stick out like a sore thumb
But I mean the whole
Painting his body white and everything
Well Quan Chi does that shit too
So he kind of fits right in with everybody else
It's a better promotional exclusive thing
Than I don't know Darth Vader and Yoda
And Soul Calibur IV
And also the other thing
That
Who was it?
I just lost my train of thought
It was somebody else that's in there
Well Noob and
Ermac were
Fandom rumors
That they actually made real characters
I love that
Ermac's fatality with the spikes
That one's really cool
Leo Shen is in our chat room saying
No Rain otherwise they would have all of Trilogy
Yeah Rain is one of the most notable
Notable characters that's missing but
To be honest because they've done so
Much with the other ninjas like
Cyrax and Sektor are not
Just palette swaps
They are fully developed
They start in story mode as humans
And you can unlock their human forms
So they are all very different characters
So I can see why they probably cut
Rain because while he was a cool
Character especially he was really
Tacked into Trilogy I think
He was purple Rain
He was a palette swap that had a couple cool moves
With a neat name
Otherwise he was really
Forced in the story
I would bet he's DLC later on though
I remember what I was going to say
One of Shang Tsung's fatalities was actually
His mortal combat
Versus DC fatality
Except it's the whole thing
Because they cut it to where you only see him
Turn into a clown
And then you don't see the other person explode
They showed the full fatality
Because people were like what happened
So they actually put that in there
The fatalities in this game are a little silly
As they're supposed to be very over the top
Babalities are in there
Babalities are cute
But friendships are not which kind of surprised me
I was very sad
No animalities or any of the other weird stuff either
I was really sad friendships weren't there
I always loved those in Mortal Combat 2
Otherwise the game is pretty fast paced
It's got a great tutorial mode
That kind of teaches you how to do things like
The x-ray attacks are a really neat addition
It does feel a little lifted
From Street Fighter 4
It's one of those things where it's like
It's not a copy
But it's definitely influenced
But it's really cool
It adds to the battle exactly what it does
In Street Fighter 4
If you are behind this gives you a chance to level the playing field
If your opponent has a moment of weakness
And the x-ray attacks look really cool
And it makes the battle flow really well
And I think that's where this game really shines
Is that just the battles
Flow so well
They're fun to play
The fatalities give that
Sense of edge to it
There's a lot at stake
Where this Mortal Combat
Really shines is where a lot of the
Prior Mortal Combat games have really shined
And that is the
Robustness of what is offered
In the title
You've got your story mode
You've got your challenge ladder
You've got the crypt thing
Which the crypt thing has been done better
In other versions of the game I think
But whatever it's still there
You have different modes to play
And the tag team thing
Kind of comes out of nowhere too
They kind of took that whole idea
I guess you could say Marvel vs Capcom or whatever
But now you have teams of two
And you can do assists and all that stuff
So it's pretty cool
Mortal Combat has really been invigorated
It's been infused with some of the best parts
For a pretty awesome experience
One of my favorite Mortal Combat games in recent memory
The best one of all time
I think that's still two
It's one of those that
That's going to be hard to top
It's worth
Checking out if nothing else
A lot of people like to point and laugh at Mortal Combat
In the fighting world
But I think this one shows that there's a lot here to take seriously
Two Beta was great
With Katana's infinite combo
Let's see
Tigerclaw in our chatroom says
Rob regarding animalities at least one of them is in there
It's one of Liu Kang's fatalities
That's true
But wasn't it also a fatality in Mortal Combat 2
I think that's what inspired it
Not necessarily the animalities
Anyhow, other games I played this week
I don't want to talk just about Mortal Combat
Because I haven't had a chance to play Mortal Combat online
Because of certain outages
But I have had a chance to check out Portal 2
Portal 2 is
I played the first game
And played that game pretty extensively
And it was always a pretty cool concept
And when I heard they were making a sequel
I knew it was going to be pretty interesting
And I've been playing through the single player mode
And I really don't know what to say
I honestly think
Games like
Super Mario Brothers
Final Fantasy 7
Games that have been
Landmark for that generation
I honestly think Portal 2 fits into that
For this generation
I think this is like a
Legendary status of a game
Honestly
It really just took the first one
And it's like, wow, people kind of like this idea
And this concept
We're just going to, again, infuse all this new stuff into it
And it's just given it all this energy
And now a story that's really taken off on its own
And all these different concepts
I mean, I really think
This game is going to just stand the test of time
As this is really a great game
That's really easy to get into
It's a first person shooter for people who hate first person shooters
That's one of the
Really interesting things about it
And the story is well done, the voice acting is
Phenomenal
And then there's a co-op mode on top of all of that
And I think it's just
A great game
I really try to keep myself spoiler free
And I've been very happy with some of the twists and turns
That the story has been taking
I was really expecting it to just be
Kind of a continuation of Portal 1
Where you would just have more test chambers
And explore the story a little more
But there's much more here
Than just more test chambers
And that's all I'm really going to say
Although there are a lot of those
There are a lot of those
But there's much more
This game digs beneath the surface
And I don't just mean beneath the surface
Of the test chambers
Which you do get to see as well
Which is really cool
GLaDOS as a character
Is legendary
Where are you right now?
In the world of video games
I have done the blue repulsion gel
A couple times
So you've seen Potato?
I have seen Potato
Okay, I'm trying to figure out where you are
So I get where the Potato Sack joke comes from now
That didn't occur to me until later
But yes, so I get where that all comes from
My favorite still is
BIRD KILL IT
So yeah
And I have to say I was reading on a few things
And you know where you see
All the old potatoes
The bring your daughter to work
Day science fair
The big mutated potato
Is supposed to be Shell's project
Interesting
Alright
So anyway
Some comments in our chat room
Randy in our chat room says
Watching Portal for the first time made me think
How does someone have the mental capacity to figure out these puzzles
You know a lot of it is trial and error
I noticed that the second game
Really limits where you can put portals
More than the first game did
And that's part of the puzzles
They've added all this other stuff into it
Like the lasers
The gel is a huge thing
I got stuck on one puzzle
Because of that stupid gel
I couldn't figure out how to
I didn't figure out that you could actually make gel
Fly through the walls that destroy things
Otherwise I would have figured it out a lot sooner
And just crazy stuff
You really have to look around for surfaces
That could be a mile high up
For you to fling a portal onto
It is really an experience
To play a game like Portal
And I really don't know what else to say
The game is outstanding
And it's well worth your money
If you haven't bought it yet
I guess you already know this is probably the type of game
That maybe just isn't for you for whatever reason
Or you know obviously economical whatever stuff
60 bucks is still a huge investment
But I don't know what else to say
I think most people who want it
Already went and got it first day
The Steam integration is great
I was really surprised at how well
Steam integrates with the Playstation 3
But you can hit select
And it's just like being logged into Steam
I don't know what else to say
It was pretty seamless
You connect your Playstation network account
To Steam
And then that's it
You can hit select and I can see all my Steam friends
And who's on
And it's just like I'm playing another Steam game
But it's on my Playstation 3
Now I was wondering
If someone picked this up
They wouldn't be able to get the Steam
Link would they?
There is a card
That comes with the game
That has the code on it
So sadly no you wouldn't be able to get it
You'd have to buy it new in order to get to both games
And it says somehow
It says on the back of the box
You cannot play co-op
On your PC and PS3
But I don't know
See I haven't really explored that yet
Maybe somebody in our chat knows
And I would imagine a lot of that is because of the Steam hookup
If I log into Steam on my PS3
It's not going to let me do it on my PC as well
To play the same game
But what would happen if I have two
Playstation 3 accounts
Like for example, Salacious Pop uses my Playstation
3 as well
What if he connected that to his Steam
And then played on my PS3
And then I played Steam on my computer
Maybe that would work? I don't know
Because I can't imagine that the discs are imprinted with the serial numbers somehow
So unless
Hooking up Steam
And hooking up the whole console
To that Steam ID
I would think you could have that
I don't know
I'm going to be honest
I haven't even really played it on Steam
I've been completely satiated with the PS3 version
I don't really need the Steam version
It's nice to have
It's a cool little bonus
But I didn't really need it
I'm waiting until I can play it on PC
Because I'm like that
I need the mouse in WASD
It really is a lot easier to play on the PC
See but see
This all goes back to joystick vs mouse and keyboard
Some people prefer mouse and keyboard
I love the DualShock controller
For playing it, it's awesome
Great for me
Spazzinator in our chat room says
Is the cake still a lie in Portal 2?
No
There is one joke that is
Blink and you miss it sort of thing
And I like that they did that
Because they didn't try to keep the same joke
Going through the whole thing
I really like that
Glados has some new insults and some of them are real good
She consistently makes fat jokes about you
Which are just outstanding
I love the Glados cut downs
Some of them are really harsh
All I'll say
The surprise?
When the confetti blows
I was dying
Alright
Next time there will be real confetti
Let's see
Go into our chatroom at chat.orangelaungeradio.com
Bonds006 says
Like the Xbox 360 recovery game tag ability?
From Sony?
No Rob, stop hoping
I don't think that's exactly what I'm talking about
Although, yeah it is a little weird
That you can
You have to
We're having this problem now that
We have two Xbox 360's in our house
If we put the live on one
We have to migrate the account to play on the other
Xbox every time
It's a little irritating
It's weird
Frisbee in our chatroom says
The console versions should let you use keyboard and mouse
That would be kind of nice
You can hook up the USB stuff and then use that
That would be nice
I guess maybe that's why they give you the PC one free
I don't know
Other games I've played this week
It doesn't stop there
Those are the two big ones
I bought a 3DS
Chapter 4 on the 3DS
I didn't realize
Every single freaking fighter
From the original
Is in the 3DS version
That's pretty impressive that they have all that
Obviously the graphics have been scaled down a little bit
To make it all fit
But it's 3D
And there's this cool little mode where you can actually play
Over the shoulder of one of the characters
That it's very 3D
Kind of neat
All the little modes that they put in that
Loki kind of reviewed the title on the show before
So I'm not going to rehash everything
But I do like that they've put in a street pass feature
Where you can fight things
It gives you incentive to keep playing
So you can collect these little trophies
Different from achievements
But the little trophies are what you use in street pass mode
To help fight other people and so forth
And 3DS is a system
I'm liking it so far
I feel like there's so much more potential there
That we're going to unlock in May
When they do some of the patches
There's a lot in the interface
Where you hit the button and it says
This feature is not yet available
It will be installed through a system update
But otherwise the online is much easier on this
Than it has been on other systems
I couldn't tell you how much
I shouldn't say the word impressed
But the first time I went into the menu
Where I could just see all my friends
And if they're online or not and what they're playing
The reaction I had of
It's about freaking time Nintendo
It's still code based
But it's supposedly one code
For everything which is nice
And I had some issues
With the facial recognition
It'll make your little
Me avatar
You take a picture of yourself
You square your head
In the frame
And it thinks that I have
Really huge jowls
My head looked like a bell
My 3DS is apparently
GLaDOS because it was calling you fat
I think it was
I'm rocking a beard right now
And I think it just thought that my
Facial hair was face
So it's like, yeah
Well the good news is if you don't like the me that it gives you
You can go in and tweak it
And I'll tell you what, the first time you take a picture
And have it do a me based on your picture
You're not gonna like what comes out
I'm just convinced nobody's gonna like the thing that comes out
It's the new technological advance
Of the driver's license photo
Where you get
It in the mail and you're like, oh was I sick
That day?
Exactly, that's a very good way of putting it
Alright, so gosh
I think I've covered about everything
I have Final Fantasy IV, the complete edition
On order as well
I was frugal in my shopping and I went on Amazon.com
And bought Mortal Kombat
And Portal 2
I got like $20 credit for buying one
And $10 credit for buying the other
I usually don't give shout outs to retail chains
Or anything like that
Because we're a commercial free show
But I just gotta say as a gamer, I was pretty impressed
They only charged me $4 for shipping
They had the games there on release day
I got $30 worth of free credit
Which I used to buy the Final Fantasy IV complete collection
Which was the other game I wanted this week
So, win!
Hey, I'm all for good deals, exactly
Alright
Let's see, going to our chatroom again
Chat.orangeloungeradio.com
Bonds006 in our chat agrees
It does make you look not like yourself
Tigerclaw says
Regarding the Streetpass, so far it's been working
I go about 4 miles from Streetpass
But the fine me still
Oh, I don't know
Oh, I think I got about 4 me's
From Streetpass, but the fine me
Still won't let me use them
How many Streetpass me's do you need in order
For fine me to work without buying the heroes?
Good question, I haven't figured that out yet
I just got the 3DS last night
So I have yet to run into people
Or run into the mall or anything
Or a place where other gamers are
Where I've had Streetpass
I've just bought the me's
And what I mean by that, the 3DS has a built in game
Called fine me
And it's a little chibi role playing game
Like very bare bones
Like fight, magic, run type of thing
Very bare bones
And you can use coins that you get from the pedometer
The pedometer is built into the 3DS
And every time you're in sleep mode
Every time you take 100 steps
You get a maximum 10 coins a day
So it's pretty cool because it's encouraging people to go out and walk
Or shake their DS repeatedly to get the steps
It's kind of like that
Walking trainer game that came out
For the DSi a couple
Years ago
It's been actually built into the 3DS
And you get coins for doing it
And you can buy heroes
And as you play through this role playing mode
You unlock hats for your me's
Like the very first thing you get is a little Mario hat
That you can put on your me
For your me
So if you want to be a little kitty
That sounds awesome
Alright so
Let's move on
Oh BlackWolf in our chatroom says
I got one me and I used him on fine me
So I guess maybe there's
Something that Tigerclaw missed in that
I don't know
Yeah I gotta try and get more me's
I was hoping Loki would be here so we could street past the DS's
But oh well
Easter's more important I suppose
We're going to move into some gaming news
But first some quick plugs for where you can find us
Around the internet we are on Twitter
Twitter.com slash OLR
As well as Facebook, facebook.com
Slash orange lounge radio
And of course once again we do tape live
At All Games Radio www.allgames.com
If you've never joined us for a live show
Why not?
You should sometime at some point
Alright let's get into tonight's gaming news
Pop's going to start us off tonight since he's filling in for Loki
This is a huge story that's been
Covered most major avenues
For gaming news and that is
The fact that on Wednesday night
The Playstation Network
Went down like a drunk
Bicurious frat boy at a Jack Jansen concert
It's just gone
That's yeah
Wednesday night
No PSN, no store
No
Curiosity
Store or anything like that
And Sony confirmed that it was
Because of an external intrusion
Which means they got
Text
Someone got into the system
In a bad way and brought
The whole thing down and I guess
Given the statement that
Cybold
Put out
It sounds like they're completely
Rebuilding their
The OS or
Whatever the security patch was so bad
That they're willing to take down their entire
Store for five days now
Nearly
And what a shitty time for this to happen
I mean you know this is the
Week to have a Playstation 3 of all
Weeks you know Mortal Kombat
Has the slight edge having one more
Character on the PS3 and let's face it a better
Controller sorry
And Portal 2 obviously
You know they
Gabe Newell got up there at
E3 and said
K my bad on Playstation my bad guys
It's actually going to be the system you're going to want to
Own Portal 2 on remember that
And obviously with the Steam integration
It's pretty great and so
I kind of wonder how that plays into it like
Maybe just the fact that now all of a sudden
All these folks who maybe own both
Systems were like opting for the PS3
Versions in conjunction with whatever
Else is going on behind the scenes it brought it
Down
Yeah I'm sure you know there are people at Valve that
I don't want to say they're you know
Pissed but it's there
It's a huge release for Valve and
The
Authoritative console version
You can't do co-op on it right now because
Of Sony so I'm sure they've got all these
Developers not just Valve breathing down their neck
Going how did this happen you know
Consumers are worried that
If the hack was
You know this bad that it would bring down their
Entire network for five days
Did they have access to customer records
Because a lot of people have their credit cards saved
Because they like just the one click purchase
I gotta admit that makes me
Very nervous because
Yeah alright mine's on there and I'm a
Little worried about this because
You know if that
Information got out I want to know
Like and I need Sony to be communicating
A little better than like yeah we're down
Because we got hacked no shit
Like we all read the internet
Even CNN was reporting about how
Anonymous was attacking Playstation Network
And whether they're responsible for this or not
I mean Sony has an obligation
To tell me exactly
What information of mine is out there
California has some pretty strict consumer rights
Laws involving
Statements made about their information
I think the federal government has some pretty strict laws on that
Stuff it's not just California many states
Do you know but uh
Yeah I mean obviously but the
Bummer is I think
You can report up to
90 days after the incident
And I'm sorry Sony I want to know now
Like stop giving all this fluff
What exactly is happening
We're going on 4 to 5 days now
You know and
You know we kind of joke
About how on this show like a lot of times
The system will go down for a day or two
And it's always like nobody ever remembers
Nobody ever remembers that
Xbox went down right after Halo 3
Came out too you know
Gamers pretty much overlook this stuff
Because once it's fixed then they can play their games
But this is starting to go on one of those
Things where it's getting harder and harder
To say you're just going to easily forget this
Especially if we find out
That our information was at risk
That is going to be a huge
Huge
Smack in the face of digital distribution
Is the new model and GameStop
Will buy breathe a huge sigh of relief
Because they'll be open that much longer
I think with the Xbox
They've had the gold which is
The 4 pay platform you know
For Xbox Live that's been around
Longer more people depend on that for the
Co-op playing for Netflix
Whereas the PSN you know
You post your trophies and you do some matching service
On it but PSN
Because it doesn't have I mean if you don't buy
The download games
From PSN there's really no reason
For them to have your credit card information
Whereas on the Xbox Live service
You need a credit card for gold period
I actually don't put
Any of my information in those if I can
Help it because with
Xbox you put it in there they will find
A way that
Even if you unintentionally
Press something they're still going to charge you
So it's best not to have it in there
At all just buy the points through
The internet for the PlayStation Network
What I would do is I would I don't know if you can
Do this anymore but I would go onto the site
The website PlayStation Network put
Some money in my bucket or whatever
Then buy the game through the PS3
That way I can do a one-time transaction
And they don't have my credit card saved in there
Because otherwise I don't trust it well this might
Be one of those tough lessons learned I mean granted
I have a pretty good bank who you know
Isn't gonna you know if I were to something bad were
To happen they're not gonna hold me liable for it
But it the whole thing will just piss me off more
It'll piss me off more
Whoever hacked this thing which now
We can't figure out if it was anonymous or not
And this is
Really interesting because this just pulls
Back this whole other layer of
What is anonymous all about
Because because of the fact that they don't
Have a face they are anonymous
So to speak it is so easy
For the media to blame them for this
Which is what's happening they may not be responsible
But they're getting the blame for this because
There's no one to defend anonymous because they're anonymous
And that adds actually to their notoriety
Yeah as I understand it
They're probably eating it up
As I understand it a couple weeks ago when the
The GeoHats verdict came down
They did a couple days of DDOS attacks
Which is where they flood the system with requests
That was it so this thing
That just brought you know brought the whole thing down
Like a house of cards they're like it's not
Whoever the people that
Yeah whoever the mouthpiece is whoever is calling
The shots which is probably
They're like it's not us we did our shit three weeks ago
Well and also the reason why they
Stopped was because they realized
They were putting the consumers at risk and that's not
What they wanted to do so I actually
When you mention that you know
They're getting more notoriety
I actually this isn't the notoriety
That they want they don't want to be responsible for the
Consumers because that's who they were trying to defend
In the first place so this whole GeoHats thing
But unfortunately how easy
Is it for the not
As tech savvy media mainstream
Media to just say well it's
Anonymous' fault you know they said they were gonna
They put out these videos and Anonymous Anonymous Anonymous
Anonymous I mean maybe they like having their name
Out there but I don't necessarily think this is
What they wanted their name on but because
Anonymous has no mouthpiece
This could be a whole
Subset of the group that's doing
This and we just don't know
It's interesting
That whole
Politics or whatever you want to call it behind
It is fascinating
And just to get to the meat and potatoes of this story
Patrick Sebold who is the head
Of PR for Sony this is his actual
Statement on it
Quote an external
Intrusion on our system has affected
Our Playstation network and
Curiosity services in order to
Conduct a thorough investigation and
To verify the smooth and secure operation
Of our network services going forward
We turned off Playstation network
And Curiosity services on the evening
Of Wednesday April 20th
Providing quality entertainment services
To our customers and partners is our utmost
Priority
That's their
See that's all they got to say about it
Part of me is kinda like something really
Bad happened this is much
More than a DDoS attack
Because if that was the case
We would not be sitting down talking about
Deconstructing the whole fucking thing
During Easter weekend
Which is the start of
Spring break when you have
Two of your biggest titles out
That is why I'm sitting here going
I think private information was
Breached and I think it's gonna come out in the next
Week that that's what happened
And that kinda worries me
Like otherwise your timing
Is just ridiculous Sony
As someone with a
Sales analyst background
The fact that their store
Is offline
Like oh yeah that's no revenue for a week
That's you know
Even a company as big as Sony that makes
You know billions of dollars a year
If you don't make a penny for five days you will feel it
So yeah it's pretty serious
Alright
Well let's move on with some more stories
This one kinda came up while we were off last week
But it's just speaking of
Demons with multiple heads or whatever you want to call it
This is a story that's just been going on and on
Over the past couple weeks that
You know we didn't have a show last week and that is
The rumored new
Nintendo console. A new Nintendo
Console is rumored to be debuting at E3
This June
Supposedly launching in 2012
It's supposed to be you know more powerful
Obviously than the Wii
A lot of talk about how it's supposed to be scary
Similar to the Xbox 360
Where if you develop a game for the
360 it's supposed to be just that much easier
For you to develop for whatever this
New Nintendo console is
These leaks are coming
From Game Informer who I believe
Was sorting a French
Site in their news which was
The same French site that I believe broke
The story on the PSP Go
So it's kinda one of those things where like
If the site was true before they're probably
Right again you know
Yeah and Game Informer is the face
Of GameSpot
And did also Forbes run
Or was it Wall Street Journal that ran a story on this
Like a really very dry
It was enough to break to the mainstream
Media and that's just making people give this
Thought that it's probably
True which
I'm kind of sad Loki's not
Here because I swear to god if you go back
In the archives and listen to a show in January
I told him I said
Nintendo's gonna announce a new console at E3
This year and he's like no they're not the Wii's still
Printing money I said what do they have coming
Out on the Wii there is no
Big title on the Wii right now except
Zelda that is it
And now they've pushed Zelda back
What's the real reason Zelda just
Got pushed back everybody
That game was ready to roll I'll bet you
Anything but now it's been pushed back why
It's getting the same treatment that the
Last Zelda game did
Guarantee it
And it's gonna be multi
Console just like the last one
And oh I wanted him to be here so bad
So I could point I told you so I told you so
But yeah this
And honestly I kind of
See this as kind of a duh
What else did Nintendo have to talk about at E3 this year
As far as consoles go
I mean I should say
Living room consoles go the 3DS
Obviously is gonna be the clearly
They're gonna roll out the Mario game and the
Kid Icarus game and those are gonna be their big titles that are gonna
Sell more this year as they talk about
Netflix and some of the other multimedia
Guaranteed you're gonna see that and whatever
Way we can make 9 year olds
Wanna have a 3DS they're gonna
Try to sell as many of those under the Christmas tree as they can
More Pokemans
Yeah and the rumor is there's gonna be a Pokemon
Announcement at some point as well
So I would take that
A little closer to Tokyo Game Show but sure
That's an inevitable as well
Pokemon Plaid and Pokedot
Pokemon 3D
But as far as you know
Living room consoles go it's been dead
On Nintendo's front I mean even with the
Zelda game if that game
Was really coming out like soon
We would be flooded with more
More uh
I don't know screenshots
And videos and things of that nature
So guarantee it there's a new console in the
Works I mean Nintendo has to play
Catch up in some regards to this
It prints money
Well there's even more rumors that um
There's even more rumors
That follow up with this
And some of it has to do with the
Controller I suppose it's gonna be
With this system
Apparently the by the way
They're calling this whole thing Project Cafe
Which I guess is like you know
Dolphin was for the GameCube
Right or was that the 64?
And then Revolution was the codename for the Wii
The Saturn was the Katana I think
This will not be called Project Cafe
When it comes out guaranteed
Yeah the Saturn was Katana but then when they
Were doing Pre for Dreamcast it was Neptune
That's right
They will do some very
Weird name that is very
One syllable type of easy thing just like
You know Wii was they'll do something like that
But anyway supposedly the
Controller is supposed to be like an iPad
With buttons 8 buttons
2 analog sticks a camera a
6.2 inch touch screen
That's kind of weird because that
Means the controllers themselves
Would cost several hundred dollars
If they're as fancy as everyone
Thinks they are now see part of me says
I don't necessarily think they're as good
As an iPad or an iPod
Because you know what I think about I've seen these
Printers for sale at Fry's
That have a removable touch screen type of thing
That you can take from the printer
And actually look at like the vices
And the screen it's okay but it's
Kind of cheap I think that
Is more what this is going to look like if this is even
True because the problem with this is
That now that you have these
Rumors that look like they're going to be true
Everybody's sucking onto
It and now once you know you're going to see
Fake pictures fake
Everybody's going to just have a field day with this
I'm just thinking of the VMU now
And that's what a lot of people
Are saying too
That would make sense and I honestly
I played little things on my VMU
I was trying to raise my
Chow
In Japanese
And the Final Fantasy
Oh wait no
This is the pocket station too
Yeah I totally just switched up
That had that really cool thing
The integration with the second rival schools
Yeah the evolution disc
And also
Nintendo has kind of
Ever since they GameCube
They've been the more affordable
Family friendly option
So they can't go all high tech and put out
You know a $600 system because that's
Going to go against what their business model
Has been for like 7 years now
I agree this has to be a cheap
System and I don't mean like they could probably
Get away with selling it for $300
Maybe $400 if it's that fucking good
But it's going to have to be cheaper
Than like an iPad
You know how much was the Wii when it first came out? 250
But of course it was supposed to be the budget system
It was a steal yeah
I honestly don't see them putting out such an expensive
Piece of technology as a controller
I truly think if this is even true
I really think you're looking at something
Like those printers
Because those printers are only like $300
And they have that little device that you take
Right off of them
I think we're looking at something more like that
They're all going to have Game Boy Micros attached to them
Well
Whatever will help them sell
More virtual console games
I would think your 3DS
Would be the ideal controller for this system
If they really want to
Have that synergy
Like remember back in the day
Remember
The Advance had the link cable to the GameCube
We needed it for Animal Crossing
To do the island
There were 3 games that used it
Animal Crossing, the Pacman
Versus, and Zelda
Sonic Adventure 2 and the Sonic
Advance games
The Chao trading
And then you can do weird things like unlock original Metroid
But I don't consider that a full feature
That's just, you know
Quick tangent about the Wii real quick
It's hooked up now at your place
For the first time in like 16 months
Yes I did, I hooked up the Wii for the first time in 16 months
And what did I play on it?
I think Super Metroid, we also hooked up the Super Nintendo
I found my bonafide Super Nintendo
And we were playing Mortal Kombat
Like the real Mortal Kombat
That was kind of cool
I'm a little distracted right now
I don't want to call this breaking news or whatever
But I just have to throw this out here because I know Dark Sakura
Is going to be interested in this
And Mikolatov, if you're listening, which I know you are, you need to post his link in chat
Because he's showing me graphics from Phantasy Star
Online 2
Yeah, my friend Krista posted those images today
I guess more information came out on this
I have not seen this at all
Technically she posted them yesterday from Japan
There's more information on 4gamer.net
Yeah
This looks like Universe
Kind of
Like in high def and these cool little screens
I miss Phantasy Star Online
I do too
And there was just something missing in Phantasy Star Universe
So I hope Sega has figured it out
Who am I kidding?
I'm going to get that game when it comes out
I'm not even going to lie
Oh, Ziba reminded me
Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles 2
For the Game Boy Advance controller
That's right
I guess there were a few, not just one or two games
And Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles
Was a pretty cool game too
And those were all games
That very few people ever really got to experience
Because the setup for it was so damn expensive
But yeah, the Crystal Chronicles
Thing was so cool
Alright
Anyhow, one other rumor
About the new Nintendo system
Supposedly, Nintendo is
Trying to make nice nice with Rockstar
Trying to get them to develop for the Wii 2
And
This is a report
From, what is this, Zero One Net
Which I think is also Go Nintendo
I don't know, it's all over the internet somewhere
Saying that Rockstar
Apparently is
Being courted for Grand Theft Auto 5
To release in, well
2012 is supposed to be when Grand Theft Auto 5 comes out
And Nintendo is supposedly courting them
To release the game on
This new Nintendo system as well
Which really, it makes sense
And it's not like Rockstar hates Nintendo
Rockstar put out that mediocre
Grand Theft Auto game on the DS
Remember, the Chinatown Wars or whatever
So it would not be unheard of
For Rockstar to develop for the Nintendo console
But I think if Nintendo wanted to be serious
About the whole, hey
We're going back for the hardcore gamer
This year
Maybe that'll be Reggie Zangle when he takes the E3 stage
We've made a gaming console for everybody
We've made a gaming console
For those that want to play their Wii games on HD
We've made a gaming console for kids
We've made a gaming console for the hardcore gamer
You want proof?
We're getting Grand Theft Auto 5
Bet you never thought you'd hear me saying that
You know that's not going to happen
Well, he won't say it like that
Oh, I think Grand Theft Auto 5, if the rumors are true
About that
This is as easy to develop for us
With the Xbox 360 and so forth
They have that synergy because of the hardware
That both systems are using
I think this is absolutely true
But
I think this is also part of fanboy wank
It kind of blurs the line
I think it's obvious fanboy wank
You know how sometimes sites
Will report on things that are kind of obvious
I think this falls in that category
To be honest
You know what, I kind of wish
That more companies would do
One of the things that made the Dreamcast
Easy to develop on
Is the fact that it would build in a Windows CE
Environment
And every time a Dreamcast game would load
That was built in Windows CE
It installed the newest version of Windows CE
And then played the game
So you always had
Your system OS tailored
To the game that you were playing
Alright, again, going to our chat room
At chat.orangeloungeradio.com
Is where you want to be
Orangeloungeradio.com and click on chat
Or on the Game Surge Network
On channel Orangelounge
Is where you want to be, that's our official chat room
Some comments there
Saying San in our chat room says
Chinatown Wars was not mediocre
From what I've heard, I'm just going off Loki
Who's like the biggest gramp, that's auto addict I know, sorry
DDR Dollar Bill
Says Chinatown Wars was just too dark
To play, and Randy in our chat room
Says Niko Bellic and Nex Super
Smash Brothers
Now that
That could be an interesting set of talks
You know what, going with
The fanboy wank and this whole thing
You know, obviously the Zelda game will be
One of the games that has a hybrid thing
Going on with the next console, but
If they really want me to just lose my
Shit on whatever this new console is
How about that new F-Zero game already?
Huh?
Now that you're going to be all high def and stuff
Give me a new F-Zero game, why not?
I know seriously
The original F-Zero was a launch title for Super Nintendo
So it's not unheard of that F-Zero could be a launch title
Oh yeah
F-Zero and Pilotwings in Mario World
Were the original launch titles
I remember because I wanted them all
So there you go
Well how about something else that was on the SNES
How about it?
And we've already mentioned Final Fantasy
But Final Fantasy 6, which was released in the US
Initially as Final Fantasy 3
It is coming
Out on Virtual Console and
PlayStation Network
So it is
Going to be there available to play
And I don't
However see a date attached to this
In fact
I am trying to see if there's a date on the
Article and it does not
The release date is soon
Yeah it's soon
But it is also going to have
The full motion video
That came with
The PlayStation
Updates with the Chronicles
Oh it's like the opera scene and
The Kefka's Tower and a few others
Hopefully it won't have the shitty loading
Times
If it's going to be playing on PlayStation Network
It's probably going to be something you're downloading
So you won't have to worry about that
If it's all off the hard drive then the load time
Should be minimal
Depending on the emulator, I don't know
We've also put Flickr in here
Yeah, no
I've already got 50 million copies of this
Plus the original, so
Yeah I've got
A ROM, the cart, and then
The GBA
Port
I will probably still buy it
I will still buy it because I'm a consumer whore
And how?
And Final Fantasy 6
Is so fucking good
It's
So good
That was the game
When I was like 17, 18 years old
Now I told you about how I
Stayed home from school for a week
To play it
By telling everyone I had the flu
Final Fantasy 7
People hate on Final Fantasy 7
Because it's not more
Final Fantasy 6
Let's be honest, people didn't like the 3D thing
And people didn't like the whole Neo
7 was a great game
It was, but people hate on it because it wasn't
More of 6
7 was rushed by Sony
So it wasn't really even done
But yeah, I really wish that
5 and 6 got the DS
3D treatment that 3 and 4 did
Because those remakes were so good
But I guess on the 3DS the same thing could happen
Oh yeah, oh yeah, absolutely
Going to our chatroom at chat.orangelaunchready.com
Lots of
People perking up at the idea
Of F-Zero on the new Nintendo console
Being possible launch title
BlackWolf says F-Zero yes
I agree with F-Zero, Mieleki F-Zero
Mieleki F-Zero
Oh no, I'm sorry, Mieleki F-Zero was from Flaming Toilet
In our chatroom
BlackWolf continued up saying
F-Zero GX equals most beautiful GameCube game
Absolutely
You could put that game in the Wii
And you would not even be able to tell
It's a game from last gen
F-Zero GX is so good
It's like my favorite racing game
I think almost ever
Let's see
Kaijuto, not much of a fan
Of F-Zero, people love that F-Zero
I never liked it, it was too fast for me
My friend tried to top trade it off to me
And I hate it, well I'm talking about the first
F-Zero, that's the only one I saw and knew of
It made me sick, never liked it
See that's what I liked about F-Zero, was that it was fast
It's like
I don't know, it's like
When I first saw the commercials for
Blur and everything, I kind of thought it was
Going to be like F-Zero with real cars
I just don't think anything
Is going to be quite like F-Zero, but F-Zero
If that makes any sense
It's just such an awesome racing game
Rama in our chat room says
People hate On7 because it's the most popular
Hoard out and overplayed in the fandoms
Yeah
That's part of it too
Alright, moving on with some more gaming news
SalaciousPop, what do you got for us?
Microsoft has registered a patent
For networked and
Personalized Kinect profiles
So that
People can get
The Kinect to remember their own
Unique mannerisms
And how to interact with the device
And also
That profile would follow you
If you ever went to a different
Xbox and imported your
It would be attached to your
Gamertag, is what I'm trying to say
And you can also use it to communicate
Possibly to other
XBLA users that may not speak
English
Or be able to communicate verbally
So they might get some
I don't know, like sign language
Stuff in there, but
Like a universal sign language type of thing?
That's kind of weird
When I was trying to use the Kinect
You know, you lift your hand up and you move it
Over the tile that you want and you have to hold it there
And you wait for the ring to spin around the hand icon
I wanted to like
Punch it
To the tile I wanted and I would go like this
And then you were like, no, just hold your hand still
And
I think if I could go and say
I don't like how the Kinect wants me to do
This particular
Command, here's how I want to do it
And have it save that and follow my profile around
I think that's what this patent is for
That'd be really cool
Interesting, but then they throw in this whole
Phones and computers into it and I'm like
What, the phones are going to have Kinect in them?
I hardly think so
The profile comes in somehow
I guess Kinect isn't just about
The motions
But voice as well
So maybe the voice will activate your profile on the phone
Seems a little strange
Yeah
Anyhow
Well I guess we'll see what comes to that
That could be something that Microsoft's planning on unveiling at E3
We'll see
Something else we might find out more on very soon
Is what is to come of this
Online survey that EA is doing
As you know, surveys are a popular
Breeding ground for rumors
And this time it's about EA Sports
Apparently EA Sports is investigating
The reception to a paid subscription
That would deliver paid
Downloadable content for free
And make some full versions of upcoming games
Available to download before the release date
So it's like you could join the club
And then you get to break the
Excuse me, the embargo on games or something
Kind of sounds a little bit like Playstation Plus
But unique to EA or something, I don't know
Some of the bullet points
That were mentioned in the survey
Discounts on all downloadable content
For participating EA Sports console based
Titles
Let's see
That's the kind of stuff they're talking about asking
Also
Of course you can get the game on Playstation
Network or Xbox Live before it even
Comes out
That could be indicative of digital distribution
And kind of moving more towards that mechanism
So you would be able to
Bypass the store and buy the game
From EA directly so they could keep all the
Profits
That apparently is
The intent here, but you have to pay to join the club
To do that, you get to pay to join this club
So you can pay EA directly
And get the game early
That's what I'm reading out
Of this, right?
It's kind of what it is
So, hmm
We'll see, also one other thing that they're talking
About, the ability to transfer
Paid content from your current participating
Titles to future title versions
So, like, if you buy
$50 worth of extra
Golf courses in Tiger Woods 12
You would get to transport them to future
Games, which a lot of other game series
Are already doing for free
Like DJ Hero did that, right?
You had the downloadable thing that would
Unlock, oh, anyway
You know, launch day DLC
The ability to turn left, five bucks
Launch day DLC, the ability to turn right
Five bucks
That's where I'm worried, but it's a racing game
So you only need to go forward
You don't have to get left and right if you don't want to
That's the one thing that excites me about what's
Going on with Sony right now, which I know sounds really
Messed up, but if it does come out
That your personal data was put at risk
Digital distribution just got set back
Four years, guaranteed
If that comes out
Yeah, but then I think of Steam, and I
Think not really, but
I think
Yes and no, but
On the console level, yes
I don't know, Steam
Steam is really just a store
Where PSN and XBLA is more of an
Integrated
Matching process
They're still stores, but they're stores that are built into your console
It's a little different, whereas the PC
Isn't so much a console
You have the freedom to do whatever you want on the PC
Yeah, and there are alternatives to Steam
For the PC, it's the same platform
Right
So we will see what comes of
This possible paid subscription
In the future, moving on
Well, since we were on Steam and this is how
I bought the game
Super Meat Boy Ultra
Edition will be coming out in the UK
Sometime between July and September
This year
It will be published by Lace Mamba
Global
And it's going to be an actual boxed
Edition
That is going to be coming
Out, so it will have a 40 page
Booklet that has never before
Seen art, and some behind the scenes
Information, an extended version of
Team Meat comics, and
The soundtrack, and additional audio
And a mini poster
Yay, a poster
And
Then you also get a slab of rotted meat
And a band-aid
And you get a meat dress
You get a meat dress
Ok, maybe not
Maybe they have that as a marketing thing
Little bandages, Super Meat Boy Band-Aids
See, that would be a good idea to have bandage girl
Band-Aids
Absolutely
Copyright, Jamie, Orange Old Radio
Pay, pay, pay
Anyhow, let's move on
And travel the world with some release dates
And see what games are coming out to a store near you
It's going to be hard to top last week
But we'll see what happens
SlicesPop, why don't you start us off with what is coming out
This week in America
We didn't have a
Show last week, there are a few other titles
Aside from MK
And Portal that came out
And that was SoCom 4
Was another big one for last week
Nobody gets to play it right now
Yeah, totally
And then Final Fantasy 4, the complete collection
On PSP
Huge week for games, huge
This week upcoming is
Pretty sparse
Considering people's
Wallets can't really take more
Gonzo weeks of
Game releases like last week
So this one is pretty mellow
We have Operation Flashpoint
Red River on PS3 and
Haunted for PC
Operation Flashpoint
Red River again on PC
Darkspore on PC
And
IL-2
I cannot even pronounce this
Stramovic Cliffs of Dover on PC
Which sounds like a weird budget
Army game, I don't even know what that is
But that's it, it's like six titles
Bobby Blackwolf in our chatroom is lamenting
The non-mention of Conduit 2
Which also came out this last week
This was
Oh there it is, yeah, on the week
And poor little Conduit 2 is gonna get that a lot
This was not
A smart week to release that game
Sorry dudes, I don't know what else to say
I think some
Companies severely underestimated
The power of portal combat
On top of like SOCOM too
SOCOM is a huge game too
I actually think it was a dumb week to release
Final Fantasy 4 too
Especially considering that
The PSP does a lot through digital distribution
Now, well, nobody can buy that game
On the Playstation Network
Right now
Yikes. Let's go to Japan
And see if it's any different over there
This week in Japan on April 28th
El Shaddai, Ascension of the Metatron
Coming out on the Xbox 360
This game
Is coming out from Ignition
It's kind of an action based game
Kind of looking at some of the screenshots here
It looks kind of cool, looks like
The art style to this is kind of interesting
It kind of looks like that
Oh, what was that game?
I don't know, now I can't even remember the name of it
But yeah, it has this really unique art style
Reminds me of an old PC game
Alone in the Dark, is that what it's called?
I can't remember that. Let me see
It was a classic game of the week she did not that long ago
But I don't know why, the art style kind of reminds me of that a little bit
But yeah, it's kind of an action game
Maybe in the same vein as like Bayonetta
Type of thing where you play a dude with a sword
That is really pretty, I'm really big on it
Again, that's El Shaddai, Ascension of the Metatron
Comes out this week on the Xbox 360
Very biblically themed
Also this week on the Xbox 360 in Japan
Espagluta 2, Black Label
Platinum Collection
Espagluta
Price Reduction
That's bullet hell, right?
PlayStation 3 also gets El Shaddai this week
That's pretty much the only big release over there
On the PlayStation 3
On the Nintendo Wii this week, nothing
You're going to hear that a lot when it comes to the Nintendo Wii
Because there's nothing coming out
On the Nintendo 3DS, Deca Sporta
3D Sports comes out
That of course is Deca Sports
From Hudson in Japan
Coming out on the regular DS
Hakoyuki, Yugi Roku DS
Comes out this week
On the Nintendo DS non-3D
That's an adventure game
With little chibi characters that I'm sure
Most people don't care about
Because it's so last gen
And then lastly, the Sony PSP
Has a variety of games coming out this week in Japan
Including Patapon 3, which I believe came out over here as well
Saigo no Yakuzoku no Monogatari
Comes out as well this week
That is from Epic
That is a Japanese RPG
On the PSP
Looks like kind of
Man vs. Robot type of thing
And lastly
Otome wa Onesama no
I'm sorry, Ni Koi Shitiru
Portable 2
Jin no Elder comes out this week
As well and that is
One more adventure game on the PSP in Japan
And this is the one that features
Pretty Girls
And it looks like you play four Pretty Girls
Going on these quests
They're like looking through telescopes and dressing up
It's like the Spice Girls get their own RPG
Look at that
In Japan. How about Europe?
We have a few things for Europe
On the
26th is Mythos
And the 27th is Outland
And the 28th is Darkspore
Shin Megami Tensei Persona 3
Portable
Also on the 29th is Thor the video game
And
Virtua Tennis 4
That's it
Yay Virtua Tennis
Let's move on with another story
From Salacious Pot. The classic game of the week
Is coming up in just a little bit. Stay tuned
Okay so
As of the
16th which would have been I guess last
Weekend
The Wii console has experienced a price drop
Best Buy got to do it first
For about a day
Before everyone else
$170
And then every other major retailer
Started selling it at that
Price I think within 48 hours
Later so yeah that as of the
18th you can get a Wii kit for
170 bucks and also
Just more recently announced
Wii Sports Resort
And Wii Party which are the two
I guess they're bundle titles that you can also
Buy separately. Also got a
More of the staple titles
Of the current Wii lineup
If you just can't get enough Woohoo Island
Yeah
Those prices dropped
$10 down to
$39.99
Per title starting the
25th which is tomorrow
So Wii console cheaper
And the two staple games
If you didn't get them bundled
Are now $10 off as well
Now I just want to point this out because this is something you're
Not really reading in the news but you know
Loki has ties when it comes to
Selling things and he made this little note
In our little thread where we always talk
About what stories we're going to talk about on the show
And so I'm going to pass this little tidbit along
Do with it what you will. He says
Just the top five direct
Nintendo retailers. Not
All retailers. This is a
Temporary price drop to clear
Overstock inventory
I wonder why they'd want to
Move Wiis
Well I mean one
Could hypothesize that the new Nintendo console
Plays into this but come on
That's going to be a year away
Although I
I don't know. Part of me wants to say why would you
Announce a console at E3 when it's not going to come out
Till next year but that's exactly what they did with the 3DS
So that kind of refutes that
But I would think they would try to get it
Something out console wise this year
But we'll see. I don't know
I don't know what this price drop should be tried into
Maybe a new bundle. Maybe that's the
Route they're going to go. Maybe they're clearing
Overstock so they can do some Uber Wii bundle
That's going to come out for the holidays
In these two games like I just said
If you buy them all a cart you can also
Get a bundle with them
So they're just
Kind of taking up space now
There's got to be some type of Uber Wii coming out
Towards the end of the year
Is it called the Wii Wii?
None
Alright
Something you will not be able to play
On the Wii but you'll be able to play it on
The Xbox 360 and eventually
You'll be able to play it on the PlayStation 3
But news came out this week that Child of Eden
From Q Entertainment has been pushed
Back to September on the
PlayStation 3. The game is still
Coming out on June 14th for the
Xbox 360 with Kinect support
So why was it pushed back to September?
Well they haven't really
Said but they have said that it
Will now feature move support for the
PlayStation so perhaps that is the reason
Why it was pushed back was to include the
PlayStation Move support
I don't know why they bothered
They should have just patched that in later because
I kind of think the PlayStation Move
Is anyone still all about
PlayStation Move right now?
I mean one could argue is anyone about Kinect right now?
But I think there's at least a few people
Still dabbling in Dance Central
Once in a while at least
But as far as the move goes isn't everyone over that?
Well maybe Ubisoft was like
Yeah Sony so your network
Has been down for five days so we're
Gonna give you some time to fix that
Well to be fair September no I'm kidding
I think this news came out before that I know I'm just being an ass
Yeah no I know
Alright well let's move on
To a segment we like to do on the show every
Week it's a chance for Dark Soccer to take
A trip down memory lane
And visit
Classic Games from Gaming's Past
It's the classic game of
The week segment and Dark Soccer
Is gonna dive into the vault head first and
Find a game that she says hey
You little brats
This is a classic game you should check out right
Freaking now Dark Soccer
What is the classic game of the week?
The game of the week is called
Narbacular Drop
And this is a game I have brought up before
I see what you're doing here
Exactly I figured with Portal 2 coming out
It's best to get to the root
Alright let's listen to some of the ambience
From Narbacular Drop
Yeah
Hopefully
There wasn't a lot of sound in this game I believe
But it had some decent music
Well
At any rate Narbacular Drop is
The precursor to
Portal it was
A free game online in 2005
For the PC ran in DirectX 9
And it was
The senior game project of students
Going to DigiPen
They actually named it Narbacular Drop
Because Narbacular is not really a word
And so it would help the thing be found
On search engines really easily
So basically
The whole premise is that
There was a princess
No knees
As in no dash K-N-E-E-S
Who is unable to jump
She was captured by a demon and imprisoned
So she found out that since
The prison is actually a
Ascension creature named Wally
And has a portal making ability she could
Escape through using portals
So basically
It has the whole first person
Shooter vibe like Quake
But it has the portals in there too
You have to solve different puzzles
You can definitely see where this led to
Portal
So you create the different interconnected portals
You can actually shoot portals through portals as well
Which was very interesting
It really helped
But you'd have boxes and boulders
And things to avoid
You have different switches to do
That you can't save in the game
And it really
Is very complex
You only have about six puzzles
In that because
Again, this was a senior project
But it's super
It's super good, it's actually pretty
Pretty fun
And so basically
The group that developed it
Was snatched right up
By Valve and said
We like this idea, make us portal
And they're like, okay
Sure, we'd like to do that
And uh
So they did
It's actually
You can actually go get this for free
It is online
It will run on just about any
PC and it's
Nothing great to look at, it looks like
You know
Sprightly like Quake
Like early Quake and Doom and Hexen
Well I mean, it is 3D
But it's 3D with sprite
Textures. And I think something is important to mention too
It looks nothing like Portal. No, it looks nothing
Like Portal. It does not have that test chamber look
It looks more like a medieval castle type of look
And I think that's one very common misconception
About Immaculate Drop, is that it looks like Portal
It really doesn't. No, it's
It's set, you're a princess escaping
From a dungeon, trapped by
A demon, so
The story is different
However, the premise is the same
You have to use your portals
Solve puzzles and get out, while not being
You know, jumped on by creatures
And falling in the lava
And having GLaDOS, wait, wrong game
Right
So, it's, it's, I've gotten Immaculate Drop
I've gotten a few puzzles through it
And honestly, it's a little bit harder
For me to get through, because early 3D
Like that kind of
It gives me a headache
If that makes sense
Like, I can do all the sprite based 3D
Like games just fine, but if it's
Actual 3D with the sprite based textures
Then it makes me kind of sick
But, um, it's, it's still
A fun little game, I mean, it's free
Why not? And
I've got it attached to, well I mean you can't
Download it through Steam, but I have it attached to my
Steam account, so, I just launch it
Through that, but, it's, it's a
A fun little game, it really is
It's just
It's a small download
It's really
Simple, it's just simple and fine
That's all, and so if you want to see the origins
Of Portal, you should definitely try
Immaculate Drop
With the little, horribly drawn
Story bits at the beginning
It's really neat to see, too
Like, how freaking far this game
Evolved, too, like it just, it
You go play Immaculate Drop, it's, it's
Really nothing like Portal
This is six years ago
But it's, I mean, it's cool, don't get me wrong
It's a cool little game, but it's, uh
And the whole point is that
The other reason why it was only six
Levels is because, number one, it was
A final project, but number two, they were trying to
Demonstrate that they could establish these physics
Within a virtual environment that would
Work, so
I want to say that the original
Way that this was done was by
Completely duplicating and re-rendering
The room when you threw the Portal
But now, with Portal 2,
It's just, not with Portal 2, but
With the actual Portal, they redid
Those, um, those
Physics to where it actually would just
Respawn you through a particular point
I remember, um
There's a
Something about this on the Portal
Commentary, where they were
Talking about the difference in, um
Programming and what went into
You know, what they changed
From Immaculate Drop to Portal
And how certain things wouldn't carry over
And how certain things had to carry over
So, it's pretty neat
Alright, and Valve is one of the few
Major studios that are known
To do it quite often
To, um, hire
Employees from the community
Whether it be the Phantom community or to just
Go to the studio that made Immaculate Drop and just
Say, um, we want to
You know, buy your shop and
Bring you in for this project, and
It's clearly smart, and honestly
I think that it's for
The best for a lot of companies to really
Look toward the new generation coming out and they
Give the new people a chance
Because
With so few
New ideas
This is my thought
People are going to eventually run out of new ideas
There's not going to be anything new anymore
People are going to think of it all
So you need to get a fresh source of
Information instead of, you know, people
Who are maybe a few years stale
So I think it's a great idea
Alright
They totally get kudos
There it is, your classic game of the week, an Arbacular Drop
A little bit newer of a game, but certainly
With all the brouhaha about
Portal 2 this week, it's important to know the roots
Of such a landmark game
I would seriously like
At least five of our listeners
To download it and send me an email
What you think of it
And it's super free, right?
You can download it all over the place
Alright
There it is, and that's usually your classic games of the week
Are like obscure fucking Sega titles
That'll cost you $100 on eBay
This one is free
It's in Space Fantasy Zone
You can download that online
Alright, there it is, your classic game of the week
We're going to take a break here live, folks
We've got plenty more show to come
It's been a pretty busy week, we've got to talk about Mega Man Legends 3
There was some news on that this week
Talk about, yet again, Guitar Hero
Rob, before I forget
I am posting the download link in the chatroom
Alright, so go download it ASAP
And let Dark Soccer know your thoughts
Especially if you haven't played before
Alright, we're going to take a quick break, guys
We'll be back, though, plenty more of Orange Lounge Radio
Lots of emails tonight, too, speaking of wanting emails
I was looking at the email bag earlier
It has built up over the past couple weeks, yay
So we get lots of voices tonight
And phone calls coming up before the night is over
So stay tuned, guys
On this Easter Sunday, episode 410 of Orange Lounge Radio
We'll be right back after this
Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio
We are live on this Sunday evening
April the 24th of 2011
With the 410th episode of our show
And, uh, yeah
We've been talking about a lot of news tonight
There's been a lot of gaming
Big games that came out in the last week
And, of course, a lot of news to go with that
We've got plenty more to cover, though
But first, we'll do some plugs for our side projects
Some of the other shows that we work on
On the side, Dark Sakura, what do you do?
You have another little show
Well, when we do it
We have Comic Insanity
Have you been off a couple weeks or something?
We've been off for a few weeks because of, you know
Stuff going on this week, last week, and the week before
So, um
But it's what I do with
Mar and Marvel, Tiara, and Dan Shadow
And we typically
Have a new podcast up every Tuesday
At infamous.net
N-F-A-M-O-U-S.net
And you can also follow us on Twitter
At Comic Insanity
So check us out
And we'll see you next week
Bye people!
But not always on
It's been a hectic month, you know
And besides that, now next month, finals
Yikes
Well, we've
We're still doing the side project I've got going on
With Extrovert
The best little Horde house in Azeroth
Also known as Horde house for short
If you like World of Warcraft
Or even if you hate it, but you just enjoy
Extrovert talking about his Wang
And everything
And yeah, we were off last week inadvertently
We had Comcast go down 30 minutes into the show
So we had like a jumbo episode
This week, so it's like two hours of wow talk
This week, that's a lot of wow
Definitely a lot of wow
Alright, let's get into some rapid fire news
Some quick news stories
That we wanted to bring up at some point on tonight's show
Loki's gonna start us off
Oh wait, he's not here
Bob's gonna start us off
Well, when you sit in the chair
Yeah
Bob's gonna start us off cause Loki has the night off
Okay, so here's a
Feel good human interest story
That's gonna make you go aww
Skip it
A gamer
Who goes by the name of Ben
I don't know if that's his handle or his real name
Started dating
A nice young lady
And eventually at some point during the relationship
When they were hitting it off
He gave her the gamer talk
If we don't have plans, I'm gonna be parked in front of the TV
For hours playing my games
And you need to be okay with that
And her response was
You play Borderlands, right? Fire it up
So, yeah
So the two of them played all through
Borderlands
And all of the DLC
And I guess Ben went to Gearbox
And told him this lovely
Story of gamer romance
And said that he was going to propose to her
And Gearbox
Made a video
Called Borderlands modest proposal
Which you can find on YouTube
Where they have their sassy
Rude
Profanity dropping
Mascot
Claptrap, he does a
Wedding proposal
Marriage proposal video
For this fan
It took him about a week to make it
It addresses her by name
So Ben was like, hey I want you to look
You know
Help them get to know each other
And then they got divorced in three months
No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding
See, it's called a Borderlands modest proposal
The YouTube channel is
Taco Bell manager
Yeah
Sorry, this is really funny
Gearbox helped this loving
I hope you like Borderlands and I hope you like
Gorditas
Because you're going to get a lot of that
And I haven't had a chance
To watch, it's about a minute and a half
And I guess they got their writers to put in some jokes
Yeah, so
Took them a week to do that?
Lord, game companies work slow
Alright, I'm just kidding, I'm kidding
Okay, so then
They got paid in 39 cent tacos
Next we have a story about
YouTube video sensation
Freddy Wong
And I look through his channel and I don't recognize
Stuff, but
He put out a character
I guess he's a computer animator
And he does a lot of, you know
YouTube mini movies
And he put out a character called
Mr. Toots
Mr. Toots is a tiny
Knee high unicorn
And this here, it's half
It's half live action, half CGI
And Freddy Wong
Finds Mr. Toots in a cardboard box
Out on the street, and Mr. Toots
Is a little knee high unicorn that
Shoots rainbows out of its ass
So those of you that are in
Robot unicorn attack
Are just rainbow unicorn
Fandom hilariousness
Oh, I love rainbow unicorns
This is that guy that did that
Portal video
The portal gun delivery
I'm looking at the video here
So here's the, he lifts up the box
And there's the little
I'm like two seconds behind you
Creepy looking unicorn
Aw, there's the unicorn
Hey, looks like we got a car coming
So let's get out of the road, huh?
My favorite is the dude exploding in like the
Mortal Kombat blood all over it
The skeleton
So this is gaming related
Because it turns out that Mr. Toots
Has been copyrighted and registered
To Volition Inc
The developer behind
THQ's Red Faction
And Saints Row series
So whether the character came first
And the THQ snatched it up
Or he was commissioned for this little dude
Um, we're like
What on earth
Is this, is Volition gonna do with this character?
This guy actually
Borrowed the model
He credits him in the end of the video
Borrowed the model from somebody
So it could be like some cross promotion
And see I love this joke in our chatroom from Randy
Cause somebody had to make this joke
chat.orangestonshoot.com
Mr. Toots and the pink anus
Remember the magical unicorn game on Steam with the
Pink anus
A-E-N-U-S that you buy as a material
Yeah, lots of anus going on in this game
Oh yeah, so it does look like
That Mr. Toots came from THQ first
And then this Freddie Wong guy
Did the promotional thing for it
You know what's funny about the anus?
What? Everything's funny about anus
I always get it confused with this candy
In Japan called A-S-S-E
I guess it's A-SE or A-S-ER
Uh huh, but it looks like ass
When you get it out of the box
Mmm, tastes like ass
So yeah
The biggest part of this story is just the whole
What factor and the fact that it's from
Volition, so where are they gonna
Drop this dude? Maybe he'll be
A playable character in Saints Row 3
You know, you're running
You're on drug missions and instead of
Getting an Uzi you're just shooting rainbows out of your ass
At people, I don't know
Ass
Thank you to our soccer for derailing the show with ass
And my last
Quickfire story is even though
Activision has pulled the plug on the
XYZ
Hero franchises
With guitar or DJ
It looks like DJ Hero 2 is getting
At least one more
DLC pack, not sure if it's the last
But it's still getting content
And it's a UltraMix pack by
I'm blanking
I just had it up here
Deadmau5, sorry
Deadmau5 is putting out a
Three song
Track pack for DJ Hero 2
House Music by Benny Benassi
Sophie Needs a Ladder by Deadmau5
And We Speak No Americano
By YolandaBeCool and
DCUP
CUP
Womp womp
You're gross
Anything else?
That's it for me
Let's go to the other music game that comes up once in a while
On this program, it used to come up a lot on this program
BeatMania 2DX
Is having its 19th
Version being tested
It's called Linkle
Not sure what that's supposed to mean
It's L-I-N-C-L-E, Linkle
It kinda looks like Uncle
But with the U kinda, I think it'll be a better name
BeatMania 2DX 19, Uncle
Uncle! Make it stop
These songs don't sound the same
What was 17 and 18? It was like Duchess, Empress
One was Empress, you got it
Empress was one, and then the other one was Sirius
But not like the radio, it's the
Constellation in the sky
So this one is Linkle
And I don't know, it kinda has like a sci-fi
Theme going on, whatever
Some of the new games, or some of the new songs
That are coming out in it, I don't, I don't even recognize
These bands anymore, like I used to be so into
This series. Sota Fujimori
I remember him with a song called Lucky Days
Let's see, Chorus K,
Drive Me Crazy
I remember
Dark Tetsuya was saying something in the
Thread about a song called F
Or something like that
From like, you know, just like, oh there it is
DJ Amuro doing F
He did the song A
Now he's moved on to other letters of the alphabet
So we get a song called F
Some of the other things that are coming to
2DX 19th style, as I will forever call it
A light blue theme
Apparently in the game
Song previews have been added
For normal gameplay mode, that's pretty cool
So you can actually hear what the song sounds like
Finally, 19 games later
Let's see, a hard EX
Option added
It is even harder than hard
That's a direct quote, harder than hard
And some songs, unfortunately
Have been removed from the game
Because, you know, they have to delete
Old songs to make room for the new ones
Luckily, because I don't follow the series anymore
I don't recognize any of these songs that they've removed
But there you go, Beat Media 2DX
Linkle. Now, I would care about
Beat Media 2DX again if they would put out the home versions
Because, especially if they came out on PlayStation 3
Yeah, PlayStation 3
Because it's not region coded
And you have your controllers that we
Packed, and I want to play those
We're already getting Tingle things in the chat room
By the way
Tingle and Linkle? Nice
You know, Tingle
If Tingle and Link had a baby
It would be Linkle
BlackWolf in our chat room says
2DX lives on where Guitar Hero dies
Well, in Japan anyway
But you don't really see anything about it here
They should have an insane 4 controller
Version where you use your toes
Beat Media 2DX was a lot of fun
It really was, I just, I don't know
Bring back the Effector Pedal
Like, two arcades have it anymore
You know, Arcade Infinity is gone
You can go to, what, Sunnyvale Golf Line
Or Milpitas? One of the two still has it
And they got rid of ours
That's one arcade in the Bay Area
They probably have the one that RVGL got rid of
Maybe
That's so stupid, they didn't get rid of 2DX
Dr. Suya says they deleted Power Dream
I did like that song
You know what, we just need to
Have a Bimani party
No, we don't
Unless you're going to kick it like it's, you know
2002 all over again
Well, after three songs
And we're all covered in sweat because we're not in the shape
That we used to be in doing 9 footer songs
No, and that's just from playing 2DX
Nice
Alright, some other things
An Xbox exclusive
Mortal Kombat fighter was discussed
According to Ed Boon
Saying, quote, unfortunately the circumstances
Didn't allow us to make a 360 exclusive
Character. I'm not allowed to talk
Too much about it, but I can tell you we certainly
Wanted to do an exclusive for 360
But that's all I can say
And unfortunately that's leaving everybody to
Try and guess, what could the
Character have been?
Well, I can't really think of that many
Iconic, Microsoft licensed
Only characters they have
Because Kratos obviously is a Sony only
Property, he's very recognizable
One of the Gears of War dudes
Marcus Fenix
Master Chief, which would be kind of dumb
In that universe, because at least Kratos has got
The whole medieval and the blades
Right, how about that chick from
Cameo, what's she doing these days?
That could have been the character
She's playing Uno with the Kameo
Uno pack, that's it
Or a nondescript dude from Fable
I think probably what Microsoft had a problem
With was the fatalities
And it's, you know, to have your character
Die a horrible death
Is something that's
Hard for some people
God of War already had the rendered
Guts and the eviscerations and the titties
For no reason, so Kratos is at home
In Mortal Kombat
Microsoft doesn't really have
A character like that, unless chat can think
Of one that we're forgetting
Unless, you know, I don't see them
Splitting Master Chief in half
And his little midsection
It's gross, some of those fatalities are gross
Which, by the way, I am gonna try and get that video
Of my mom playing Mortal Kombat, just so you know
Working on that
I told her about the project today
She's like, what?
So I don't know what character it could have possibly been
I mean, if it had been Marcus Fenix or something
I think the problem would have been with the fatalities
That's why they had to change up DC Universe
But, I mean, it's one thing
To do it for a single Xbox character
It's another to change the game for
DC Universe, I mean, that's why they
Or, I'm sorry, THE DC Universe
I'm gonna be confused with the game DC Universe
You know what I mean, though
One other quick thing I want to say
It's about the 3DS Ocarina of Time
We all know that game is coming out on the 3DS
That's another big thing they're gonna pimp for this holiday season
There's gonna be a new feature in the game
Called the Boss Challenge Mode
It's an all fighting mode
You go up against any of the bosses you've encountered on the main quest
You can take on the bosses individually
Or all at once in a continuous battle
That's all we know
One little unlock feature that'll be in the game
Is an extra mode
Kinda sounds a little silly to me
But I guess whatever extra crap they can throw in there
To make it seem worth it again
They will do, so we'll see
DarkSakura, you got a few stories for us?
I have a few
Konami Style, which is notable for often having
Pretty expensive stuff up there
Remember the arcade style 2DX
And pop and music controllers?
Well, they have a
$380 Pyramid Head
Sculpture now
Tomopop
Is basically saying this is the only
Officially licensed Pyramid Head
To date
The actual price is
31,500 yen
Or about 382 bucks
And it's a pretty sick looking figure
I gotta say
He's all wearing his
Skin
Outfit with the big
Pyramid on his head
And the great knife
Is actually specifically Silent Hill
Homecoming
So it looks pretty cool, and I'm gonna show
Our chat room what it looks like
None of you get to see hahahahaha
There you go
Chat room
Can I jump in with some comments real quick
About Mortal Kombat specifically
Some ideas from the chat room
About who that missing Mortal Kombat character
Could have been
Randy suggests Larry Erb
Come on, it's not supposed to be real people
Let's see
Defective Candy suggests Clippy
The Microsoft Help character
I like that idea
And then Black Wolf says
That the Wii character
Could have been Woohoo Island
Could have been the character in the game
Because imagine how that fatality would have worked
The fatality would have been you would have had to run
Like in Wii Fit
I don't know
Imagine Mario and Luigi in a Mortal Kombat game now
Where they take a monkey wrench and just
Show it through someone's throat
All these angry parents writing letters
Like I just, I love it
I don't know
Sorry Jamie, I just had to get that out there
I love the Clippy one too much
That's a good idea for a character
Microsoft Bob
Awesome figure, awesome figure is awesome
And
In Portal 2, the little
Egg shaped turrets have an easter egg
I have not heard this
So I'm going to have to check it out
Myself later, but it's on YouTube
You guys can check it out
Should I be bringing this up here?
Um, if you like
I'll go read the next story while you do that
I got it, I got it, I got it
What, this is a little song they sing?
What is this?
It looks like around level 16
Trying to see if I recognize this level
Let me skip ahead a little bit
The turrets serenading you
Is an event that happens later in the game
I remember seeing this part
In one of the levels
Where the turrets were like unreachable
This part looks familiar to me
But I don't remember them singing like this
Weird
Alright, anyway
It would be funny if
When you're doing the defective turrets
If you could get one that sings instead of the
I'm a turret, huh
Turret
All of the lethal functioning turrets are female
But the incompetent dunce turrets are male
But there's
Well, and the same goes with Wheatley
Yeah
But I've noticed that
Actually something that they pointed out in the first Portal
Is that there's so much
Female oriented
Stuff in the game like
Bring your daughter to work day
And GLaDOS being female
And the main character being female
So they're just keeping up with that theme
Yeah, go Pawa
It's like the Silent Hill movie
Before they added the needless character
Sean Bean
So
More Portal 2 information
Is actually for PC and Mac
On Steam there are some
Fixed patch that will
Fix unrecoverable black screen
In the elevator save
Fixed infinite loop on
Mac OS X server
Fixed Mac OS X font rendering
And glyph corruption
Fixed GC memory leak various location
Content improvements
Support for English subtitles and Turkish builds
Because people in Turkey love their Portal
Minor string interface glitches
Fixes for multiple crashes
Improved detection handling
Various errors and or crashes
Activated UI to enable joystick in game
That's pretty cool
However it
Did get a 10 out of 10
From Eurogamer so
I think it's pretty sweet
It's sick
And that's it
Nice
I was gonna say part of the reason
That they had to give the
Turkish language support
That Hakan from Street Fighter 4 threatened
To kick their ass if they didn't add that
He was gonna threaten to oil himself up and send nude photos
Yes he was gonna oil himself up and send
Nude pictures if that didn't happen
Let's go to the Twitter
Get some Twitter topics, actually shit I forgot to ask
For them so we may not have anything on Twitter
But let's see what happens if I go to the Twitter
Twitter.com slash OLR and let's see what happens
When Rob forgets to request these things
Let's see if we got anything anyway
Let's see, logging into Twitter
Clearly I'm prepared for this
Segment tonight, Twitter.com slash OLR
Oh we do, oh we do have some tweets
Look at this, uh let's see
Redertainment says
On Twitter, given her biting
Yet funny insults
How do you think GLaDOS would deliver a
Yomana joke, I think he meant to say
Yo mama, but he typed Yomana
Which is actually really funny, I don't know why
It would be this, your mother is dead
Yeah
That's very good
I like that, I like that
There's a joke in there, alright
SSJ100Matt is on
Twitter saying
Hey it's Easter, what ever happened to Pete
Jousting, also what's your
favorite totally not kosher for
Passover Easter candy
Oh good question
Waffles
I couldn't have waffles
I wanted waffles so bad
What ever happened to
Pete Jousting, actually I was trying to explain
Pete Jousting to my mother this morning
Right, remember I was explaining
You brought it up
Yeah there's a very
Like
You're either
Someone that doesn't mind peeps or will eat them
Or you think they're the most vile
Fucking candy on the base of the earth
Yeah so we
Brought up peeps at this
Easter breakfast and
Rob's mom and I think
Aunt
You say the two relatives were like
Peeps
Like cousin in law
So they were going through their whole
Peeps are gross rant and we mentioned
Peep Jousting
That was after my cousin's son
Who's 9 years old was threatening to
Look up the show on the internet so God I hope
He didn't find it
So you need to turn it off
Your mother's gonna
Mother's gonna kick your butt
I'm surprised that there wasn't
More bacon at the
Event
Let's not get into that
But yeah Peep Jousting I don't know
I haven't done Peep Jousting in a long time
What about the other part of the question
What's your favorite totally not kosher for passover
Easter candy
The problem with that is that
Candy would be okay as long as it's not
Made with flour
You know like something with a crust
Pocky
Yeah you could have Pocky
But I don't really think of Pocky as
Easter
My favorite Easter candy
Would be jelly beans that aren't
Jelly belly like and I can only
Really eat them around Easter because
I can't eat them everyday
You don't like the gelatin stuff
Anyway you can't really eat that stuff but I like
Regular jelly beans especially the black ones
That are just pure licorice
Barf black licorice barf
Barf
I'll pick the black ones out of whatever
You can't have milk chocolate while you're
Having fried chicken
But I can really only eat them at Easter time
I can't eat them other time of the year
Jelly belly is the rest of the year
Is all I can eat
Now I'm imagining chocolate covered
Chicken and that would just be gross
Go to any state fair in the south
Well you're from the south you know
It would be chocolate covered chicken deep fried
In like bacon fat
Ew
Alright we got some other uh
Oh I will tell you one thing
My friend made bacon brownies
I see that
I told her that when all this is over
She used to make me some turkey bacon brownies
Uh what about you? So I just popped
Favorite Easter candy?
Uh the Reese's peanut butter cup eggs
Just cause it's just a big flat
Peanut butter cup and those are amazing
You know what I don't like are cream eggs
Gross
People worship those things but they are too
Much they are too much
The mini they have those mini
Cream eggs now those I can eat
Touch of Britain sells Mars eggs
Marzipan?
No Mars bars eggs
And they also have um these uh
Dark chocolate truffle eggs
Cause there are all kind of cream eggs
Sold you know in England and these
Are just they're all Cadbury
The ones that they carry they also have the um
The
Galaxy ones
They sell those too and the arrow ones
They're all puffed air chocolate eggs
So good anyway I need to go get my
Mars egg let me get some more tweets
Flaming toilet is tweeting us
Upgrading to a new swim swim
A new slim PlayStation 3
And tired of waiting for PSN to come
Back is it okay to do
Data transfer utility or do I
Risk losing data?
I don't know I have no idea
Data transfer between his old
System and his new one? That's what I'm assuming
Okay uh like kind of like a license
Transfer I'm assuming like what you do on 360
I've never had to do that before uh
I wouldn't risk it like honestly
Right now not a good time to try that cause it
Depending on when
His slim was
Manufactured and put on the shelves
He's probably a few OS
Updates behind and that
Once he actually gets the slim
Online it's like oh we need to update you to
Point six I don't know what number they're on
And that might invalidate his certificates
So just wait
Good point yeah you're gonna have to wait it out sorry
Uh and let's see
One more tweet from TigerCloth305
On Twitter says it's a tweet
The DS Lite is going to be discontinued
Uh yeah that was some news
That was circulating this week is that the DS Lite
Is no more and he's linking
Us to a story on oneup.com
That apparently references a NeoGaf post
Where there is documents going out
Uh Nintendo is not offering
Any comment on this right now
But I guess some of the older DS's are
Being discontinued which makes sense I mean
Well I think every person
In the developed world
Has one
Including their pets
Like my cat has a DS Lite I'm kidding
But no I think yeah that's
They're pretty um
Prevalent
Yeah and they're not getting
Rid of the DSi or the
DS XL that's important to know
And I still want one of those too but yeah
So there's no why why not just get the 3DS
I don't know those screens are big
It's well the 3DS is backwards compatible
With the regular DS right
But not the advanced games
So you like must play Game Boy advanced games
Well they haven't had the GBA port on the DS
In a while oh that's right they got rid of
That with the DSi yeah so I guess that's the
One thing you're losing with the DS Lite
No more Game Boy advanced games
So there you go
Let's see one more tweet
Tigerclaw got in one more and why not
I'll go ahead and read this one
Chrono Trigger apparently is
Also coming out so I guess this is in the same
Vain as the Final Fantasy 6 thing we heard about earlier
Apparently Chrono Trigger for the
PlayStation 3 and PSP
Was outed by an ESRB listing
So this is probably just right in that
Up the same alley as Final Fantasy 6
Because Chrono Trigger was released for the
PlayStation 1
Yeah so this is yeah the
What was that called was it the Final Fantasy
Chronicles that had Chrono Trigger in it?
Chronicles yeah the other one was the Anthology
Yeah so um
It's probably just obviously a port of that
Because that's already been out on Sony the
DS port with the extra
Dungeon and the endings and stuff
Is probably still the better
Chrono Trigger
Release that you'd want to
Get rather than this one but
Give us a legit Chrono Trigger sequel already
Like I know there's Chrono Cross but I mean
Seriously how long ago was that?
Damn Square
Everybody loses their shit
Over that game and yet we still don't have
Like something in that canon
It's weird one of the reasons why I still
Want a DS XL is because
Chrono Trigger
Port on the DS
I can see it fine it's not like I'm blind but
Just those sprites I want them on a bigger screen
So fair enough
Alright let's move on with some more
Gaming news and then we're gonna get to your
Phone calls before too long and emails
We have lots of emails tonight can't wait to do that
Dark Soccer's gotta work tonight
Yay alright
Slaces pop more news
So after that
A couple weeks ago we
Announced that the Mega Man
Project that Capcom was working on
Was scrapped but they're still
From what we understand working on Mega Man
Legends 3 that has a huge
Fandom that really wants that game to come out
The Capcom
Has announced that they are putting out
A Mega Man Legends 3
Prototype version which is
Sort of a beta
Slash demo it's
I'm not sure if it's gonna have a full
Start to finish or it's a separate episode
That may not necessarily be in the full release of the game
But it's just
What they have compiled that runs
Well they're gonna put it out
For the 3DS
And on their eShop
It's supposed to hit in late May
And there's a playable
Character named Barrett
And it offers a few missions
Not to be confused with the first person ever to
Say shit in Final Fantasy
Just so you know
So you play as Barrett and it's gonna have a few missions
Though it's probably gonna be spammed
With loading screen messages
That just say this is not a finished product
This is a game in progress any bugs blah blah blah
So yeah we're gonna get
Something for Legends 3
But yet you're gonna have to pay for it right?
Let's see
Quickly let me throw this out here
It's going on the eShop
Let me throw this out here to a little follow up to that
Is that you know I guess Capcom isn't
Really sold on this whole thing
So they are saying that we need
Interest we need participation
From fans or this game could be axed
At any second like for some reason
I'm just reminded of like when Tinkerbell
Is dying clap if you want
To save me just clap clap louder
Clap louder and say I believe in fairies
I believe in fairies that's that's literally what
Capcom is saying you need to clap
And say I believe in Mega Man
I believe in Mega Man and then give us your money
Is basically what they're saying so
They have come out and said in a blog post
On Capcom Unity Masakazu
Eguchi the director of the game
Said the prototype version that's coming out
On the 3DS is based
On the prototype that they made
To prove to Capcom that the game could
Happen the heat and excitement surrounding
This downloadable title would determine
Whether or not the full game could be greenlit
If hype is strong the full title
Will be a go if not
It's a no go
Clap clap I'm dying
I believe in fairies I believe
This doesn't mention if there's
Going to be MSRP
Extra Mega Man costume $2
So if you want
Legends 3 if this thing
Costs money and it's basically a glorified
Beta that's kind of lame
Yeah pick it up
They're tracking heavily the response to this
So now not only do we have pay to unlock
Content but we have pay demos
Pay to finish developing
You want us to fix those
Clipping issues or you know
The game crashes if you try to
Walk backwards you know
Slip a little
Like a 20 we'll figure it out
Alright
Well I guess to be fair the
Gran Turismo 5 prologue
Was kind of the same thing
It kind of sounds like where this is going except we always knew
There would be a Gran Turismo 5 eventually
Although was Bobby ever
Convinced that Gran Turismo 5 came out?
I'm not sure hopefully he's in chat and can let us know
Anyway a follow up to a story from a couple weeks ago
I remember when there was that awesome Streets of Rage
Remake that they've been like making for like 8
Years and they put it out on the internet and we were
Talking about it how like hey they finally get
To put out the Streets of Rage remake you remember that
Dark Sakura? Yeah
Dark Sakura updated graphics well guess how long that
Lasted? 5 seconds
That's right the link
Was taken down of course
Now that it's out on the internet it's not that hard to
Find but the official link was taken down
And after some proking and prodding they did
Admit Sega has contacted
Regarding the download hosted on this site
While this issue is being resolved
Please do not upload the game for others to download
Right any links posted on
This site will be removed thank you
Now apparently they were kind of
Asked well didn't you like try to get this cleared with
Sega or what's going on?
Bomberlink who's the project leader on the progress
Said they did contact Sega
I would like to say this is a quote from him
I would like to say that we did actually
Contact Sega last year through an email message
Regarding the use of copyrighted material
To which they answered asking us to send
A formal letter to their legal department
So that's what we did we accepted the ESA
Policies regarding the DMCA as well
Otherwise this website would not exist
Anymore
There you go
They had to take it down cause Sega didn't like it
Eight years that thing was in the making
And you know Sega is just trying to really
Utilize that Streets of Rage license
Right now it's a big IP for them
A part of you know trademark
Law is you have to pursue
Every infraction against
Your brand even if you're not doing anything
With it or else you could lose
The trademark to be fair
Because I'm sure someone in chat will bring it up
They have released the Streets of Rage 2
Something on the iPhone, iPad
So they are still trying to cash in on
Genesis nostalgia as they have for the past
15 years on various
You know consoles and Streets of Rage was in that
Awesome like the best Genesis nostalgia
Of them all that Sonic Omega collection
Thing that was on PS3 that's super
Cheap and Xbox
So yeah this isn't unfortunate to hear because
The community obviously really cares about it
And have to take eight years to put this out
But the fact that they were C&D'd is
Sort of I know seems like a duh
But do we mention
About the whole Sega building in San Francisco
Now belongs to Zynga
We did bring that up on the show huh
Speaking of sad stories
Sad sad stories
I didn't know Zynga owned
Words With Friends now either
Zynga's the
I stopped playing Words With Friends you know why
Because everybody wants to fucking play Words With Friends
And then it's like my phone keeps going off
Every two seconds
Your move with Dark Sakura
Random people you didn't know right
Were trying to start new games with you
Fuck Words With Friends
It's a terrible game
Yeah I said it
Get a Scrabble board you'll have more fun
Then you can yell at somebody in person
It's much more satisfying
Rather than Words With Friends play out
Everybody fucking cheats at Words With Friends anyway
You know there's an app that you can actually buy
One of my managers at work was showing me
How to do this by the way
A screenshot of the screen from Words With Friends
And then upload it to this other app
And it just cheats
When I was playing a lot of Yahoo
Literati
There was a JavaScript
Website that was in Anagram Finder
Where you would put in your
Yahoo Literati URL and it would say
Oh here's your word
You're a cheater?
You are a cheater?
You cheated on Yahoo Literati?
You're going to hell
I can however say that
I have not cheated at Scrabulous
I miss Scrabulous
What's Scrabulous?
Scrabulous became Lexulous because
Scrabble or whatever
Is that on Facebook?
Ah fuck that game too
Well I don't play it on Facebook
But I used to play it when it was Scrabulous
And it had Scrabble Solitaire
Now it's like it makes you play with people
And I hate that because Scrabble Solitaire is super fun
Where basically you just play until you're out of words
That's your score
Are there any fun Facebook games right now?
I've been going in and deleting
Just about all of my apps
There's seriously nothing I play on Facebook
I got sick of Knights of the Clicky
I'm sure I have like 4 trillion blood points in Vampire Wars
That I haven't touched in 3 years
Knights of the Clicky haven't touched in 2 and a half, 3 months
I deleted it
I've deleted almost all of my games
I want to play the Civ game
That was the only thing I was interested in
Does that come out? I don't even remember
And then there's some
Supposedly, and it's a story that didn't make our show roll tonight
But some music game is out on Facebook too
That I need to check out for next week
Something that was posted in our thread
About like a Facebook game, but I wanted to actually play it
Before bringing it up on the show
But apparently there's that too
So, alright
Cassandra in our chat room says
Scrabulous sounds like a Decepticon name
I like that
Alright, let's move on
DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
Well, there is
An Activision memo that was linked
That says there is no
Appetite for Guitar Hero
Aww
It actually was saying is that
But there is an appetite for destruction
And there's also an
Aperitif for destruction
If you like, lounge against the machine
Anyway
Basically
The whole thing that they're saying is that
Yeah, right now it's dead
But it should
Eventually come back up
They're asking
The CEO Eric
Hirschberg said
Why are we walking away from Guitar Hero
Instead of just trying to reinvent it
And that basically it's because
There are so many
High quality games that are just
Saturating the market
Wasn't this what we were saying before?
Is that the market was just way too saturated?
Well, they're like, oh, duh
That's what we were doing wrong
So
They're sort of
Setting it aside for now
In fact, it actually says that they are
Perhaps after a cooling period
We will revisit the franchise with fresh innovation
They're gonna wait for people to go
Remember when Guitar Hero was cool
And then Activision will be right there
To say, hey, we still own the rights to this
Hey, there's a whole new Guitar Hero game for you to play
Haha
It's retro Guitar Hero
Meanwhile, Rock Band's like, we've been out here and we're still cool
Hi, we're still cool
Hi, we're really cool
We've attached
The clarinet attachment
Although I do, I even feel like the Rock Band
Thing has really died down
It's really died down
It's kinda sad
We were just playing the other day
The cousins were over when we were playing
SSJ100 Matt in our chat room says
Notice how no one ever asked these questions when
DDR died, in Konami that is
Well, technically DDR is
Still not dead
I mean, they are still cranking out those games
Like, wow, there's an Xbox 360
One coming out, the port of the
PlayStation 3 one is coming on the Xbox
360 and you guys, it uses the
Xbox Live Vision camera
That's how hip Konami is
The little webcam
Not the Kinect, but the little
AOL-looking thing
We'll use that, apparently
I hope to God for Konami's
Sake, the Kinect will stand in
For that, because the Kinect's
Basically a camera too, but
I think the 360 only has the
One I.O. USB port in the back
For goodies, so you'd have to
Unplug your Kinect to plug in the little webcam
That's not gonna happen
And if seriously
It only works with that little camera
And it doesn't work with Kinect, then everyone point and laugh
At Konami
Anyhow
Oh yeah, Guitar Hero, yeah
Well, someday it'll come out
It's being cryogenically frozen for a later date
So that they can bust it out in the future
To save humanity
It's next to Walt Disney's head
Alright
Moving on, so let's just pop
There was a story that we reported
On a few weeks ago about
Ratings tampering on the
Indie marketplace on the
XBLA
And some indie games
That had anywhere from three to five star reviews
Were getting hundreds
Of one star reviews
Within a short amount of time that was throwing
Their game listing
And their rankings down
Into the toilet so they weren't getting as much
Exposure as they would otherwise
If they had their four star review
So, Microsoft decided
To come up with a fix to this
And they have decided that
In order to
Rate an indie game, you need to
Have a gold account, which means you are
Paying Microsoft
For the Xbox Gold
Live services, if you are a free or
Silver member, you cannot give
A rating to a game
An indie game
That's good, because it was probably a bunch of
Sock-free accounts that were doing this anyway
This story that I looked up
Also references a previous story
When the manipulation was first discovered
About a
Firm that had posted
To a contractor
Job site
Basically saying, we need someone
That can write a script that will generate
5,000 free silver
Accounts
They were looking for a coder that's like, can we run this
Overnight and just get the username spit out to us
Doesn't necessarily say
Why they wanted those 5,000
Accounts or if it's even related to
This
Rating manipulation, but just as a coincidence
There are firms out there that are like
We want
Wow, if I was Microsoft
I would be bringing the smackdown
On these firms for abusing their network
Yeah, I guess it was a
Graphic design firm contract
Script for 5,000 Xbox Live
Silver accounts
Again, don't know for sure, but the fact that
The interest for that is there
Microsoft's like, if you have a free account
You don't get to rate on indie games
Which, I guess, makes sense
That sucks that you have to pay, but it will
If you have a
Gold account, they can take action
Against you, they can ban your credit
Card, they can ban your account
You lose your gamer tag, you lose your achievement points
Why didn't they just
Make it so you have to actually play the game for 10 minutes
To rate? I mean, is that
So hard? I don't know
I guess that's hard to do
It's easy to build something to shut it off after 4 minutes
Oh, demo over 4 minutes, clank, buy
Or get out
Can you buy indie games a la carte with a silver or do you need gold
In order to even buy stuff on there
You can buy a la carte with silver
Yeah, I don't see why they would shove
It's money, why would you shut off a money maker?
I'm pretty sure
So, uh, and Randy
In our chatroom at chat.orangetonsrated.com
Agrees with me, they should make it so that you have to
Actually play a game for a set amount of time to rate it
That way people have to go out of their way to be jerks
At the same time, though, what's
To stop somebody from building a script that signs
In 5000 Xbox Live users into
A game? I mean, it's possible
A botting thing could do it
Sad but true, somebody would figure it out
Yeah, I
I agree that you should
Be able to
Have to play the game before you can rate it
But at the same time
If I play a demo that is so
Bad
And I want to be able to warn people
That this demo was horrible
Like that maze with balloons?
Yeah, I'm not gonna
Pay the 300 space bucks
I think people should
Download maze with balloons
Just to see how freaking bad it is
It is like an old, you know what
Maze with balloons reminds me of?
An old CD-ROM game from when that technology
First came out and people were like
Let's put softcore porn out
And try to make a game out of it
I'm thinking of the slumber party game
That that one girl was in from the
Night Trap
Yeah, it's like that
Exactly
Alright, anyhow
Let's move on to one other story
And I've kind of brought this up before
So this is a bit of a duh
But Super Mario 3DS, of course it is going to be
Announced at E3
Well, I mean, I guess it was announced
Quote-unquote at Game Developers Conference
But we're gonna get the official details
I guess you could say at E3
Apparently, though, according to an interview with
Edge, Miyamoto has leaked out a few details
On this
It's gonna have a combination of Super Mario Galaxy
And Super Mario 64
Two games that's still completely original
Perhaps that's because of the tanooki
Or the raccoon suit, which we haven't seen in any
Of those other games
That could be part of it as well
Or maybe it'll just be kind of a mechanic about the story
Of the game or how it all kind of plays together
Maybe instead of, I would like to see this
In a Mario game, maybe I'm just, maybe a pipe dream
But a bump
But instead of all these broken up worlds
What about one massive world?
I'd like to see a Mario game like that
Yeah, like a sandbox Mario game
That'd be awesome, actually
Imagine if the warp zones actually took you
Places to other parts of this one giant world
Instead of a heavily fragmented
You know, now you're on Bee Planet
Now you're on Candy Planet
I think that there should be, you know, things you have to do
To unlock different areas
Sure, just like any good Metroidvania
Type of game
You have to get an item to get behind the door
I would like to see that in a Mario game
That would be pretty awesome
That would be very awesome, we'll see what happens
Let's see, Redertainment in our chatroom
I want to read this comment too, speaking of the whole demos
And down ranking, chat.orangetownsradio.com
Is of course where our chatroom is
Redertainment says, if you want to warn people that a demo
Sucks, I'm sure you have a Twitter account
You can bitch on that reaches more people
Than that downloaded that indie title
And Randy says that Grand Theft Mario reminds him
Of something that happened in Robot Chicken
I haven't seen
Every episode of Robot Chicken, so I guess that went over my head
Oops, I did see
The Final Fantasy VII fast food
That was great
Alright, let's get to the emails
Every week you guys send us emails
At mailbag.orangetownsradio.com
The mailbag has been rather thin the past few weeks
So I'm really happy that this week you guys
Have fucking blown it up
Dark Soccer is going to work tonight
Well, we got a request
From
Ronnie
For an autograph
With an address, this is a five year listener
So I figured I was going to find
A postcard that I have
And we could just sign it and then put it in an envelope and send it
So I have one that says Juicyful
And it's orange
Either that or I was going to use the congratulations on your Bar Mitzvah
Card
That I got at the dollar store
For any upcoming Bar Mitzvah
Because there's a lot of kids
And I was like, no I better save that for an actual
Bar Mitzvah
So yeah, I set this aside
And we'll get everyone to sign it
So I mean, SalaciousPop I'm sure
Would not, his autograph would not
Go unappreciated, but I'm sure somebody wants
A complete trifecta of official OLR hosts
Yeah, so
I just need to make sure that
I mark the right one
Yeah, don't click delete
I'm not deleting it
There, it's this one, so I will
Do unread, there we go
And moving forward
This is from
Holly D. Hey guys
I swear your email was the above
But I recently heard you say mailbag at OrangeLaundryRadio.com
Is the Gmail
One an old email or something?
I don't know, do we have a Gmail?
Do we have a Gmail? If we do
What's the
Sender's name? Holly
Is that the Holly that writes it to Hordhouse?
Oh, it's probably the same Holly from Hordhouse
That is a Gmail account
Yeah, that is a Gmail account
The email for Hordhouse is
HordhousePodcast at Gmail.com
OrangeLaundryRadio is mailbag at OrangeLaundryRadio.com
I want to see if
Maybe somebody's swiped it
I don't know, let me look
So anywho, just wanted to confirm because I sent a couple of emails
And I thought it was weird that Sucker kept saying you only had one or two emails
Maybe other people are confused like me
Thanks
Yeah, it's
You sent it to the right one now
So it's mailbag at OrangeLaundryRadio.com
Okay, hey
OLR crew
AZHP here
So if anyone at OLR has played the PS2 game
Shin Megami Tensei Persona 4
But I wanted to share
The gaming related project that I've decided to take upon myself
Persona 4 takes place in the year 2011
From April 11th through the rest of the year
That being the case, I've taken it upon myself
To tweet the events of Persona 4
Roughly as they happen
It's just a very deep game with lots of relationships
Drama, mystery
And just lots of things to do in general
And I'll try to make it as interesting and funny
To follow along with as possible
The Twitter account is
NarukamiU
That's N-A-R-U-K-M-I-Y-U
NarukamiU being the name of
Being, let me start over
NarukamiU being the name
That the people developing the new Persona 4
Anime have given the originally nameless
Main character
I'm not looking to become some sort of D-list-y
Celebrity by doing this
But I do want people who would be appreciated
In this sort of project to know about it
If you spread the word on your show
I would be deeply honored
Again the Twitter account is at NarukamiU
Also happy birthday DarkSarka, thank you
Your birthday is just a few days before mine
And mine is the day before Wendell's
So yours was yesterday, well happy birthday
Keep up the great work
And thanks so much for helping me spread the word
AZHP, and also a very big happy birthday
To Mr. Wendell, thank you for reminding me to say so
Cause Wendell is one of our old school buddies
Happy birthday all y'all
And glad you got that plug worked out
He's old
I just wanted to follow up
It does look like there is an Orange Lounge Radio
Email account at Gmail
It is not us
I sent a password reset thing
So if it is one of us we'll get the email
But it's not in my email, it's not in my Orange Lounge Radio
It's not in the mailbag email
Somebody else could have signed up trying to impersonate us
I certainly suppose that's possible
Loki could have it too
He might have done that for the YouTube channel or something
But that's very possible
So one of us will have the reset email if it's ours
But as far as we know right now, we don't own it
I've got about six different emails and none of them are
And we don't write from that address
So if you do get something from OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Forward it to the official email of Orange Lounge Radio
Which is mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
So we can investigate
And other than that, we're probably going to have to send a notice
For them to strike it
It could be Loki
Loki could have done with the YouTube channel
So we'll have to ask him next week
Thanks for letting us know
Greetings, O.L.R. This week was torture without your podcast
Don't ever take another week off again
Even if Rob and Jamie have to go somewhere
I'll suck it up and just listen to Loki eat chicken
And complain about Nintendo for three hours
Which is exactly what it would be
Peace and chicken grease serious turtle
He's a very serious turtle
Seriously, you're not allowed to leave
Long email is long
I just want to point out
A lot of your favorite shows take all summer off
We take one week off every three months or so
I think it's okay if we miss four shows a year
We need a vacation sometimes
That's right
It felt really good to not have a show last week
I love doing the show
Don't get me wrong, but it was kind of nice to have Sunday night
To do something else
Usually when I take Sunday off
If it's not for family stuff
It's for doing something else for the show
I've gone to gaming conventions
And stuff called in and reported on it
And sometimes, honestly, I wish I was here instead of there
But, you know
Because this is my house
Okay
Hi, OLR, this is from Spazznator, by the way
I'm pretty sure that the three of you have covered the story
About PSN going down this week due to hackers
In part A of this week's show
So I won't bother rehashing the details
Rather, I'd like to do a Loki-style rant about it, if I may
While I'm not pissed at Sony
Hell, from what I can tell
They did what they needed to do
I am, however, extremely pissed off
Okay, dude, it's not hackers, okay
But I will read your rant, anyway
I am, however, EXTREMELY
PISSED OFF
At these fucktards that hacked PSN
Despite Sony not explicitly saying
Who it was that did it
I'm 100,000% sure
It was these anonymous dickwads that did it
After all, as the old saying goes
If it walks like a duck and quacks like a duck
It must be a duck
Who the holy hell are they to do this
What the fuck gives them the right?
They're a small minority
Have other consoles to play online with
Yes, there are single player games as well
But that's besides the point
There are games such as
Mags, SOCOM, Confrontation Free Realms, DCUO, etc
That are multiplayer only
As well as a few Capcom titles
I.e. Final Fight Double Impact
And Bionic Commando Rearm 2
That require one to be logged into PSN to play
Hence, right now, they're unplayable
Many of those titles I play on a regular basis
And tend to love
Just over the fact that, for the time being
I can't access the PSN video store
To get either the freebies
And or paid content
And the three of you know how much I love that store
Hell, as is, I will never shut up about it
At any rate
When Sony finds these torps
And they will, it's just a matter of time
I hope they get the legal system on their punk asses
Like white on motherfucking rice
And, as Samuel Jackson so eloquently put it
Gets Medivial on their asses
May the hackers burn in a nuclear fire
Than drown an ocean of piss and acid
Slash end rants
It actually did exhales
But I exhaled
This rant is brought to you by one really pissed off PSN user
That wants to lay the smack down on some punks
By the way, your anger may be a little misdirected
Wait until it's resolved
An official word comes out
I kind of agree
With what you're saying, can I read this real quick from Bobby
In our chatroom too? DarkSakura
Yeah, I kept telling him it wasn't anonymous and he told me I was wrong
He told me it didn't matter what the truth was
I was going to blame Anon
See, Anon was very proud
To take credit for that first Sony attack
And that's the problem
Is that now that this is happening, I mean
This could be happening from somebody who's trying to get at Anonymous
For all we know
But Anonymous flat out said
We understand that this tactic
Only hurts the people we're trying to protect
We are not going to do it anymore
But
But because Anonymous has no leader
You know, it's not like
WikiLeaks who has that, whatever his name is
They've got a group that's
But there's no clear leader out there
And that's what's causing them
To look bad is because it could be
A subset that's doing it
Regardless
I don't think this is Anonymous
I think they may benefit from the notoriety
But
I don't think this is Anonymous
They flat out said
No, this is counter productive
To what we're trying to do
So don't
Don't look for a scapegoat, wait until they actually
Officially say what's going on, because I have a feeling
That it's actually one of those situations
Where, like, okay, at my work
We got an email out that said
This number of
People are affected
Because a laptop was stolen
Who hacked
The
Site that does all the
Email campaigns?
That happened about, what, two, three weeks ago
Do you remember the salacious pop? You read a lot of internet news
Somebody hacked, it wasn't Anonymous
It was somebody else hacked some
Spam, no, not spam, I'm sorry
They do, like, the email campaigns for all these various
Websites, and all
These websites that use this email
Service to maintain their mailing list and so forth had to
Write people, because I got some from a couple
Companies saying
Your personal information may have been breached
Your email and so forth, because we
Got hacked. Oh, are you talking about
The Gawker network, Kotaku?
No, but there's that too
So that wasn't Anonymous either
That wasn't Anonymous either. Somebody's out there
Hacking for personal information
Because maybe somebody in chat will, I'll ring a bell
Somebody hacked Gawker
Somebody hacked this email network to get
All the emails and so forth
I think it's them
That's getting Sony. I think somebody went after
That private information, it's Sony
So, yeah, and this is
What I have to say to you, is that
When
When you have a situation like this
Where, yeah, you may have an easy person
To place blame on
Keep in mind that
Wars have been started
Over people putting the blame where there was
On an innocent party, just because
Of quote, circumstantial evidence
Don't be one of those people
Don't be a dick like that
And also, with the DDS
DDoS attack
You know, you've got hundreds or thousands of computers
That have been compromised in some way
You're flooding the network with garbage
It's very hard, because you've got all of these compromised
Computers of just regular
PC owners
It's hard to
As obnoxious as it is
It's very difficult
It's not an actionable crime, is what I'm trying to say
Because the computers are compromised
If you're hacking into something
And you're getting customer information
Which hasn't been confirmed yet
That's like a federal, that's serious
And that's not their MO
That's totally not their MO
Keep in mind, all of the stuff that they've
Been doing is basically forms
Of vigilantism
They have gone after people who
They have perceived have committed
Some sort of crime that's
Not being punished in the proper way
And they are going after these people to make their lives
Miserable
Yeah, they'll waste some of your time and some of your money
And then that's it, they'll get their plan across
But when they've gone after people's information
It's been specific people
To have a specific thing happen
I've got to read some of these comments in chat, they're piling up here
In the true Easter spirit
Redertainment says, the Jews did it
Happy Easter
Fuck that
And fuck you
DefectiveCandy in our chatroom says
The Epsilon email hacking was supposedly
Accomplished by one rogue individual
Thank you, it's Epsilon
Could be a former employee
That's true
SSJ100Matt says
Blaming everything on 4chan
I thought that was anonymous
That's the home of anonymous
So there you go
I like what Cogito said
I don't think Sony was a hack at all
Someone lost the keys to the big Sony computer and they can't all get in
Check the crayon boxes
Get that leash out
There's like a cat that unplugged the thing
Meow
I'm in your Sony hack in your store
But seriously
Look at everything
Don't pick one convenient scapegoat
That's just
That's not very smart
Next email
Yay, happy sunshine
Unicorns that shit rainbows that kill people
Yay
Dear peoples
We're peoples
Oh, it's Redertainment
Like you, I've been following the recent PSN outages
Since I started popping up on Wednesday night
When I first discovered these outages
I was frustrated
Raged out and cursed to the love my neighbors thought I was killing someone
Not kidding
Anyway, in the process of following the story
I found the story that I'm sure you covered
Earlier on the show
Uh
Let me see what this is
I think that's just
Yeah, it's the same story we covered basically
From another source
Once I read the story, I became considerably less angry
As I can understand that Sony taking actions like this
In response to this threat to a point
However, there is one part of the story that really concerns me
This is
In order to
Verify the smooth and secure operation
Of the services Sony pulled the plug
On both services April 20th
This sentence gives me an impression that this isn't
A simple hacking job
Given Sony's recent movements in relation to piracy
I believe that this may be the nature of Sony
Taking down PSN
I believe someone figured out how to pirate games
Distributed digitally
Oh, this is a good idea
Distributed digitally via PSN
If any of these conclusions are wrong
Also, why do I have to go through PSN
Or live to access Hulu Plus or Netflix
I mean, when I want to watch Hulu
On my laptop, all I have to do is fire up my browser
Go through my ISP
To get to what I want to watch
I don't have to go through my laptop's manufacturer
Exclusive network to access things
So I don't have to do it on home consoles
Because they're evil
Stay black, redertainment
This message has been brought to you by the successor to Anonymous
Who was actually responsible for PSN
I wrote it down and it's totally unknown to the public
Nyanya
Sent from my iPad
Actually, we do have a theory in the chat room
On who might be to blame
For all of this that's going on on the PlayStation network
An interesting theory
We need to know
Play Canada
All their beady little eyes
Clap their heads and roll their lives
Play Canada
We need to form a full assault
Yep, it's all Canada's fault
Actually, we should blame SkyNet
We did survive Judgment Day
We did
In response to that email about why you have to authenticate
With the console before you can use Netflix and Hulu
For Netflix and Hulu
To allow a third party appliance
To run their service
There needs to be some sort of accountability
So that someone doesn't get an $8 Netflix account
Give their username and password to their 40 friends
That have a PlayStation 3
And have them all
Running Netflix off the one account
So I think
By authenticating into PSN
It's saying
This PSN account with this
PlayStation 3 ID is using this Netflix
And there's a sync there
And that's why they do it
However, it does not stop people from sharing Netflix accounts over the internet
Black Wolf says that Netflix will still work
You just gotta keep trying to log in
Three to five times, you can get in eventually
I haven't tried on PS3
I've just been
Playing Portal
Offline
Addict
Like it's a bad thing to be addicted to Portal
You can get down with that one
Totally
Okay
Hey OLR, I hope the move went well for you Rob
While you were busy with that, I was busy playing Portal 2
That game has some of the best writing in anything, period
Me too, Salacious Pop, unpack that box
I'm gonna play Portal
Let alone video games
It certainly puts out
What's out there to shame
For some reason I thought of you Rob when I saw this article
Okay, I have to look at this
Uh oh
It's still loading
There's gonna be huge spoilers
And you're gonna freak out
Kagura director thought of Nintendo 3DS
3D brushed 30 seconds later
Hey man
There's a guy who did
Half minute hero
I'm telling you
Didn't I talk about that on the show
In the 3DS we were talking about
They just need a game that's boobs, boobs and more boobs
Boobs in 3D, big boobs
Little boobs, black boobs, white boobs
All boobs, big
Boobs with big nips
Boobs with small nips, all types
United Nations of boobs
Coming soon on the 3DS
I don't know if you've ever heard of this before
But for the last few years there's been a convention
Dedicated to the world's favorite hedgehog
Held in London, Summer of Sonic
They usually have early previews
Of coming games and occasionally
Panels slash Q&As with developers
As well as writers for the old UK comic
And I hear this year for the US comics too
This year's is on July 25th if anyone's interested
I would love to go
Somebody get me to Europe
Hear you later, Catastrophic Moggy
P.S. I'm really excited
About the announcement of the Persona 4 anime
P.P.S. Hey Jamie, have you seen
The new episode of Doctor Who yet?
Every time someone does the colon P
I do, yes I saw it
And it was amazing
And then I was really pissed off at the end
And then I saw the preview for the next episode
So I wasn't just pissed off
I actually did pause it one time and go
That is bullshit!
And then kept watching
As I understand
I'm not the only person that did that
Do I do that when I watch TV?
Yell back at the TV?
I downloaded it
Sometimes when I watch Survivor
I go, oh no he didn't!
That's about as bad as I get
You talk during WoW when something bad happens
I do talk during WoW
Thank god Ventrilo
Isn't always on, let's just say that much
Why do you think I don't log into Ventrilo
That often?
Because Dan is usually sitting right where you're sitting Alan
Looking over at me like
You really, really get
Dirty mouth when you play this game
I was like, bitches
So yeah
And sometimes
Rob will sign into Vent and just be like
Oh, hey what's going on?
And I'll be sitting right next to him and I'm like, I'm fine
I'm reading, oh no they didn't
He's like, I'm on Vent, duh
I don't know your life
Yeah
Alright, is that it for emails?
That is it
We need more emails for next week
We need to beat the emails we had this week
I want Dark Soccer's email bag to take like an hour next week
Mailbag?
Hey, if this happens, okay if we get
If we break 10 emails
Next week, you have to get me tacos
I'm gonna get you tacos?
Fine
We get more than 10 emails next week
Not all from the same address
Unique, real emails
That are at least a paragraph in length
And with good grammar
3-4 sentences with proper grammar
Rob will buy me tacos
Or pink berry
Taco flavored pink berry
They're gonna be from emails
Like, you know, ShermyCat
Or this is totally not Dan
Hey mom, I pooped in the kitchen again
Love your cat
Number one Dan fan at Gmail
You should have Dan on more often
P.S. Bart
We should get like a taco tote board
And like show how many emails we've got during the week
And then be like, let's see if Jamie's gonna get tacos
Oh, we're at seven emails
So far this week
No taco for Jamie
Can we install that on the website?
The taco meter
Taco Tuesday is an official holiday
Every week
Black Wolf says, can I write a paragraph about how tasty the tacos would be?
Yes, you can
I will accept emails about tacos
Cause tacos are amazing
Or, you know, you can also do it about taco
Which is octopus
I love takoyaki
Or you could write a dissertation about the 80s song
Putting on the Ritz by Taco
No
It has to be video game related
Delicious, crispy taco related
Or tostadas I take those too
For fuck's sake, can we move on to another topic?
Taco
Okay
Alright, if you want to send us an email, of course, mailbag at orangelaundry.com
This is the part of the show where we get angsty
It's the FUs of the week segment
Dark Sakura
My FU goes to being really hungry right now
Because over the last whole week I've maybe had
At most
100 calories a day
Because I haven't really been able
To keep anything down
By the way, that candle came from the dollar store
Does it? That smells nice
I'm gonna have to raid the dollar tree
It's a pumpkin bread
Yeah, I love them, anyway
So, I haven't been able to eat anything
So now today is our annual Easter brunch
And my appetite came back with a vengeance
And now I'm super hungry
Like, I think that's why I'm thinking about tacos
Because I seriously haven't eaten
Since 10 this morning
No, about 10.30 this morning
And then I came home and took a nap
And I'm freaking hungry
I ate matzo when I woke up
And I normally do not like matzo by itself
I ate some
I want food
I want a salad
Actually, what I want is pinkberry, but it probably closed
Yeah, the whole Easter thing
Kind of makes places close
But I heart to you
From my wonderful coffee
Oh, you're welcome
Which is why I have someone from Lertness
Folks don't know, but a lot of times before the show
I do make a Starbucks rhyme
There's Starbucks everywhere
Like, saying there's one not far from Jamie's house
Is like, you know, gee, there's grass in the backyard
But yeah, there's a Starbucks nearby
I tend to get coffee a lot
I'm actually
I'm actually going to decaf
If I have it at night, it's gonna be decaf
Yeah, I did request a decaf
I'll remember that in the future
Do you have any FUs for this week?
Just, uh
Not being completely 100% done
With my old place
I'm happy for my former roommate
Because he found someone to move in with him
But just that
Having to go back to San Francisco one last time
And just unpacking in general
Is obnoxious
Otherwise, that's all
Pretty minor
Yeah, I don't have a lot to be angsty about
I mean, there's a lot of really good stuff going on for me right now
A lot of, like, happy news
I don't want to make you par for nothing
But it's good stuff
I will say FU to that freakin' headache I had earlier
That was almost migraine status
I would say, like, if headaches
Were on, like, the terrorism
Color chart
I would say the headache I had was code orange
It was pretty bad
But it wasn't, like, really bad
So, there you go
Alright, that does it for the FUs of the week
For now
I think Wolf is pointing out in our chatroom
That apparently Taco Bell has a lame Flash game
Called Taco Fu
At TacoBell.com slash TacoFu
That's okay
Way to merge the worlds of tacos and video games
Just want to give an A plus to Bobby
That's why he has his own show, folks
Burger King's, uh, Reigning
Dude, those, like, Sneak King and shit
Those games were awesome
Like, why? Like, for five bucks, they were great
Why? Why didn't they ever do that again?
They should do an update
They should do Burger Time and call it Taco Time
Weren't they supposed to do something with, uh, Kinect, I thought?
I think they are making a new
But they should do Taco Time
They are making a new Burger Time
It should be Taco Time
Okay, how about Choco Taco Time?
The villain that tries to, um, kill you
In Taco Time is the diarrhea monster
It's Montezuma
Wow, you guys are mature
Alright, two more stories
Then we're gonna get to the phones
Two more news stories
So, uh, Salacious Pop
Okay, so
Ubisoft is developing
A guitar game
It seems like maybe they'd be a little
That train has left the station
Perhaps, but, uh, they're working on a game
Called Rocksmith
Which sounds a lot like, uh, Pro Mode
In Rock Band
Except with a guitar
You can play this game with real guitars
And the
The UI and how the notes
Because you know how, um, DJ Hero
Guitar Hero Rock Band has the, uh,
The note highway that scrolls
Vertically
This one uses more of a
3D plane where you're in front
And you see the notes coming from the back of the screen
Moving towards you
Um, so it looks really complicated
I'm not sure how much of a market there might be for this
But anyway, they are demoing the game
At South by Southwest
In Texas
Which is a
It's a music and movies
It's kind of like a hipster-y
I know, I was like, if you want to find a place where all the hipsters are at
At one time, like, that's not
Tumblr
Yeah, but it's not like a Lollapalooza
There are a lot of great bands there, but it's also
Movies and art, and it's a whole pop culture thing
So yeah, Rocksmith is going to be
At South by Southwest, they're going to have musicians
Play it, and just show it off
I think they've got a whole Rocksmith tour bus
That sets up
Bass, and it's going to be at
South by Southwest
Yeah, I like the way they've done that
Where they have the guitar silhouette in front
Of the falling stream of notes
It's kind of a neat little way to do it
Alright, we'll see if this game can actually
Be successful, kind of break the recent curse
Of music games
We'll see
One more story for you guys
Everybody get out your 40s and get ready to pour it
The PSP Go
Is officially dead
That's right folks, pour out the 40s
Devastated
How did this happen?
This is, I don't understand
Apparently the whole thing
Is started by a Sony shop employee
Saying that the store was not going to get
Any more shipments, and then the PSP
Go disappeared from the Sony store
Page, Sony is not confirming
The news, but in their
Statement, they're kind of trying to say, well why
Are you asking about the Go? Shouldn't we be talking
About the NGP? The awesome
News system coming out from Sony?
Yeah, so
Although Sony hasn't confirmed it
They haven't really denied it either
In the UK as well, the PSP
Go production has ceased, that has been proven
So the PSP Go
It's dead
So it's basically become the sort of
The
The cousin that is
Touched in the head that now lives in the attic
That the family doesn't talk about
Those thuds that you hear, we don't know
No, he died when he was
Born, we don't know who that is
Some of the comments from our chatroom, of course the
Raging comedy club that is the Orange Lounge Radio
Chatroom, Frisbee calls it the
PSP Go away
Let's see, Redertainment says, wait, the PSP
Go wasn't already dead?
AlphaCanandagram says, wait, wasn't this debunked
Saying only Europe isn't going to carry it and
US is still going to have them?
Dude
It's going to go
Sorry
There you go, BlackWolf would like you to know that
South by Southwest was actually last month
So we're a little behind on the news apparently
But that's where all the video was from
I believe, I think it's just being compiled
And put on the internet now
So there you go
Alright
Shall we open up the Skype line?
Yeah, let's do it
1877 GameOLR
Our username in Skype is Orange Lounge Radio
Now earlier in the evening
Bobby had a problem seeing us
On Skype, but we assure you we're on
And I see plenty of our regular callers
Signing into Skype right now, so I'm assuming
It's fine, but I assure you we
Are on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio
If you aren't down with that though, you can always call
Our toll-free number, 1877
GameOLR
Of course, this is usually the part of the show where
I'd ask Loki if he has any last minute stories
He's not here
And I didn't tell anyone else to prep for that
Way to plan
I have a story
What's that?
Taco
Give me
Alright, let's just go to the phones
They're already ringing, thank god
Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
It's Legend of Zaku
Hey, Legend of Zaku, what's on your mind buddy?
Nothing much, just like chilling in my room
Fixing other people's PCs
Resting up for tomorrow's work day
What's tomorrow? Oh, work? Back to the grind?
Yeah, back to the grind
The evil grind
Evil post-Easter grind
You want to talk about something from our show?
Or some other stories that didn't come?
Folks at Gearbox have been really good sports recently
With that proposal that they did
You know, that Borderlands proposal
That they did for this fan
Out in Texas
I have the video where
I think Claptrap, actually
The voice of Claptrap
They put up a video using that
As a way to propose to a girl
Just pull it up right now
Yeah, we did cover it at the top of the
Show, or at the top of the segment
Just so you know, you missed it
We did talk about it
What did you think about it?
It's pretty good that Gearbox of all companies
Is pretty much playing the Valve card
And giving their fans
Pulling all those stops for their fans
Why do you say Gearbox of all companies?
The way you phrase that is very interesting
Do you think Gearbox is trying to be Valve?
Gearbox, you know
One of many
Of all the other companies out there
Gearbox is also
Using that same
Basically playing that same Valve card
You wouldn't see Sony
Or Activision pull that
Pull those stunts
You wouldn't even flip over
For any fans that still want
DJ Hero
I would say Gearbox's shining achievement
Is that they are actually going to fucking put out
Duke Nukem forever
That is how history will smile
Upon them fondly
Unless the game is the most atrocious piece of shit
We've ever played
It's not that bad
Even though you do mention
Shit in that sentence
You do know you could actually use
Excrement as a weapon in that game
Hooray, I'm so excited
Yes, you could actually
Shit bomb people in that game
I've always wanted to fling my poo in a video game
Where I wasn't playing as a monkey
I'm
I'm touched
Just a while ago I actually seen the video
And yeah
I know it's shocking
Right now I'm just trying to gather up
Just trying to see what I can
What I can get right now
In terms of games
I know Mortal Kombat is on my list right now
Since it was either that or
Marvel vs. Capcom 3
But after seeing the fatalities
A week before they got
Before it launched
That pretty much convinced me at that point
It's either that
I mean, it's that and L.A. Noire
Spring
We're approaching some busy times
I think the busy time
Was this past week
Something that didn't even freaking occur to me
Is that this week
And the next week depending on where you live
Is Spring Break
Usually it's either the week before or the week after Easter
So these games coming out
Like so many all at once
Is not a surprise
PlayStation 3 Network going down for 5 days
That is a little bit more of a surprise
Hence why I think what's happening over there
Is really bad
What in Japan or getting hammered
By Anonymous?
I don't think this is a simple
DDOS from Anonymous
Again earlier in the show
I'm pretty sure they cracked open
One of their holes
I don't think this is
I think this is somebody who's done something
A lot more serious than DDOS
I think personal information has been compromised
I think there's going to be more to develop on this
Again I could be talking out my butt
That's fine I'm some schmo with a podcast on the internet
But when Sony isn't being up front
I'm left to speculate
Sony is basically acting like any other
Japanese person would
By not revealing any damning information
You know at the moment
They're trying to make it seem
I don't know if I'd say that but okay
I mean as I said
You could draw parallels to the way
Japan handled the whole
Nuclear reactor crisis
The way they were with that power company
Aren't we getting a little
Okay isn't this a little
Tinfoil hat
No it's like any government
The Japanese are very
They're open about it
They're basically
They openly lie to people
So that way they can look good
Not necessarily panic
Because would you rather
Hear from Sony that personal information
Has been compromised now
And then you're going to have people bitching in the forums
And everywhere else and congress getting involved
Or would you rather have that later on
When it's less of a problem
And they're actually back online
I would rather have it now
Because it's my fucking information
Well that's up to Sony to decide
They personally have it in their possession
You gave it to them as a contract
Of which you know to join PSN
So it's not like you can get it
Back somehow
But you have to realize that
I'm pretty certain it's a lot worse than
What they're actually going to say
They don't want to create panic
Or else that's going to hurt their stock
That's going to hurt their reputation
What about their legal obligation
From doing business in the state of California
And the United States
Where they are an entity
We've already had the whole
They are a California company
Has been established before
And they are going to have to disclose
If personal information has been compromised
They have to
And that's all part of the panic
If they say that
If they say that now
Unless they find a way to do damage control
Then it's going to sink
Their stock pretty fast
Unless they find a way to
To say it in a way
Where it's not that big of a threat
Even though it actually is
But that's the whole point
They have to, from a PR perspective
They have to release it
In a way that it doesn't impact
Their reputation
And whatever else they have on the line
Next week
I think we can both agree that next week
Is going to be a very interesting week
And hopefully we're not sitting here a week from now
Saying no, we're on day 12 of the PSN outage
Alright, Zacho, I gotta let you go to get more calls
I can't wait to see what emails we get in response
To your call tonight, but have a good one, buddy
So I have a good one
Alright, the views and opinions expressed
By the callers, not necessarily like those
Alright, 1877 Game OLR
Our username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
SalaciousPop doing his due diligence
During that call finding some last minute stories
Gold star for you
South Korea yesterday voted on a curfew
That would prevent
Children under the age of 15
To play online games
From midnight until 6 AM
No more all nighters for the Starcraft 2
It's all PC gaming it sounds like
Instead you need to be studying
And I guess it's being blocked
On the ISP level
The DNS to the gaming servers
If the parents register that they have a kid
They get cut off
Kinda scary what the government can do at that level
It's very interesting
Alright, we got a phone call, hold on
We'll revisit this thought in a minute
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
Hey guys, this is Blue Swim
I'm doing just fine, how about you guys?
Good, I wish we had more callers calling
Hey guys!
Hey, first time caller as well
Yes, that's true
What's on your mind, Blue Swim?
I was wondering what you guys thought of
Blaze Blue Continuum Shift 2
And Dead or Alive Dimensions
Going practically head to head
At the end of May
Well, you know
It's not the first time that fighters
Have really gone against each other, I don't think
Didn't Street Fighter 4 come out
At the same time as
Oh god, there was something else
That came out, I thought right around the same time
Maybe somebody in chat will get me
Yeah, but we ignored it because it was Street Fighter 4 coming out
For real
I think these two series
Are kind of separate enough
Where they can coexist peacefully
Because let's face it, Blaze Blue, Blazblue
Whatever you want to call it
Very heavily Japanese influenced
Very anime, very, you know
Dead or Alive
As much as it's very Japanese
As well, don't get me wrong
It's very much more for the T&A audience
And it kind of
There you go, it's more of the Texas game
Because everything's bigger in Texas
And
So that's kind of why I'm like
I think these two games can coexist
They have very different audiences
Do you think that
You know, with the 3DS
Having three major
Fighters in the first two months
Of its life, it's going to turn it into a
Portable fighting game
Like the portable gaming
Fighting game platform
Yes and no, I mean when those three games
Are probably the only three games worth owning
On the 3DS right now
No, I shouldn't say that
I also bought Pilotwings, I haven't played it yet
It's just, it's a little frustrating
There wasn't a bigger title
But you know, looking at what Street Fighter 4
Does, I mean it really brings
Pretty much the whole experience
Of the Xbox version
To the portable console
And what's interesting about that is that a lot of times
You used to hear this shit, right
Like when Mortal Kombat came out on the Game Boy
It was like
Experience, the arcade experience
On the go, and it's like
Dude, this game fucking blows
Like I've got two buttons
And it's all like
Like you know, it's got like three frames
A second, this game sucks
But Street Fighter 4
It pretty much
Plays really like the Xbox
Versions, I'll tell you my biggest bitch
About the game is the controls
Like I think it's because I'm not a kid
And I have fat hands
But the 3DS thing does not feel
Very good in my fat hands for trying to play
A fighter with the L and R buttons and everything
The analog thumb thing
In my opinion is too slippery
And the D-pad is too small
For my giant spindly man hands
And I don't like where the D-pad is positioned
As far as like a fighting game goes
It's a little weird
Yeah it cramps the crap out of my hands
When I'm like playing Bison trying to
Do like a knee press nightmare or something like that
It kills my fingers
Yet I decided to go online and do the whole internet match
Earlier and I got my ass handed
To me by some asshole playing as Cody
Seems like every asshole
On Street Fighter 4 plays Cody
And I call them assholes because they're better than me
What are you
What fighting game are you looking forward to
Out of those two?
I pretty much bought the 3DS at launch
Expecting the Dead or Alive
To be there
I've been a hardcore Dead or Alive fan
Since 2002
I want to say
It prevented me from trading in my original
Xbox when I discovered
The Dead or Alive 3 demo
On demo disc
And ever since then
I've been absolutely
Hooked on the franchise
I've put maybe 300 hours into
Dead or Alive Ultimate
And another 100 and
100 plus in Dead or Alive 4
I find it very interesting how they've
Talked about this whole it's gonna run 30 frames a second
In 3D but it will run 60 frames
A second in 2D
That's a distinction I don't notice as much
In like Super Street Fighter 4
It kind of looks the same no matter what mode you're in
Did you turn the 3D off in the options
Menu because if you turn the slider
Off it will still render the game
In 30 frames per second
But when you turn the 3D option
Off in the options menu
And you're playing like offline
It is absolutely gorgeous
I haven't
I need to try that what a good tip
I'm glad we do this show see even I learn shit on this show
No I haven't I'm gonna try that
Nice maybe that's what I'm missing
That's gonna run very fluid
When I try that that's cool
The 60 frames doesn't carry over to the online
Portion unfortunately
But I mean if you're playing you know the arcade
Mode or versus mode or whatever I mean
It's just yeah it's gorgeous
Have you had any real quick before we let you
Go cause we gotta fit in at least one more call tonight
Have you had any luck with the street pass in Super Street Fighter 4?
Not a bit and I've been carrying
That thing with me almost constantly
You know I live near Nashville
And there's a ton of
You know ton of stores around here you know
Best Buy and GameStop and stuff like that
I have not had one street pass fight with them
Interesting I mean I'm hearing
Those things aren't activating very much and it could be a variety
Of things it could be that the battery life is so
Eh on those things that it's not pulsing
The street pass very often
That's kinda one thing I'm hearing and then the other is just
You know how many people carry their DS in sleep mode
With them everywhere they go very few
So I don't know I'm gonna try
This week I'm gonna try going to the mall this week
And see if I get anybody on street pass
At least walk into GameStop you know some of those employees
Have gotta have it going we'll see
I think that's where I got
Where I got one of my
Street pass me's was
GameStop and the other was like a demo unit at Best Buy
Other than that I haven't had any action
On it I never thought of trying a demo unit
At Best Buy that's a great idea
We'll see alright BlueSwip I've gotta let you
Go so we can get more calls but thanks for the call
Thank you very much have a good night
You too happy birthday Jamie
Thank you
See I like enthusiastic
Callers people that just I'm just really happy to be
Here
Exciting alright sorry
I want more happy people
Everyone
BlueSwip should be your role model
Alright other
Stories that you've got Salacious Popper I don't know
If you want to finish your thoughts on that last one
Well I was just saying that for the
South Korea gaming curfew that's a
Part of the world not necessarily
Just South Korea where people will just
Stop peeing when they play
Starcraft 2 and then they die
Bladder explodes and they die so obviously
I think there's a demand for that kind of regulation
I forgot to mention I played some more Starcraft 2
This week Starjeweled is my new
Favorite add-on ever for Starcraft
It's great you play Bejeweled
And then you use the points you get in Bejeweled
To like buy units and it's like a tug
Of war match it's awesome
Like Jamie you might
Actually like Starcraft 2 if I were to buy
That I don't know we'll see
Hi I'm here
I'm here
Echoing you got to fix that
I don't know why but I'm hearing myself come through
You got to fix your settings
But thank you for the bags
Alright we'll see maybe he'll fix that
And try calling back
Which nobody else but the people in this room and he will get
1877 game
OLR username on Skype is OrangeLoungeRadio
Echo123 is always a good way
To test this that's somebody who calls us pretty regularly
Though so I don't know what's going on
Quick last minute story Minecraft
2 million paid
Fuck that's a game I still haven't played
2 million people have paid for the
Beta access which is roughly
28-29% of its
Entire user base
So a third so a little under
A third of their player base is paid for the game
For a little indie sandbox kind of
Aspie
Thing that's pretty impressive
You know some are saying it's too early to call Portal 2
The game of the year when you have something like Minecraft
Out there
It has that same 3D
With the weird spritey problem
I can't play it for very long
I need to check it out
We need to play Minecraft
We need to have Minecraft night
Try to figure out why people lose their shit over this game
I think it's 15 euros
Which translates to like 20 bucks
Or 22 bucks US because the euros are worth more than the dollar
Yeah
I remember it being like $19.99
They have a demo though right?
Isn't there like demo levels?
Do you?
Yeah hold on I want it
1877 game OLR username on skype is orange
I'm going to try keeping it open one more second
Especially if that last guy can get there
Oh maybe I deleted it
I'm so bad I always forget
I still have Ragnarok online
Let's see
An obvious spam person out of Bulgaria wants to be our friend
Block
That's no fun
Alright we're going to try this one more time
Give this guy one more chance here
Let's go back to the phones
No it's still echoing
Hello?
Now I'm not hearing it
Yeah I wasn't doing it before
You hung up and I was like okay that's kind of weird
And I tried to echo and the echo came out fine
That's weird alright well it works now what's on your mind buddy?
By the way this is xlink
Hi xlink sorry
I recognize your voice at this point
What's on your mind buddy?
You know actually it was kind of funny
Another caller kind of talked about this earlier
The whole Valve thing in Portal 2
I was watching the whole thing as it unfolded right before Portal 2 came out
The ARG
And it's kind of cool reading the stories of how Valve gave pretty much open access to these indie companies
You know basically telling hey you want to be part of this come on in we'll give you full access
We'll help you any way possible
We'll give you all these materials
We'll do anything we can to make this work
And it was really cool reading some of the company stories of like how everything progressed from day one to the night of the release
When everything got completed
Is that the whole thing I heard at the tail end of Bobby's show where there's like an iPad app that Jeff Keighley was involved with
Where they've like chronicled the entire last development cycle of Portal is that what you're talking about?
Likely yes and I don't know exactly what the app has in it because I don't have it right now
And I don't have the money for it so I can't really tell
But the impression that I'm getting from our pal Bobby who talked about it a little bit more on his show tonight
Is that it's basically like imagine like an interactive news article
And when I say or I should say magazine feature
Because it's more like what 10,000 word article or something like that that has videos, pictures, behind the scenes stuff
Probably
Yeah it kind of sounds like honestly what more magazines ought to be doing on the iPad
Yeah
The people and how all these people, these groups of people don't know each other
And they're willing going hey I have a free copy of like audio surf I'm willing to give to you
So that way you get your potatoes so that way we can make the multiplier faster
So we can get you know it was very cool seeing everybody come together the squad going
Okay which game should we play we should play this one so this way the timer can go down more and more and more
And it was just very neat watching the whole thing as it unfolded it was very cool
That is yeah I did play I did my part I played audio surf it was fun even though I had no intention of buying it on PC
Because I knew I'd already had the PS3 one ordered but it was still it was you know it was fun
I like those things kind of get the community riled up like that and Valve is a heck of a company
That's really what it boils down to I mean they just has Valve ever put out a bad game
No not that I know
Yeah Valve is in a very elite group of developers that just does not put out bad games
And I would say Blizzard's probably in there too
Blizzard I don't think has ever put out a bad game until Cataclysm no I'm kidding I'm kidding
And then let's see what else there's got to be at least one other I'm sure there's many folks
Bioware has a pedigree but that's then you're getting to the more you know
See part of me would say well Bethesda because they put out such awesome stuff
And then I'm like oh but they did that Star Trek game that was really not good
So you know a lot of developers do have a little blemishes on their record
Or bizarre creations before they close but they made that Bond game that wasn't so hot so unfortunately they had a blemish too
You know so but there's very rare companies
It's in a myth market depending on what the people want at the time so I mean you know
And it depends on who does it to a lot of it depends on how much work they put into it you know
If they're gonna put it in work for six months they throw it out there in the market inspect it to sell
And it turns out to be a complete piece of shit I mean you know you can't really get too much from it
But it's obvious they took a lot of time and effort behind what they want and it really paid off
It paid off in big time so like I said before people were very happy with this whole thing
And the way it unfolded at the end so and then of course with Portal 2 being the way it is so
Kaiju in our chat room says Valve put out that shitty poker game I believe that was Telltale wasn't it
That was Telltale and it's not really that bad unless you really find it
It's a budget title
It's a budget title and it's really short and I wish they would I kind of wish they would add
Maybe a few extra people or extra things to it but for a budget title being ten bucks for poker
It's not really all that bad
And Telltale's about in that pedigree too I mean it kind of depends how into the games they're putting out you are
But they put out a lot of quality stuff too
Yeah
So anyway sorry I don't want to turn this into a developer penis size contest but you know I thought it would be fun
And the gearbox was very interesting too that whole story about the proposal too
You should watch both the videos first the video of the proposal and then how it all came about
Because he checked a bunch of his friends saying that he got the exclusive for the
Because being a big fan they gave him an exclusive for Borderlands 2
And it turned out to be the proposal video so it's very cute how the whole thing came around
Wow
Gearbox got off the ground thanks to Valve because Gearbox got the Half-Life 1 expansion license
They did Blue Shift and
Oh wow I didn't even know that
Something Force with the Marine Adrian Shepard but the Half-Life expansions that came out in 98-99 that was Gearbox
Well there you go
Alright well X-Link I got to let you go so we can wrap up the show but any other quick final thoughts
Nope that's about it sorry about the call earlier sorry about all that usually I don't have any of those problems I usually call Echo 1, 2, 3 beforehand so
Minus 50 DKP
Yeah no joke
Later
Alright that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight if you didn't get through help Jamie get tacos by sending an email instead mailbag at orangelawnsradio.com
Well how did I fucking agree to buy her fucking tacos
I am awesome
Alright and Skype crashed right as I closed
Rob's great heart
I know alright well that's a sign that we need to wrap up the show and get on out of here so we can't wrap up the show though until we go around and get some final thoughts
Oh actually I should ask if you have any other quick last minute stories you want to get out
No
No you're good alright well then I will say thank you very much for being here Salacious Pop tonight really appreciate it especially on short notice and filling in for Loki you did a great job with the stories and everything
It's been a very fun show
Not everybody can just waltz right in here and read the stories so really appreciate it hope you had fun
Thank you as always
Do you have any final thoughts for our listeners
Remember to go outside and don't play too much portal 2 in Mortal Kombat back to back
That's right
Alright my final thought is now I want tacos I hate you
You don't
You're right I don't
But right now I do
Dark soccer your final thought tonight
I'm hungry I want a taco
I guess that seems to be the theme tonight so tune in next week when you'll find out where did we get tacos on the very informative episode 411 of Orange Laundry next week see what I did there see what I did there
Alright by the way if you like the show
If that's gonna go then I hate to see episode 420
Which was supposed to land on our 9 year anniversary but apparently they're off by like a week so we'll see
Alright anyhow thank you guys so much for downloading our show by the way really appreciate it thanks for checking it out thanks for listening to the whole thing
Thank you guys for participating thank you for showing up every week as you do you know we don't put commercials in the show sure I say nice things about Amazon once in a while or whatever company is on my good side this week
But all we ask you guys if you like what you hear on the show leave us a nice review on iTunes tell a friend about the show help us spread the word because we don't have a giant magazine company behind us
We're not you know getting paid $70,000 a year to do journalism or whatever just spread the word that's all we ask tell a friend about what we're doing here and that's the juice that keeps our show powered
That and peeps
Just kidding
Alright that does it have a good night everybody
Nutella
We'll see you next week here on Orange Lounge Radio
Goodnight
Now with outro goodnight
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production
To join us for a live show visit www.allgames.com
Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific time
The views and opinions expressed on Orange Lounge Radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of Orange Lounge Radio or allgames.com
But we're probably right anyway
See you next week