The console arm trace continues to be interesting, since graphics quality can no longer grow
as dramatically as it did generation over generation. Xbox rode the wave of Kinect across
two generations, but as of the series generation they have no extra piece of gaming tech, while
rumors say that Sony's PSVR2 or PS5VR will be impressive, challenging even today's
VR headsets. The story of consoles never ends, now it's time for your hosts Rob Roberts,
Jamie Summers and Loki to tell you about it and the rest of the week's gaming news, starting
right now in the show where every gamer has a voice.
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show
where every gamer has a voice. It is Orange Lounge Radio and we are live once again tonight
with episode number 869 of our show for this May the 18th, no 16th of 2021 I can't read
my own numbers. Hi I am Rob Roberts and I am joined by my co-hosts say hello as always
to DarkSakura or Jamie Summers. Hello. Hi how are you? I've had a long day but a fairly
good day. Yeah. I went to one of my favorite places to eat and loaded up on, finally they're
back to having the pink garlic sauce at Pita Kitchen. Nice. Just saying. Oh I don't think
that was there. Sumac is delicious. Yeah, yeah one of our favorite local little restaurants.
We are based in Sacramento, California so sometimes it's, and all three of us live in
the area, we live in the suburbs if nothing else, and so sometimes we can't avoid the
local chat such as favorite restaurants, but if you happen to be local and you know
this place Pita Kitchen, I was just telling Jamie before the show, Alan and I were there
like a week and a half ago and it was it was marvelous and it's a small little restaurant
you know it's like a small team that runs it so I'm really glad they're still around
that's for sure. Absolutely but you know we they had some different stuff there in their
little grocery store and I picked up some spinach and cheese pies they're wrapped in
filo dough they're absolutely they're like giant spanakopita it's really delicious. Get
the baklava because I've had bad baklava but theirs is really good. Theirs is always delightful
and we actually got into a discussion on like how terrible making filo dough is and she's
like we don't make it. Awesome. But yeah we had a really good time but I'm really irritated
that the the pet store that I go to does not have Midniss food nor had they had it for
the last three weeks and I get her refrigerated food so they don't like keep any extra stock
and pack so I had to buy her raw food. I was gonna tell you we can't even like the food
that Smoosh eats we can't even get it at like the big brand we have to go to the indie pet
store over by Lomond's that's the only place that will have the food and that's not the
closest pet store to us but it's whatever it's the only place that has the food that
Smoosh will eat so you should check that but maybe they have the food. What are you feeding
him like caviar from a live sturgeon? No it's just a certain brand he's he's a weird kitty
you all know that he doesn't he doesn't really care for kitty treats either it's it's interesting
so anyway we will get to get look local discussion is inevitable sometimes if you if you are
unaware with the history of our show you know we we are the longest running video game podcast
because we started well video game show because we started this in online show we started
this in 2002 so podcasting wasn't even really a thing yet but we we did get in on podcasting
really early it was before it was on iTunes when you had to use things like lemon pod
I think it was called to a sink your podcast was like 2005 we won the very first podcast
award in gaming we were fortunate for that but anyway we've and I have the award yes
you do there it is uh yeah 2005 uh dark soccer Loki and myself um hi tech master Loki by
the way I hate to make you sit there in silence my bad but we all met playing dance dance
revolution at Roseville golf lands so we there is a local sense of connection here
on the show and you know in those early years if you didn't already know the story at OLR
we talked a lot about DDR that was our scene and that was our community and then Konami
kind of abandoned DDR for a few years and then wanted a seat at the table again once
guitar hero and rock band got big and it was awkward but our show grew into all sorts of
video games because we just love video games dang it right they're like looking at at rock
band going um but what we had this oh you've got better button that's right Konami you
had the opportunity and you didn't take the risk so someone beat you to it you blew it
bitch that's I that's you know they even they even screwed up their own rendition of that
as well considering that they had a winning formula and they're just like now let's put
out rock revolution instead Loki I think your audio is coming through your webcam not your
mic just you know it's it's kind of tin canny okay yeah you might want to check that anyway
but while he fixed that live I'm gonna check our chat room over twitch.tv slash vog network
because we do tape live every Sunday night at six o'clock Pacific nine o'clock Eastern
right after the Bobby Blackwell show at the voice of geeks Network twitch.tv slash vog network I
almost said twitch.tv slash Bobby Black Wolf area for two yes much better for two reasons one I
forgot to say happy birthday Bobby Black Wolf on our throw call tonight that was on my mind his
birthday was this past week so happy belated birthday again I know he's 20 wriggling day go
go figure so for the first time obviously happy happy birthday Bobby Black Wolf and congratulations
to our pal Bobby Black Wolf who announced this week he will be an announcer during summer games
done quick for the it's his third time at a games done quick event pretty much all the virtual ones
at this point so congrats we don't know what games he's announcing yet we're expecting to find that
out tomorrow but as I understand there are no Yakuza runs this year so there's not gonna be
like a baby thing or any of that stuff that yeah I know too bad huh but it's well it's also at the
same time we can say ah but I do love the games done quick like mixes up the games right because
how are other games supposed to get a shot if you know it's always the same games so I think that's
great um let's see some of the comments speaking of the local chat and then I promise we'll get
into gaming news pod culture says how long has it been since Pinkberry was mentioned well that that
is a bit of a local place but I think that I think it's a like a West Coast no it is it's
international I've seen it in it hurts I've seen it in airports pinkberry in Atlanta I think it
started at the airport I yeah I think it started in LA so there's like a lot of them in the West
Coast but anyway long story short the one that are soccer and I used to go to closed and Alan
also my husband kind of let it known that he has a preference for another place called Menchie's
and so that's one of those yogurt battles I just give in on like my husband's allowed a nice thing
once in a while and well they also good they also have dole whip it or Menchie's yes yes what
yeah what yeah they do they do like a dole whip type thing so this has to happen I don't know if
it's official though it but it's their own version of it they I don't think they can call it that but
it's basically that yeah the you know what I still think we need to do is that we need to have a
dinner at Brookfield and then go to pinkberry well you know especially now that I don't want
to say the pandemic is over because it certainly isn't but now that we're getting vaccinated and
you know it make light right now well you know I you still want to be cautious and I know there's
the CDC guidance and a lot of people are a little skittish about that because unfortunately this
panda I mean whereas the science says vaccinated people aren't gonna spread it you can hang out
with other vaccinated people without a mask the reality is a lot of us are a little bit unfortunately
this whole instance has seen the best in people and the worst in people and I don't trust people
to be honest exactly and I don't think a lot of us do we don't trust other people to be honest and
that's really unfortunate but hopefully more and more people get vaccinated and that'll that'll do
the trick because the vaccinations are working that's it period so the more people to get
vaccinated the less longer this is gone but anyway it's nice to think that some of those
things are a possibility again like the you know Brookfield's trip and you know who may be going
to see what a sad place Rosewood Golf Land is these days and what have you all those types of
things so yeah who knows a lot of exciting stuff coming in the next few months I'm sure I think
it would be fun to film a trip like that and put it as like a bonus video at vog network for our
subscribers that might be fun so you know what though I legit haven't been to Pinkberry since
2019 I haven't been in about a year myself I still like it like just because I give in and
my husband gets to pick most of the time I still I still I still sneak and have it I'll be at an
airport and I'll be like oh I'm gonna have that so didn't need blood orange back and then I'll go
huh speaking of air pop go ahead I was gonna say I stopped going there because I just didn't like
their flavors like I had one like they started doing these like kind of they were sort of ice
cream but not ice cream and they just started like really weird flavors I didn't like so that's what
pissed Alan off to their their flavor selection was so limited and once they would get a flavor
that he really liked it would be gone at the end of the month they rotate something else yeah do
do you know though what I what I miss hmm is I miss Naya the gelato place that was all in the
area oh I don't I don't think I ever ate there maybe once so so alright and I'll get off of it
after this but just imagine you have a place that has something like 20 different flavors of gelato
and they rotate a lot of their flavors and they had champagne they had Guinness they had whole
wheat that tasted like eating cereal they had like all kinds of just different ones and the
alcoholic ones were actually alcoholic and I ate a big ol bowl of Guinness and champagne it was
delightful no I miss is we had a place over here and I think it's a chain Rita's that's frozen
custard yes the one that's nearby all right all right look super disappointed that's so so good
look can you tell me when ice cream I get that snacking is important and if if the chat wasn't
lighting up going mmm gelato yes Rita's like if the chat wasn't supporting this we probably would
have cut it off a while ago but I do want to get into some gaming news because there was quite a
bit of it this week I'm gonna say okay I won't even talk then about the whole week kit kats oh
we could do a whole other spin-off show on Kit Kat flavors and we might but anyhow and my new
obsession is Pringles from around the world all right let's talk tonight our kickoff story tonight
we want to talk a little bit about Final Fantasy 14 Fan Fest and you may be thinking like Rob are
you giving preference to one of your favorite games and letting it have the lead topic tonight
partially yes but even if you don't play Final Fantasy 14 please don't tune out completely I
assure you there's a very good reason I'm bringing this up at the top of the show talking about Fan
Fest I'll get to there in a minute so obviously the Final Fantasy 14 Fan Fest convention is
virtual this year every other year they've done three of them in person they do a Vegas one they
do a Europe one they do a Japan one and it's usually like doing a tour of the latest expansion
announcement obviously because of COVID it was supposed to be in San Diego this year actually
they're gonna move it from Vegas but you know long story short we all know what COVID did to that so
they ended up doing these online events instead so they did that they did a original like keynote
announcement back in February Shane and I co-stream that with some of our buddies that we
play Final Fantasy with here at VOG Network and Shane and I did that last season not last night
Friday night as well is we actually were streaming the keynote event that showed everything else
about this expansion coming up and that was here at VOG Network so for those of you that subscribe
to us here at Twitch on here at VOG Network on Twitch first off thank you second off you can go
back and watch that if you want it is a longer keynote because the translation because they have
to say it in Japanese then they say it in English so you know an hour keynote now is two hours and
even within they were kind of having they were kind of stretching time like you could tell the
parts that you know the audience response would be yeah woo and like screaming and they that was
gone and so it would be these interesting moments of Naoki Yoshida the producer kind of leaning in
and looking at the TV monitors like literally reading chat as he's trying to do the whole
thing you know and and so for what for what it is with the state of the world being that it is
he did his best and I thought it was a he tried and it was it was a good keynote overall and a
lot of the expansion announcements about the game look great as we learned previously Final Fantasy
14 is going to be the latest expansion called Endwalker it seems to have a heavy Final Fantasy
4 influence because we're going to the moon and they are now selling a lunar whale mount in the
game as well as you can get Rosa Edgar and one other one I'm sorry not Edgar edge Rosa edge already
of course you can get I'm in the shop little minions are right now for in the game and there's
pre-order bonuses I think porum is the pre-order bonus and then Palom is in the collectors box I
might have gotten that backwards you know those those of you that really need to know that
information probably already know they gave us the release date though November 23rd that's a
little ways out I think some folks were a little bit like oh that's a bummer we're gonna have to
wait so long but I mean you know the the development of the game was really kind of stopped for four
months during kovat so if you think about it it does make sense so when he as awesome as this
expansion looks it you understand you want it to be done right of course right we hate it when God
they're trying to do it yeah we hate it when game companies release games and there's problems with
them hold that hold that thought it'll be relevant later anyhow oh and I'm gonna have an F you for
the record we'll get there meanwhile let's talk about some other information with obviously 14
and Walker they revealed the other class that will be playable in the game it's it's one of
the things that pains me the most in the world is having to admit when Shane was Shane is right but
damn that boy nailed it like he called that the new class would be the reaper class and it would
have a scythe and sure enough it was the reaper class with a scythe I think the thing he didn't
figure out might be enough to make me play again the thing he didn't figure out was that you get a
little ghost companion when you play it and you kind of like absorb the ghost hugs you it's the
most adorable thing I've ever seen and go look up the reaper trailer dark Sakura on the fantasy
14 channel it's pretty amazing the problem is is that I would have to buy the whole thing on Mac
again yeah that part's a bummer yeah cuz the yeah yeah so but anyway so you you kind of can merge
with the ghost and you do special attacks and that's cool they also unveiled and this was big
for me at the end I was not expecting it and if you go back and watch the feed I was literally
just in a state of shock because I my brain literally did not understand what was happening
when they announced male Viera are coming to the game as the next playable race by God male Viera
the bunny people from Final Fantasy 12 that have always been like Fran was the biggest most well
known Viera and the lore you only ever really saw female Viera I believe male Viera kind of known to
exist but they're not really seen but anyway long story short we're getting them in Final Fantasy 14
I've been a big advocate for this for a long time so I was thrilled and now that I've had time for
like my brain to process at all I am really thrilled with this and absolutely I'll be race
changing to a boy bunny as will lots of people that play Final Fantasy 14 I'm sure so that is
a very exciting announcement and then of course they detailed some new areas in the game and soon
some new things about the story they really detailed the collector's edition they wheeled
it out they have a pin and they have all this other really cool stuff that is coming out so
for the most part that was the keynote now the event continued on throughout the weekend and
they would do some panels talking about like they had one the live letter that kind of gave
a roadmap about what to expect between now and when the end Walker expansion releases like here's
the next story patch here's when we're gonna implement the data center moving which is another
huge thing about and Walker I'm so excited for that for example like Ziba here at vog network I
don't know she's listening live tonight but I know she listens to the show and she's always kind of
said a bummer you know she's on a different data center than I am we can't play together but in
Endwalker or shortly before Endwalker starts we will be able to do that with the data center move
so a temporary move I visit whatever they call it so that is gonna be very exciting and they also
do these big concerts this is the big big you know thing when you're there live the concert is
it man they did like a Friday night piano concert and they do a Saturday night concert with the
primals which is like a rock band that features Soken he's the guy that does all the music for
Final Fantasy 14 he actually like plays guitar and sings a lot of songs and all his band kind of
does that it's really cool unfortunately because the time difference they were doing this in Japan
it was on at like 3 in the morning for us here in the US so I didn't watch it live here's the part
okay perk up because here's the part that is a really big deal and had a lot of people in the
community talking today so they did the concert and after the concert is the closing ceremony but
it was a little bit different what happened is Soken wanted to talk to the crowd that was watching
for a little bit and he basically said you know thank you for your support thank you for everything
you've done this has really helped me get through the year and I'm very sorry I don't have the
official audio I tried to get that working before the show unfortunately it didn't work I tweeted
out that video earlier today if one of our resourceful folks like Tiger Claw or dark Tetsuya
could like pull that video from my tweet from this morning and like post it in chat and maybe the
discord I'd really appreciate it cuz and so that those of you listening on the podcast feed can go
check out on discord this video link um Soken was thanking everybody because he revealed that in
March of 2020 right before the coronavirus pandemic set in he was diagnosed with cancer and he didn't
reveal what type of cancer it was so we don't know those details but what we do know is that
Square Enix and the Final Fantasy 14 team basically allowed him to work while he was in the hospital
and if you've played things like patch 5.3 there's a really big boss fight in that game with a really
epic song in it called to the edge I believe is the name of that song that song was basically
written while he was in the hospital undergoing chemotherapy for cancer and that song if you
listen to it has a huge impact like that like go back and listen to that song again now that you
know that information that is huge Soken's contribution I'm sorry I'm just this is a very
heavy topic we're getting into and I'm just like I actually got choked up watching the video today
and I get choked up thinking about it because you cannot understate the contributions of Soken to
Final Fantasy 14 I have said this on the show before there can be no successor to Nobuo Uematsu
what that man has done for Final Fantasy what that man has done for video game composition and
all of that can can never be replaced however what Soken has done with Final Fantasy 14 and
when you really consider that the project was a realm reborn and all of this the contributions
of Soken he's a worthy successor to Final Fantasy's music and I would assume I don't know I would have
assumed before I heard this news over the weekend that he was probably doing Final Fantasy 16's
music as well this situation I'm not sure if that's the case anymore who knows or any of that
um he didn't tell they did not tell the production team about his cancer because everybody was
working from home so people didn't know so this was the first time a lot of the production team
was finding out about this and so it was it was really heavy because you could hear the story
producer going like I I feel so guilty I was giving you so much work and asking all of these
changes for you when I was going through all this and Soken is basically saying and I am paraphrasing
here like I I am having this to work on having the fans feedback from things like the to the
edge composition having all of this kept me going and that's the part that really gets you choked
up and then something else to consider is that Naoki Ishida who's the producer of the game and
you know a big figure he's the face of the game he's you know the guy that gets out there and does
all these keynotes this entire time that Soken is talking he has his back to the audience and you
can tell he's he's he's breaking up he's tearing up and after about 13 minutes of discussion with
Soken and the team and everything he says I know this is a strange note to end the closing
ceremonies on but I just want to say that I am so happy that my best friend is still here and if you
don't get a little choked up in that moment watching it and again I'm sorry I can't be here
and play it for you guys but it might be triggering to some folks I don't know so if you go and watch
it if you don't get a little choked up hearing that I don't know you've had a different life
experience than I clearly because I had a hard time holding it together this morning watching
that you know when you consider what that this game what this community what this has done for
people and and Yoshida also explains this a little bit with that when he was giving his first speech
to the team when he was rebooting Final Fantasy 14 Soken was one of the first people to jump up
and advocate for him and say let's do this let's go and so you can tell there's a tight friendship
between these two and Final Fantasy 14 and Final Fantasy the franchise is better for it so to hear
that all of this happened and none of us had any idea and the game sure it had a four-month delay
but are any of us gonna complain at this point no we are not because of everything we've heard
that this team is going through and what they're going through personally it's like wow now why is
this relevant to folks who maybe don't play Final Fantasy 14 I mean yes it's a nice story but I tell
you all this and I tell you about what you know Soken is literally pouring his heart and soul into
this game and using this as therapy to get you know to fight what is a horrific battle tell me
video games aren't art people I mean people that have said in the past video games aren't art or
people that mouth we had a story a couple weeks ago about somebody getting mouthy on their cable
talk show about oh twitch is just people watching plate people play video games not stupid I dare
that individual to watch that 13-minute video I watched earlier today fucking look them in the
face and say video games aren't art or the video game community isn't important or video games
don't fucking help people that fucking stereotype is done we've had it I don't know what else to say
that's that and that's why I wanted to bring it up is that like if if you can't listen to this
story and understand that video games are more than video games for a lot of people then you're
never gonna get it period so um Bobby Black Wolf in chat said Shane complained complained initially
but that was in the keynote I not to speak for him but a he's the one that texted me this morning
about all of that that went on and I bet if I asked him again he'd be like oh I get it and he
did kind of like during the keynote he was kind of like oh well you know yeah it's kind of the same
thing I landed I he's he's he's only bummed because it looks so good he wants to play it now but he
gets it I'm sure again I don't want to speak for him but I'm pretty sure he would say something to
the equivalent there fifth dream in chat says yeah Jesus that guy talking about soaking I have
literally hundreds a thousand songs by him on my PC I have all those Final Fantasy 14 blu-ray
soundtracks do yourself a favor folks even if you don't fucking care about MMOs and I get it like
it's monthly fees they're they're tough sometimes even though did you know Final Fantasy 14 is free
to play including the award-winning expansion heavens work this is like a meme at this point
but I'm serious you could check it out the first part for free but you go listen to the soundtracks
at least they're so good and there's so many like ways that they've remixed different songs in the
game and so forth it's it's pretty amazing let's see and sacred J points out it was it was
triggering I had tears yeah I mean it's it's it's very difficult to watch and yeah but I think it
just goes to show that like you know again video games are much bigger than pixels on a screen
that's for sure and especially when you look at a game like Final Fantasy 14 that has such a huge
community as it does it was it was a difficult but also a very beautiful thing to watch so it
just it just makes my heart for that game grow 10 more sizes honestly it really does but if you
if you don't play it and you're not into it that's okay too I'm sure you still agree with my bottom
line and recognize that there's a lot more to this game than a game that's for sure you know I still
listen to the old da theme when I want to chill yeah yeah there's some there's some there's some
great songs for lots of moods in that game at depth says there's some Final Fantasy 14 A Realm
Reborn tracks in theater them that are pretty good yes especially the arcade version has a lot of 14
tracks in them if you're ever lucky enough to play one of those that's for sure so all right so that's
why I wanted to talk about the beginning of the show video games more than just pixels all right
and kudos to the Final Fantasy 14 team for being vulnerable for one and just a well-done fan fest
even if even if I was a little critical that it was moving a little bit slow I give them a break
because they were expecting it to be in front of a crowd and it wasn't it's gonna be awkward it's
okay I'm excited to play the expansion very very very much and listening to all of the music that
Soken makes for that expansion and he's they I believe they said chat please correct me if
I'm wrong I believe he did say it is in remission um so um I I so uh yeah that's that does does
have a happy note there okay um moving on let's get into our gaming weeks and talk about the
types of video games and and maybe some gaming things off the screen too that we've been into
this week uh Dark Soccer I'll start with you well I'm starting off with anger but I'll get to the
anger in a little bit so um of course I've been playing some Animal Crossing and uh my friend
Mika who has been in chat before is also playing so I gave her about 30 to 40 DIYs of which six
remained since you just started playing um thank you for helping to clear out my recycle bin um
I also am doing and I don't know if a lot of people know about this but on the Nintendo online
app for your smartphone um if you go into that and then open up nook link you can redeem or you
can like earn points and they have six was six yeah six items that you can redeem at different
uh at different price points but uh there's like switch cases and a a door placard that looks like
the leaf but um three of the items are photographs and one of them is Isabel one is nook and the
other are the nooklings they they really boost your uh uh AHH or AHA whatever HHA score the
happy home academy yes happy home academy um and then of course I've been playing Dead by Daylight
because I haven't gotten the freaking gnome yet and I played a lot but I had a funny experience
and I do have to talk about this because it was hilarious so um I was in Hawkins which used to be
one of my least favorite maps and I guess the guys I was playing I guess realized I was you know
fairly new you know I was doing okay but I think that they were giving me looping practice because
they would wait for me and then point and then they would run the loop and I just follow along
and then they let me 4k nice how random is that though like that never happens usually people are
assholes it's it's interesting the way that people and this is in general for all games we're talking
about just dead by daylight in this instance but isn't it interesting how people can communicate
without communicating uh because I had a very similar sort of thing except I was the survivor
and for the record they were all console so I couldn't chat them oh bummer um I had a very
similar circumstance where I was the survivor and there was a nurse in the match and I was like
I was being chased by the nurse and the nurse wasn't using blink and I was kind of like this
isn't normal like what's going on I thought it must be a baby nurse oh my gosh so I would just
I did things like I just started booping the nurse like I would turn around and look at the nurse and
I booped the nurse into which response she'd hit me once but she would she didn't hit me twice
yeah so I so that was the communication to me oh she's here to farm so finally and without
communicating because again I was with randos we figured out this nurse wants to farm and so we
were doing healings we're letting the nurse hit us and all this stuff and then we left the match
pretty much helping each other out and left well uh dark soccer we were all on steam so we could
chat and the killer was like gg I have a daily to chase for 180 seconds as nurse yeah what the
fuck quest is that thanks for letting me get it and I was the one that ran him because I was like
why is this nurse chasing me and not using blink and I'm thinking in my head oh well I'm just gonna
keep running and like practicing doing that little did I know I helped him beat his quest and I had
that as a generic yeah so it's um so I had to do that on plague yeah yeah so it was just uh
interesting so communicating without communicating anyway sorry sorry to derail your daily week but
I really like that although there are times where if I do get somebody in chat I'm just gonna flat
out say you know if they're being little troll assholes I'll be like real mature and then I'll
just leave because don't care um usually I'm playing the plague so I can blood vomit on them
so that it forces them to leave the match anyway um so this is the thing I'm pissed about
so I did all of my reading up on the windows arm environment I am on a mac mini m1 I need it for
the majority of the work that I'm going to do I can game on it just fine except that you know
I installed parallels I got the windows arm beta up the developer's beta so I could have the
increased uh emulation and it won't run mass effect and I have paid for mass effect so I have
a uh a kvm switch arriving tomorrow and um I'm going to hook up uh my my pc again the old dinosaur
so that I can steam link on my mac okay yeah um and I think it's gonna be okay
it's just I then have to figure out another cord or cable to get I'm just I'm not happy about it
and I know that they are still working on the x86 emulation um for windows arm and I'm pretty
positive that you know it's not going to be too long away and I'm not the most super hurried about
it I guess because I have played them ad nauseum at the same time I need my space bird husband
I need I need the voice of garris to just read the phone book to me yeah the struggle read the
presidium directory thank you garris well I hope you're able to um get that figured out or the you
know the emulation kind of pulls through I mean I get it's a newer game and it's really pushing the
boundaries of graphics and stuff so there's a part of me that kind of gets it but I also
understand how it's frustrating but it is isn't it nice that we have you know now that cloud and
streaming technology again jamie you've given more cases for why that stuff is a good thing
here on the show than any of us like you know you play dead by daylight on stadia you do you know
and uh it's it's interesting to hear how you're using this cloud technology to your benefit in
these different ways well and I'm really I'm really happy about it I mean right now the only
thing that I I would need uh my pc for is just for for mass effect and if I wanted to play dead
by daylight on on steam I'm going to log into dead by daylight on my pc just long enough to link my
steam account to it yeah so that my purchases will transfer yeah smart um but I mean I I'm still
considering keeping parallels uh and keeping her to run the windows arm because I can now play hot
a full boyfriend again um but a lot of the other games that I'm playing are available on mac like
uh I still have to play uh uh the second edition of uh homestuck hive bent um you know which uh
I've just been putting that off and I'm probably gonna stream that too but other than that I'm
also playing fantasion which uh I'm moving into I've moved it to Tuesdays to do my weekly you know
chapter so my goal is to get through like a story segment every time I play nice and so I'm really
pleased with that and then I've also just discovered a lot of other streamers um and uh I'm really
really happy about that and uh pod culture asked me if g-force now would work for me um probably
because that's how um amethyst rose witch plays but it doesn't have mass effect don't so again
because it's because it's steam linked through origin yeah and so that's where the
ea probably wants to do their own thing eventually whenever they get around to it so
right right um I mean if ea puts out a streaming service then heck yeah I'll be able to you know
the the thing is that it's still probably need to play some sort of uh copy on my computer so
that I can mod the shit out of it later well maybe maybe as some xcloud and microsoft's technology
moves along that might actually be a good thing for ea because we know that ea play
and xbox game pass have an agreement together so that could that could mean something I it's
I'm hypothesizing but maybe when microsoft's cloud technology launches publicly that's going to be a
good thing well and you know what I've saved I have saved all of my character save files from
the earlier mass effects they work but not well not one they did change the save file format for
one but two and three will work that's what I heard yeah but what this means is that when I
start making a save file for one I can use the gibbed editor and change the way my shepherd looks
nice so well you know that's always kind of fun for me you're gonna the the thing you need in
mass effect legendary dish or you you've won it the photo mode that's all you need there's a photo
mode now you're gonna have a field day oh well you realize I was doing that anyway with fly cam oh
no I know I know that's why I'm like you're gonna have a field day because now it's built in
and everyone when I'm playing again look forward to the return of mass effecting
it will happen I might do it on tumblr I might do it on twitter it it it remains to be seen but
I've had people poking me already because I mean I got like over 10,000 followers on
tumblr for mass effecting nice so we'll see all right I didn't mean to go off about that and I
will never do tick tock just saying all right uh let's move on to loki loki we barely heard from
you tonight how was your gaming week it's been all minecraft surprise no um so I've been just
more progress on the server that I'm on um dill haven't put out the second episode yet but I've
got a lot of footage I have to go through my my problem is I'm stuck in this kind of bad habit
where I keep doing stuff in the game and keep recording it but not editing that all down so
I need to find a good stopping point and then right now kind of the stuff I'm doing has more
of an episode three type stuff but it's been lots of building farms and debugging stuff I've built
a piglin bartering farm but the problem with is the normal design where you can separate them by
one block because the server I'm on they have a dropped item entity reduction thing to help with
lag and so what happens is when you drop stuff too close together it kind of clumps together
and so that broke what I have with my farm so I had to um I have eight piglins right now to trade
with but I had to drop that down the four so every other one um in order to space them out enough and
I have to figure out I'm going to do the other four probably move them around or something
but that's what I've been working on it's a lot of work it's all of this like farm stuff just to
get the supplies I need to actually do more of the creative stuff um and then there's also the
way I plan for episode three is building like an actual shop in the shopping district so I've been
working on getting it all together I have a design done for it um just supply gathering right now so
that's what I'm doing with the the farms I have um and then outside of that a little bit of orna
um that's pretty much been it it's it's the same old stuff um sacred jade in chat is asking what
game is playing behind you tonight live on twitch you've got an interesting looking 16-bit game is
that is it is ghoul patrol that is the sequel to uh zombies ate my neighbors that I don't think
ever came out over here um but that's also something that we're I think it's one of the
stories we're talking relevant it is it's relevant to pay attention all right I have never played
this one but yeah it's uh I like the first one all right we'll talk more about that later meanwhile
my gaming week um so I've been continuing in dragon quest builders 2 um you I'm still in the
first area like my gosh there's there's a lot to this game I don't know if I'm gonna get through it
um I I really don't know if I'm gonna get through it with other stuff that's released now but I I've
been continuing on in that uh playing a little more final fantasy 14 uh thanks to fan fest and
there's a special moogle tome event going on in the game right now so I'm really motivated to
get back in there and do my roulettes and stuff again so um there's that and then I'm still
playing dead by daylight myself as well working on killer and survivor unfortunately I got to
this point where like I've gotten my killer up to you know like rank 12 or 11 which you'd think
would be a good thing but it actually is really annoying because I there's a lot of killers I'm
still working on I have no talents with and uh when I get matched up with players survive I get
survivor squads that just bully me and I can't do anything because I don't have the talents to
really go up against them the matchmaking in the game is really screwed up right now and I really
wish they'd work on that and then this whole thing with the rank reset went totally I didn't
even get rank reset so that and some people got like people at high ranks got reset all the way
down to like the lowest ranks and like that I don't know why that stuff was happening but yeah
behavior I really they need to work on that bugs aside I'm still at least having fun with the game
at least I don't give a shit about my rank I really don't and at least the blood points and
development of your character always goes forward never backwards so there's that so even if I lose
a game horrifically I still get some blood points and I can develop my character and that's what I
really want so there's that um and so those are all uh the the ones you'd expect me to talk about
that I've talked about a lot of weeks and then of course there's the big one so like dark soccer
talked about um I am a huge fan of mass effect and I've talked about that ad nauseum on this program
so it is no surprise whatsoever um that I picked up mass effect legendary edition as well this week
and I've picked it up uh yes and I I decided to pick it up on xbox one or xbox series x as the
case may be um uh that's where I first played the trilogy uh was on xbox 360 and I was like you
know I want to have a nice little plop on the couch and play through game I I want to I want
to play through the game this way and so that's what I did um I bought the physical version
because I heard that the digital version was like 120 gigabytes and I'm thinking in the back of my
mind I don't have the bandwidth for that right now like we we went over our bandwidth cap last week I
can't and Alan's gonna play this too and I'm pretty sure he did do the digital so we really
don't have the bandwidth for this right now so I'm like I'll get the physical and uh that'll work um
I gotta say I love the mass effect trilogy it's one of my favorite trilogies or honestly favorite
game series that's ever happened um having played the game a little bit I love what they've done to
the original mass effect it looks a lot better um the Mako stuff doesn't annoy the shit out of
you it's it's usable um there's a there's a lot of fun that being said if you haven't picked up
the mass effect legendary edition I don't know if you should get it right now uh and that might
surprise you but unfortunately there are some problems and unfortunately this is a fucking
trend with BioWare games lately and EA games lately and unfortunately I've hit my breaking
point with this shit and that is there's there's too many bugs I don't know if the game should have
been released I don't think it was necessarily 100% ready and I'm going to talk about the
biggest bug that's annoying the shit out of me it crashed my xbox which you know whatever of
course that's going to go right after an important part of the game it crashed thankfully it auto
saves a lot I didn't lose too much progress but that was annoying and dark soccer will talk about
some of the other reports coming in about bugs and things like that later on in the show but
I'm going to tell you the thing that's pissed me off more than anything and it might seem like a
little thing but I and I don't know if this is just me being 40 so I'm going full Karen in this
moment or whatever it is but I I fucking had it with this and this is the companies and the the
internet companies and the gaming companies not figuring shit out when it comes to bandwidth caps
and us losing as a result of that and I'm gonna this is exactly what it is so the xbox version
of the game comes with two discs one is labeled disc one that says uh play disc the other one's
labeled disc two which is installation disc I want to stress the xbox disc and the playstation
discs are not labeled the same okay so when you go to xbox here's what I did I put in disc one
of course because why wouldn't I I put in disc one to fire up the game okay I'm gonna install mass
effect one and uh then uh it installed mass effect one and it downloaded an 11 gig update
uh fine all right games need updates whatever 11 gigs worth I don't know okay I thought I thought
a patch actually just patched files like actually just substituted the parts 11 but I don't know
enough about programming I guess I shouldn't talk so 11 gigs then I'm like you know what while I'm
here since I've installed the first game why don't I just install the other two games because I'm
gonna play them eventually so I go to mass effect 2 I hit install and it props up on the screen and
says we're gonna download 36 gigs press ok to continue whoa whoa wait what what
you're gonna download 36 gigs for mass effect 2 what is this other what is this other disc
okay maybe it's mass effect 3 let's go to mass effect 3 I'm gonna download 38 gigs what what
what's this other disc sake okay let me um all right maybe I was maybe I need to oh I'll launch
the game from the second disc that'll that'll fix it so I put in the second sorry you need the
first disc to start this game okay all right so I put in the first disc maybe I need a disc swap I
eject the first disc I'm kicked out to the xbox menu long story short that second disc doesn't do
a goddamn thing what is it well from sleuthing around online what I have learned is if you keep
yourself offline when you initially install the game you will use that data disc as your second
and third install for mass effect 2 and 3 and then you can patch them but if that's stupid if
you're at the point where I'm at where you've already installed the first game and so I thought
oh okay I'll put myself in I shouldn't have to do this but I'll put myself in offline mode trick it
into thinking I don't have the internet then I can install from the disc and guess what nope the game
crashes because it can't figure out that it can't download the game because that initial patch I
downloaded apparently patched out the ability to install from the discs unacceptable and I'm sorry
if I've blown your ears out but I am so fucking mad this is so ridiculous that this is happening
like is it really that hard and I admit I don't know shit when it comes to programming games is
it really that hard to just have an option when you hit install that says download install from
disk it doesn't Loki you've made a game does that sound difficult what I'm asking for no and also I
don't understand why you wouldn't just install from the disc and not I get it downloading a
patch but like you would think that you would try to conserve I mean if you cared about your
customers you try to conserve their bandwidth as much as possible especially when we're talking
large downloads thank you this is and you know what I know there's going to be some people out
there that's like Rob is throwing a fit over something ridiculous and I warned you in the
beginning I admit this is like a little but it's I've hit my fucking breaking point I need the
gaming companies and the the cable companies to fucking figure out this bandwidth issue and I need
gaming companies specifically EA Electronic Arts and BioWare I need them to figure and honestly
let's say Activision as well because I know they're guilty of this shit with Call of Duty
and I don't even play it you guys need to figure out this fucking patching problem these day one
patches these 70 80 gig patches because we don't have the fucking bandwidth for it and I'm at the
point where I'm not going to buy games anymore if I hear that there is these gigantic fucking
patches on day one because apparently the game is just fucking broken to begin with
like it's it's I I my mind is blown that there's a second disc and it doesn't do anything now at
this point and of course I've I've tried to do the Twitter thing where I've to nicely mind you
much nicer than I am now tweeting EA help Xbox support BioWare Mass Effect tweeting everybody
saying uh does this is this too not supposed to do anything am I doing something wrong what's
going on nothing of course not I'm just some jackass on Twitter they're not going to respond
to me who cares but I know I'm not the only one facing this issue and it's just and there's a lot
of people out there who don't care because they're like oh I've got unlimited bandwidth or oh I love
Mass Effect so much whatever I'm just going to take the 30 gig hit or whatever but like
as time goes on and as these you know things go on with COVID and and all this stuff like these
bandwidth issues are getting worse and worse so what am I what am and what so I dropped 60 bucks
on the game I I I opted to I could have actually gotten the game cheaper digitally because of the
Xbox game pass agreement and that whole thing with EA I could have actually gotten the game
cheaper I could have gotten it for like 52 dollars that way but I actually opted to pay the 60
dollars so that I wouldn't have to worry about the bandwidth thing and this is what happens
I also want to stress this is one example of things that are wrong with the game again the
game crashed on the as series x as I was playing through it later on Dark Soccer is going to bring
up some other stuff later that I know is affecting PCs and some people that are in some similar
issues what's like I've hit I'm sorry I'm just speechless because I in my mind I've hit this
point where suddenly some of these things we've laughed at and called frivolous lawsuits no longer
feel frivolous to me I want EA and Activision to be held accountable for this unnecessary shit that
hits my bandwidth I really do because I don't know what else is going to stop this trend
and I don't know it's not gonna they're not gonna do anything until it hits them financially
exactly exactly it's not gonna hit them financially so they're never gonna stop and it's
more like it wouldn't be such a big deal if it was like if the internet companies weren't the way
that they are and maybe and maybe that's what has and maybe that's what has to give in this
situation I don't know but it's still kind of weird though like you would think though that
it would prior illing because even like just not even necessarily bandwidth but like you're
unnecessarily like making people wait to download something and then install it when you have the
data on the disk that you just purchased why wouldn't you just use that I would think that
would even just be faster like I don't understand what the point is just just so I'm clear also
this does appear to be and somebody in chat if you know definitively can correct me from
this does appear to be an issue that is unique to Xbox because the PlayStation 5 discs
disc the one disc is labeled put me in first installation disc and then the other one is the
play disc oh yeah it's still fresh and honestly the way and that's just the way the PlayStation
5 is built with the whole backwards compatibility thing and the Xbox is built and for most
circumstances Xbox has kind of had the better backwards compatibility system but in this one
very specific case unfortunately it's it's it's fucked things up with the whole patch and
everything yeah E3VL is in chat saying second disc just launcher on Xbox second disc does
nothing but tell you to put in disc one believe me guys I've tried this every way you can think of
BioWare needs to put out a patch that allows you to install from the disc instead of automatically
going to the internet the disc I paid for that now does nothing to to do that and I I could
uninstall the 11 gigs I just did and start from scratch but that's I don't even know if that would
be a guarantee to work though number one and number two I shouldn't fucking have to and I've
had it so as much as I you know now that I've got and I've played Mass Effect and I've just you know
grinned and bared it through some of the crashes things like that and it's it's a great it's a
great remaster and you know what Mass Effect Andromeda had a lot of great shit in it and what
ruined it stupid shit that was rushed out too quick and that is why do I want to say it I'm
gonna say it this clip this is gonna haunt me so this is somebody's gonna clip this it's gonna
fucking haunt me I don't care this is why I am not buying the next Mass Effect game day one
I'm not gonna do it
this happened with the legendary edition this happened with Mass Effect Andromeda
this really happened with Anthem did this happen with Dragon Age Inquisition Dark Sakura I don't
remember not really Dragon Age Inquisition worked fine from day one okay yay so more more of that
when I started playing it I didn't notice a problem and less of your track records
you've recently developed under EA I've had it well and they also need to have arm support just
saying I I'm not gonna play the new Mass Effect because I know it's gonna get patched after a
month or two there's gonna be problems when it first releases and I'm putting my foot down this
is one of my favorite franchises ever and I really want to support the team and I am so sorry to the
team and I'm so sorry to the people that this affects when they have nothing to do with it
but I've had it period going to chat quest buster says I can echo dark soccer on Inquisition it
installed and worked right from the start for me too okay great let's have more of that then
great but unfortunately I just named three in a row that are that are a little busted let's see
uh let's see RHM087 in chat says relatively small potatoes but I'm a little salty the switch card
for Starlink Battle for Atlas requires an update of around 10 gigs out of the box yes not a fair
comparison since switch cards can't hold as much data as a blu-ray okay that doesn't discount your
point and what you're saying though is that this is an industry-wide problem it really is
like we have to do something about this day one 80 gig patch culture this is enough is enough
like okay a small a couple of gigs to patch things you know okay but this is too much this has to
stop and gamers gamers have to be willing to speak with their wallets and have to be willing
to forego some things their heart really wants to give him on and that's why I said what I said
about the next Mass Effect game when it releases in what 2024 2025 whenever it is and that's why
I'm like I'm probably gonna regret saying that because it's so far out but I've had it I've had
it so Bobby Blackwolf we were talking at the end of your show I said you might want to wait now
you know why because it's the same thing you might as well wait till they patch the crashing is the
trilogy will be great and the trilogy will still be there and I know the industry lives and dies
on you know how much a game sells in its first week but that is something that's going to need
to change too because I'm sick and fucking tired of buying games in the first week to have this
shit happen and going back to the comment on what RHM said Nintendo is about the only company
I trust to do this right I may get proven wrong in the future but Nintendo is about the only
company that's doing it right so I think I'll continue to buy Nintendo games the day they
come out but everybody else can go fuck themselves until they figure this out all right unless it's
a Dragon Age game no oh no I won't be buying Dragon Age day one either trust I I am well
and that's that's fine I'm not telling anyone else they have to do anything I'm saying I've had it
and I'll buy Dragon Age once I hear once I get the validation it's fine it works you know it's it's
okay well and you know me any of those games I don't play on console anyway yeah I know and a
lot of there have been a lot of people saying that that a lot of people playing on Steam are having
an okay time of it yeah but what again if you get past all this bullshit like I said there's a great
game in there just like just like Dark Soccer just like Mass Effect Andromeda it was a great game it
got ruined it got ruined by all this bullshit and it's it I feel like the guy in Twin Peaks
and the Red Lodge sitting there going or sorry the Black Lodge going it's happening again it is
happening again I I am gonna say my Andromeda worked perfectly as well from day one so all
right I've been very preachy I'm sorry there's gonna be people that are like Rob's too preachy
I have feelings okay I just think that we should also bear in mind that for some people your
mileage may vary yes that is true and um and maybe maybe you don't give a shit because you
have unlimited bandwidth good for you good for you know because I would like to know what part
of the world well they would like to be a part of that world they live in I installed 96 gigabytes
on my virtual machine and there's a very good play there's a very good chance folks in the northeast
who have Comcast haven't had because uh Comcast ended up pushing back that bandwidth cap thing
until next year because they were under pressure with coronavirus and everything that's great for
the northeast love you guys but what the fuck about the rest of us and this and my anger
is just as much directed to cable internet providers and the fact that in many parts of
the country we don't have choice on so we're stuck with a lot of this stuff especially in this you
know very internet tuned in age where that cap hasn't really changed I think they might have
said oh we bumped it up 10 percent big fucking deal I have some suggestions for you offline
yeah I know well there's some other things but we'll talk offline about that so anyway
all right um I've preached enough I'm sorry but I have I had feelings I got something to say
I do actually have something that I want to bring up if that's okay just a quick thing
yes I'm sorry I'm just now looking at I was so preachy I wasn't looking at my watch go ahead
Darcyra it's all right so um oh hi Renee Renee's in chat who I haven't seen in a long time me neither
um but um as everyone knows I'm from Alabama and we've uh talked to uh my mama son before
she sang a song for us um well one of uh one of her roommates that there's you know uh my mama
son my papa son uh another friend and then uh uh another friend who's actually been mama son's
best friend for a long time um but she is in hospital on a ventilator due to pneumonia and
covid and um I would just like some good vibes if y'all don't mind just some good vibes to
send uh k kitty's way I'm very sorry to hear that yeah she's she's my best an amazing person
you know she's one of those people that's better than she thinks she is so good vibes please and
please please get vaccinated please like yes yes like I know people that the vaccines are
experimental no the mr mrna stuff's been researched for years and if you've ever
taken a flu shot there's a new one of those every year as well so guess what like the the
vaccine's been around long enough like like just get the vaccine just all right yeah well and
thankfully I mean the rollout for vaccines in Alabama has been atrocious um thankfully finally
somebody in that house is vaccinated or on the way to being vaccinated my mother still hasn't
been she's like I can't find a place to do it and so wow I'm really disappointed I'm I'm and that's
I'm glad to hear a mild word knowing your mom and knowing um because I it blows my mind the vaccines
have become a political issue and that is so frustrating but knowing that your mom has a
certain stance when it comes to politics I'm really glad to hear and this is something I'm
hearing more and more which I'm very thankful is that people's parents as their kids are like
fuck yeah I'm getting vaccinated people's parents are kind of like coming around a little bit so
like I'm I'm really happy to hear that I'm sorry about the fact she can't find one right now but
I'm really happy to hear that she's open to getting one yeah um and I'm I'm trying to do a little bit
of you know digging uh on her behalf and uh I I don't know it's just I'm really worried and this
one hits really close to home because if I was still in Alabama who knows what state I'd be in
sure sure yeah so again it goes back to seriousness um and if I remember correctly I think she's
in her late 50s I think this friend of mine so just be get vaccinated get your friends and
parents and whoever harp on them so just do it um because I know I'm going to be heartbroken
if if I lose my friend all right well I I really really hope she comes around so fingers not to be
a bummer no it's it's it's one of those nights here at OLR sorry we have feelings yeah I'm just
laughing at a just because I don't know what other expression to have right now um anyway
uh I will say you know what the nice thing about being vaccinated um you know uh Allen and I are
both he got a shot uh his second shot and he's he's through the motions where he's fully vaccinated
I'm fully vaccinated we actually went to a small gathering of uh also other vaccinated people last
night probably like eight people I know in the area it felt so good you guys it's been like a
year and a half and it's like the extrovert in me was like you know and we were only there for like
an hour because it was a chance thing we went out to dinner downtown and it was like a friend
messaged and said you should come over and we like fuck yeah we will everybody's vaxxed right yep
okay let's do it so um it felt so good so I'm it's like it's a taste of what the other side can look
like if people will just please please get the vaccine all right I ran into a friend after I
was almost past my uh second vaccine and uh uh and he had been vaccinated and I just and we
just both went screw it and gave each other a hug and it's one of the first non-friend hugs I have
had in almost two years um Bobby Black Wolfenchat says and I can also explain to you why Costco
asking if you're vaccinated is not a HIPAA violation that is correct that is not a HIPAA
violation and as somebody who worked in the healthcare industry for 18 years and designed
HIPAA training for a company with thousands of employees that took the HIPAA training I will
stress to you HIPAA has to do with information and how it is conveyed from one health insurance
entity or I'm sorry excuse me a covered entity which means a healthcare provider or a healthcare
clearinghouse anybody handing handling healthcare data to another it has nothing to do with um
disclosures personal disclosure your own personal disclosures you can that me telling you I got
vaccinated that's not a fucking HIPAA violation because that's me disclosing it to you and Costco
asking that question to you is not a HIPAA violation because they're not doing anything
with your health insurance information that's a question they're asking you so you can get
through the door that is their policy and they have the right to set it as when I was a massage
therapist I also had to adhere to HIPAA which basically meant that some third party could not
come to me and ask about someone's medical conditions we signed the document I did not
disclose it basically HIPAA is a huge NDA on a personal level yeah one could argue that if Costco
then told what you said to somebody else then they would be violating HIPAA but actually Costco is not
really they they're not a they're not storing your data so it's a very different situation but anyway
we can get into the nuances if you'd like but I'd rather talk about video games right now
get my mind off of this all right let's talk HIPAA nuances no no we've had enough off topic tonight
all right let's get into past seven o'clock and not even on our first fucking story so Loki
please all right so uh I don't know this isn't really much of a shock I think but Sony is saying
that they expect that the PlayStation 5 shortage is going to continue into next year the reason
for that is the continuing chip shortage and the um the demand still staying quite high through
2021 so basically the financial chief officer uh Hiroki uh Toki basically said that um I don't
think the demand is coming down this year and even if we secure a lot more devices and produce many
more units of PlayStation 5 next year our supply won't be able to catch up with demand so continue
to expect um ridiculous queues and scalpers yay but I mean to be fair I mean not a lot of games
coming out like I don't know it I still wonder when some of these first party like really big
titles are coming out there I mean Returnal came out I guess recently but like more of
system seller type things like I haven't yet seen anything necessarily that I needed to have day one
even with the series x which I did get you know at launch there wasn't really anything that's like
oh my god I gotta get this system because of this right now yeah so I I'll have to wait and see um
She-Hulk 10 in chat is uh saying it's not a chip shortage they just don't want to pay more for the
chips yeah they don't want to their loss is only so much that they're willing to lose it no it's
still it's still a shortage because being that the supply is low that the demand is high that
the prices go up so it's still technically a shortage it's just that you know they don't want
to pay the the inflated price because of the shortage but you know you hopefully you know with
maybe the interest in cryptocurrency I don't know if it's waning it's still pretty popular um but I
know there's just a lot of demand right now so maybe that we'll see more factories you know or
I don't know if it's necessarily the you know the manufacturing of it or the actual silicon that's
you know in short supply but I guess we'll have to wait and see if it calms down sounds very 80s
Nintendo I'm I'm really glad and I'm not gonna usually hype up what this guy says at all but I
am gonna give my polite golf clap to um Elon Musk who's been quite the face of a lot of this
cryptocurrency stuff at least he's been using his platform to kind of say in these past few days
hey we need to look at something that's more green and that's something that's not like using
so damn much energy when it comes to this cryptocurrency stuff so I will give one round
of polite applause to at least folks that have a voice to be able to um realize that something's
got to change with all that craziness uh when it and look I'm guilty of it too I've gotten in on
the cryptocurrency thing just a little bit uh but I don't mind it you know I I've been basically
legalized gambling with it uh is is what it is so uh just tell them to stop putting brain uh
chips and pig heads and chickens and all that yeah anyway anyway um but back to the PlayStation
issue um I will say uh you know I'm bummed because yeah I'd like to pick up a PlayStation 5
especially with Returnal I've been watching friends play that and stream it and it looks
like a lot of fun and a type of game I'd be into it looks really cool but I like I just I'm like
I'm not gonna fight scalpers and all this stuff there's still that part of me it's like I will
get a PlayStation when I can walk into the store and pick one up off the shelf that then I'll know
it's for me um I don't really want to play these fucking games now if Final Fantasy 16 releases
this year I reserve the right to change my tune but I don't think it will and I don't think I will
so um but we'll see we'll see I'm not I'm not gonna say it as definitively as I said the other
thing I'm gonna regret um but if I can walk into the store and pick one up off the shelf I'll be
happy to do that um let's see uh Pele Hanumea in chat says whichever system had 20 million
consoles ready at launch could have won the console wars this gen easily that was always
going to be hard during COVID and even though COVID is declining as we're seeing it in the
states as more people are getting vaccinated I hope everybody realizes a lot of your gaming
consoles don't come from the states they come from other places where maybe COVID vaccinations
aren't getting around as much as well so yes COVID is still an issue even if it is an issue
in your house right now so um yeah anyhow um okay let's move on and talk a little bit about Xbox
because this is one of those things about Xbox as much as I've advocated for them uh on the program
this is one of those things that kind of didn't make sense and I'm kind of glad that they're going
to be addressing this and that is with the quick review uh resume excuse me quick resume feature
that's the one that allows you to like pick up a game and go which by the way also crashed my mass
effect game earlier today but I said I'd move on um the quick resume future is uh allows you to
pick up a game without a lot of loading time or waiting and kind of flip from one thing to another
um but it's hard to tell like what games are actually in the system's memory right now and
what's been pushed out well the good news is uh the quick resume feature is going to be getting
a little bit of a facelift with the upcoming Xbox update this month so you can see what games do you
currently have suspended on your series x or series s depending on what you're using um that's
going to be nice uh especially as more and more games are supposed to be supporting it as well
um they say uh in a announcement you will be able to list all the games currently saved in quick
resume and you can also pin that thing on your dashboard so you can get to that quickly which
is kind of cool as well uh on a somewhat related note uh Microsoft also released some new themes
uh with Xbox one uh excuse me well Xbox one and series x uh including a like anniversary background
that lets you uh kind of relive what the old school Xbox look like and uh it's kind of a neat
theme I also really like green so um I've been using that theme lately which is um kind of fun
so all right moving on dark sakura I I promised we'd get to this I I've been staring happily at
this picture of garris for a little while because he's space husband so basically um with the mass
effect legendary edition launch um of course people are having issues you know you spoke of
your own um but uh a few people are already encountering just some other in-game problems
uh one user on uh in a thread on reddit says happens walking around on citadel and spontaneously
when interacting to talk with npcs the game just disappears but I can hear the sound and task
manager it is not responding and I have to force quit and reload um other people are saying that
they're experiencing the same thing um several are saying that they're unable to uh launch the game
um and then they have like the the boot going in circles um
trying to you know like origin isn't even loading um and you know I wonder if some of that might be
why mine's not playing in compatibility mode but then again like I said uh I did by the
let's doing the same thing um on steam itself um it'll it'll get to the first boot and then
trying to launch the origin client it crashes um but there's other options that people are missing
as well so um it only supports the combat and interactive gameplay in 21.9 the cut scenes though
all go back to 16.9 using uh pillar boxes um the aspect ratio basically this one I like the term
for this they're saying it gives a sense of visual whiplash um and no one has made anything about it
um there's no graphical options no forced mouse acceleration no field of view slider
pillar box ultra wide um so yeah people are just talking about mods and patches to fix the port so
I'm I'm kind of glad that I'm not gonna play it yet um and I'm actually just watching like a little
video of people going through this so um I hear myself echoing anyway um at any rate though I think
that uh there's a lot for them to fix we're gonna see more more patches and I mean I wouldn't be
surprised that even if this is something that's on purpose that there's gonna be something up on
nexus to change it too I mean I don't know if these people are playing full screen or playing
windowed or what have you I mean there's a reason why I typically play my games windowed anyway
I get a little bit less of of that uh that massive change but even so I mean I'm on an
ultra wide screen monitor what's gonna happen when I try to play it you know
hopefully the modders have fixed the game since apparently it wasn't totally done I I don't know
it's just it's and and here's the bummer here's the real bummer especially when I'm talking to
people like bobby who is like I've always been I'm paraphrasing what I'm hearing um but bobby's
like you know I the way you guys talk about mass effect all the fucking time maybe there's
something I'm missing maybe I ought to pick this up maybe I ought to play this legendary edition
now that it's in 4k and it's pretty and I hate I hate to say give it like three months because
he may not be interested in three months and he may mean you know but but the reality is is that
it's unfortunately I think it's gonna take a little while for them to get these problems
fixed and it's just like one of those bummers where it's like I wish they would have had it
right on day one and I'm not telling people wait three months for them to do all the patches that
will definitively fix the game well see and now I want to go back on my uh my virtual computer and
try to load the first mass effect um but I mean when I was playing through mass effect two and
three um because I think they were easier to mod those two I had basically super high res
mods that would work in 1080 right and I I don't see how like what did they reprogram it's the same
engine they boosted graphics pretty much I mean they might have I mean the the first one of course
was revamped to work on that engine but I don't really I don't really get it you know well they
went in under the hood and did stuff to combat and the Mako so I mean I think they did more
with that one than two and three but yeah but yeah but I don't know it's just I I guess I'm
having a hard time phrasing what I want to say I it makes my heart hurt it's just it's just
disappointment because we know there is a good game in there and we know this shouldn't be
happening but it does and it's it's frustrating to put it lightly it's like it's like when you're
served like a layered casserole and the top layer is like half cooked turnips but underneath that
you got some lamb you got some chicken and some cheese or something you just need to
get past the turnips what was that trifle with beef and potatoes all right let's move on to the
next story which I think Loki's talking about yeah so Target has decided to post where they're
discontinuing selling Pokemon cards at their physical locations right now and this is
including actually a lot of different type of collector cards because they've had issues with
grown adults fighting each other in parking lots trying to get some of these more sought after
packs so apparently the restriction kicked in earlier this week they're going to no longer
sell the NFL, NBA, MLB, and Pokemon cards except online you can order them through their online
stores they just don't want you coming to their locations and having altercations in the parking
lot because you really wanted you know some foil card or something like that so it's grown adults
I mean what are you gonna do but yeah that's I think they're not the only store too I think
Walmart's also been cracking down on selling stuff as well so it's just can we just please
act like adults please I mean come on act Efton chat says the summary to the story FU scalpers
and E3VL in chat says scalpers need to keep themselves in check Quest Buster says this is
why we can't have nice things and Tiger Claw says it's because those cards have gone up in value
all of that yeah like it's the scalping culture I bet a lot of those people fighting over cards
are just going to flip them online and so they see it as money and people trying to steal their
money and when people try to steal money they want to fight about it and this is probably where
a lot of the scalping stuff has to get fixed too and ebay and facebook markets and all these things
really need to come together to figure out what they're going to do about scalping but you know
of course others will say well there's not a lot you can do um one thing I do like though what was
it there was a store I bought something on recently and it had I think it was actually
Square Enix when I bought the expansion for Endwalker actually um who's who's who's getting
a lot of praise from me tonight for doing things right and this is another one I wasn't even
planning but I bought the expansion and it actually texted me a code to my phone because
it was just kind of like we just need to um check this order I don't know what it was actually
checking behind the scenes or whatever but it texted me a code and I had to put in that code
but I noticed by doing that it also is making sure that I have a number in the region that I'm trying
to buy the game in uh that I'm only getting one that I'm one person and it also kind of slows
things down because I have to put in this code and all this stuff so I would love to see more
retailers kind of do this force two-factor verification which kind of slows the process
of buying things down so it's hard to do and yes I know there will be some people that are still
probably able to find a way around it and so forth but it will really cut down their their speed of
that sort of thing I think so uh ZenMonkey11 says they can't stop it it's the culture only the fans
can stop it and uh you know there there is there is very much truth in the fact that if this wanted
to end tomorrow it could if everybody could just agree to not buy from scalpers anymore
but unfortunately there's some people that are going to do whatever they want to get their kid
their damn Pokemon card um and that's another part of our culture that's kind of disappointing
I guess uh yeah Tiger Claw says the problem is eBay is enabling all this I agree but they're
making money off of it this might be a thing where the government has to step in and regulate
it or at least do that thing where they threaten if you don't fix this problem we will that's what
I'd like to see happen if you don't fix this problem we will you're starting to see a little
bit of that because I do believe the current administration or congress one of the two maybe
both kind of have said that this whole chip shortage stuff this is an issue fix it so there
you see it's starting to go that direction so we'll see all right anyhow let's move on talk
about something that's happy and wonderful and that is the upcoming 35th anniversary of Dragon
Quest did you know that series is 35 years old that's exciting and depressing all at once because
I don't know about you guys but I have fond memories of playing the first game when it first
came out in America anyway when it was Dragon Warrior and I know we got it a little later but
still you know it wasn't wasn't that long after and uh yeah 35 years Dragon Quest will be doing
a special 35th anniversary stream on May 26 to celebrate it and they're going to be giving all
the latest information on the latest Dragon Quest games so you know keep in mind there's like a
Dragon Quest cell phone game uh they're I think they did a Dragon Quest version of theater them
at one point in Japan only I don't know but the one that has everybody excited there may maybe
there'll be a builders 3 that would be pretty exciting actually but the real thing that has
people excited is that could this be a Dragon Quest 12 and there's strong hints that this is
going to be an announcement of Dragon Quest 12 of course the last game in the series was uh Dragon
Quest 11 uh but that's been out for a little while you know to the point that we're getting these
like enhanced of definitive edition re-releases on Xbox when you know it was out on the the switch
in Japan and uh the the PlayStation 4 in both regions for quite some time so I'm expecting
that we're going to hear what console the new Dragon Quest game is for if that's going to be
a Switch thing as well uh or what they're going if they're going to do Xbox parody as well who knows
uh we're going to hear all of that hopefully uh at this stream on um I said 26th of May but
actually I'm hearing the event starts at on May 28th at 8 30 pacific time so maybe is there two
of it I think maybe it's just a typo in this story because I'm looking at a big graphic that says
May 26th is when this is all happening so um look forward to some news in that capacity um
Dr Tetsuya in chat says I did finally get around to finishing Dragon Quest 11 this last year yeah
you know the Xbox release made me take another look at it so that was fun now if that's not
enough for you how about some Dragon Quest in the real world did you know there is a
Dragon Quest island that is going to be opening actually it opened yesterday uh this is the
Nijigen no Mori amusement park uh that has this attraction it's this little Dragon Quest land
um I guess you it's there's interesting pricing tiers to this uh and then you know some different
rides and things uh with all this it's been delayed a little bit because of COVID-19
but it did finally open so fun I'd love to visit someday um but probably not going to be anytime
soon all right Dark Sakura what do you have for us um I have some stuff about PlayStation and Steam
so PlayStation's Steam page is live and there's actually something that's listing number first of
all it lists 41 pieces of content but only about half of it is visible so that's 41 games and their
DLC associated with the Sony division but there's only 24 things that you can see so um the only ones
available to purchase right now is horizon uh horizon zero dawn predator hunting grounds and
hell divers um days gone is set to release later in the month but um they uh they're saying that
they want a lot more to come out they have a whole bunch of games coming out and it looks like the
evidence for it was there it's just this stuff isn't there to see yet I think we've got you know
hidden placeholders or something yeah it's interesting that there's like you know this is
going to this level of where they have like their own branded page and stuff and I know um there
wasn't as much juicy news out of that court thing this week but one thing we did get it from the
court thing last week was uh the whole news about that PlayStation it had a conversation with Steam
and and this looks to be something uh that that could be a result of that I'm sure there were
other things discussed too but definitely it seems to be there's um a tighter partnership there and
so that's interesting yeah so all right well I think Loki has some more PlayStation things
yeah so this is exciting I'm always trying to figure out what you know they're going to be
doing for PlayStation VR too and here's some more like kind of from a reliable source type of thing
so Uploaded VR had done a kind of a piece talking about the technology that's going to be
in the next PlayStation VR so some of that including foveted rendering which for those
who don't know it's using eye tracking to render just the highest resolution image
where you're directly looking and then everything around that would be lower resolution and then as
you change where you're looking at it would actually alter where it's rendering the highest
you know resolution part of that image so it allows it to save some bandwidth being able to
just render um a smaller section of the screen at a higher resolution with everything else being
a little bit less um in focus I guess uh they're saying that that sounds like straight up science
fiction that's crazy yeah it's pretty crazy um they had the uh there's gonna be an IPD adjustment
dial which is kind of uh typical with a lot of the headsets out there uh per eye resolution they're
saying is uh 2,000 by 2040 pixels um they're doing the inside out tracking kind of like the
most modern um headsets out there right now uh also they're saying that they're going to have
the haptic feedback which I assume is going to be the same type of stuff that we had um with the
DualSense 4 controllers so uh I'm sorry they're new uh controllers that they have that have that
enhanced haptic feedback I'm assuming those are going to be in the new controllers that they
put out images for not too long ago um it's still going to be a wired headset which is fine but
being that technology has gotten a lot better than what it was with the original PlayStation VR
it's just one USB type-c cable I believe which I think that's pretty manageable um what else that
we don't know when it's coming out yet of course not of course not and uh you know haven't really
seen anything confirmed yet these are just you know like I said you know from a reliable source
right now so it's all rumors and speculation until we actually get some news from Sony but
maybe this year maybe we'll find out I'm assuming some next year maybe yeah I would be shocked if
PSVR is a thing for this year I really especially in light of the continuing supply issues and
things like that um I think it'd be really wild to try to put out a VR unit when you can't put
out enough consoles to meet the demand so I I would say for that reason alone PlayStation VR
for PlayStation 5 has to be at least another year out um but I I don't make sure bets on anything
anymore exactly well I mean it's just it sounds cool I hope all that's true now um some interesting
perspective in our chat room over at twitch.tv slash vog network uh Bobby Blackwolf our pal uh
in chat is saying um that uh I'm very interested in seeing how this will work with my astigmatism
which means my eyes jiggle a lot I haven't tried any eye tracking headsets yet and you know what
Bobby uh is talking about there that's not exactly an uncommon thing there's a there's quite a few
people out there with astigmatism uh that uh I deal with it yeah and so so what's gonna happen
you know is there a way to turn this feature off that Loki's talking about or is it gonna
compensate for that somehow or I I don't know because I don't develop this stuff um but it'd be
some of those accessibility type of things are very interesting questions
especially when we're talking about new technology with VR I mean I I hope everybody gets to enjoy
it I would assume though it's very fast I mean assuming that most of these a lot of the newer
headsets you know render at about 120 megahertz I mean that's that's pretty fast I think that's
a lot faster than your eye can move so I would assume that assuming that the eye tracking is
that good and it would have to be if it's you know putting the rendering or it's basing the
rendering where you're looking um that's going to be interesting it's also going to be interesting
that they sell that data and use you know advertisements like oh let's we can now measure
advertising your advertisement engagement and stuff like that yeah that's pretty dicey there's
lots of evil yeah uh evil possibilities Bobby in chat says you don't know how fast my eyes can move
against my will well I will say this I I look to Bobby to be a voice on this because I know he's a
huge VR enthusiast he talks a lot about it on his show he works a lot with VR stuff um so so I know
I'm going to get the answer from Bobby uh when uh the PS gets closer to release and I imagine you
know I don't think they're going to talk about any of this on a big stage but I imagine they will
address some of the stuff behind the scenes when it comes to things like accessibility and what
about this what about that you know um it'll be it'll be interesting to see so all right well let
us move on and I'm going to talk a little bit about speaking of announcement type of things
uh EA Play uh you know they usually do a thing uh it kind of concurrently with e3 because e3's
changed a lot and I'm not just talking about the COVID thing but you know EA started doing their
own thing across the street and EA is going to be continuing to do its own thing this year and
what's interesting to me is that it's a little ways out it's on July 22nd this time so it's not
exactly when e3 is happening which um you know there there's probably great reasons for that
probably so they can you know have every additional day to work on trailers and things like that so
we'll see um I also think it's interesting they really invoke their old school logo
back when they were eca of the square the sphere and the triangle if you didn't know
that dates all the way back to eca and what the the loading screen would look like on old games
but anyway just a little tangent there uh they did announce it's coming back on july 22nd of course
we have no idea what it's going to cover or what games are going to talk about but you know you can
assume uh new games and all their big sports franchises that's for sure um probably an update
on dragon age quite frankly I think it's a high time to get some more on that maybe that'll
actually be a thing this year I don't know um but regardless uh there's going to be a part of me
that's skeptical about everything they announce because I'm going to be like oh is it really ready
or are they just going to put it out uh before it's done um but we'll see we can make our own
judgments in July all right let's let's go back to a simpler time you guys let's take a step back
and we're going to visit you know this is a time when you had to get it right the first time because
your game was burned to a cartridge and unable to be patched really until years and years and
years later now we have that technology but not back then uh it's the classic game of the week
and dark soccer is going to step into the gaming vault and find a game that she thinks hey you kids
should be checking this game out uh and this this I gotta say dark soccer it's I did I didn't know
this game that you picked tonight this is a pretty obscure one for me maybe I did I just picked
something that people might not have heard of um it's not even like the best game but it's it's
neat I'll say it's it's different it's different so anyway but please let's get to it so the classic
game of the week is called Pierre Le Chef is out to lunch um because there's an ellipsis so I had
to pause so at any rate um it is a video game that came out for game boy and the SNES in 1993
um it actually is another one of those games that didn't come out in Japan it's a side-scrolling
platform game about a French chef collecting ingredients for his dishes by going to different
countries to catch them since they have escaped um I'll go into other editions of that but it came
out in November 1993 in the U.S. and September 93 in Europe so it was uh European first um and
I don't think we got the game boy version in the U.S. we uh I think it was only um only in Europe
but um in 1994 it did get a release on the Amiga and the Amiga CD32 so it's it's kind of a
who who knows these games right um so at any rate um there is a single-player mode and a two-player
alternating mode so either way you play as Pierre Le Chef and you have to capture a certain number
of your ingredients before your time runs out so kind of like a little bubble bobbly you know
um the way that the levels are set up so you know you jump from platforms around and you have to
capture everything and you know you've got some you know you have basically you can set them on
fire too which is pretty fun um anyway though uh you uh you have to catch them in a net and
put them into a cage in the level and then in every level though you have to find the net
first before you can catch something so once you have all of your ingredients then you get a door
that pops up to the next level you will encounter some baddies including germs and bacteria where
if you get touched by them you lose your life the bacteria can also turn your ingredients into
hostile enemies so you have to watch out for spoiled food hehe and then there's also the
uh arch nemesis chef chef le noir um who will uh show up to hinder your process
um you can also get weapons like uh hot sauce and bags of flour you can use to
stun your ingredients and the bacteria so you have to basically take him all the way
through uh various places um Switzerland Greece Jamaica of course in this game is known as West
Indies um Mexico China and then France you have eight levels you have to navigate through in each
country and at the end of each country you can play a bonus game where you can get more points
for extra lives so once you lose all your lives or complete the game then you're given a final
scorecard that says how many points you got throughout the game and then you get a high
square ranking so there's not much out for like big reviews on this one um like uh game rankings
gave this a 59.5 um but you know it's cute and I thought you know as much as we love our our bubble
bobbles and various games as such this really makes me think of it but like a little bit of
mappy thrown in and just I mean it's a fun little unique platformer I thought
um and and again it's one of those games that had the distinction of being a fully uh western
release the music was giving me um adventure island vibes too kind of yeah yeah apparently
the um Amiga CD 32 version looks really good but I mean I think we're looking at the SNES version
we are yeah and it's don't look half bad it looks like early SNES you know because it kind of is
but it kind of looks like a port of an Amiga game which is what I find interesting about
this selection is that there weren't a ton of Super Nintendo games like this but um ironically
one you've picked recently Lost Vikings is another one that gives me that vibe where you can kind of
tell it's a computer game ported for the Super Nintendo um SimCity is strangely an example of
that but not not as much because SimCity had that Nintendo flair thrown in as well um but anyhow I
digress well another one about this is that the company Mindscape uh actually started off as an
American company and then uh was acquired by a French owner so it's now um located in uh
um it so it's a French this game is actually a French developed uh uh game they did like the
the MacVenture series Moonstone uh Warhammer Shadow of the Horned Rat a few a few uh
Warhammer and Lego Island so it's pretty it's just pretty interesting you know I
it's something that I've noticed though is that European developed games in general like during
the 16-bit era had the same kind of look and feel for the most part maybe that's what it is
it's not so much a PC you know equivalent or Amiga equivalent um but it's the European well
Commodore was so huge in Europe that an Amiga port almost kind of goes hand in hand anyway I
digress again sorry but I was just thinking maybe this is more like you can just kind of tell it's a
Europe uh kind of developed game well my other thing too is that you know the only thing that
doesn't make this distinctly European is that there's no dropping water to kill you
but anyway um so yeah it's a cute game um like the again you'll see it as out to lunch but the
full name of it is Pierre Le Chef is out to lunch I wonder does anybody in chat have memories of
this game because you know I did not know this game but when I was looking for the video the
b-roll of it and yeah you'll have a easier time kind of finding information on it if you look
for out to lunch as opposed to the full name um but uh I saw like a lot of YouTube comments that
were like oh I love this game when I was a kid or this you know so even if something has a low
you know Metacritic score or whatever there's just certain games that are always going to take us
back you know like there are games that didn't review well on Metacritic that I love um the NES
port of Ultima Exodus is a great example um it doesn't review well at all but I have huge memories
of that game there's always gonna be a special place friend who had this oh cute and we would we
would do the the two-player mode I mean I really didn't play it a whole lot but I had seen this pop
up not too terribly long ago and I was like oh that game was cute I sucked at it um and so I decided
to throw it in because it's you know the the Nintendo library in and of itself for Super
Nintendo is bigger than you think it is oh yeah um and I like to find just these little things that
might have flown under your own radar and say hey you know yeah bust out that retron or or the 400
you might have paid for the analog um a bobby black wolf is in chat and being a little bit
tongue-in-cheek or sassy asking some questions here such as it says I have questions such as
what causes these foods to escape why are we only sending a chef after these sentient foods
what happens if these escaped foods spend too much time in the sun and why do we not air drop
the chef into this war zone without a net is it Billy Mitchell hot sauce I think talking about
one of the foods there does it's on-site requisition and what does the BurgerTime
universe think of this development of more sentient foods that's it's it's hard to not
make the BurgerTime comparison when looking at this game about you know chef fighting bad food
for sure you know you know what I think of every time I see the little eggs rolling is I think of
weebl and bob remember back when I used to do the website of the month oh yeah that was back in the
day that was before your little uh facts you had the facts on the early days of the podcast
I don't know if that was a life lesson or whatever that was yeah yeah maybe I should start giving out
life advice again but this time I should charge for it um but but anyway I okay so the big rocks
are truffles this is definitely a French game anyway um they look like rocks but I always just
call them rocks like why is it eating rocks but they're truffles um but the eggs make me think
of weebl and bob which I did review the uh the website and actually one of the the folks that
works on it you know reached out to to us so um but yeah the eggs make me think of uh of bob rolling
in little nice all right so there it is your classic game of the week out to lunch or um
the full name one more time um Pierre le chef is out to lunch all right thank you very much great
pick all right it's fun to learn about new games sometimes too even years and years after the fact
all right yeah the truffle also kind of looks like a big poo all right let's uh travel around the
world and quickly check out some rapid fire news and some quick headlines loki will start with you
yeah so as you can see in my background here um ghoul patrol and zombies ate me neighbors uh that's
a brand new uh collection that's going to be released now on uh playstation 4 xbox one switch
and pc june 29th coming thanks to uh limited run games um they're also going to be doing a uh
physical version of that a little bit later on as well um if you can find that and then um yeah so
it's going to be coming with the two games so one of which i've only played i don't know too much
about google patrol other than it looks kind of similar um they're also adding art collection
soundtrack developer interviews and plus they're going to have trophies and achievements and stuff
like that local co-op so uh 14.99 is what that's gonna run you so it looks awesome can't wait to
get that a nice surprise because these are really some cult fate like the zombies ate my neighbors
is like a cult favorite i'm sure dark soccer picked it as a classic game at one point because
it's or maybe you did when she wasn't here one week but but uh it's really a cult favorite of
uh type of game and uh it's great to see it getting a re-release and some attention again
yeah and so there's always been a lot of uh rom hacks out there and one the more um i guess
popular ones for uh smash is smash remix which is the rom hack of the original smash brothers game
for the nintendo 64 um they've added lots of new characters to the game and the latest character
that they added in there is conquer from conqueror's bad fur day also they have um looks like
wolf O'Donnell is also in there as well so uh pretty cool to see that in the newest update
but yeah it's kind of funny seeing conquer with a chainsaw in a smash brothers game but
i would i would do down for seeing that in a uh modern smash game as well
all right dark soccer what do you have for us well um you know evercade is a cool little
device and their uh their launch lineup has a few people scratching their heads um so of course
they have some traditional stuff like namco museum coming out um but other two that have been listed
recently the uh jalico collection one and the pico collection two um they are pretty classic
but i think you have to kind of stop and think about what you might have played in those series
like for example the uh the jalico one has the original earth defense force unrelated to the
current ones base is loaded a styonax city connection rival turf um and then the pico
one has things like soccer kid and shut up and jam so it's it's got some craziness on there so
if you like those family of games and certainly check it out and then uh sony has new uh ps5
dual sense controllers that they have announced a fied um and i just made up that word so you can
get uh these galaxy inspired colors one of them is midnight black and cosmic red and honestly
they both look pretty sweet although the red one kind of looks like a bathing suit i just bought
um but uh the uh the midnight black will be 70 and the cosmic red will be 75 i mean maybe
red costs more or something i guess it's that red dye but it's it's damn it's gorgeous so don't lick
it yeah yeah but at any rate you know um if you want a little bit more flair to your non-existent
ps5 there you go all right all right now we're going to take a look around the world at some
games you'll be able to play on those pretty new 70 controllers or 70 plus i should say
uh starting in the us loki yeah so we have a game called archaea which is coming out on nintendo
switch uh days gone on pc there's another one of those uh sony titles for you uh leisure suit larry
wet dreams dry twice i don't know why that series is still around why are they still making those
games i don't know and then to the switch playstation 4 and xbox one uh snow runner
on nintendo switch void terrarium plus on playstation 5 akiba's trip hellbound and
debriefed on nintendo switch and playstation 4 and jonique luminaries that's on an antenna switch
layers of fear 2 on nintendo switch manifold garden on playstation 5 ruin factory 5 on nintendo
switch just die already on pc nintendo switch playstation 4 and xbox one what a pleasant
sounding title exactly it's awesome um we've got uncharted waters 4 with power up kit hd version
that's quite the name on pc and nintendo switch uh knockout city on pc nintendo switch playstation
4 playstation 5 xbox one xbox series x me topia on nintendo switch rust on playstation 4 and xbox
one and that's it all right wow busy week uh bobby black will respond to my question why are they
still making these games saying people buy them regarding allison do they though because doesn't
this i i could be completely wrong but doesn't this franchise keep changing hands because like
is sold to the lowest bidder because like all these games are turd sure i don't know if it's
this one or like the last one but one of these was a kickstarter i think this may have been that
kickstarter game oh okay i got it all right all right let's go over to japan and check out some
releases over there uh it's it's getting busy i know golden week was a couple weeks ago we had a
kind of slow week after that but it's it's picking back up again so here we go on the switch this
week in japan rune factory 5 regular and limited edition angelique luminous luminarize uh in a
regular and limited edition as well uh akiba's trip hellbound and debriefed in a regular and
10th anniversary limited edition uh the wanderer frankenstein's creature in a regular and special
edition uh and then manifold garden also out on the switch uncharted waters 4 there's some type
of power-up kit that comes with this uh there's a regular hd version and the 30th anniversary
edition that comes with this as well i'm assuming the power-up kit must be an online thing um
because it doesn't look like it's a like some of the peripheral in the box or anything like that
yeah it looks it looks a little bit like a nobunaga type of game but i could i could be
completely missing the mark there i'm seriously looking at just a couple screenshots here it's a
koi tecmo game though so uh and they are the ones with uh nobunaga's ambition so i wouldn't be
surprised if it's um related um let's see also on the switch this week we have um that's it let
me go to the playstation 5 and 4 and check out releases there mortal shell is out this week in
japan on the playstation 5 and that's it that's the big release on the ps5 this week uh probably
a little more on the playstation 4 i imagine you'll see a lot of those same twitch switch
switch titles yes akiba's trip is out uh there as well and the ninja jaja maru collection
is out uh this week on the playstation 4 as well i'm trying to see what collection this is oh this
is some old school arcade games oh and nes games wow um i'm trying to figure out if these games
were ever released in the states and what they're called it's a bunch of old famicom games and they
even have a new one in it um chad if you guys know feel free to help me out i'm trying to look
at screenshots to see if i recognize it i oh um is it kid nikki is it that kid kid nikki the
mystical ninja i could be totally wrong on that somebody else might know it's kind of what i'm
drawn to at first though yeah um a kid nikki uh was i won this it was actually a different game
it was called uh the wonderful yamcha uh yamcha maru oh okay my bad so it wasn't a going on game
okay uh oh no i know it wasn't going on game uh dark tatsuya says i think it was japan only okay
fair enough all right um let's move on uh to the uk dark sakura six things on the 18th is snow
runner for switch on switch and playstation also on the 18th is leisure suit larry wet dreams die
twice on playstation on the 20th we have super street racer um on the rest of these are on the
21st on switch we have kowloon high school chronicle on playstation xbox we have a rest
console edition and on the 21st again on switch me topia
yay a lot of people looking forward to that one yeah but i just like i kind of like wasn't
expecting that because i you know hadn't really been looking too much at the uh some of the
upcoming switch releases um but what what decade did or what year did i pop back into
where we have leisure suit larry and me topia well if you go back to the way way back uh the
original leader suit larry i'm pretty sure was in early 90s maybe even late 80s type of thing
uh and um yeah uh uh the other is a little more recent yeah yeah oh this game's bobby
blackpool's reminding i enjoyed me toby on 3ds dark soccer was the big baddie in my game because
you could you could make your friends the um monsters and i seem to remember a conversation
at e3 or something about this and you ended up being the daddy yeah that's great all right uh
let's move on then we have some more news this first story is is interesting to me but loki
i'll let you talk about it here yeah so sega i guess uh part of their latest financial results
report they had sort of i guess realized that hey they've got a bunch of these really recognizable
ip's that they've been sitting on forever that um perhaps they could remaster remake or reboot them
um they were listing off um you know some examples like crazy taxi jet set radio
uh space channel five rez panther dragon knights shinobi virtue fighter altered beast house of the
dead serisa rage soul hackers etc um basically saying that you know after careful examination
you know we can remade re-release these perhaps people would want to buy our popular games
well they have re-released a lot of those um yeah i understand that but like yeah alan get
to give alan a cheap plug he plays a lot of those games on his uh stream on the music mondays that
he does he i know he's played through space channel five part two uh and uh rez he's done before jet
set radio so like you know they have re-released those two games on steam but how do you not
realize like hey maybe this is a good idea like it seems very obvious to me i don't know oh
i'm sure go on twitter and i'm sure there are plenty of people that are saying who do i have to
bang in the parking lot to get a new jet set radio there's a lot of people that would love love love
to see that so um i hope so i'd love to see a new space channel five to be fair we did get the vr
thing um but i just haven't gotten around to playing the vr thing yet but i know i know there
is that so at least we know it's not forgotten forgotten but yeah i think i think a lot of us
would like to see uh you know some of these old sega classics make a resurgence uh pod culture
and chat uh quite loudly says just do a damn dreamcast mini ffs we all know what that means
so yeah i think there's a lot of people that would be very excited about that but it has to have the
little the little um thing the tamagotchi thing you take with the vmu thank you uh that you take
with you so all right uh dart to see you in chat says i know people beg hadeke nagah numa uh for
a new one but he just redirects them to sega i mean what's he gonna do about a new jet set radio
that's right yeah yeah go to sega all right more spiritual successors yeah um going on to the next
story which i think this is really cool and i talked earlier about like you know hey more
accessibility type of things is awesome and i i love this uh microsoft is talking about something
they are working on with speech transcription and text-to-speech synthesis for party chat
so xbox insiders actually have access to this which i i think i'm one of those so i need to
go look and see if i have access to this even though i i hardly ever talk with people on xbox
i don't know what i'd use it on um but maybe it would work on pc uh presumably i don't know but
anyway i think this is great uh so this feature is going to make it easier for people who maybe
you know have hearing or speech difficulties they can actually read what's coming up in party chat
because it's being live transcribed on the screen uh these features are in the ease of access tab
under game and chat transcription uh with this on words spoken in a party are converted to text
displayed in an adjustable overlay uh and if you have text-to-speech enabled anything you type in
party text chat will be read by a synthetic voice to the rest of the party so it's a way for you to
have a speaking voice as well if you want um so that's really cool and uh a feature i'd like to
play around with i love that i would love to have transcriptions of this podcast available
unfortunately the reality is all the services that offer it um are way too expensive like you know
and i get you know people don't do work for free so it has to and all these services i'm looking
at are actual people working so i get it but the problem is um a three hour or you know at worse
maybe two and a half two hour whenever on some weeks this podcast like it's really expensive so
i just i can't afford it but if there were some type of like automated way to do it which somebody
was telling me to use youtube to do the transcriptions and um i it's not youtube isn't
great at it but it might be a start um so yeah i i would love to have that um just even for this
show check on some options yeah that'd be cool just if it costs money the answer's no all right
the answer might be maybe all right um depends on who's fronting it yeah so um all right let's move
on uh i think this one's two years dark talker yeah i was just about to start it now this is
already passed so this was actually for friday uh may 14th um itch.io uh held its first ever creator
day which i don't know how that went um but they were they went to forego its usual cut of sales
um so a hundred percent of any transactions that day after taxes and payment processing fees
were going directly back to the creators so basically it was a good way to to put these
indie developers give them a little bit more money in their pocket i mean and the thing with
um with itch.io already is that they have a default 10 cut of sales but it could go
between zero and 100 depending on what the developer wanted to do um and so they take a
much smaller cut than the 30 industry standard um so i thought it was really cool that you know
they gave back yeah i was gonna say i'd known about it i know i wish i'd known we would have
hyped your game more to get uh sold then but uh s is showing her matt does remind us in chat
speaking of itch.io loki's game is on it and drops the link there to uh buy pixel poops number two
i appreciate that and i sold uh just reordered my labels because they got screwed up the first time
so still working on that physical edition all right nice all right well maybe we'll do another
one of those uh creators day again uh in the future that would sure be nice all right meanwhile loki
all right so um you know this is kind of funny because it's almost like a meme here but
uh we we remember the ever given container ship on the suis canal well apparently uh
nintendo's switch shipments were impacted by that now i might say though that's a likely story
nintendo that your your shipments were this is the reason why there's a shortage on your consoles
right it's because of this um i'm skeptical if you may say um but apparently they said yes that
that caused delays for the product in europe and some of the uh inventories are a little bit tighter
in those countries sure sure nintendo we'll believe you this time but i'm skeptical i'm on to you
you think it's just a convenient excuse i'm sure that they'll say that the ever given like the
digital version of the ever given is just like it's just jammed into the e-shop that's why we
got to take down mario you know in march because it's just that mario games just can't get through
there so i don't know i don't i'll believe them this time uh bobby blackwolf in chat says remember
that ship didn't just block its own stuff it blocked all ships yes it wasn't just about the
one ship that was stuck but obviously it caused a traffic jam uh but like the worst possible kind
that went on for weeks really um no so yeah it's just like nintendo always has hardware shortages
on everything so this doesn't help but i think what i think when it happened we all sat here
going it's not going to help you know so right yeah there is that all right um let's move on
and uh get to our last story tonight which is rumor-based but these are rumors that are
gaining a lot of steam so you know take for it what it is they're rumors um but anyway uh so
there's uh this blogger out there zippo that i guess has got some things right before and
it's kind of talking about what nintendo is doing for the rest of the year um and i guess based on
his track record some people are kind of you know running with it a little bit so what is it that
he's talking about for the rest of the year and this isn't the first time i've heard of this
apparently a 2d metroid is something that's being worked on and that apparently it's it's done and
it's ready to go um so that would be something if we got that really soon you know i love mesa
metroid apparently runs at 60 frames a second but you know as i would encourage everyone else to do
don't set the bar high with this stuff i'm not gonna okay i'd love this but i'm not going to
assume it's happening metroid prime 4 is happening nintendo's confirmed that someday apparently a
donkey kong game from the folks behind mario odyssey is being made it is uh like a 2.5 d type
of game sounds a lot like like the tropical freeze type of thing uh it could be very interesting so
that is something that's being worked on as well as a new fire emblem super mario party 2 more 99
games uh and um apparently and what i think is interesting about this rumor and one reason why
i'm willing to kind of believe it a little more than others is that they go as far to say zelda
2 not this year so i think that's interesting that they're actually kind of placing the bet
there that that isn't happening this year uh and the reason why uh issues uh raised from the
pandemic it's almost complete but the end of the year doesn't seem feasible but it seems plausible
if we want to go back to that word uh that nintendo could announce uh that it would be like
a spring type of game so maybe the same release time frame as say animal crossing since clearly
they can put out a new zelda whenever they want they don't have to do it for the holidays uh they
could do it whenever they want and it'll still sell like crazy and then of course a big one the
new mario kart game there is a new mario kart game that's being worked on as well however it
may not be mario kart 9 um and the the blogger here doesn't know if it's maybe a mario kart 9
or if it's nintendo kart or maybe an expansion for 8 or something so like isn't willing to kind
of place stock in any of those but that there is a new mario kart in development and that that
is coming at some point so you know this is what people are talking about on twitter and things
like that uh certainly a list like that it's it seems believable enough but again i'm not
going to place bets on anything who who called the game builder garage thing nobody so that came out
of left field so i think there's also a lot of there could be unexpected stuff as well and there
are some things in there that are kind of safe bets again we've heard the 2d metroid thing before
uh to say breath of the wild 2 isn't going to make it because of covid um isn't that big a stretch i
know i said but it's not that big a stretch um a new mario party and a new mario kart of course
you know even though nintendo killed mario some of his franchises are still popular and so they
will weekend at bernie's him through some more games uh to make the money so uh tiger class says
would that world circuit be considered mario kart 9 because there's jokes that's joe 100 matt saying
mario kart 10 they're skipping the nine uh i i mean they could do anything they want you know the
the blogger said what about nintendo kart it doesn't even necessarily need to be a mario kart
what if it's super smash kart i don't know like but i could see that maybe nintendo wants to go
beyond just mario i don't know we'll see we'll see um but i think it will be mario kart 9 or
it'll be i don't want to say a reboot but it'll be like a re like it'll be a mario kart's world
or mario kart's universe or mario kart like they'll give it a new subtitle that kind of takes
it away from the other sequel games we'll see oh and uh the folks are talking about the home circuit
yeah home circuit was like a spin-off it was a different thing that's a good call out because
that was a good example of something different that wasn't in the mainline games no that was not
canonically mario kart 9 um but good call yeah that that was short-lived in my household too
yeah yeah i mean i i'm i'm no more physical things from nintendo anymore i'm not purchasing anything
that has a physical device because it's just not going to get used ever whether that be labo or
the mario kart thing it's just it's not worth it boy we're making a lot of big statements tonight
all right let's get to our listener round table if you have some comments you'd like us to discuss
in our chat room over at twitch.tv slash vog network we can certainly get into those um and
then of course we want to check our emails you guys email us every week over at participate
at orange longtrady.com and dark soccer is going to dive into the mailbag and get some emails uh
for us no i'm not oh are there none tonight nothing boo yes we have no bananas and i don't
even think i have really anything on drag race there's literally nothing to discuss i'm not
watching the drag race down under so now what happens oh okay i'm laughing i have no tea to
spill so okay i will get to the discord comments but i have to get to this this is making me laugh
as 100 mad is asking so rob how does it feel to go viral this week i finally after years and years
on twitter had a tweet that ended up getting like a thousand plus likes on it so i'd say it went
pretty viral even though when i told alan about it he was like well a viral tweet would be like
20 000 likes and it was it wasn't even it's weird that's the interesting thing about what tweets
hit is that i've had some tweets that are pretty fucking funny that don't go anywhere people don't
retweet them i might get 40 or 50 likes from my followers but it doesn't get retweeted or anything
so it doesn't really go and that's fine that's okay but like the tweet i wrote that went viral
so what it was it was a play on this whole there was some dumb magazine or something that had a
feature that was talking about geriatric millennials in the office place that apparently they're now
leading tea i don't even know what the article was about i didn't want to link it because i
didn't want to give it the hits but everybody on twitter of course is dunking on this term
geriatric millennials i think loki would qualify as one with his age yeah but dark soccer and i
what the fuck does that make us we're technically gen x at that point not even a millennial though
because i'm 1980s so okay so you're like right at the end there so so i i just that would make you
gen y i just i just made this sassy tweet and i found um a picture of a skeleton at a computer
and i put me i put me born in 1978 reading about geriatric millennials that tweet got fucking like
a thousand likes on it and like a hundred retweets so it's it's weird is the answer to that matt i
mean i'm just laughing at it because like it's always the stupid tweets that go viral um the
closest i ever got before was um like i think i think i got 300 or 400 likes on a tweet that was
using the hashtag um national send a nude day and it was just like a gif of judge judy and i just
put times almost up national send a new and i got like 400 likes it was a gif of judge judy banging
the desk going hurry up like it was stupid like i wish one of my tweets about video games would get
or a tweet promoting the show but we all the the reality is twitter doesn't do that all right anyway
they haven't found our show by now i i know it's a lost cause at this point um all right so there
there's my answer to your question in chat as to another man all right uh going to discord um i've
been uh starting to read discord comments you guys leave throughout the week over at vog network dot
com slash discord in the orange lounge radio channel and uh thank you tiger klai so you posted
that a movie i talked about at the top of the show so appreciate that um interesting a tweet from
corkay in our uh orange lounge radio channel that um blizzard is relenting on the uh cloning fees
i didn't even know they were doing this they were gonna charge 35 dollars to duplicate your
character holy fuck i thought that was something they were doing for free well apparently they've
retreated 20 worth so now that cloning feature is gonna cost 15 dollars woohoo i guess thanks
thanks for that hell uh dark sakura uh tiger claw reminded me of this in our discord did you see
this week the mass effect video that had all the fans talking about what the series means to them
and all that cute stuff all the like cosplayers and stuff you should go check it out uh tiger
claw linked it in our discord so be sure to check that out vog network dot com slash discord new
orange channel at the one minute and 44 second mark our friend travis donovan is in it um he
doesn't say anything but it's his uh when he renewed his wedding vows at dragon con and he
was dressed us up as shepherd and jenna was dressed up as miranda it's it there's it's really
quick it's like them embracing after saying i do but uh that was the thing so it's it's actually
in the video that's really cool so that's sweet yeah it was i i and uh you know when they uh
when that part came up it was like i know them i know them actually and actually that wasn't
the only person i had a twitter uh mutual that was in the video a little more featured talking about
um like the gay representation in mass effect and what it meant to him so um there's a lot of
a lot of like wow this is a small world i almost feel guilty for going off earlier but i don't
i mean like you can love a game and still be pissed off that it's not given the love and
affection it deserves we it's that's what it is we protect we we protect our babies uh and that's
that's what it is when it comes to mass effect all right um let's see oh tiger claws link reminds me
of this did you guys see loki you had to have seen this all the hubba balloon around the calculator
game on nintendo switch have you seen this i saw that they had like a calculator app yeah and it
looks exactly like the iphone calculator like right on down to the colors but it's like a
scientific calculator going for 10 bucks but internet gonna internet this is like the whole
like rage like oh man this calculator is the best thing ever it does everything it says it's gonna
do it's so powerful and it's like i don't know why this is becoming a meme but internet what can you
say they have like like there's like art programs and stuff on there as well like nobody's making a
big deal about that i guess it's just silly that calculator's on there yeah whatever you know um
act deft asking the real questions can that calculator run doom um i don't think so because
it doesn't have that kind of screen on it but but never say never act deft um w04 in chat asks
what are the chances of a new maximum carnage video game now that the new venom movie is coming out
um i mean as good as anything else uh but usually like i feel like they haven't like the marvel
and even dc stuff they haven't really been doing a lot of like this is something the industry used
to do that they don't do as much anymore they haven't done a lot of stuff directly from like
current movies it's like the avengers exists in its own universe in the games now and it's not
just a port of the movies right some spider-man skins maybe and that's about it yeah that's
probably it but again never say never all right um let's see never ever never ever sj100 matt and
discord with a big headline we didn't get to tonight uh bobby talked about it a little more
on his show but it's the whole hubble about starfield from bethesda is going to be exclusive
to xbox and pc uh originally uh it was thought that this game was going to be exclusive to sony
but is anyone surprised that microsoft bought bethesda and now this game is going to be
exclusive it'll probably be just like a timed exclusive maybe well i don't know if it's gonna
be a complete exclusive i want some of that money it is suggesting that it is a complete exclusive
and it's going to show up at this e3 and it will release in 2022 nice so uh we'll see hope it
doesn't suck i'm more interested in the uh new uh sky or new skyrim new elder scrolls game whenever
that comes out yeah all right um i think uh let me see if i can get through a couple more of these
but first let me go to uh loki and get some last minute stories and then i'll do a couple more
discard discord yeah i don't got any of those what all right um looked there wasn't really anything
worth covering i'm sorry i want to say marcus in our discord uh shared that article about the ps2
exploit that talks about uh certain versions of the system being region free you have to scroll
up a bit because he posted it on may 10th but i know that came up on a previous episode of the
show um so there is that um going back okay well here i got something um so ebay is banning the
sale of adult video games so they're going to be implementing a new adult items policy on june 15th
and they're going to be you know blocking anything that's basically unrated you know triple x x um
also explicit uh comics books films animation manga hentai yaoi um i don't know if it that
necessarily applies to video games though but maybe if it's unrated so sorry no bmx triple x
uh used or i guess you're not gonna find that anymore you have to go to the facebook marketplace
for that we have to steal it online like a lot of people do these days not that you should do that
now you should do that but sometimes when it comes to games preservation we're left with minimal
choices all right i want to mention this in chat so bobby blackwolf in chat is talking about this
and dark soccer this is up your alley um literally in a way uh was this was there something earlier
about mandalorian pinball no i didn't bring it up because you did bobby so we we don't always
have to talk about the same things but uh dark soccer of course is a pinball geek so i think
the world wants to know her reactions you're not getting it bobby is so you can fly to atlanta and
play to his house there's already a bunch of people who are like selling their pre-orders
on ebay that well it's probably because there's the whole like three editions right you talked
about a black knight table recently that had this whole thing there's like a limited edition
a extra edition the same thing's going on with the mandalorian yeah well the thing the the big thing
is is that we just got a new to us uh pinball anyway we have uh the jersey jack guns and roses
oh cool yeah it's really cool i actually i actually kind of like it i want to come over
and play pinball come over yay all right let's play come over tomorrow uh maybe
don't you stream on mondays no alan's yes oh i actually stream on mondays earlier
oh well yeah after the show and all that but yeah yeah all right after what show the the one we're
on tomorrow oh tomorrow well i thought i thought i'd do tonight i do monday and i do tuesday
okay all right i'm so confused all right uh at some point it doesn't have to be tomorrow
just whenever uh come over and play pinball um and then in in uh september hopefully uh enough
people get vaccinated where dragon con can be a thing and uh even if it's a little even if it's
a downscaled show this year which i'm expecting that might be the case they'll probably still
have dragon con but they're probably going to do some things to try to not have people gather
quite in mass as they do but i don't know i at the same time my perception's fucked because i'm
in california not georgia and my understanding is things are very different out there so
it might just be the same old dragon con we'll see but i i know the folks behind it will not have it
if they don't think it's going to be safe i have that trust because i know there's people many
people in atlanta who work at the cdc so uh and uh many folks on dragon con because of that but
anyway assuming i get out there um in september i will look forward to playing bobby's table he'll
have it by then right i think so i think so um which by the way they changed my flight out to
dragon con i had to call delta to try to get an earlier flight i was on hold for 40 minutes and
still didn't get through so i have to try calling again tomorrow because the online wouldn't do it
for me trying to get on an earlier flight because um it has me getting there at like eight getting
to the airport at like eight o'clock on wednesday eight pm and that's um pretty late in the day so i
want to catch a early morning flight and get there a little sooner if i can because we have a
tradition we always go to that 24 diner around the corner on wednesday night and that was the very
first place i took alan when we went to atlanta was that little diner where he drank way too much
sweet tea and uh we always go there on wednesday nights before the craziness kicks in and if i get
there that late i mean i guess they're 24 hour but still still still still all right um okay
i think i think that's about it uh i think uh we're gonna wrap up that's about the end of the
show uh before we do let's get some final thoughts um let me say of course as i always do here at the
end of the show thank you for listening to orange launch radio whether you were listening live here
at the voice of geeks network or you were listening on our podcast feed we appreciate you
help us spread the word we are the show where every gamer has a voice tell a friend or two
about the show a nice five-star review on a site like itunes or wherever it is you found this show
goes an awful long way thank you so much thank you to those that go the extra mile with their
subs and bits and all that stuff here on twitch we really really appreciate you and the fact that
you do that um and we're working on more behind the scenes to try to give value for your twitch
subs so please uh please look forward to it as they say um auto hosts on twitch go a long way
as well those of you that auto host the vog network channel thank you thank you thank you
really appreciate that um and i hope you all have a wonderful week gaming and uh as we talked about
at the beginning of the show gaming is so much more than pixels on a screen i just appreciate
you guys that spend your sunday nights with us or whatever a two-hour three-hour period throughout
the week you dedicate to listening to olr even if we're your background noise while you do your
day job hey i'm glad we could be there with you and i hope i hope the customers didn't suck today
all right um let's uh let's get some final thoughts um loki i'll start with you your final
thought uh my final thought is i'm hoping to have episode well i promised episode two will be out
this week for my youtube series i'm starting it's not really a series yet because there's only one
video but it will be a series eventually um so that'll be out this week episode three will be
much sooner than that because i'm pretty much already filming everything for that so i'll just
turn around that much faster but um yeah look for that all right and dark sakura i'll let you have
your final thought um stay tuned i'm gonna play dead by daylight and try to get a gnome all right
good luck with that yep all right and my final thought um i don't really have a good one there's
there's a lot of exciting and scary stuff going on in my personal life um just send your good vibes
my way um there's a lot a lot going on i will talk about it on the show but it's going to be
a little bit so um yeah um nothing of concern nothing of concern um okay that's it and gaming
is for everyone i think it's a good note to end things on yes it is as well since we always talk
about gaming is more than pixels on a screen i think it's a good reminder gaming is for everyone
don't you forget it have a wonderful week everybody have a great stream tonight jamie
have a great week everybody gaming we will see you next week here on orange lounge radio
good night you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr
studios to join us for a live show tune into fog network.com sunday nights at 6 p.m pacific
9 p.m eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those
of the staff of orange lounge radio or vog network but you know they were all still true
see you next week
so