You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, the Monty Talk, and then some.
Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
Orange Lounge may contain hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge will not contain hot monkey sex. In this episode...
Hey, are there any balls down there?
About the biggest bear you've ever seen, Diggleberry.
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls. Absolutely frightening. What's yours?
There are no stupid questions, just stupid people.
Don't torture yourself. That's my job.
Now's the time on sprockets and we dodge!
I don't get you, my pretty!
And your little dog, too!
I know kung-fu.
I'm sorry, but all questions must be submitted in writing.
Why did they have to take the word gay?
No! What he expects for Spanish exposition is kendo.
Hey!
Dark Sakurai.
Shut up!
Where's my gun? This is my boomstick!
Skye.
Come on, girls, it's time to drop the bomb!
I can't, for the life of me, get the hooker to have sex with me.
What kind of war human being would find that funny?
Orange Lounge Radio
We are live, and this is episode number 44 for May the 11th of 2003.
You're tuned into the Bamani Scene's most sleep deprived radio station of all things Be Money.
Also with us tonight say hello to intern zero. I can't get this fucking cookie out of the package
Like pissing me off. That sounds kind of sexual
Damn it. I'd now like only gonna be able to get that one out
That was great Jamie went and she got the cookie out of the package and then she ate it
That was almost zing worthy
Nice, she got one for me
Redeemed so it's just the four of us here tonight
kostjamrh And they're like dark German chocolate, but it doesn't really taste like dark chocolate, between two thin cookies, and it's really good.
kostjamrh And it tastes good too. Are these people moving?
kostjamrh Yeah, our neighbors are moving.
kostjamrh Good.
kostjamrh You don't need neighbors.
kostjamrh Mr. Rogers isn't around anymore, we don't need neighbors.
kostjamrh You're so nice, everyone's so nice here.
I got his and that thingys.
This MP3 is two and a half minutes, which for a 2DX song, that's a long-ass time.
The intro was really long.
Yeah.
So it was when we go,
Two and a half minutes?
Well, then it's a possibility, but it's kind of, you know, we're not saying it's official.
We're not saying it's official, but it might be.
And if it is official, then we were the first to play it, right?
So enjoy this. We're going to play this V remix by Naoki.
And then we'll play something from Taka and something from Naoki.
And then we'll be back.
Enjoy!
Oh
Love me, you love me
You love me
Orange Lounge Radio, we put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
I can say words in reverse, too.
Do it.
Mom, God and dog, radar, or that'd be radair.
Race car, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, race car.
Speaking of mom, happy Mother's Day.
Happy Mother's Day, and I didn't let my mom listen to the show.
to all of our mothers out there listening, which hopefully is none of them.
Mom's like, I want to listen to your radio show.
Um, no you don't.
My mom knows I have one, but I think her and my dad made the mistake of listening to about
two minutes of Undersedation Live once.
And not only that, but it was the same night my sister was on too.
And I think it was probably the same time that Travis was giving her the sex quiz.
So needless to say, they won't be listening to any future radio projects I have.
We don't do the sex quiz on this show, though.
No, we don't do the sex quiz on this show, but it's still pretty bad.
You know, it's too bad, though, that we do Rocky on Saturday nights, because we can't listen to Travis and Jenna.
Well, I'm trying to see if they're ever going to rebroadcast their show.
I know they do. They have new shows. They have spin-off shows now.
They have, like, the 80s show and some club, goth club show that Travis does.
So, oh, yeah, so we'll plug Understation Live, our buddy's over there.
Yeah, goth talk.
Hello.
So, Jamie, I know you had some comments on that supposed ninth-style song.
It's a piece of shit.
If that was Naoki, then it means that Naoki sat on V and farted, and out that came.
I'm sorry.
As much as we bag on Naoki, he's very talented.
And I know he could do much better than that. That is not Naoki.
And anyone who thinks that that's Naoki, who actually believes that that's a Naoki remix, needs to get their head examined. Or either that or get it out of the toilet.
So what are you going to do if it comes out that that's real?
Are you going to have a cry?
No, I'm probably never going to listen to another Naoki remix again because this is all Salva's talent.
We let Paul Eteri remix it and put his name on it.
Oh, maybe that's it. Maybe let Paul Eteri do all the work this time.
this time
i can tell that it's unique
it's special
um...
first of all i was in band music theory and appreciation i start off as a
music major
i have listened to winter so many times it's not even funny
and um... i could tell that the that uh... second half of the song
was completely ripped from winter it was actually you know
unique parts
so that could is the only way i could think that that's a new mix
But Naoki could do better. So much better.
So I don't think that's Naoki.
As like Le More et La Bierte, which is the other song we heard in there, the last
song we heard in that break, which is a good Naoki song. Very good Naoki song.
And in the middle there was Tomorrow Perfume.
Everybody knows that one. From Taka.
That song pissed me off.
Why does that piss you off?
Just because it's difficult. It's a seven.
Have you seen the latest custom non-stop that's in our machine at Scandia? No.
it's sad i mean it's like a really hard decided that one goes in the i'd i'll
give you two guesses
and the first guest are too many and ends with rick
uh...
it
uh... issue let me go but one and i'd be like
seven-star jamie can pass with me
we have no issues on the point
the uh... way to be like ones you almost passed
they come really close
But no, this is the songs that he has in there.
Summer Vacation, Tomorrow Perfume, Traces, Xenon, and A.
And you know what's really fucked about that?
You can't change your speeds in the middle of the nonstop
course on 8 style or whatever.
When you're playing 2DX nonstops, you
can't change your speed.
So whatever speed you play Summer Vacation on, like I
play High Speed 3, you have to.
You have to play A on.
What are you talking about?
When you just take a hit right after, like right before A,
then everything is like bullet time, just like
i see the keys coming down
yay
you and drugs
you should
i'm just kidding don't do drugs, drugs are bad
drugs are bad
i'm very happy
why are you happy?
because i just had a cookie
you know what that whole drugs thing reminds me of?
omni crash made a song called bemoni song
is that the one that sounds like the sunscreen song?
yeah here we go
clip don't play the whole thing please
it is short but you gotta play the best part in the middle right after 100 seconds
Oh, sorry. That's just me, though. No, I don't know. That song is so funny, especially when it talks about jokes.
I want to hear the whole thing.
You'll like it, but he can't say D-W-I. He says D-W-I.
D-W-I.
Okay, what we'll do to make this interesting is we'll let Loki play the whole song, and we'll make live commentary.
It's just, like, funny content. I'm going to download it again.
Alright, Logie's gonna find that, so we'll broadcast that to you in a little bit.
What else is new? Any other Mother's Day thing? What did you guys do for Mother's Day today? Did you call your mom?
I called my mom on my cell phone driving into his house.
Driving into my house?
I was turning to go down the street to your house and I was on the phone with my mom and I had to hang up with her.
Because I'm not... I prefer not to be retarded and drive and talk on my cell phone.
Because I would likely...
I know you do it, and I still think it's retarded, okay?
I tried to call my mom. She didn't answer her phone. I don't think she wants to hear from me today.
But we only talk like once a month, so I mean-
Are those your neighbors that I hate?
No.
The ones upstairs?
No, the ones downstairs.
Oh, poo. I wish the ones that I hate would move.
I can go kick their door in. No, I'm just kidding.
The ones that I hate?
Yeah, when we met them, they were nice.
The people over there?
Up here.
Yeah, they were.
anime is better than sex
I hate this political crap.
Can you hear the song?
Hold on, hold on.
Wait, ah, what's this say?
George W. Lazardo, it really does say that. That's sad.
Alright, let's hear the song.
There you go.
Loading, loading.
This is the Bimani Sims song.
Can you hear that below?
Bimani Rulers V was not the greatest DLOI ever.
Neither is his A.
We're going to do it again.
sped up with different sound effects.
Pretty much, yeah.
Kevin is not actually a 57 metallic gray.
That's debatable.
Ever notice how all the best deal of the wise
were made in a notepad, not set mania editor?
How would you know?
Kevin is only as cheesy as he wants to be.
I don't, I don't, I don't.
We need more LEDs-
That was dumb.
Last message for you.
Paranoia Survivor and Paranoia Survivor Max are the same song.
Thank you, yes.
Stop DWIing Sakura.
Anyone with a name like Dynamite Rave 68246 Ani is not to be trusted.
Okay, yeah, huh?
All the things she said has been done.
I don't care! It's a great song.
All the things she didn't say.
My next two DWIs involve poltergeists and pants.
X-step is the antichrist.
Bemani style owns me, yes it's true.
At least 100 seconds is enough time for me to get a sandwich.
Moogle Hunter is on speed on possibly
every other drug known to man. You know that's actually true.
The world needs more spontaneous para para dancing. The background to Zenon
is really stupid. Yes! Not every song needs
challenge steps. That's true. I'm done.
Good.
Oh, you spent. Good. Shut up. I'm just kidding.
You know what's funny? How come we've never had Moogle Hunter on this show? He frickin' lives not too far away.
On drugs.
Yeah, because he's too busy doing drugs. Apparently.
And then to quote Dennis Suri, when he dies we'll smoke his ashes.
Who did that song? Who gets credit for that?
Omni Crash.
He didn't say Oni, right?
Yeah, he mispronounced a bunch of words.
He must be Canadian or something.
Why?
Is he Canadian?
Yep.
Because Canadian's pronouncing's funny.
What the hell is circular?
Yeah, he said like circular and D-U-I's.
Zenon.
I think he's Canadian.
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
Whenever you make a mistake, just pretend you're Canadian.
I'm Canadian.
Hey, I fucked up.
I don't expect you to be smart.
You should put the right emphasis on the correct syllable.
uh...
because he's thinking about his blood job that is getting right then
and i'm thinking about it has to adapt i'm thinking about the new intro and all
the clips from jamie i think that
I'm going to do a video here and do a blowjob, you know, that's great.
This is why you told your mom not to listen.
Well, this works.
street blowjobs
did well that's why it is not just it would have to freeze on you
he's media player
in the meantime i will do a song and dance as many of you will see who are here
beautiful beautiful
roc did a nice dance last night
i was here watching across the screen in a tutu
i have never had so many people yelling at me
in a tutu
come to think of it i've never wanted to do before last night really it's easy to
be you should have won at least the frank wager something
i know i should have had a way that you were still fabulous trying to dig up a
way backstage we can find one of the we literally pulled that routine out of our
ass
you know it's ironic to you or my outfit i want to get me up there
did they try
and then he tried to get me to go in for a minute that he doesn't know
you know it's time you want to help
a little shopping yeah what are you uh shopping for
okay listen i'm gonna be honest with you do you want to uh be interested in making a little
extra money hey to help you out with your shopping oh yeah okay all right then dude
That looks like Arden Fair.
Oh my god, it does!
Now I'm following you.
for some company. I just wondered if you're interested.
Um, what do you have in mind?
What do I have in mind?
Film a server, that's not going to turn the blood off.
Oh, but...
So, like, out of that whole thing, there were, like, maybe two seconds of a blowjob.
Dude, you should send that...
Obviously an actress.
You should send that to Evan for a pre-show.
That totally, I swear to God that's a mall I've been to.
I think it was one in L.A. though.
This is the sad thing. This shows you like what a queer I am, okay?
I recognize the Campbell store in the background.
I want my old papa blocker back because this one sucks ass.
hey while you're on that site give me the one for uh... new york
yeah anyway what are we talking about before we start talking about sex
oh yeah our moms um...
because without that our mom we wouldn't be here today
dude we were having a cool conversation though at that truck stop
uh... but that's great
Some people we know were likely conceived.
We're talking about life being a sexually transmitted fatal disease that's hereditary.
That's the secret of life?
It is a sexually transmitted fatal disease that's hereditary.
Think about it.
It is.
Hmm.
Kind of makes you think.
Things that make you go, hmm.
We should have philosophical quote of the evening.
I think that should be it.
That could be something that we bring in for season three type thing, you know, our new
and improved Orange Lounge Radio.
We improve the quality of your life through higher thinking, mainly because some of us
might be high.
I don't know.
I don't do drugs.
I drink soapy.
I don't do drugs either, but I do eat a lot of sugar.
That stupid old people store didn't have any for pal.
You went to a stupid old people's store?
We went there with a price less.
Oh, God, that is an old people's store. I don't know people's stores.
But, like, if you need to get, you know, like, toothbrushes and all your drug store needs there,
it's really cheap and you can get prescriptions, they're cheap too.
That's the only store where you walk in and you have lawn furniture, lawn care, you turn the corner,
have herbal, like, stuff, and then you go back around and you see nothing but prune
juice and diapers. Tampons! Tampons! Tampons! Do you need a tampon, Rob? Are you feeling
not so fresh? They just have diapers for that over there. And like, their soda is like one
case. They don't even have like, anything. And there's like the whole section dedicated
to soy and wild yam products. For women who need their energy. Spam, spam, spam, spebity
No, wild yam. Women can take it when they're going through menopause to help with hot flashes.
See, something that none of you people probably knew. I worked at GNC for a long time.
I needed to know.
Trust me, women, you're going to get through menopause in one day. Mine's 20 years off.
I'm never having kids either.
Dear women.
Dear women, this is Jamie's herbal tip of the day.
You smoke the weed, not eat it.
Somebody in the chat room is insinuating that I have that not so fresh feeling.
You don't.
I feel, I've been feeling a little, I wouldn't say I don't feel not so fresh, I just feel
not so like...
See, I think, I think that Frank would have been in a better mood if he had feminine wipes.
See, he was probably getting, from all of the rampant mookie that he has been known
for, if he had just cleaned himself up a little bit, he wouldn't have been so itchy and would
have felt a lot better.
And been nicer to people.
Maybe if he had a puppy.
I was a little bit itchy after last night's show, because I just sweated so much.
Has any of that stuff been washed?
The costumes?
They wash them, they don't wash them every week, but they wash them like once a month.
Okay, cause I was gonna say, it's probably a good idea.
I do wash my underwear.
No, I wasn't talking about your underwear. I don't care about your underwear.
If you want to wear itchy underwear, you can.
That's your prerogative.
That's my ride as an American.
If I want to wear dirty underwear in public, you can't stop me.
No, we'll buy you panty liners.
Hey look, your neighbors are moving.
Hi neighbors.
No, you know why.
right now is in the middle of it
low-key what are you doing
i was getting my acid for work because uh...
i have created my computer and i'll talk about that later
delay
are you to make the a speed remix here at the end of the a male key remix
oh yeah i know i have to find it on the internet cuz i think i know a place
where it might be is going to download it from
from mbz.com, you know, my butthole.
See, I could probably sit on a record and fart out a better remix than that one.
I'm not going to still use record player.
I didn't sit on a record player, I just sit on a record.
You missed movie night last week when we watched a Troma movie.
When was movie night?
At Evans.
What'd you guys watch? I don't know what the name of the movie was
I don't know. I don't remember but it was one of those trauma movies where they get all these cats
No, it was Catholic schoolgirl hell
That's the name of the movie. I think cool where they go into this house
But there were no boobs and there was you know, the blood was made out of a1
But like they go in this house and
like this little boy goes in first on dare and he comes out and has a seizure and goes in the hospital and
And then these girls go in to because the man who lived in the house died and the girls go in to
Catalog the paintings and things with this nun the nun was cool. I
Bet like that little kid went to a seizure because a priest touched him. No
Oh my god the acting that was so horrible and then like no one died cool
Except for the girl who got caught in a meat hook, but all they showed was her feet with a1
And one girl got electrocuted, and another one got pulled into the swamp and some guy
got run over.
My friend Garrett has this trauma movie, Killer Condom, that he's been trying to get us to
watch that for weeks and weeks, and we never seem to get around to watching it, there's
always something better to do, like play pop music or something, but we're gonna watch
Killer Condom one of these nights, you'll have to come watch.
I'm sure Garrett would love to have you come over and watch it.
you do now? My headphones are attached to a giant pile of cords. It's like, what Loki's
doing right now is pulling out the Christmas tree lights at Christmas time and finding
they're just in one giant pile. You know what? In my house, that never was an issue because
I was evil with the twisty ties. I always hated pulling out the lights and having them
be all tangly, so I would wrap them in a circle and bunch them together and twisty tie them.
You're so anally-retentively fun.
I bite my ass. I'll show you anal-retentive.
See, what happens when you have a steel-toed boot shoved up your butt from kicking?
You'll be coughin' up nails.
I don't think I've ever heard you so, like, threatening on this show before.
You're a badass bitch tonight.
I am?
Yes, you am. I didn't mean that, by the way.
I mean it with puppies.
Wait, you're going to kick Puppy in the ass?
No.
What did he do to you?
You're a mean old lady.
No, I'm going to get Puppy a puppy.
Are you going to get Puppy a puppy?
When he has somewhere, he can have a puppy.
That's very nice of you.
I'm sure he appreciates that.
And now we have the little frowny face from Puppy in the chat room
as the buffer hits him.
I'm not kicking Puppy.
I like Puppy right there.
I didn't go there. I'm sorry I'm sorry. She did. Yeah I did, I did. Here, have some more
hazelnut bites. Okay, give me. What are these? Let's re... Sorry, Loki's ass. Oops. I didn't
I threw nut cream at his ass.
This is Locher Quadratini Hazelnut Premium Wafer Cookies and they're filled with hazelnut
cream.
They're European.
Number one in Italy.
I got them at the old people's store.
They were $2.00.
They look like old people food.
No, they're international.
Even if you eat them, you're cultured.
You sure could use it.
I don't feel any culture.
Hey, look, ain't I done by the guy who did Tenchi?
What is that?
I don't know.
Masquerade?
Is that what it's called?
Yeah.
I want to finish watching Breakin'.
Let's read what Masquerade is about.
Give me the nuts.
Endless passion.
Insatiable desire.
nineteen-year-old gins family i've watched this one okay it's about this
check that's going after this one guy because he has
what was it the essence of permanence or something like that
in other words he has golden sperm that's like proves that he's immortal
and some something
key of immortality anyways it's just an excuse for her to try to like
get them off
in which he does and then he becomes like some demon thing that bites her and
so she becomes a vampire
and has to like uh...
live in their house with this other vampire servant that like
All of a sudden gets weak, and the only way she can become stronger is by having sex, and then, uh, and the end.
I wanna watch it.
That was beautiful.
I wanna finish watching Breakin'. We were watching Breakin' before the show.
We can finish watching Breakin' after the show.
But if we start watching Breakin', there's not gonna be a show, and our listeners will get mad, and they'll write us death threats.
No, they won't.
They'll just whine online.
They can listen to the cool music.
Yes, lots of cool music.
They can listen along.
What other 80s movies do you love, other than Breakin'?
Breakin' 2, Electric Boogaloo.
Sorry, did I say that again?
I don't appoint because they can probably see us all pointing at us.
And they're moving out.
When I see that bed moving by, I'm like, I wonder how many times people have said sex on that bed.
Did you see how old they were? I don't think they had too much sex. Just because they're old doesn't mean they don't have sex
Well, that's like 50% of the old people population actually do what the fuck am I talking about? It's not an old people having sex
I'm weird, you know, you're really pulling down the quality of the show
All I did was sat there it just said everything you guys said over and over again
So you guys talked about the chub stock truck stop
But it's cool when we do it.
and how we were all bored at
truck stops or something like that. But it's cool when we do it.
Go download more blowjobs.
Go hang out at a truck stop.
Wow.
Wow. I think now is a good time to take a break.
No. What are you doing?
Oh no.
Okay, uh...
Let's see here.
Is this going to sound like something Twen did?
No, he downloaded it.
Maybe.
He downloaded it, Rob.
He downloaded it.
Downloaded it, yes.
Off of LBZ.com.
I have to fix something because, hold on.
Oh, I'll play it after the break.
OK, so this is something to look forward to.
Is it the Naoki remix?
Did Naoki do some pew-pews in this song and stuff?
and then we'll be back in a little bit. We'll see you soon. And then we have a request from
the chat room to talk about Pump It Up, which we haven't done that in a long time, so we'll
talk about Pump It Up, that might be fun. Okay, so we'll be back in a little bit. Enjoy.
You're standing there with your arms folded like you couldn't care
Even before you glanced at me, I already felt the chemistry
Don't know what it is about you that's got me feeling mesmerized
I won't let you get away, boy, you're the lucky one
I don't need you, cause the truth is, got my hands full of fatties
But I want you, gonna put you, at the very very top of my lips
I don't need you, cause the truth is, got my hands full of happiness
Yeah, I want you, gonna have you, and that's the way it is
Mr. Random Person on the Street, who, by the way, is not an actor, what do you think of
the Orange Drowned Spring Money Music and More show?
The music is like being transported to just this dancing spaceship place.
It's unearthly.
It's like being in a club, except you don't have to actually ask someone to dance.
Hello, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
We need to find that movie again.
That thing is freaking hilarious.
It was pretty funny.
I remember it was on Konami's official site, I think.
Yeah, it was linked from there somewhere.
So, Loki, did you finish downloading your A remix?
Yeah, I had to figure out what I did.
I had to figure out what I did, because I
had to plug in my headphones just
to make sure that it was the right copy, you know?
So I had to hook it back up.
It'll just take one second.
All righty.
One.
Anyone seen any good movies lately?
No. Have you not seen X2 yet?
No. No? Not yet?
I'll take you later.
When? Because I want to go see it again. I don't know.
But then The Matrix is coming out. I have to go see that too.
So I don't know.
Because I want to go see X2 again for Iceman.
Hey, I'm going for my fuzzy elf.
You're going for your fuzzy elf? My fuzzy elf.
Who's your fuzzy elf? Nightcrawler. Nightcrawler. Do you remember how they...
You never read the comics? No, of course I didn't. I watched the cartoon on Fox though.
I like Jubilee. That's not even. I like Jubilee.
I read the comics when all of the way out was in high school.
When they were cool.
Yeah, well we need to go see. Alan Cumming as Nightcrawler? Oh, he's great.
Did he keep them Cumming and Cumming and Cumming? Yes, he kept us Cumming. All right.
So take me tomorrow. No, no.
Now, I don't know if this is a fake one because, you know, I got it off of MGZ and, you know,
but i know that they're very reliable with you know all these uh... breaking
you know song just like and you know for the market
here the first to have it
so on
here we go with uh...
a
that's uh... remix by nyoki i mean it's amazing this guy's history mixing shit
like this is going to be in in one of the night so i can of course is right
always
glues of the night style
only
move challenge
mode
uh... basic experts on
news do it loki
do it all night
oh this is fucking great
I love that drum beat, there's going to be some mean scratches
oh wow oh that's that's a cool part oh yeah there was a freeze right there yeah they're
gonna have exclusive reasons the night style we have to turn the turntable over and over
and over again oh this is gonna be some mean key presses right here i bet you this is gonna
the first eight-star song.
Oh, this is great.
Wow.
An Orange Lounge Radio exclusive.
You know, I wonder if somebody submitted that to the Bimani-style remix contest.
contest. If not, I think we need to do it on their behalf.
You know what? I don't really think that was snucky. I think that it was good cool.
You know what's sad is my sound card sucks ass and is brand new. I am so... I'll leave
it for later. I got to make a list. Yeah, I can do that.
Your sound card is number one in Italy.
Your sound card is the sexiest bean tadpole on the planet.
I hope somebody got that joke.
Your house is hot.
You know what, I think we ought to enter that remix and say it's Twin, and I bet people would believe it.
No, because Twin's not talented enough to put another beat behind it.
I bet he's listening.
You want to say hello?
Hi, Twan!
With love, Orange Lounge Radio, XXLO
You still ain't getting back in the chatroom.
That was a good laugh.
We're having a day on Orange Lounge Radio.
This is so different being here. I'm sitting on a couch.
Is it cool?
Is it?
I was laying down on the couch.
You have a vanilla coke.
I have a vanilla coke?
It's gone.
Shit!
What the fuck?
The vanilla coke jumped out and attacked my phone.
I thought there was still stuff in it.
Rob, you need a trash can by your computer.
Well, I can get up and walk to the kitchen.
I am capable.
But you'd rather not.
I say next break we open the door.
Just to let air out.
We need to open the door, just to let air out.
Yeah, we can open the window.
To let air out.
To let air out in here.
Or are we just trying on a fan?
Save electricity, open the door.
Anyway, they're saying in the chat room that we were dissing Italy.
We weren't.
We were reading it off a bag of cookies.
This bag of cookies is number one in Italy.
We need to get the webcam, no we don't need the webcam hooked up.
We need a scanner.
I'll scan this when I get home and put it up. We'll figure out something creative with the webcam
I think we're going to do is we're gonna have the webcam and we'll just put it in the corner and pointed it away
oh my god, it really is written in Italian and
and Chinese it don't open it now and
Holy crap, it's written in Hebrew. I
Kid you not the the stuff about the the cookies is written in Hebrew look
Look.
That's scary.
Can you read it for us?
Fuck no.
Well, as we promised, there's many things coming up this week that's exciting, E3 being
the big one that's on everybody's minds, the Electronic Entertainment Expo or maybe I got
that backwards.
I don't really give a shit because I'm not going.
And Jamie unfortunately isn't going because she has that job thing going on.
0, it's not going. And Loki is not going either.
But Dan always brings back neat stuff for you guys.
Well, he hasn't been there before, but he did from that manager meeting he went to.
But E3 is going to be like this big fat deal, and we're going to get a lot of Imani news next week,
which is interesting because we don't really have a show next Sunday.
No.
But in two weeks we'll be back with episode number 45, our season 3 premiere,
We will have lots to talk about from E3, because in those two weeks, there's going to be so much news it's going to make you cry, because maybe we're finally probably going to hear a confirmation on DDRXBox, whether it's legit or not, although it's looking more and more legit, because...
Don't forget about 2DX USA.
2DX USA rumors will finally be put to rest one way or the other, as well as Max2 USA will have lots of news, I'm sure.
A friend who goes every year, always videotapes the different big booths they go to.
I'm going to ask him to record a bunch of the stuff on the Bimani, thanks for me.
And Metal Gear Solid 3 is going to be a big thing too.
Oh my god, that was cool.
Because the trailer's out now.
There's also the new Metal Gear Solid for the GameCube that they're coming out with.
Ooh yay, I don't know why I love my GameCube.
My GameCube is my favorite system now, and I would buy that on the GameCube.
They said it was like Metal Gear Solid, the first one's story with the second one's graphics in Game Boy. That's what it's supposed to be.
I want to know more about that Final Fantasy game they're doing for GameCube. I hope it doesn't suck. Please don't suck. Please don't suck.
And Mario Kart Double Dash, oh yeah.
Squeenix is back with Nintendo.
And I bet you they're going to show a lot of Final Fantasy XI stuff at E3. Although it's already out in Japan, but you know.
My demo disk needs to hurry up and get to my house.
Will you have a demo disk of it coming?
Well, I signed up for the beta.
And to be a beta tester for the PC version.
And I have a feeling that I'm going to get it because I've at least played every game out there except for 4.11.
And that and I've beta tested a bunch of other stuff, so I'm pretty sure to get it.
And Dan signed up for the PS2 one.
I'm just pissed though because I was thinking of getting the Japanese one when it came out, except that it would have been really expensive for me because I would have had to get an external hard drive for my PS2 because I have a first model Japanese one.
Two hundred something dollars still and I refuse to shop at BuyRight because they suck.
I was telling my friend Garrett about your BuyRight experiences because he thinks they suck too. They did something to him that picked him off.
off.
They really suck a big ass.
Never shot from Bi-Rite.
I know.
Would you explain this to me?
I kind of know what it is, but I thought our listeners might benefit.
The difference between, because I know this is your beef with Bi-Rite, the difference
between buying a game that's Asia and buying a game that's Japan.
There's really not a difference in the game itself, but when you get your manual, it's
going to be written all in, I think it's Mandarin Chinese, as opposed to being written in Japanese.
And for me it was a big thing because I would have at least a chance of reading a Japanese
manual instead of one written in Chinese.
And the other thing is, is that I could have gone to YesAsia and gotten it for $30 cheaper.
Instead I paid more and there it went.
But I see that a lot.
Like I was looking around at stuff on NCSX the other night and they have Asia, Japan,
they have it pretty clearly defined the differences between the two when you're buying them.
That's why it's good to shop at NCSX.
Um, but I was just, you know, I was kind of curious what the difference is, and, you know, I thought maybe our listeners could benefit from that too.
They should just never shop from BuyRight. And also if you sign up for their mailing list at all.
Because somehow they signed me up for it when I emailed a question.
They, I've, I've submitted so many times. Threatened legal action, because you can actually sue them for that.
Um, and they haven't removed me, so I blocked. That's part of the reason why my Dr. Soccer mail is blocked.
Ah, I got it. But, um,
I'm actually going to get on the line one day and call them,
and tell them that if they do not remove my name for their mailing list that I am going to press charges.
And I will!
You know, well that's going to be a law in California pretty soon about the whole
you can
sue them for five hundred dollars or something like that. It's crazy.
And you get a hundred dollars of that?
No, I'm sorry, you get the state to give them a fine. The state can
fine them for that and you get a hundred dollars of that.
That's awesome.
All the spam lists? Uh-huh. Uh-uh. I'm going to save every last one of them.
I'd be rich.
Yep.
What else?
Oh, yes, Logie.
I hate you Creative Lab.
You can die.
I'll get into that later.
Okay.
Also coming up this weekend, big, big, big, big news.
This is something we will be attending.
That's B3, the other three thing, and that's this weekend.
Whatever happened to C3 and D3?
I don't know.
Maybe they happened in your chat.
C4 blew up C3.
was a c3 m movie with chris rock
I think you'd see before
my bed I'm anyway I
b3 is this weekend and that's a pier thirty-nine in San Francisco
huge you DDR termin it is going to be taken places people coming in from
Seattle
so Cal it's like to oh Jamie's ringing
anyway moving on to discussion about
B3.
B3 is going to be this huge-ass tournament that's going on and it's taken place in San
Francisco on Pier 39 and they're having four or five competitions.
It's Perfect Attack, Freestyle, Dance Maniacs, and B Mania 3.
I think there was something else going on, I probably forgot, but you can get onto DDR
Free, you can check the official tournament thread for more information on that.
we will be broadcasting to you that weekend on Saturday for sure, Sunday hopefully, if
we can get it to work out. I just received some news we might not be able to get it to
work out, but hopefully we do. But we'll be coming to you all day long on Saturday for
sure. And we're going to have a really good location from what I understand. So, hold
on. Do you want to say anything to the listeners? Wait one second, say it one more time on the
one look at the one
to gary
that i could barely hear it yes
enlisted one
p
the
very he he
he
pattern
that was jane's hand.
My microphone's really loud now.
Where were we?
Yes, B3, all those companies.
We're going to have a really good location Saturday from what I understand.
That's going to be awesome.
You can't freaking...
Are they going to feed us?
I don't know.
I don't think they're going to feed us, but I hear we get other perks, but I can't say
what those are yet, but I'll tell you off air.
Ooh.
There's some cool things.
So we get free man servants.
Ooh.
I don't want a man servant.
That's weak sauce, man.
We have intern zero.
We don't need another man-servant.
I'm talking about naked men-servants.
I'm talking about harem-men.
Maybe we can talk puppy or something into being a man-servant.
I don't want puppy to be a harem-man.
I want my harem-man to- Because we're going to be celebrities at
B3.
We need to have like Insta on a trailer.
We're the Orange Lounge radio people.
We're celebrities now.
We need people coming to our booth asking for autographs and we go,
Sorry, no time, no time. See my publicist. Call me. We'll do lunch. Blah, blah, blah.
I'm still thinking about auctioning off my bat.
At the tournament?
Maybe we should auction off my bat at the tournament.
Aren't you going to be sad to see that go?
Yes, I will.
How could I ever consider getting rid of my beloved bat? Dude, they're moving tables now.
Bye, neighbors!
We already have people in the chat room claiming dibs on the orange bat.
So maybe look forward to that.
Maybe we'll do a silent auction for my bat.
Are we giving away door prizes?
Don't know?
Maybe.
Hopefully a few.
We at least have that one box of stuff, right?
The one that you wanted to...
Make up my circle.
Okay.
I think we should do a silent auction for the orange bat.
So you're thinking about a silent auction for the orange bat?
You should do one for yours.
We should auction off your bat to you, signed by us.
We could do that.
The host.
Okay.
And then you would have to go get your bats.
And then we can enter and do a routine at the biggest tournament in NorCal.
No!
Okay, so we're probably going to do a silent auction for Jamie's Bat and My Bat, so that's
something to look forward to.
We are going to be giving away some door prizes, we don't know how many, but we'll be giving
away some.
So stop by our table, maybe we'll do like a random drawing or something like, come get
interviewed on the show and get a ticket in the drawing.
Maybe we'll do something like that, that'll be fun.
And yeah, so definitely look for us.
But except, it can't just be come be interviewed on the show, like we have to interview them
and ask them really humiliating questions.
I just remembered that one question on the sex quiz.
I'll ask Travis if maybe we can borrow the sex quiz, if he wouldn't mind.
Shrimping.
Rusty trombone.
Take the sex quiz, win a DVD, maybe?
Maybe.
Take the sex quiz, get spanked by Rob.
Bring a paddle.
we've been hired on that could be that that would be with
uh... since will be in frisco you know uh... date with robin castro
i could be a that could be a prize
is i hate the castro i really
there's like one or two good stores there but the rest is dirty it's a dirty
place
it really is already
it's dari you
well i think i said green
i don't get it was welcome away
you created a big bottle of snot with a hat on it
puppy had a great idea we can get violent hyper girl to bring her with
again to do
we can see if we can borrow one out of the what the hell that's why i think
creative labs has every single version of the sound blaster listed on their
say except the one-and-a-half
what is up with that they have the basic sound blaster live
and then mine sound blaster live five one okay
they have sound blaster live five one mp3 plus and sound blaster live
five one gamer
The
chat room is suggesting that I cosplay Mr. Spanky for B3.
And you know what's scary is I have seen that exact thing that Mr. Spanky wears in a leather store in San Francisco on Folsom Street.
So I could go buy it.
Rob, we've seen you in a corset, Rob.
You need to do Dr. Dick.
You need to go up there as Frank.
I have contemplated doing a Dr. Dick routine, however I have no time to plan one.
Who needs to plan one?
cuz this is B3 and I feel like I should put some effort into it.
I don't know if I even can compete. Technically we're staff. I might not be able to compete.
Let's not worry about it.
We'll do an exhibition.
Ooh exhibitionism. Dr. Dick does an exhibitionism. That's an exciting idea.
But I have to find some big, I have to find like a big fur coat and some shiny shirts and things like that.
I'll have to go shopping at some gay stores this week and see what I can find.
I should buy my costume at Naughty and Nice.
Who are the Goldies?
Dr. Dick in Mantis.
We'll get you a school uniform.
I could dress up like an Asian schoolgirl.
We could do Battle Royale.
Ooh. What would be a good song?
Oh my god, I downloaded a high resolution scan of the collar.
What would be a fun freestyle song for Battle Royale?
Like all of us could get up there and we could keep killing each other off during the song?
Dead End?
dukeofthebump
I've been helping him gain levels because I am so happy because I have a plus five stiletto now.
And that means in English?
That means I can kill things faster and have them kill me less.
Cool.
If there was this one critter, it would take me a whole life bar to kill and now I can kill five of them.
Very nice. Congratulations.
I'm a nerd.
LOKI and I wanted to talk about G4 real fast, because we got cable a couple weeks ago, I think you remember on the show we were talking about how we just got cable, so we've had a little time now to actually watch some G4, and this is television for gamers, and we know that a lot of you don't have G4, so we thought we'd talk to you, we thought LOKI and I would talk to you about what we've seen on G4, what's cool and what sucks.
Okay, what's cool? First off, best show on all of G4? StarCade.
StarCade rocks.
Old school game show from 83 where they play video games like Pac-Man and Pango and Pole Position, and they win video games.
They win arcade machines.
Hands down the best show on G4.
Okay, now what sucks about G4, Loki?
Well, actually, there's one more good show on there. It's called, uh, that's called, like, Electric Play or something like that, or something like that.
It's where they review only action games. It's pretty cool. And they do these little skit things that are kind of funny. Those are mildly entertaining.
Now, what really sucks, um, is this one show, Portal, is the gayest show I've ever seen. Seriously, this guy that looks like...
Wait a minute, gayer than queerest folk?
Yes, it's pretty bad.
It's like, OK, this guy is like, I
would say he's pretty much like the gamer
version of Blue's Clues.
This guy is just sitting there talking to nobody,
except for this imaginary computer thing that's
supposedly in the studio that talks to him about really
stupid things, and they're making it sound all high tech
and cool.
And all he does is he talks about different cities
and towns and stuff that are in online games.
Then they do this stupid little, like, skit where they have these people walking around or whatever in, like, online games, and they're, like, making them talk, you know, dubbing over their voices and doing little stories. It's really retarded. It is just dumb. It is damn awful.
That sounded like, um, an idea that I was gonna do for a Ragnarok Online fan comic.
Yeah, that game sucks.
It's dumb to watch on the show.
This game called High Score really sucks.
It's some, like, UK version of Starrcade, but, you know, obvious.
Starrcade!
It's just crap.
And then Nick Arcade isn't on G4, but it is on Nickelodeon Gas,
Games and Sports, Nick Gas.
Yeah, and also what really sucks is they've got these stupid commercials
The commercials where they show the Twin Galaxies world records for like these two games.
Two games, they have like...
That's old school Orange Lounge topics right there talking about Twin Galaxies and their old DDR.
They're just awful, awful, awful.
But I'll have you know though that they did, what was it?
Entertainment Weekly and G4 did the top 100 games of all time.
And Dance Dancer Revolution was number 40, I think.
What was number one?
Legend Zelda. I forget what number two was. There was another series. Another series.
Guardian Legend wasn't on the list. Those bastards at all. Was ET on there? No. What
about Custer's Revenge? No. No. What else? There's a few that were really stupid that
beat up like other ones. Like Grand Theft Auto was under, I can't remember. There's
just a lot of really dumb games on the list.
Maybe I could find that list online somewhere. Maybe it's on G4. I'll see if I can find it.
Keep talking about G4 while I look for this list.
Then they have like these stupid like intimate moments with Laura Croft where there's this
guy talking to her and it's just like retarded. I mean, this guy is like talking to the chick
that's supposedly next to him and he's not making a play at all. I mean, what a loser.
If there's going to be some, like, you know, intimate moments, I want to see some intimate
moments, I want to see this, hi, don't you hate it that people think that, you know,
your unintelligent stuff, he should be like, bitch, get down on my lap, you know, stuff
like that. Because, I mean, it's just really awful, really awful TV. And then they have
these stupid screenshots, they do have different games and stuff and that was awful and it's
p0k3smot42o 1 dude just got a total jackass
You about to fall asleep, Jamie?
We need to do Fuck You's of the Week.
Do you want to do the Cage Mash now, or do you want to do Fuck You's now?
Huh?
You want to do Fuck You's now?
Excuse you!
I'm just kidding.
Uh, we'll take a quick break and we'll come back and do the Fuck You's of the Week.
So why don't you go ahead and send those to me in the chat room.
Hello, I'm Skye.
I'm sitting in the chat room right now.
Huh?
Play Angry Thing.
I'm going to play some...
I'm going to play...
Wait.
There's quite a difference between those.
I'm going to play Show You.
Jamie says, play show tunes.
What songs are show tunish?
My god, I don't know what songs those are.
Can I play angry songs?
I can find those easier.
OK, I have to play all tack?
All right, we'll take a tack break.
We'll take a tic-tac break.
And then we'll be back.
Yes, we will.
I have to find some tack stuff first.
Hold on.
Okay, yes, we're gonna play some tag, and then we'll be back, so send those FUs to me.
You rhymed, that was cool. I'm Skye. Tag in bed.
I'm in the chat room as Skye. If you aren't in our chat room, you should be. Get your
ass over there. Go over to www.calibomani.com, click on orange lounge, and then click on
chat. And while you're at calibomani.com... Did you say chat?
Visit our forums. What? You said chat.
pump it up is korean
uh... we'll be back we'll talk about pump it up a little later
it's
we're teasing it so that you have to keep listening
quit playing crap so i can play the break music
para para dance
what the fuck is this
uh... what's this
Stelly.
I'm gonna be a little bit disturbed, guys.
Let's listen in on an Orange Lounge Radio staff meeting.
Do we care what people think of us?
No!
Do we want people to kiss our ass?
Yeah!
Extreme Bimani Radio, that's us, Orange Lounge Radio.
Hi, we are back now.
oops, sorry about that.
We're having some technical difficulties there.
Loki and I are trying to share our computers here,
and it's fucking things up.
But we're back.
Yay.
I'm so excited that we're back.
I'm so excited, and I just can't hide it.
Let's see.
Jamie, let's talk about Pump It Up,
because Chad wanted us to talk about Pump It Up.
It's Korean.
And we haven't in a while.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
You hate it?
I like it, but it's Korean.
what's that mean
it's korean
okay i hated the version that was at uh... new york new york
was in vegas oh my god
or personal
the stages so messed up
it kept going past the front i wanted kids
every time you stepped on it it would hit you
and they're like a bajillion songs in the game is like one of the last ones out
and then
i couldn't find the songs i wanted it took me forever to find one to you
and then i killed automatically due to the difficulty is sucked
But, I mean, I like Pump It Up, though. I hate playing caution on Pump It Up, though.
Because it's so slow.
Um, my thoughts on Pump It Up, I absolutely hated the game when I first
played it, and I'll tell you why. The interface sucks
on all versions, because they don't- you have to use your feet to move around, and it's
too slow. I mean, I like
on DDR how you can really fastly throw through the songs. Even on 4th Mix, you can move through
the songs a hell of a lot faster than you can
and pump it up, and that just pisses me off. I shouldn't have to stand there for five minutes
trying to select my song.
i know you can
i mean so whatever but other than that
it's alright i mean the videos in the back of pretty cool i want to take on me
was the best of some of the songs are pretty cool i really like to the songs
and pump it up
and uh... you know i could be extreme i think it takes a lot of crap
but it's really horrible interface hurts it a lot more than it really should
a lot of people are just turned off by the
it's just not easy to use
That's just if we had DDR on a big screen like that.
I've seen it.
It'd be pretty.
No it doesn't.
Pump It Up does not suck.
Why do you think Pump It Up sucks, Zero?
Well, one reason why I think it absolutely sucks is the interface does suck.
I mean, I can play this, I can play the game, and there's a couple good songs that I like.
Half the other songs are trash, the damn thing takes forever to load after a song.
I gotta stand there for 45 seconds just to take 30 seconds to pick a song.
I don't really like having to, I don't like playing diagonal instead of up and down, left and right.
You know what though, the diagonal thing, for some reason it makes freestyling a lot more natural.
Because it makes you freestyle.
Yeah, but I think that's kind of cool. That's one thing I like about Pump It Up. Yeah, I think that's the point.
I mean, I think DDR could actually use maybe some type of the style of the videos that are in Pump It Up on some, and there's some that are horrible, but I think that there's a lot of ideas DDR can take from Pump.
The same thing what Pump could take from DDR.
Like, yeah, having just an easier interface, being able to choose your songs quicker, and possibly changing their hardware so that you don't have to stand around for a month.
Isn't a Pump It Up machine just a big computer inside that box?
Yeah, that's what I heard. It's just a big PC in there.
They could have changed that if they really wanted to. It would have been a little bit easier for everyone else.
I've played a game that's worse, though.
What?
And, God, I can't remember the name of it. It was put up by Jalego.
Take no motion not taking motion. No what it is. They have one at this bowling alley. I went to in Hayward
but um
It's got three monitors middle monitors the videos, and it's like it looks like one of those make your own video things
Huh people doing really crappy dances wear really crappy clothes
But it's got like you know how somebody amigo how your maraca places are shut are set up
Well, it's like that on the floor, and you do your steps like that, and they're different colors that tells you where to go
What's that game called?
Is it put out by the people who did Someday We Go?
It's by Jaleco.
Do a search.
Weird.
Do a search real quick.
Hold on just a sec because I'm queuing up some of the stuff for later in the show.
I missed playing Techno Motion.
They have one at Excalibur.
I missed playing it.
Thank you for bringing that up, Logie.
That's why I wanted to bring up what's cooler than Pump It Up is the game that the same
company made called Dance Station 3DDX and the way it looks is so cool because instead
of the arrows that are set in, you know how the buttons are kind of sunk into the pad
a little bit?
Well, the way 3DDX is, and the same thing with EZDancer, is it's a big black panel that's
over the whole thing and then different areas of it light up so it's a big flat panel.
So it kind of makes finding the buttons a little harder but it kind of adds a challenge
of the game. Well, in 3DDX, not only that, but there's para-like sensors all around the
sides so you have to wave your arms too to play. It's awesome. And it has such songs
as Jenny in a Bottle. And that game makes you freestyle. I got to adjust the volume
on this one. Yes, that game makes you freestyle. I don't talk very loud. Here, look, if you
You can use this one.
Don't change it too much.
What was I looking for?
Shoot.
Hey, they're number one in Italy.
Okay, so are we about ready for the FUs of the week?
Sure.
Why not?
Here we go.
Jamie, you know what to do.
My first one, my first few of the week goes to being tired and not sleeping.
My other one goes toward my poor body for being sore after Rocky last night and I don't
I don't know. I'm not really all that angsty.
Gasp!
Well, there's the usual, like, the idiot drivers and driving here to do the show.
Driving to South Sac and run up here.
Love you, Jamie.
He got me food, so he's forgiven.
I was teasing anyway.
One of them goes to...
I love my fiance a whole lot, but he ate a whole box of Life cereal and I didn't get any.
Was it Cinnamon Life? Because Cinnamon Life is the best.
Cinnamon Life sucks, it's normal.
If he ate the whole box of Cinnamon Life, that is a crime.
That's okay, I found another box though.
Because I thought they were super-five.
Cinnamon Life is the show.
I hate Cinnamon Life.
What is wrong with you?
Thank you, Cinnamon Life tastes like shit.
I like the normal one.
I don't like oddly flavored cereals. I like crackle and oat bran. I'll put it that way. I like grape nuts. I like total.
When I was a little kid, I ate adult cereals. And I hate marshmallows. Fuck marshmallows, okay? Because they're nasty.
And, um... I guess that's it. Yeah, I'm tired. I'm being tired.
Next
I don't know what's wrong with it. It's pissing me off, because I'm looking on their site to find drivers, and they don't have any drivers for this car, because the car doesn't exist according to their site, which is also really annoying.
So, I had to find drivers for this somewhere. I'm thinking that's probably what the problem is for it.
So I've even my sound card to the sucks also since we're on the subject of that every my motherboard because you know
I like I got this nice motherboard and processor combo. It's supposed to be an AMD
2200 well, it's supposed to be you know, ready about you know, two gigahertz or whatever. It's running at 135
My old processor was faster than that. So I basically paid $300 or no $150 for a downgrade
Thank you, fries. You can suck ass.
Let's also talk about old people.
I had an encounter with this really old bag that was at release,
and I was just waiting in line to get some Chinese food,
and she's pushing her cart.
Oh, I'm old!
Cutting right in front of us, and then stupid Chinese lady,
Chinese lady she freaking you know and so I'm sitting here going yeah I guess
we don't need lines and the stupid bitch in front me started saying and I just
story jr out there and i think that you're not talking you can you agree
and then uh...
so you know i feel a little bit because then she didn't even know she wanted in
your arms when you're on come on come on come on come on move move move move
come on come on come on you're old come on move
wasted like a good
extra half an hour than i really needed
so now i am also
and at the two uh... stupid drivers
but then it
There's this road down here, and everyone backs up because they want to turn, because it backs up a good half a mile, because people want to turn.
Well, these stupid people don't realize, oh, I have to get in that way to turn? Yeah, well, there would be more there.
So they stop in the middle of your lane, trying to turn over, and won't move out of the way.
Then I had another jackass when I went to McDonald's yesterday, who was checking his food in the middle of the parking lot.
direct middle of the parking lot, I couldn't go around him because he was sitting in the way
and he's just kinda going
du-du-du-du-du..
So, I view that
anyway the people on Ain't It Cool News for giving away the ending of The Matrix
they keep trying to read reviews on stuff
and they keep giving away the end of The Matrix and it's like sneaking up on me
I keep finding out more stuff I don't want to know about it
and it's really annoying
But I only have four more days until I get to go see the movie
which reminds me, uh...
my girlfriend doesn't really want to go
so I have an extra ticket if anyone wants to go with me
go with me
policy here and by forty five
that's the only thing that's right over there
uh... and then uh... if you to my website
who's gone
it's gone for good
no say it's gone my hosting died and i'm not going to pay for hosting and it
it saves me time that way
so i don't have to work on my website anymore
so what, i mean i guess what you know you can just find your web your stupid files
anywhere else on the web because i'm not responsible for doing your searching for
you
i don't give a shit anymore you know because you don't do anything you don't help me out
so um...
you consider a bastard you can go ahead and find your files on the web like i do
and spend time like i do
and you know what it builds character you know
the hard works character
hard work. So if you want a huge sim collection like mine, you can go suck ass because you're
never going to find it because most files are off the internet. So ha, I laugh at you
because I have a large collection and you do, I have a large collection and you do.
So yeah. And um, yeah I have Asian porn. That was cool. But um, I have Asian porn because
it's censored. That sucks. They have hot Asian chicks and they're like all blocky. Looks
like a mosaic attacking them. That's not cool. So I think I'm done. You know, it's just that
pisses me off that my site's gone, because I really like my site, and you know, but I'm
just not going to know. Maybe I'll come back. You never know, because my friend who does
my hosting for me says that sometimes the web server goes down and it comes back up,
so it may reappear and then everything will be fine, but.
And what do you have to say to those that say that the point of Leech from Loki is to,
who, in fact, leech from Loki.
The point is that I left space for people to put files up so that people can leech from
my site, but no one put any files up.
And for that you must die.
And for that you must die, and I know the whole purpose of getting files, but really
all the files I had on there I got from like DDRUK anyways, so go get them from them.
Shit, this is like, what?
Seriously, Bomani Sims of DDRUK is pretty much where I got all my files, there wasn't
anything new on there yet. I mean, I was planning on it. I just never got around to it. So now
I have more time to make cool files. I mean, you should think of it as like an advantage
because you get to see my files anyways.
Yeah, more times to remix.
Yeah. Well, yeah, if the sound card works.
Okay, I'm done.
All right, you're done.
My turn.
Let me think. What are some things I want to give an FU to?
My first FU goes to my erratic sleeping schedule because I was a half hour late to work on
p0k3smot42o
p0k3smot42o p0k3smot42o p0k3smot42o
my stuff on the counter and it's like floating. I'm like, shit man. I have no idea. I'll keep
track of that. Probably shaving. Actually, I have that problem with Dan. Cause after
he gets out of the bathroom for some reason there's an inch of water on the floor. And
an inch of water on the sink. And I have to grab toilet paper and wipe down the sink.
That's why in my bathroom, even if I get a little bit lax with cleaning off the counter,
kostjamrh It's probably from shaving, and I probably just don't notice it because I'm in such a hurry in the morning. But I will try to be more conscious of it in the future.
kostjamrh I found out something. The girl who was the onee-san in Battle Royale. She's the voice actor for Asuka in Battle Royale.
kostjamrh Wonderful, your useless tribute fact of the day.
0 Do you have any FUs today?
1. I was wearing a new shirt
Just waiting to get on a ride and this lady starts smoking in front of me, right?
And I'm sitting here thinking first of all, we are in an enclosed area
which means you're not supposed to be soaking and I didn't say that I just kept to myself and then I told my
My friends who were with me and said, you know, this is like really annoying and she turns around and like screams at me
I don't give a fuck. I can smoke all the fuck. I want blah blah blah and
I said, okay, that's great. I'll actually know she can't I know she can't because she's in an enclosed area
And, um, and there's a security guard sitting next to me, and I told him, and he told her to put it out, and she wouldn't put it out.
And then she decided to yell at me about my shirt, and saying, what, am I not attractive? And I looked at her, and I said, no.
And she was all, your shirt's very offensive, and I said, your smoking's very offensive, and all your little running around bratty-ass kids are offensive.
And your face is offensive! At that point in which, she decided to try to storm on me, and then the security guard scrapped her, and ejected her from the park.
That is how you do it!
And uh...
No, and then I have to say fuck you to all the people at MarineWorld who can't obviously run a fucking ride right.
Every time something comes in, oh we're out of technical difficulty so you're going to have to wait for another 45 minutes.
They're not drunk, they're just cardies.
They need like pot-smoking cardies.
And once you like do crank and-
Cardies will make the ride work even if it needs duct tape.
Do cardies make a ride work if it doesn't work?
they don't care they'll put you on it but so yeah i ended up spending like two hours in this one
line waiting for a stupid ride and i was like two cars just waiting to go and i ended up standing
there just because i didn't really want to walk and wait in another one um but still fuck you
then for being assholes when you ask them what's wrong you're like i don't know i just pushed the
buttons stupid bastards and then um fuck you to the people what the hell nevermind anyways fuck
I'd like you to know the people who said that all of you up in Sacramento are all known to absolutely suck at DDR.
We're the worst DDR players in the world, okay? Because other people say it, it's true.
Well, I know. They decided to try to tell me this as I go down there and I'm messing around the 4th machine.
Which works perfectly. That's the best place ever.
Yeah, I mean, I'm thinking, what, March Madness? What, 3 or 4 of the top 16 were from Sacramento?
We suck. We really, really suck.
I know, bastard.
I didn't know.
Well, let's have a dance off, and I'm like, what.
First off, first off, first off.
Anyone that calls it a dance off.
I know.
Okay, you should've known right there that, well, yeah.
And I'm gonna say-
I need not say no more.
The kid was pretty good, I guess.
I mean, he did play really well, but I mean for them to sit there and just get done telling
me how much I suck and then wanna challenge me.
Because of where you're from.
Yeah.
I've never seen you play, just because of where you're from.
And not to mention, their extreme sucked at that point, because the unlocks were up to sync, and that was it, so none of the really good songs had been unlocked.
And then, um, so they said, alright, we do best two out of three games, and blah blah blah, I'm like, fine, alright.
So, we did the first two rounds, the first two games were PA, and surprisingly I beat them, because I never thought I was that good at PA.
And I beat him by a pretty big margin, and then the second round we just went for, I guess, the overall score of all three songs.
And, um, huh? Basically, yeah. But, I mean, there was some stupid little thing they said, and I said, alright, fine.
And then I beat them, and then they were all pissed off because I won, and, you know, I'm from Sacramento.
And then I came back later, because the guy was going to put in the unlock code, and he did.
Legend of Max is there, and I just wanted to play it.
And then, of course, you know, the happy little winners are there again.
And now, can you beat Legend of Max? I said I'd beat it, like, maybe 2 out of 18, 20 tries.
No.
Okay, um, well, he can beat it all the time. Why don't you challenge him?
I'm like, why would you, basically, why would you want to challenge me if I'm so inferior to him?
And I'll just do it. And I beat it, I think it was, like, with a C or a D.
And he failed it miserably before the freeze, before, like, the first main freeze.
kostjamrh And it was funny when they tried to do doubles, because there was a broom right there where they could have wiped off the machine.
And so they didn't. And I watched all three of them try to play doubles and slide right off the side of the machine onto the fourth plus off of the extreme.
Because they are just too stupid to clean up. And I got up there...neither of them have memory slots.
But it is still a fourth plus though, which was nice because it was fun to play.
But it's just, you know, if you're going to come up and say people suck and you think they're so bad, don't challenge them to play because they might be better than you.
namagem1 yes, this message has been brought to you by Zero
namagem1 worth his information and kind words for all
namagem1 and yeah so fuck them
namagem1 fuck Marine World dude
namagem1 that place is shitty
namagem1 I wanna go back to Six Flags Magic Mountain where the roller coasters actually worked and it was fun
namagem1 so fuck Vallejo and shit like that and their stupid crap
namagem1 I'm done because it sucks
cpcgamer1- Let's talk to the chat room.
cpcgamer1- Hello chat room.
cpcgamer1- BlackLab would like to give FUs to fucking migraines. They always ruin things for me. I would have been at Rocky last night.
cpcgamer1- Fuck Easy Mac. I'm sick of it already. There would be more but my roommate finally moved out and I have the room to myself for the next five weeks and that makes me happy.
Stapler X would like to say F you to annoying bitches who can't stay quiet in a fucking screening room.
And of course the president. No reason given, just F you.
Darkdatsui would like to say fuck having to wait for E3 and the official footage of MGS3.
Also he would like to give a suggestion that perhaps the game you were thinking about earlier, Jamie, stepping selection or stepping stage.
p0k3smot42o
kostjamrh
0blivixx, i think
0blivixx, yeah
Snubdyspenoid would like to say a whole lot, here we go.
hell is with all this Korean crap? Pump It Up, Ragnarok Online, who gives a crap? There's
a bunch of other MMORPGs out there that are much better and much less repetitive and Pump
It Up sex.
Fuck you buddy.
Would you like to respond to that, Jamie?
Fuck you buddy. I like Ragnarok Online.
Fuck you.
I have more fun playing it and it's free.
There you go. Free is a good thing.
And my thief is level 26.
I still like that. Fuck you.
kostjamrh And it makes me think of Secret of Mana, so I like it, and all my friends wrote it.
experiences with Fries, you think that the employees being paid commission would stop
them from being shit-nosed, asshole-sucking, dirty-ass cock-dobblers?
Okay, you know, Fries really does suck, but they actually did something good for me the
other day. And this is like, well, no, they didn't even have any! They were sold out!
No. They actually did a good, they actually did a good job, and actually, you know, sold
kostjamrh And then at the end of that rant, he said, oh, free.
You don't know me. You don't know my life. You don't know...
And who think they know what I'm thinking? You're not psychic, bitches. Go see Miss Cleo.
And finally, F you to not being able to go to Scandia for lack of money. My skills are slipping, dammit.
Here's the part where you go,
WHAT SKILLS?
AHHH! AHHH!
I'm so mean. You mean his total elite freestyling skills? Must keep passing eights, rar. Okay, out.
Okay.
Rock on.
uh... next
code zero
would like to ask you to annoying people in the movie theater who must
blurt out the name of every unit next to even though they are wrong eighty
percent of the time all
that reminds me
all all all occur occur occur
at you
to that little kid who is sitting behind us next to act like this whole family
they didn't even speak english they spoke russian or something
and like there were three kids
and they would like to shake the seat and stuff and we are just like her own
stare and be all, what the hell do you think you're doing? They're stupid. They were really
stupid because they had no idea why I was mad. I hate kids. There should be a law against
bringing certain age children into a movie theater. I don't realize there are somewhat
laws in R and X, but that should be punishable by death.
I don't remember what theater I was at, but there was this kid there who was doing that
to me and her parent was very nice to them. I turned around and I told the mom or something
that if she didn't control her child, I'd report her to child services.
To child protection services.
And she was like, what?
I was like, yeah, because it's going to be for neglect because I'm going to take her
child and ship them off to some third world country of slavery.
And she just looked at me and her child never did it again.
I just, God, I hate kids, and we need to, you know what I should do?
I should open up a movie theater where children are banned.
I'd be the richest fucking man on the planet.
Our Dave and Busters creation will also have a movie theater in it.
Yes.
Yes, we need to, I swear to God, Loki, we need to get alone and make this.
We need to make our Dave and Busters slash movie theater slash children free world.
It would be beautiful.
I would cry tears of joy.
Poor new land.
Oh yeah.
You know what else you need in there?
You need the Discovery Zone in there with no children.
All those nets and balls and things.
I used to take my brothers there just so that I could go play.
Alright, one more F you from the chat room.
I used to take naps in there.
Rice, ryc3 would like to say fuck you to my computer for buffering too much.
It means you got to get broadband or if you are on broadband you need to get better broadband I guess.
More memory.
That's it. That there completes the F you's of the week.
Yay.
I'm so going to go on air.
dukeofthebump
So, let us do the cage match.
That will be fun.
That will be more fun than a barrel of monkeys.
Did you find your cage match song, Loki?
Yeah.
Good.
Alright, let's go into the orange lounge cage match.
Last week on the orange lounge cage match, a real shocker, I don't know how this song
won, but it did.
vinuvinumusic
break sorry guys cuz I fucked something up I moved my mi RC directory somewhere
else and now I can't access have my files I gotta move it back we'll take a
quick break we'll be right back and we'll do the case match sorry
I don't know what to do, I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do
Hi!
when it started rhyming I'd float to the fence
I could get laid back on your neck patty back
give the dog a bite and now some candy and a back
roll him over roll him over bake him in the pan
I'm the little girl that makes the gingerbread man
understand how big his dickie done you understood
and you can thank me for sure Mike hot at the jam
Chris hot at the shop, Lauren hot at the shop
and Bo got his chick so my piano swing
Prince hollers just drawn outta duck and bowl got his kick
So I see how they swing
This is what girls are made of
Sugar and spice and I'm born to slice
I got no rhymes because we got show
I got no nose because we got no eyes
But for the women I was like a sock on my back
I brought a judge in my hands and my pants were slag
All right, our mics were off during that whole little pass thing.
Why is the cage match music playing when no one is talking.
She is on the I love the 80's show every once-in-a- while on VH1.
Again, that was last week's winner that you just heard a little clip of, Raven Simone.
We were doing Chris Cross over it in the background.
She was the youngest girl on the Cosby Show with Thats What Little Girls Are Made Of.
Thats the first song you can vote for in tonight's cage match.
That was Raven Simone and Thats What Little Girls Are Made Of.
All right.
I wasn't here to rate it, so I gave it 3.
Jamee, when are you going to have time to do more work on the Battle Royale roleplay?
Um, who's that from?
Uh, puppy.
Puppy? Um, puppy. Um, we'll work on it Tuesday night if I'm not out.
Okay.
But I'm not gonna be up late because I'm working now.
Okay. Okay, into the cage match. Back to the cage match.
Loki, what track on the CD do we want here?
Oh, son of a bitch. It's not showing me the...
Sure.
I know.
It's a, it's a, um, um...
What's your pick this week?
which is in four days. Matrix Reloaded is part of the score. It's actually really awesome.
It's the scene that they're going to be having that kick-ass awesome car chase scene. This
is also named after a book that came out a while back. It's called Mona Lisa Overdrive.
It's Juno Reactor and Don Davis. Now, are we really playing the whole ten minutes of
this? We can play like five to eight minutes. Okay, we're going to play a portion of this
The edit of it is on my computer, but my sound card sucks ass, so yeah. But because there's an edit of it, that's because I'm doing it for tourneymix 4, so look for that.
it for Tourney Mix 4, so look for that.
If it does win, there's going to be an edit put in rotation that's even shorter. It just pretty much has the techno parts of it.
But it's cool. The edit's really cool. Hopefully we can play the edit for you at the end of the show. We're just having some problems with Logan's computer right now.
Anyway, let's go around the room and see what people thought, starting with Jenny, because she has the mic.
It definitely sounded like something that's supposed to go behind something. It wouldn't be something that I would want to listen to over and over and over again, but it didn't suck. It's just not something that I would listen to a lot of, so I'd give it an 8.
Brad?
Yeah, Brad and Irene are here.
Oh, hi Brad and Irene, who got here, by the way.
I think it was a good song. I kind of agree. It's a soundtrack song. I can't wait to see the movie. I'm sure it's going to kick ass there. But it's a good song. I give it a 9.
Irene, the rights princess.
I have a short attention span and it was a long song. It doesn't mean it was bad. It's just hard for me to concentrate on it. Yeah, I know. It's like a freaking long song.
But, um, it was a good song, like, I mean, for a soundtrack song, I mean, it was good, so I'd give it an 8.
Mmkay.
Zero!
Going by the fact that it's even on the movie, I would give it a 10, but I can't do that because I wouldn't be nice.
No, actually, it definitely seems like something, yeah, that would be on a movie.
It's not something that you'd hear anywhere else except the soundtrack or the movie, but I liked it a lot.
And I actually downloaded it and I think I enjoyed it. I give it like a 9.
Low-key is what we need to ask.
It was fucking awesome, dude. I listened to that song, I kid you not, 60 times at least since I've gotten this soundtrack.
And that was only a couple days ago. And it's awesome driving music. Perfect for driving.
You just get going and it's like, yeah!
Your own track real fast.
No, but it's really awesome. I wish you guys could listen to the whole thing because it does pick up even more afterwards and gets really cool techno-y stuff.
But like I said before, it is going to be my pick for Turning Mix 4, and you're going to have a pretty good cut of it then.
But since, you know, it's two minutes and a half, two and a half minutes, it kind of loses some of the stuff, but yeah, really cool. I love it.
Ten, ten, ten, ten, ten, ten, ten.
I really do agree with the sentiment that Jamie kind of started about how it's a soundtrack song, it's kind of in the background.
But I have an unfair advantage. I've heard that edit that Loki's done, the two and a half minute edit, and he really has taken all the best parts of the song
song and made it a stand-alone song like he took all the dude like kind of it
kind of sounds a little tackish actually to me to me I did kind of think that but
yeah back to the soundtrack thing right actually there's another song and they're
called just Chateau that does sound like gravity would that be cool if they
detected the center that'll be it let's do it that is a topic of discussion when
we come back the money artists we want to see do movie scores but anyway um I
I think it's a good song. I think the edit's really, really good and that if that goes into rotation it'll be fine, so I give it a 9. It's a good song, it really is.
But yeah, if I heard all that kind of symphonic stuff during the dance, our normal, the money means more for them, I'd probably go to sleep.
Well, I think it should be mentioned that I was going to do a remix with that being part of the remix.
That was supposed to be entered into the remixing contest, which the deadline is tomorrow, but I don't think that's going to happen.
But I was planning on doing a remix of it.
Alright, let's get into Jamie's pick. Jamie, what did you bring to the table tonight?
Mine's old. I couldn't think of anything else again, so I just picked Herbie Hancock Rocket.
And this is from a game, isn't it?
Well, they did different versions of Amplitude.
Okay, but this is a cool song, so here's your last pick for tonight.
This is Herbie Hancock with Rocket.
Fuck you.
Uh huh.
Alrighty, that was Herbie Hancock with Rocket.
Hope you all enjoyed that one.
Let's go around and see what everyone else thought of Herbie Hancock, Rocket.
Starting off with Jamie.
Ten.
You want to give any reasons why?
Alright.
I'll take that as a no. Irene, what do you think?
I liked it a lot. I liked it a lot. 9.
Alright. Loki.
That was alright. Reminds me of Breakin', so give it 8.
Zero, what did you think of Herbie Hancock Rocket?
What don't I think of that song?
No, actually, that is the second song of the 80s I remember, besides that super happy stalker song by The Police.
But I give that song a 10, just because it's been a favorite of mine forever.
Brad, do you have anything you want to say?
10. Brad gives it a 10.
Brad throws a 10 out through the door.
I like that song, it's pretty cool. If they ever did like a 2DX classic version or something and like brought back a bunch of old 80's songs, I would cry my eyes out if that was not in it.
I'm working on a file for the 2DX simulators for that song, and for DDR.
So I give that like an eight and a half.
Eight and a half?
Eight and a half.
Eight and a half. Didn't you play it?
It's hooked up now.
tonight's cage match. It's a raving, moaning cock.
No, it's a cock rocket.
Only on Orange Lounge Radio do you get the
raving, moaning cock rocket here on the cage match.
Weee-haaa-boom.
You know what's funny about Asian porn? What? It looks like Legos have execs.
Why do you say that? You have to explain that for those who may not have seen Asian porn.
It's all blocked out and stuff, because they're Japanese laws, like no private parts can be shown.
So it just looks like a bunch of Legos having sex.
Based on the American invasion of the Aztec.
It's Aztec sex, baby. Oh yeah. Go mosaic.
The law is actually passed because I'm American.
It's because we have Asian fever.
fever. We want that Asian punani. And we have to import it like nuts. And the Japanese are
getting jealous because, you know, the Japanese men stand a chance against us American men.
And so, they don't want us taking their women away from them. And so, despite us, they censor
their porn.
Oh, we're doing this one way.
Um, great, dead airspace here.
Sorry, I'm starting to tally up some of the votes here, so...
No, you guys missed the philosophical message of the day.
Uh-oh, what was that?
Life is a sexually transmitted fatal disease that's also hereditary.
After your mom gave blowjobs at a truck stop.
I said after your mom gave blowjobs at a truck stop.
He downloaded the mall blowjobs.
No, no, no.
It was like street blowjobs.
It's this guy with this camera and his glasses and he convinces some girl to give him a blowjob, supposedly.
Yeah, also.
I...well...shh!
You lie!
Your scene's all set. Next thing you're probably going to be seeing is,
The amazing flying microphone.
Bad catch.
No, wrestling is not fake. It's real. Real fake.
You funny.
Looks like Jamie's going to go off the turnbuckle with the elbow there.
She's slapping her elbow.
Alright, last call for votes in the Orange Lounge Radio Cage Match. In the meantime, let's take a quick break.
Vote, bitches.
What do we want to do when we come back from the break?
Polka.
Polka?
Oh, yeah, yeah, we're going to do that topic about Bemani artists and soundtracks and movies they should have done.
Nah, it's too weird to be a listless, but we could do a listless.
But then again, I'm too lazy to get paper, so we'll just talk.
Oh, never mind.
Never mind.
Alright, fine.
Fine.
Okay, last call for Cage Match, folks.
That was lunch.
I'll play it later.
Alright, we'll be back after this quick break featuring, um...
Oh, I don't know. What kind of song should I play here?
Cal Snyder Remixed by...
Oh, let's do something. I should do something from EX3.
Dance Mania EX3 was out a couple weeks ago and I got a copy of it. Thank you.
And we'll play...
I'm a little yellow fish in the deep blue sea Won't somebody help me?
Do you wanna know how livin' this in me's the way?
Do you wanna know how everything I knew was changed?
It was just like a big commotion I just had a couple magic oceans
The regal was with, slightly damaged
I was a fish, help me
I'm a little yellow fish in the deep blue sea
Won't somebody help me
Won't somebody save me
Do you wanna take a whale pass
Do you wanna meet a stupid shot?
Do you wanna ride the steel or so high?
Did it always survive?
It isn't such a big commotion
All you need is magic motion
And with a wriggle and twist
It's such a big fish
You're a fish!
Help me!
I'm a little yellow fish in the deep blue sea
Won't somebody help me?
Help me, help me, I need a remedy
When the strings of the night are in your sight
You won't believe the things you see
This world's only way to last time
If you don't wanna feel like it
I'm a little yellow fish in the deep blue sea
Won't somebody help me?
Won't somebody, somebody help me?
Little Little Fish in the deep blue sea
Somebody save me
I'm Little Little Fish in the deep blue sea
Won't somebody save me?
Save me!
1, 2, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7
All the rest can go away
So little time, so many months, yet it never seems enough.
So many people passing by me and so few are made out of the right stuff.
There seems to be a shortage of heroes.
There ain't enough ones or too many zeros
One, two, three, four, oh, oh, seven
All the good guys go to heaven
Five, six, seven, eight
Hey, hey!
All the rest of them go away
One, two, three, four, oh, oh, seven
All the good guys go to heaven
One, two, three, four, oh, oh, seven.
Before that, help I'm a fish by Creamy and really fast, we're still in the middle of
a break here but Irene would you share your bean burrito theory I came up with
the bean burrito theory a couple years ago when I heard that song the one two
three four oh seven because artists some artists on DDR they just pull random
themes or just random words and put them together in a song and it just sounds
stupid like you know and the reason I came up with bean burrito is just like
Oh, you know, hey, I'm hungry. Oh bean burrito. La la la. It's just like it's stupid. Yeah bean
Moly sour cream and extra cheese. I haven't thought up any other let's get that GDR
It's the Mexican version he's seeing that one more time
bean burrito
guacamole, sour cream, and extra cheese.
I'm going to punch you.
Rob, you're a dork.
I just want an extra clean copy of that for any remixes we
might plan.
Thank you.
Oh, you're welcome.
OK, well, let's look at Crash here.
I'm going to go my way.
Come with me, you mothers.
Let's go.
One, two, three, four, five.
Break the doll and get out of here.
Come with me now.
Now we're all going our way.
Makes no sense.
I want to show you baby the world that you've never seen because it can happen now, so hold
you tight babe.
Just pick any Eurobeat song.
Let's see here.
Any Eurobeat song.
I don't want to know what they say, no, no, I don't care, they can tell me nothing, I'm
going to go my way.
Wait, you're not doing it right, it's I don't want to know, it's like Mr. Spanky singing.
Well, you know, I don't want my voice being made into some sort of DWI, so obviously I'm not going to do it with any rhythm.
We really don't need to hear it all, Matt.
Hey, we're still in break time!
Come on, go on, and fall apart. Let's go. Ah.
Ah!
Ah, alright. Back to break. I'm going to play this. This is something that Justin's working on. It's a world premiere. It's an original piece.
And he's even calling himself different names now, too. This is pretty funny.
This is pretty funny.
He's calling himself Hyper Orchestra.
So this is Hyper Orchestra with Musette in D. This is a little sample.
It's a work in progress.
And then after that, we're going to hear a request that Jamie wants you all to hear.
So, we shall do that.
Oh
You're gonna see me die
Drowning in the dark
Where were you to hold my hand
To the things that we had planned
Yes, I need you by my side
When things go crazy
I just need to know you here
Can't we see that you'll see this
When I wake up in the night
Will you be my guiding light
I don't care how far I'll take a place tonight
Tell me where you are and everything's gonna be alright
Like a shooting star
Running in the sky
Wanna fly, just to be with you tonight
I can shoot it down, across the midnight sky
Want to fly, just to be with you tonight.
A and the number 59.
I'm sorry, Zero?
Huh?
I didn't say anything.
I thought you said anyone.
I just said death.
But anyway.
What's death?
Burritos.
Chicken.
Okay, so while they play nachos, vinyl over there, the winner of tonight's cage match,
by the way, can we get a big drumroll?
I'm gonna use this next week.
Okay, the winner is Mona Lisa Overdrive won the cage match.
Yay.
Of course.
can use that next week, Jamie. But, this is the first week I can remember in a long, long
time where every song did get at least one vote. Usually my picks don't even get a vote,
but tonight every song at least got one vote. It's Raven Symone. Everyone's a winner. At
least two votes, no. Everybody loves a seven year old. Raven Symone was not lucky enough
I have to get two votes tonight.
Stop putting on Raven Simone, she sucks.
Sucks!
I didn't vote her as the winner last week.
You guys voted her as the winner?
I'm dismayed.
Our listeners suck.
Why are you dismayed?
Because Rocket owns you.
Because what?
Rocket owns.
Rocket does own, and it did get a good reaction, but unfortunately you just got beat by the
Matrix like everything else.
Who'd be on the Matrix?
I don't believe in the Matrix. Watch me bend this spoon with the power of my mind.
I'll hack the world!
Anyway, more topics. Like promised earlier, we wanted to talk about movies that Bemani
artists should do soundtracks too. Now this could be like upcoming sequels, or just like
ideas for films, or movies in the past that would have been cooler with it.
X-Men movie, TAC. X-Men movie with a TAC soundtrack?
Matrix with TAC. Matrix with TAC?
Babes in Toyland featuring TAC. Is there any movie you wouldn't want to see
TAC doing in the soundtrack too? Um, Secchi movies.
Yes, Loki. Uh oh.
Glitter 2 featuring Paul Eteri That was cute, he did a little happy hop
He did a little happy hopper I bought Orange Lounge, the band, doing a
soundtrack to a porno French porno
to
that would be funny and you know it
yet i could see talk i do like a really epic kind of film
talker do like an epic i was thinking like a summer kabadda
that would be cool to do you know i feel like zero says a gothic porno
kabadda doing rpg music
Well, I don't know if anybody listening knows this for a fact, but since it is Konami, Metal Gear Solid, I don't know, maybe.
But Red Nikita does remind me of Metal Gear Solid, kind of, so maybe that he actually had some actual production in the music of Metal Gear Solid in some way.
One thing for my Metal Gear Solid CD that I have, there's the theme song remix by Quadra from the end.
And you know Quadra did Five Key stuff?
And yes, he is back in it.
So they might as well see that.
They might as well dig, of course, the Bane bad guy is supposed to be a kuna.
Oh my god, oh my god, is Kylie Minogue going to be back in it?
I would.
That would be the best.
She better be.
That'll be the only reason.
I know, she has a career now.
I'm the Green Fairy.
No.
Break-In 3.
Featuring Good Cool.
That would be awesome.
What's this in the VCR right now?
We're watching Break-In.
The only break-in movie I'd ever seen was the sequel, Breakin' 2 Electric Googaloo.
Is it Breakdancing?
Breakdancing. It's done in 82, 83.
Nice. I like that.
I like that.
Here's a cute joke. Here's a cute joke. This is from the chatroom.
Terminator 2DX with Tran as Terminator.
Yes, but if you've ever heard...
Alien Tran for Tran.
Have you ever seen the Terminator movie, guys?
I mean the music is like
It's just a bunch of weird sound effects
It's like the guy pressed on his keyboard a couple times and said here. This is a soundtrack have you ever seen them?
Have you ever seen the Mr.
Science theater 3000 version of pod people where they're doing their new age music now put put your hand
Okay, now put your finger on this key
Now you're playing new age key. Okay now put two fingers on there now
I remember playing a New Age chord. Now hold it down until you get a record label.
And hold it down until you...
It was hilarious.
Back to the soundtracks idea. I'm thinking of like a scary movie.
Let's say The Ring 2, because you know they're going to do a sequel to The Ring,
based off one of the Japanese movies.
Like, Ringu 2. How about Akira Yamaka doing the soundtrack?
Dude, he did the soundtracks for Silent Hill.
Some of the creepiest games ever.
I went on a road trip once and my friend Garrett drove me out to these roads that are not lit very well, so it's like a scary place.
There's all these trees and railroad tracks that are all abandoned and stuff.
And we played Silent Hill while driving through there, it was scary.
The music, the soundtrack?
Yes.
Oh my god.
Because it really messed up. I've never really heard Silent Hill music before because I've never played the game.
It kind of sounds like post-head, I think.
I was really surprised. It doesn't sound like anything Kiriyama has done in 2DX.
Nope, not really.
The name of Silent Hill sounds like Sour Time.
Yeah, the Portishead song, because it's got that guitar or ukulele or whatever they were doing.
Hey, we love dead air here at Orange Lounge.
Sorry, I've been reading private messages.
There's a really funny one I'll have to share with you guys off air.
Insect zero agent porn one.
The boob...
The misshapen boob chick killed the bug.
Any other soundtrack ideas?
Yeah, we can have True Kiss Destination doing...
The Haul's World 2.
What the hell?
Um, yeah, I got it this time. I caught the mic.
Argin has one.
Deval doing Disney?
Like, what Disney movie?
I don't know.
Deval doing Disney, like doing them.
As the chat room suggested during Help I'm a Fish, that should be in Finding Nemo, the new movie coming out.
You know what? No.
Enemy Zero, featuring Desrow.
that you made me watch, with the aliens?
Oh, Wild Zero?
Wild Zero, yeah.
Featuring Desrow.
Any trauma film featuring Desrow?
No.
How about who?
No, I think Guitar Wolf.
Orange Lounge?
Guitar Wolf and Guitar Freaks.
Guitar Wolf is awesome.
Orange Lounge to do the soundtrack to the next John Waters movie.
I think I killed the station.
Well, let's see here.
We could have the next American Pie movie with Mr. Brian in the final band.
There is an American Pie movie coming out.
American Wedding, I know.
I know.
The last one.
Yeah.
I have a movie called 42K that you need to watch, it's hilarious, in parts.
It's got punk music in it.
Mr. No, it's funny, it has to do with these zombies attacking.
They're like these zombies attacking this house and then they get these like Renta Ninjas
they come over and then
and there's like no there's these eight for alien chicks are
it's wick
let me find a tape is hilarious
now robert you know when you tell me about
they're actually doing a true sequel to write your picture show
robin it's a rumor that comes up
it's a rumor that comes up every now and then they did that one have the music by
orange lounge
that would be cool
except you know the problem with that ritual brian has to do it yesterday he
should so that he should bike
contract orange lounge
okay orange lounge can make a contribution
but they're not all in french
i think he gets uh... some help from rena gumo to do something like secret
tale
that's really bad i'm sorry
but in all honesty i think led should do something in a music industry yes like uh...
like a matrix type movie you know action because some of his really uh... you
know
like like uh...
the outer limit outer limits that song something like that break beats
Here's a question for you guys. Maybe this has been brought up on the show before, but I actually don't think it ever has, which is surprising.
If a Bamani artist, any Bamani artist, were to release a CD here in the U.S., which one should do it, and why? Who would have the best chances of success?
Well, Jamie says Tak, and she releases that.
I mean, I only said that because she just said that. And, go ahead, Matt, Lucky.
Well, obviously, it's got to be, I believe, isn't Last Message the good, cool featuring Meg?
Well, then it'd have to be Meg, because she has a nice rack.
One thing, actually, Fantastic Plastic Machine does have a CD in the US.
I have it.
Outside of ones that already do have one, and maybe like the one to, like outside of Dance Mania artists, let's say,
because Dance Mania artists already have CDs, most of them, let's say, like, actual Baloney.
Actual Baloney, you know, sounds sad.
Konami, which Konami sounds sad.
I guess, we could say.
In all honesty, Jamie and Matt both say Good Cool.
I agree, I think Good Cool would have the most chance of success.
Actually though, it's funny you mention, I think one person that would have a really kickass CD, L.E.D.
And I say that because he has so many different styles, like something like something wonderful,
like kind of slow, kind of ballady epic type song, to like in your face, Strong Jaeger type music.
I have something to say.
Sure.
The staple artists in the Konami Sound staff who are making music for Pumani games, Taka,
Tak, L.E.D., Naoki, Good Cool, and I'm probably repeating names because they use the same
names all the time.
Anyway, they all have a chance releasing and selling good music because they all have good
resumes as far as the music they've written, so it's really hard to choose which one.
i mean if you're a local
he's made music in games that are very popular america so
for the same
i don't know
with them
so that they can't dismiss
will be okay i don't know if it's on state
i don't think you'd have to show a little more diversity break say that
yeah that's why i think
that stuff would be picked up by these days like
yet
Because all trance music is pretty much the same anyways.
It's just all synth with a backbeat, that's it.
I'm surprised with the popularity of DDR.
You're not hearing such cultish songs from DDR
that are mega-popular, like Look to the Sky on some dance radio station at night.
It's because we're in Sacramento and we don't have cool stations like that.
Ours got kicked off the air, remember?
Well, there's actually one kind of weird thing.
One night I was actually coming back from CCL, just getting done playing DDR,
I was listening to quad you know on Saturdays or whatever they play that like all that trancey stuff
I actually did hear holic and actually did play it
Yes, it was because we sat there and debated it for like an hour and a half
And it actually was holic which I don't know how it got played
Book fields and heard some to my beat playing out the kitchen
I know, but that was the thing, I thought that was funny.
I think Scottie D should have some stuff.
Yeah.
I forgot what I was going to say.
But they should contract Avix tracks again.
Like they did with Para Para.
Why do you think Konami doesn't release Bimani soundtracks in the US?
Besides the fact that DDR USA, the arcade versions, wouldn't have had a good soundtrack?
There's about 25,000 registered users on DDRFreak, and a lot of soundtracks to real movies sell 5,000 at the most.
I don't know, because usually what happens, they'll print mass amounts of the CDs because, you know, they do...
I mean, you think actual artists like, you know, Britney Spears, millions of CDs get printed, and millions of them get bought, because that's just pop, you know?
Because Konami is cheap and they don't want licensed music and licensing music for a game
is expensive enough, let alone soundtrack rights as well.
Yeah, you have to go for more red tape.
And the fact that making the CDs themselves only costs pennies.
I mean, it's just the whole licensing rights and because over here in America, we're bastards
and we charge, or actually, the RIAA is bastards and they charge, you know, up the ass for,
you know, licensing rights and copyright laws are crazy and it's just, it's a bad situation.
That's why.
All we're going to hear is more, like, uh, more fucking covers of Welcome to the Jungle
and shit by crazy people who don't sound anything like Axl Rose.
I'm not talking about trying to make, like, DDR music, like, mainstream, like, oh, next
on MTV on Total Request Live number 10, drop the bomb, yeah!
I'm not talking about that kind of thing, but just, like, trying to just at least put
the music out there.
If the music isn't out there, if you want the music, you have to go underground.
Yeah, here's what I think. What I can debate why they don't do is maybe they're doing these releases on these home systems, you know, maybe for once release a small sound CD with the game if you pre-order or something, you know?
Well, they did that with Max. Yeah, Toys R Us. Jamie's got one. Toys R Us did that. They had like a... What was the requirements, Jamie? Remember what you had to do to get that CD?
No, I got mine from, uh, from...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, you got yours donated.
Quote, unquote. No, no, mine was, mine's real.
It was given to me, uh... Quite, I know, but it was...
For attorney.
It was a, yeah. I got a few of them that we gave out as prizes for attorney. Right.
But, um, they do, right, I remember Toys R Us was doing something with those. I think if you
pre-ordered at Toys R Us, you got that. I think that's how it worked.
But still, I mean, that's not, that's not like, I can walk into Dimple and see it
in the soundtrack section, or, Dimple is, I'm sorry, because that's only in Sacramento,
It's a record store, so let's say I can't walk into Virgin Megastore, and Virgin Megastore imports a lot of stuff. They don't import anything Japanese, which baffles me.
Very limited, though. Very, very limited.
I will grip a Dragon Ball DC.
Okay, well, I'm talking like, I don't think you can find a Yumi Hamasaki even, right? You can even...
You can order it from Dance Media.
Really? Could you order Dance Media albums through Virgin? Hmm.
You can totally order anything from Virgin.
I went to the Virgin Megastore in San Francisco and I never see anything interesting Japanese-wise.
And it's kind of the thing with America in general and the history of music, it's like pop has always been popular and it's always been the main thing, you know, and we, yeah, we all hate pop, but America goes through its phases.
It's like, okay, first there's rap, like original rap, like 80s, late 70s rap, Sugarhill Gang rap, and then we go back to pop, you know, Billy Joel.
Then we go to whatever the next thing is, you know, grunge or whatever, you know, and then we go back to pop.
We go through these phases, and we already went through our techno trance rave music phase in the mid 90s, and it's gone now. It's not popular. There's a lot of people doing these things, but there's a lot of freaking people in America. A lot more people are listening to Britney Spears. I'm sorry. It's always going to be that way. It's always going to be pop.
Not always, because music rotates itself every...
Not that, I wouldn't say that long, probably about more like every four years.
Okay, then watch.
Four to ten years from now, we're going to see some Beaumont ECDs printed, finally.
I'm going to tell you, now this is going to be a really strange sounding theory, and I know I'm going to get booze for this,
but I'll tell you why Britney Spears and all that's on their way out the door.
And this is going to sound funny.
Because they suck.
American Idol is the reason why Britney Spears is going to be on its way out the door.
Because it's just, it's saturating, we're seeing too much of it.
No.
Look at the three people who are in the finals in American Idol right now.
You have two overweight people and a dork.
Exactly.
What does that show America wants right now?
They are sick and tired of seeing the same cookie cutter image.
Yeah.
And... exactly.
So I'd say that's...
That's why I'm saying they actually want to hear the music for once and not just the image.
Far-fetched as it sounds, I think that might be starting to send a message to record companies
I bet you, even sales of Christina's latest album wasn't as good as her first one, and Britney's putting a new one out in October, and it's probably not going to do as well. I think it's October, but it probably won't do as well.
Well, wouldn't it be funny if Britney Spears pulled an Alanis?
What do you mean? Disappeared and came back?
Stop doing Happy Happy Poppy?
Alanis used to be a very Happy Poppy person.
I actually have a video, Alanis Morissette was considered the Tiffany of Canada, and she had the big poofy hair,
Matt LeBlanc was in one of her videos, she was on the Canadian television, but she used to have, like, these songs.
I could probably dig up the MP3s on my computer, but I'm too lazy.
Um, but she used to have, like, really dancy songs.
She disappeared completely for about four years, and then came back, and she'd, like, grown up, and that's when she did Jagged Little Pill,
and it was such a, such a controversy, you know, like, oh, now this teen princess talking about blowjobs in a theater type thing.
But I mean if you think about it the real Tiffany did the same thing didn't she come back and pose for Playboy?
Well like I mean one thing that I've noticed too is all these people have hella videos and have all these concerts and all these
fucking appearances
They you know everybody hears that music so much that people just grow to get tired of it
Then you got the underground people who?
Will send their demo to a radio station or something get it played more people want to see more people want to hear
the people who you don't see every day as opposed to who you do see every day I
mean that's why I think like if we did have a lot of Bimani's music Bimani
CDs coming over and or anybody even a lot of the underground you know rappers
and DJs and stuff like that most people sit there and they don't really want to
go to really see them they like to know who they are but they like the music so
much and the music is what keeps the mystery and what keeps them want to be
there if you don't do a lot of appearances people gonna want to know
They're going to want to hear your stuff more than, like, oh, look, there's that hoe on TV. You know, it's that whole thing.
Well, the DJs, they're just a name. They're just a name, so you know which CD to find. That's it.
I mean, if you met them in real life, you're like, oh, they're really cool. You wouldn't be like, oh, I got a, oh, my God, you know, they're so cool.
No, it's just, they're just...
Wait, if I saw Paul Walkenfold, I'd probably give him a hug.
Yeah, yeah.
But like, for instance, um, DJ David X, I mean, he's kind of popular over here, I mean,
you see him personally, like, damn, I don't, he's old.
Yeah, he's just some...
He's an actual friend of one of Dan's friends, he's a DJ in Santa Cruz.
He's cool, but, and the music he plays is really cool, that's the whole point, though.
It's not like, you know, Britney Spears, you hear more controversy and shit about them.
When's the last time you've heard, like, a DJ and something weird happening with them?
like oakenfold you never hear anything on the news like some controversy is it
because he's just too busy making music and you know doing actual stuff like
that. You know what actually has made me really happy is that one of my favorite
Japanese DJ's has his CDs now released in the States DJ Crush makes me very
very happy and from what I understand I mean he'll do music for anyone you know
mixing for anyone just you know goes to clubs all the time. I wish he'd come actually
Well, he had performed here because she even went to see him
In San Francisco, I think but I would you know, I would like for for just more people internationally
To make their music available
Like one thing too and not a lot of people are familiar with the music
But there's like the band called Dream Theater and I don't know how many people know about them
But they're over in Japan a lot
I mean, that's their basic residence is in Japan
Even though they're completely English singing group and their music sells a lot more over here
Than they do over than it does in Japan
I mean and they do they're just random appearances like once every five years you actually get to see them and it's enough to make
A person want to drop everything and go see image because they don't have huge videos over here people like their music
I mean, I honestly was about to cut my Santa Cruz trip because they're gonna be in Sacramento on Sunday
And I was about to cut it, but I like nah, that's okay
But it's still it's like the point is people will drop with what you're doing if they don't see you getting in trouble
And they don't see you dressing like an absolute moron and all that kind of stuff, and there's still a hair band
They are still a hair that is the hair band
Interesting point I'm reading in the chat room
I'm just trying to read what folks are saying in the chat room jabberwocky makes an interesting point hi by the way
He was responding to a comment made on me by Justin
The record companies put out hundreds of albums each month.
The terrible music is what people are buying.
Why is that?
I was about to say something about the record companies because they basically, I think,
tell us what we're going to listen to.
We all are speaking from what we know in our sphere of influence of how we love the music
and stuff, but you got to remember the main population is going to follow what the record
company puts out.
they're putting out all this crappy music and it's getting sold. Why? Why does the record
company do anything? Money? I don't know.
This is my theory, the publicist behind the artist. I think there's a lot of wheeling
and dealing that goes on, especially with MTV. And MTV is to, you know, if you want
to use the word blame, credit, whatever you want to choose, MTV is really what's shaping
the music industry right now, like it or not.
It's all politics.
Exactly, it's all politics.
If my politics is the lobbyists pay the politicians, and that's how certain laws get passed. Although
I kind of buy into the Josie theory. The Josie and the Pussycats. I will elaborate for people
who haven't seen it.
One thing too is this is only stuff that I picked up while working at Intercom Radio
and stuff like that and a lot of it is not so much who is you know who's gonna
dress I mean who's how old and who looks like what or whatever but part of it is
the fact that they will go with whoever will dress trashy you know there's
plenty of girls I out there I have seen shut up don't start no anyways no it's
It's like, there's, they go to see who will dress like the slut, who will do, I mean there's
plenty of girls out there who probably look like Britney Spears and who may sound like
Britney Spears, but they're the ones who won't go as far as the others went.
And then yeah, it is MTV partially, because they get tons of videos crossing their path
every day.
It doesn't mean they're going to play them all, they're going to play with the ones that
that all the people are fantasizing about and go home and whack it off about or so if
they do it.
I mean, that's all it is.
Nince makes...
Okay, some interesting points here.
Nince says in the chat room, people buy the terrible stuff because they don't know about
the better stuff out there.
Nince.
That's actually exactly true.
Well, and then this is interesting, a response from Jabberwocky, name terrible music, or
is it just what is popular and what you don't like?
Well, yeah, I guess terrible music is a...
I mean, first of all, nobody in this room will pretty much admit to being a fan of Britney
Spears or any of that stuff.
I will admit that I like her stuff, I like some of her stuff, but it's getting old.
I feel like, okay, the pop thing is getting old for me.
I'm cycling on a four-year thing, you know, I don't really care about her new album anymore.
She was cute back in the day.
Oh, look, what a little slut dancing on the screen.
But I don't care anymore.
I'm a fan of her future porno with her and Christina Aguilera, hot lesbian action.
Back to the point here, there's no real way to force people to expose themselves to new
music.
Yeah, I guess people will like what they want to like, but I feel like sometimes it's ignorance.
We only hear what we can hear on the radio, most people.
Your average music listener isn't a music lover, as in it's their life, they love it
like I do.
It's like I have to listen to music all the time, I go watch live music and stuff.
All they can hear is the radio, so they're being told what to listen to, so that's one
thing.
Another thing, yeah, you can't tell them what to listen to, what's terrible music, one person
likes something else.
There is actually terrible music.
I think Britney Spears and stuff is terrible music.
There's no talent behind it except for she has boobs, she has an ass, she can't sing
worth shit.
I've heard so many people who can sing better.
What do you, okay, what do you think, hold on, hold on, hold on, question, question.
What do you think about those people on like the fan shows that talk about Britney Spears
and say, Britney Spears changed my life?
I think it's sad.
There's fans of everyone, okay? I'm sure Bob Saget has a huge following. I'm sure Carrot
Top has a huge following.
I love Bob Saget, man. I just saw Dick for Coker. What was it?
There's fans for everybody. There is, there's fans for anybody that appears on TV for like
just a second. Perfect example, G-Force Portal, that stupid guy that had, he has fans, okay?
That proves right there that anybody can have fans. We have fans, okay? I mean, it's a-
Oh, there you go. There's proof right there. We have fans.
So, no-
Maybe not me.
Here's my point. The point is that they'll have fans. They'll have, you know, a certain
group of people are talking good about them and everything. That's gonna be a given. The
The fact is that they just, you know, it's just mainstream stuff right now. Like, for
instance, I don't know really why people buy their CDs and stuff since it's played on the
record all or on the radio all the time. Like, for instance, 98 Rock in our Sacramento area
here plays the same shit every day. I can guarantee that I'll hear like a few songs,
you know, certain songs every day. It's just like a same playlist that's randomized.
When I worked at 98 Rock, we, my eight-hour shift, you would hear a song 12 times and
I know it would be the exact same, say, maybe 13, 14 songs.
It would hear the same song 12 times a day, at least in one eight-hour shift.
You know what, though? I'll say this, though.
I got called from 98 Rock a couple times over at the radio station.
I don't know how I ended up on their list or whatever,
but they called and would ask me to listen to little seconds of songs.
And the only reason I did it, I usually don't participate in those phone survey things,
but I actually knew I'm like, okay, what I'm saying might actually really have an effect
on what they're going to play on the station, so I should participate.
funny because a lot of the songs I'd never heard of before. It was actually interesting.
So they were trying to test stuff I'd never heard before, but the majority of it that
I found in myself liking was kind of a lot of the mainstream stuff, I'd say, just because
I was familiar with it. But at the same time, there was a lot of that stuff I did recognize
as me not liking.
I took one of those where they'd have me compare to, and my response to actually a lot of what
they'd play, I would be like, I don't like either, I don't like either, I don't like
either until they'd play like music that sounded like it wasn't cookie-cut
because for me and you know what I listen to I've listened to some really
interesting stuff while you've been in it what's in my car right now
kana and yeah I'm a Japanese music okay I forgot to tell you there's totally a
different subject Garrett ordered a video of kana videos and so he's gonna
get it soon and you're gonna have to come over and watch them because I
showed him the I it's not a DVD it's a tape but I showed him the one and like
He's just like I have to see the other so I just sorry I forgot to tell you earlier
CD Japan
It's like basically I mean if you want to find like you like good music
Why don't you just do it a lot of people do because every different type of music has this why don't you go out and buy?
Like samplers because samplers a lot of the times not all the time it depends on which label you go through
They will play new bands that not a lot of people have heard of and that yeah compilations and stuff like that go find those
Play it listen to them honestly
Yeah, movie soundtracks also because honestly you're gonna find most music
You're gonna have you're gonna have in your music collections if you start buying compilation samplers are gonna be all the ones you got off
Of those it's I mean, it's so basically
You know it really sucks
But stop listening to the fucking radio for five minutes and go out and spend five bucks and buy a damn sampler
Irene oh, yeah, I just have a really simple basic theory, okay
It's just that people are going for what's familiar and what's
Simple something that's not too complex
Yeah, exactly. You know they they you know
Oh, yeah, so they go for Britney Spears and Christina Aguilera because it's simple
It's not too hard, but then everyone goes through you know their cycles of music. They change
I mean, I'm not listening to same stuff. I listen to ten years ago five years ago, whatever so I mean it always evolved
So yeah, I'm gonna pass let's try and wrap this up. I just wanted to say I just want to say really quick
Okay, go for Jimmy. Well, if you look at it like what do we have today the Backstreet Boys?
You know when I was in middle school, we had new kids on the block
In the 70's there was the Partridge Family, but there was David Cassidy. He had fangirls when he died. We have the same thing happen today over these poppy people. It's because they have an image that can be sold.
Here's the thing. Michael Jackson, he is a pop artist, but he is talented, and that's why he deserves fans, because he writes good music, and he helps produce good music. Maybe not recently, but he certainly knows how to make headlines.
You can still be a nutjob and do good music, so to say.
himself cholera-infected water so that he would die because
i was going to say that passed about five minutes ago
as i say i am
uh... as you're saying about their radio and you know stop was really or whatever
trying and this is going to be really cheap blood but i'm serious here
good internet radio
look around the light three six five a m
uh... thousands of stations
that uh... with your time to listen to if you want to sample new music
internet radio is a great way to do it because you have
you have weirdos like us sitting here to put together their own stations of
stuff they like and how do you find out about a lot of music through your
friends and what they like so go go look at some uh... other stations of our life
is exact we give you permission
we give you permission to go away from one hundred for a little while to go out
check out some other stations but not very long you got back
uh...
uh... thirty minutes ago
but what i was going to say
you're talking about uh...
uh... van gogh or that i had to do is a very good
instead of talker
artist he's high on absent and cut off your way do
he said it was girlfriend he said his girlfriend as like a mall
well i wonder at the letter said can you hear me now
and that doesn't make sense but it was funny
uh... looking together
you have a final thought i did have a thought on the
stuff but i think we
here's the thought that i have
Go online, get your nice file-sharing service, and download massive amounts of MP3s from
artists you don't recognize. Don't buy the CDs, because, you know, stupid artists, you
know, they don't deserve money, because if their music sucks, then, you know, they should
learn, okay, no one's buying my CD, maybe I should think of a new career, you know?
Did you put the disclaimer at the beginning that some of these people, their views and
opinions do not, you know, reflect the opinions of Orange Lounge Radio?
They don't know that by now they're retarded
You know what? He's absolutely right though
If you can't make music stop making crappy music if you have enough people telling you hey, buddy
You're shitty did stop making music sometimes that doesn't work
But what okay back to the Britney Spears not only what about the one that says you changed my life through your music
There's always going to be somebody who says that.
Guess what, um, Ghost in the Shell changed my life.
Because it made me want to be a ghost in the shell.
You know, it's stupid.
Yes, now I know how to make Lego sex.
First off, all those people who are saying, oh this changed my life.
First and foremost, the only one you should change your life for is yourself.
You're shallow.
You need to take responsibility for yourself.
That's sad that one song changes your life.
That is the biggest problem with people today is they don't take responsibility for themselves.
Yeah, that scares me that Britney Spears is changing all these youngins' life.
It just scares me for my future.
They're hitting the responsibility for their changes on other people.
They're blaming other people for what's going on in their lives.
They need to start taking responsibility and be their own person.
So you're changing your life?
Yeah.
Yeah, changing my life.
Now I wear short skirts and I have sex with everybody.
We need more of those people.
Okay, well, what an excellent way to fill a half hour.
We're kind of past our 9.30 time now, so away from that topic now.
Thanks you guys, that was really good.
Wow, this has been a really good show tonight.
We had a professional discussion.
We had intelligent conversation and debate.
I guess that's debatable, and I'm sure our chat room debates that right now.
We talked about porn, we worked porn in.
Okay, yeah, we got the blowjob thing in at the beginning.
Alright, we worked at the truck stop. Okay, so now I'm going to ask everybody, thank you
everybody, what a good way to end season 2. What a very nice way to end the season 2 finale
there. Just a reminder everybody, next week, no show, but we got an even better thing planned,
Saturday live all freaking day from B3, the tournament of the century at Pier 39. We might
be there Sunday as well. Don't know yet. We'll see. Anyway, let me go around and get some
final thoughts from everybody. Jamie, you want to start or you want to be last?
I'll be last. Okay. Brad, final thought. Tough.
What lesson did we learn today, kids? Music industry is communism. Don't follow him.
Okay. Irene, final thought? It doesn't have to be about the topic we've been discussing.
anything you want
i'm tired you're tired yeah i'm sorry babe what happened to bed last night
uh... i think about last night was that this morning uh... at like what six
o'clock
it's where we went to denny's
every job or did you
i was so tired you guys it was so crap i had to drive me home anyway and people
don't want to hear that people want to hear about that stuff i was
very tired slept for twelve hours today i didn't wake up to a four
uh... drove it home too
Loki final thought. Oh, sorry Rita. I'm done. Okay Andrew spent Loki's busy working. Let me ask zero zero final thought
Basically my final thought is
Take everything I have we have said about the radio and use it in your daily life
Don't be conformist and be an individual and don't let don't let people tell you
What to do and don't let them tell you what to like
Be yourself, or else we'll just have a bunch of robots running around and it'll just end
up being the destruction of the human fucking race.
Goodbye.
I guess I will go ahead and give my final thought.
My final thought is thank you everybody for supporting Orange Lounge Radio.
Thank you everybody who listens to this show every Sunday, our fans.
Thank you by the way to Keisa at FeelThePulse.net for letting me be on her show on Saturday
and promote tonight's show.
Thank you.
if you're into Sims Online and all that.
Thank you everybody who supports Orange Launch Radio
and listens to our Bahmani Music Amor program.
It's been almost a year now that we've been doing Orange Launch.
It's been a blast.
And in two weeks, we come back to you with Orange Launch Radio Season 3.
We're going to have a webcam of some sorts to show things
when we want to show them to you.
Phones, we're working on it.
Loki is busy.
We were hoping that the phones would be the big thing
we can bring into Season 3.
We don't know if we can have it the first week,
but Loki is on it,
and we all know that that means scary.
Scary, so thank you everybody for your support. We appreciate it.
Now 1-900-HOT-THUCK.
Loki, quick...
Well, I'm going to let Jamie do her final thought and then we'll end with yours.
Jamie?
Mine is give me a dollar.
Len Loki, dare I ask what's your final thought?
What I don't understand in this world is how there can be so many hidden camera people with these ugly guys going out,
finding people in random places and then gaining them to do sexual acts on them.
So I leave you with yet another streetblowjob.com video.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Skye, and Loki.
If you'd like to leave us a comment, send us an email at orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
Who's always giving strong bad a hand?
The King.
Who's always messing up home stars plans?
Who's gonna start a rock and roll band?
Who's making out with Marvie fans?
The cheat, the cheat is in the house
Who's the man that looks like the cheat?
Who's the one with yellow feet?
Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.
.