You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio Season 3, now with 200% more hot monkey sex.
Just kidding, Orange Lounge Radio will not contain 200% more hot monkey sex.
It will contain 300% more hot monkey sex.
Hey guys, cut the track!
Okay, I guess it's back to the real intro.
Yeah, me and him have fun, too!
Toto?
I have a feeling we're not in Kansas anymore.
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio for Monty Talk and Then Some.
Uh, mostly the and then some part of that.
Orange Lounge Radio is created by a bunch of potty-mouthed adults.
Orange Lounge may contain sexual, perverted, and mildly retarded content.
You probably shouldn't let your children listen to Orange Lounge Radio.
Yes, I will spank your child.
If you're not going to do your job, goddammit, I will.
Well, here's my big opening.
A sphincter says what?
I'm super. Thanks for asking.
Oh, you little bitch troll from hell.
What am I doing here?
No.
Dodge this.
Mm-hmm. This is a tasty burger.
Look, you stupid bastard. You've got no arms left.
Yes, I have. Look.
Just a flesh wound.
Searching for a boy in high school isn't useless.
It's searching for meaning in a polyshore.
Oh, yeah? Well, I hope your babies look like monkeys.
Dark Sakura.
but I'm playing it for the bartender, so suffer.
Loki.
I hate you!
Orange Lounge Radio.
Orange Lounge Radio is now live for this episode 45 here on May 25th of 2003.
You're tuned into the Bemani Scene's most starzy radio station of all scenes of Bemani.
My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
Joining me, as always, are my awesome co-hosts.
In this corner, the happiest bunny on the farm, Miss Jamie Sommers.
You know her better as Dark Sakura?
Who just copped up a lung?
You might want to go buy some masks at Walgreens or something.
No, I was going to buy some in San Francisco.
We found SARS masks in the Japan Center Mall.
That's cool.
I almost bought some, but I bought them on my bed.
have more battle royale
uh... in that corner say hello to our tech master loki
is anybody feeling well is it
also with us tonight we have a whole ass load of guests some of them are out in the pool
but some of them are in house first off she's never been on the show before
be gentle and say hello to
marin chan
beautiful
also uh... some old favorites old and moldy but still still fresh
say hello to dark tetsuya
old and moldy
say hello to ddr angel
and say hello to the twenty third magus moldy but still fresh
what was that about tofu?
and uh... all we've got some people at the door great more people just we need
right now let's let's see
let's hold off and see what comes through the door
always
all all it's low-key girl friends
are you are to come here come here and say hello you've never been on the show
oh she's shy
she's shy
So I guess we'll get started with the show.
There's also four people that are out in the pool right now who aren't even in here right now, so
maybe we'll hear from them later. Hey, guess what, kids? It's our season three premiere!
Yay! Which means, on the show tonight, somebody will get married, have a baby, or die.
Are we gonna jump the shark?
Tonight, we jump the shark.
I think we did that with the first episode, though.
Yeah, Orange Lobs Radio jumped the shark on the first episode.
tell all your friends and all your lovers that the orange launch radio is now on the
air and all your enemies and we're set for a big show tonight we have like two weeks
of stuff to catch up on there's a lot tonight uh we're gonna start this off with a song
that created some big news this week it's a brand new song it's gonna be a max 2 usa
and it's a group called four strings and this song is take me away into the night and we'll
We'll be right back, boys and girls.
Take me away, million miles away from here
Take me away, find a place for you and me
You're taking me higher, high as I could be
Take me away, forever you and me
Take me away
Tears I cry, kept them all inside I needed time to make up my mind
Take me away, million miles away from you
Take me away, find a place for you and me
You're taking me higher, high as I could be
Take me away, forever you and me
Take me away
You really have to fly away from me
But I'm ready for you and me
To take you higher
As high as I could be
Take me away
Forever you and me
We bring heaven and space, and the breeze blows
Why forever?
Every night I look in your eyes
For your name and what you've brought
It's more contagious than SARS!
or is it
welcome back to orange laundry of boys and girls
well
there's shirtless men walking into my apartment
it's april fools it must be
uh...
anyway hi
everybody everybody just got blacks
You're listening to orange lounge radio. It's our season premiere as you can tell we just had some nudity
On this show here cuz wow it's like we're having a whole fashion show
New characters coming in with with gratuitous nudity in the first two minutes of the show
Damn too bad we weren't able to get the webcam up today after all
Say hello say hello new people introduce yourselves to the listeners of orange lounge radio
uh...
both reading the way you're not shy come on
and i don't want to be on the air and a lot
or
it's only one of those nights
uh...
here's the state of orange lunch radio
if you want to join our chat room because the other parties on in the
chat room
w w w
dot uh...
cali bahmani dot com click on orange lounge and then click on chat
and that's
you can join in our chat room
i can't believe you guys are already getting out of the pool
i'm so sad
how to cry
uh... what
anyway
oh snooty people came in and ruined the pool okay anyway hi back to the show
oh irene and brad just came in say hello
uh brad's still outside but hi everyone
how was the pool
So, there's too many people there.
Oh.
I'm afraid of pools and apartment complexes.
Why are you afraid of pools?
Yeah.
Jamie, why are you afraid of pools?
Because little children pee and go poo.
I was in a public pool once and I saw a big turd floating in the pool.
That reminds me of Caddyshack where the baby roosters fall from the pool.
I actually saw it happen.
Let's talk about things that have happened while we were last on the air, which was two weeks ago.
I got SARS.
Okay, go in the shower.
We're trying to do a show here, hello.
Jamie, how was your two weeks?
Um, it was okay.
We sort of did a show last weekend, sort of.
Yeah, we broadcasted all day long from B3.
What did you guys think of B3? What did you think of B3, the big tournament that happened at Pier 39?
I sort of missed all of Sunday because I decided to go to the mall.
I don't know, do you think B3, because a lot of people online were kind of like, kind of
had this kind of, like, you know how B3 was supposed to be like this huge tournament,
you know, it was going to be like the biggest tournament ever, and a lot of people just
came back from it feeling kind of mediocre.
They were like, uh, PA kind of down the hill thing.
I think it was timing because there was a lot going on around there.
I agree.
I think it was just bad timing.
I think the original plan for B3 is that they were supposed to do it over spring break,
and I think that would have been cool, but the time they did it just kind of turned out
I don't know. Yeah, it's too bad because they ended up doing it the same weekend as e3
Which caused a lot of confusion in the names alone
I think it's weird though because everything at the tournament was put together really well and everything was run really well
I mean sure ran a little late, but all tournaments do but yet despite how everything how great everything ran
It's just kind of everybody was just kind of bleh and freestyle with the exception of two routines was kind of bleh.
I don't know. That's my little rant on b3. I mean it's certainly nobody's fault. It's just kind of like I think everybody just kind of
Must have had what I think everybody was on their collective period or something. I think that's what it is
Jamie you're staring off into space
You have anything you want to say about B3, Logie?
I didn't get a badge and I didn't get a chair until after I asked.
And I didn't get my free shirt done, as promised.
I liked being able to broadcast though because like we were like five feet away from the machine and that was cool
Because we were like broadcasting everybody there were stop stop stop stop stop. Yeah, stop stop stop stop
There were a lot of you guys listening to the stomp
I think a lot of you tuned in and just kind of had it as background noise noise for the day
which is cool, you know, whatever whatever floats your boat and
I
Think it gives me anyway battleship. Yeah, it gives me incentive anyway to
to uh... broadcast for more terms in the future
well
can you guys shut the door
season
and i mean speaking in and get it
i have three people in my shower right now
this is all the season premiere stuff going on we had nudity new characters
and now they're all in my shower at the same time
I saw Garret's ass. He's showing me a scar by his ass. How funny.
I'm not taking a shower. I'm right here.
She says she's right here, staying in the studio, not taking a shower.
But she's in the shower. I don't believe her.
Segue, segue. While we were sort of on the subject of B3, Loki, I believe you owe me something.
Perhaps, I don't know, an apology. As promised. You are on the spot!
Loki's eyes got really big like a deer in headlights. He doesn't even remember.
What the hell are you talking about?
What? What the hell are you talking about? Seriously?
Of what?
you need to remind loki what he said to make that actually keep up with what
does on these episodes
i believe there is this really
uh... bad
wait what was the second day freestyle or
first it was p a m freestyle
yeah i think it was a really bad freestyle and you're like
oh my god if these people that were here
or at uh... shaft and brewing maggots off that they would
screw the other guy up instead and cheer Magus on. I was confused. Anyway, whatever.
Yeah, because that guy really sucked.
I mean, he was like, oh my god, spazzing up on the pad.
And this is relief for me, who went out to go get Oyakodar.
But no, no apologies, sorry.
Ah, he died.
As Magus shows Loki his IQ of one.
Very, very nice.
I hear you turning dials.
This camera is the suck.
No wonder these are bi-link hit-win-free, they're ass.
So why are we having all this dead airspace, Rob?
I have no idea, because I'm too distracted by the people in my shower right now.
Because I keep hearing nudity and oh my god and ass and tattoos and scarves.
Did you just like put them all out in the yard and get the water hose?
water hose.
First, Irene walks in the door when Garrett's changing, she doesn't bother knocking.
This time, she knows that he's in the shower, but he opens up the shark urn, she opens the
shark urn anyway, and he's naked.
No, I just realized that he was all changing and getting naked, he had a towel around him,
okay?
Well, great, we got our nudity out of the way in the first ten minutes of the show,
beautiful.
But we haven't even talked about porn yet.
I know and there's been no porn discussion yet
uh... also
what movie?
Oh, tell us about the movie we watched last night, Angel. I'll let you tell the story.
Oh, was that last night when she was here?
Or Thursday night?
Yeah, I caught it!
Yeah, tell us about the movie we watched Thursday night.
It sucked ass.
It was kinda boring and
I don't even know why the hell you got me to watch it.
Never rent
whatever the hell that movie was
the film that we watched was called
Envy, actually it says Envy on the box, it's actual full title is called Penis Envy
it's a story about these two drifting chicks, they're walking through the desert
they go to this bar and they get really drunk and I mean this is talking about
like white trash America
they get drunk and they're walking through the desert and all of a sudden they go
Wouldn't it be great to have a penis?
And so they walk around, and lo and behold,
when this one chick's taking a piss,
they find the penis fairy, which is this giant drag queen guy.
And then they go and ask the penis fairy for a penis,
and they get a penis.
But with the penis comes great responsibility.
And they have mustaches, and body hair, and tattoos,
and they start acting like guys.
Hey, Loki?
Was it Mr. Spanky?
And then they start like, you know, screwing this one chick and then this other thing,
they screw this other guy and then eventually they get tired of having a penis and so they go
and find the penis fairy in LA where she's at a gay bar.
And then they ask for the penis fairy to remove the penis and then,
but the one chick likes the penis so much and then she ends up getting killed in the end.
That was beautiful, thank you.
Anyway, let's try to focus on some Bahmani news, because there was lots of it while we were gone for two weeks.
So, Max 2 USA was the big kind of announcement that...
Well, there were several games that were announced at E3, the big convention that none of us got to go to, because nobody takes this show seriously.
Hey, I could have gone.
You could have been able to go, but not because of this show.
I couldn't get off work.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But there were lots of fun things discussed at E3. First off was Max2USA and we heard a bunch of songs were announced for inclusion, including Days Go By by Dirty Vegas, the song you heard in the last break, Four Strings Take Me Away into the Night, and also Jocelyn and Rika's Little Bit of Ecstasy. All those songs, by the way, are in rotation right now in our stations, so if you want to check them out.
But what I find really interesting about Max2USA is that the real music videos are going to be in the backgrounds now.
That's going to be pretty cool.
Do you think that there's going to be an option where you can select, oh I want the big seizure, flashy looking graphics, amazing Japanese fun, or you can have the real music video?
I don't know, but it doesn't bother me either way.
I wonder if they're going to have long versions because of the music videos.
Long versions, that would be interesting.
Now, you know they've promised, I guess, different modes that we haven't seen in the U.S. before?
Music video mode.
So, like, music video mode, like, where you could just watch the videos.
Kind of like, okay, you're remembering 2DX6 style, how you could just watch the videos if you wanted to?
Do you think they'll have something like that?
That'd be cool.
Yes, that would be neat.
Because I know that I've had gatherings where people just put in sick style and watch the
videos and drank.
I could go for some drink.
Do they have the mode where you get to meet Kiryamoka?
Because he was at E3 and yeah.
Because I don't really give a shit about Max USA or any DDR or whatnot.
I want to be Kiryamoka.
Why don't you give a shit about Max 2 USA, because I'll tell you right now, it's going
to be better than the Japanese Max 2, because I played the Japanese Max 2 for three days
and I haven't played since.
Because this DDR sucks.
I play Beatmania.
When are they going to bring out a new console, Beatmania?
That's all I care about.
That was the other interesting bit of news.
There was this big rumor going around that Konami was going to, I know we talked about
this on the show and we read it with extreme caution.
I think I called it, didn't I?
Oh yeah.
sure we all approach it with this big bit of skepticism.
If I remember right, the news source wasn't a very trustworthy one.
But they were announcing 2DX USA, and they were going to have a machine brought to E3,
and they were going to bring in like Take and Yes, or no, not them, Lisu and who's the
other guy?
Agop.
They were going to bring in Lisu and Agop and have them playing at E3 to show Americans
how to play 2DX.
What a bunch of crap.
So that didn't end up happening.
But I don't know.
I'm pretty sure we talked about it on the show before, but does the USA really deserve 2DX?
It just happened anyway.
If they brought 2DX to the USA, it wouldn't sell for shit.
Like, how everyone said that...
They complained that frequency was too difficult, so they made amplitude easier, and hence it became an even bigger piece of crap.
I like amplitude.
What would you like to repeat that for our listeners?
I like Super Sproat, that song is cool and that's about it.
Wait, so before we move on to other games, nobody has any other thoughts on Max 2 USA?
Is anybody looking forward to it? Nobody cares?
It'll be out, but you know. It'll be fun for about a week.
You know what though, I am going to have the Xbox One. Oh yeah, that's the other one we can talk about.
I have no choice because we get everything cool that comes out on Xbox.
I mean, I got Steel Battalion, of course I'm going to have DDR.
DDR, although the dance pad looks retarded, it's green, and it's official though.
I don't know, the dance pads are kind of scary to me, they're all freaky looking.
Like they're red.
They're Xbox-y.
Well, Xbox everything is freaky looking.
But they're actually Konami made pads.
Hmm.
Well, you know the producer of the DDR Xbox game was on DDR Freak earlier this week and
he said a few things about the game, which are interesting.
He says that the look of the game that they showed at E3 is not representative of the
final gameplay.
So in that version there was no 3D, no music videos, and haven't even begun to show what
the Xbox is capable of.
So I guess that's kind of interesting because I guess in a way they're saying, hey, Max
2 USA was further along than DDR Xbox was.
Also Freezeros will be in DDR Ultramax except there were none at E3.
You're going to be able to play it online, so you're going to be able to get on Xbox
Live and have live rankings and statistics, and your individual scores will be able to
be ranked with the rest of the people via a live connection, and you can also have edited
step data, and you can upload and download that by users, and new songs will be released
on a monthly basis for download.
However, there's a rumor going around that says you might have to pay for these songs.
Who knows?
Yeah, what is that about?
I mean, if it were, like, for the licensed stuff, I could understand, but if it were
I mean, that doesn't sound fair.
Especially if they're all songs we've played to death already.
I don't think I could rationalize paying like five bucks for a new song or something, you
know?
Would anybody here actually admit to paying for new DDR songs just so they could have
everything?
No.
Okay.
That's a no.
How about the chat room?
I don't know.
I'm not even watching the chat room right now.
Chat room?
Who cares about them?
We do. I love chat room.
You hang out in our chat room?
It sounds like a cheap, interesting way to make money.
But don't you, correct me if I'm wrong, Jamie, you're the one that's played Xbox
online. I don't think anyone else here has.
No, I watched Dan play it. But don't you have to... He's a street fighter.
Don't you have to pay per month for that anyway?
Xbox Live? Yeah.
So now you're going to have to pay per month and pay per song you want to download? You shouldn't have to.
I know, that's gay.
It's called Licensing Rights, yay!
Pretty soon there's going to be a Napster for DDR.
Actually, why not?
I mean, think about it, you're downloading a program.
I mean, people could share programs online.
I mean, why not?
I'm sure they'll have a site where you can download them illegally.
Anyway, also the producer of Ultramix says that there's going
to be 55 songs planned for the US version, 10 of those licensed and if I'm not mistaking
only 5 of them in Max USA were licensed so that's going to be interesting.
And also kind of a big one, there's no Ultramix PC version.
There was a big rumor that it was going to be out for the PC.
That got shot down.
The reason why I pretty much figured it wouldn't happen, there's already DDR PC.
But it sucks.
It really sucks.
It does, true, but you know what Pump It Up for PC worked?
Why?
Because Pump It Up was made for a PC anyway.
That's very true.
It runs off the PC software anyways.
All the big Pump It Up machine, that giant machine is, it's just there's little PC in
there that runs everything.
Yep.
But, I don't know, I think, but you know, what's weird about DDRPC, look at StepMania.
StepMania does it way better than DDRPC did.
So it's kind of like you can't use the excuse that it's not possible to do on a computer
because StepMania, hey, if they'd released something like that as DDRPC, I bet a lot
of people would have been, you know, would have been, wow, this is great.
Yeah.
But they only have StepMania and then we'll go, oh, I'll just download all these songs
or make my own that I think are better.
Yeah, maybe, do you think that maybe that's why they've given up on DDRPC because of StepMania?
I would probably think so.
You know, how can you compete with something that's free?
Why do you think Konami hasn't sued the people who made StepMania?
Anybody want to venture a guess?
I would think, well, first of all, the programming itself, if they did not reverse engineer it,
if they actually made it right from scratch with their own source, they can't sue them
for using...
That's the whole problem with BLEAM, why they couldn't do BLEAM.
Because they made their program for BLEAM from scratch.
they sue for the whole look and feel thing though? I'm thinking back to, you remember
when Street Fighter II was out and then I think some other third party company, I want
to say Data East, put out a game called like Fighting Streets or something like that. Was
it Fighter's History? Okay. They used the Street Fighter engine. And they got sued and
all this stuff? I think it's because they used the Street Fighter engine. Did they?
But I would think, you know, that whole look and feel thing will come to play. I mean obviously
none of us want to see this step many people get sued, but you know it's just, it's a question
that has to be asked. Why hasn't it happened yet? Especially if Konami wants to be competitive
in the PC market. Angel. Yes, Angel. Puppy just pointed out in the chatroom that Step
Mania is open source code, so I mean he's got a point there. Okay, that's a good point.
Which is what Jamie just pointed out, so you know. It's open source, so even if they did
get sued, it's kind of like, it doesn't matter at this point because the cat's already out
of the bag.
Interesting thought.
How do you guys think the online play is going to work?
Is there anything you guys would like to see online for DDR?
Because I think that whole being able to play with somebody at the same time, it's kind
of stupid because you can't see them.
What would you see?
the second side of your screen getting perfect good boo
i think you'll see fifty wasted dollars coming out of your check everyone
spending on xbox live the biggest piece of bullshit ever
thank you for that happy comment mister brad
uh...
okay so we've got DDR xbox out of the way
How about Karaoke Revolution? What do you guys think of this?
This is kind of the...
I hate karaoke, so...
You hate karaoke? Yeah, because I don't sing, remember? I cry.
I like watching other people so I can make fun of them, but I don't like doing it.
This is interesting, though, because it's the first...
it's kind of the first U.S.-only Bomani game.
Kind of? Yeah, they haven't made any... well, I mean, they have games like it in Japan, but not Konami,
and not in the Bomani series.
I'm sorry? I thought they had a karaoke revolution machine or something.
The closest thing they have to a karaoke revolution machine, I remember seeing
this, it was a DDR slash karaoke machine.
Yeah, it was like both.
But who could follow that? You know what I saw at Network the other day?
What? Aerobics Revolution.
Oh yeah, that finally came out, huh? I was tempted to pick it up, but it was like
seventy five dollars and more expensive.
And if I was going to pay seventy five dollars in the game, I would have picked up Final Fantasy X-2.
You know, it's like aerobics revolution wouldn't even be worth it. I saw a bunch of screenshots of it and it looks
Really kind of odd loses. So this is the whole point. I mean really seriously
It is like they just like they said you're doing some 80s James Fonda kind of kind of thing to it
It's got like some chicks on it. You know, you're trying to follow their moves as you're stepping on the pad
Well, you know basically yeah, you're doing aerobics stuff and you just so happen to be standing on a pad too while you're doing it
What was that song that we figured out was confirmed for Karaoke Revolution?
We figured out there's some Jennifer Love Hewitt song we figured out by the screen captures
that's going to be in it for sure.
We found out the other day and we forgot already.
But Jennifer Love Hewitt was there at E3 singing.
We are going to go ahead and take a quick break and when we come back we will talk about
more of E3 and we will do the fuck you's of the week so you can send those to me over
private messages in the chat room.
My name is Sky and you can send those to me and if you are not in our chat room you should
be.
Go to www.calibomani.com, click on Orange Lounge, and click on Chat.
So we'll talk a little more about E3 and all that garbage when we get back.
Enjoy!
I feel it, I feel it, I feel it You are the only one, let's leave it all this way
I feel it, I feel it, I feel it You are the only one that makes me feel this way
Follow the sun, follow the sun And even the rain behind
Together we'll be in harmony Taking the time, we will find our way
Sometimes I feel your energy, I need some time But I'm on my way now
Sometimes don't you hide away I want some time
You should never stay
I feel the energy I need sometimes
But it's not on me now Sometimes
Don't you hide away I want sometimes
Each and every day Sometimes
I feel the energy I need sometimes
But it's not on me now Sometimes
I'm going to hide away, I want some time, I'm feeling every day
And that's the end of the video, thanks for watching, and I'll see you in the next one.
Welcome back, everybody.
We decided to play some Happy Ray-var songs in that last break, so we hope you enjoyed.
We also figured out what song it is that's going to be in Karaoke Revolutions, called
Hey Everybody.
It's from Jennifer Love Hewitt Gay.
And I'm sure it sucks, but how did you find that song?
Based off of the lyrics that are showing the screen caps on the Konami website, actually.
They have a few pictures up that are from the E3 showings, so I've got it off of that.
And then you did a lyric search and there you go. Amazing.
But, um, it was during the break, somebody, I think it was, I don't know if it was Garrett or somebody commented that the chick in Karaoke Revolution in the screenshots looks like an American Idol reject.
She actually, you know what she looks like? Has anybody ever played the Spice World video game for PlayStation?
Oh God, that game sucks.
When they have the giant head and the little anorexic body, that's what that chick looked
like to me.
I'm hoping everybody was moaning and groaning because they haven't played it and they're
sad that you're the only one who has.
Don't cry for me.
I don't want to know that all these people have played the Spice World game.
I know your girlfriend has.
I had a free rental and I wanted to see how bad it was.
Get this.
The first time I met my ex-girlfriend, the very first day I meet her, she's like, hm?
She said, you know, you have to see this game, and so I'm like, oh no, Spice World, what is this?
And then she showed me what was so funny about it, and yeah, it was pretty funny, but you guys must have been really drunk
when you first saw that game, right? Or when you thought about buying that game, Rob. You had to be drunk.
Oh, that's right, Rob owns that game, right?
I do own that game. It's in a deep... I think it's in my closet. I'm going to have to go take it out at some point.
uh... so you know what else is an lc greater rather get what about other cool
games is non balmani necessarily that you're looking forward to
i know brad had one
brad tell me about some games you're looking forward to the agree not
necessarily the money
uh...
can only suffer just anything
and anything okay uh... half-life to
uh...
no you're sold three
The weird voice acting?
What's the weird voice acting?
Yes, but it's not as bad as DIE, MONSTER. You don't belong in this world.
They need to do another Dracula X game with Richter.
A new Gradius game, definitely. Mario Kart Double Dash.
There's a new Sam & Max game.
Really?
New Sam & Max game, New Full Throttle game from LucasArts.
Who cares about that game?
Uh, let's see what else. There's, um... I don't know. There's cool games.
Mario Party 5, bitches.
Mario Adv- Mario Advance 4, Super Mario Bros. 3.
Or the new, um, Pokemon Stadium on GameCube.
Huh? Huh?
Metroid Pro Mission.
Oh, yeah, the new Metroid!
Really?
really
neopets
or that's right in coming out on the issue
of god
the world is ending
the end of a million copies of that army game
that's not really an army put out
the u s army another game
they put out a game on pc a while back uh...
to
Doom 3 is gonna be horrible
says somebody. Doom 3 is gonna be horrible
Why is Doom 3 gonna be horrible?
I don't know. Because the person doesn't like first-person shooters? I don't know.
That's fine. If you don't like first-person shooters, I don't expect you to like it, but as far as first-person shooters
concerned, it's gonna be freakin' great.
I played the Alpha League. It is incredible.
It runs like shit on my computer, but it's great. This is the justification.
No multiplayer, and it's going to be completely linear.
Well, Brad, then play Unreal Tournament or Quake 3.
That's what those are for.
They make Doom for online play. They never did in the first place.
The reason why Doom 3 is going to be shitty is because they've spent too goddamn long on it.
I am 20.
I remember my friend showing me previews of this when they had, you know, like at conventions with movies of it,
When I was a sophomore in high school, it's kind of gotten outdated because when they had their brilliant engine back then and it looked gorgeous, now it looks like shit.
It still does look gorgeous. I mean, that happens with a lot of games. Look at Dragon Quest VII. That has been in the making for five, six years.
I actually had an issue of New Type where they had a review of Dragon Quest VII that
was two years old.
I want them to do like another Secret of Mana using sprites.
Oh, then again, we have Ragnarok, so what else do we need?
Yeah, Sword of Mana, which, like, they call it over here, it's the redo of the Seiken Densetsu game, the first one that was called Final Fantasy Adventure on Game Boy, which is a great game, you know, but this one looks, they updated it to make it look more like Seiken Densetsu 3, so, mmm, looks awesome.
That's what I need to say, Condensa23. I'm a GBA. That'd make me happy.
All they need to do is slap the ROM on there, there you go.
Yeah, well, they do have the Flash Advance cards, if you want to spend like $250 just for the little ROM cartridge,
and then you can load ROMs with a front-loader programmer, not front-loader, a front-end program that'll emulate the ROMs for you.
I heard some other hardware things I heard about from E3, they're going to have something
they're releasing for the GBA where you can watch full motion video for like 30 minutes
on a cartridge.
Yeah, they have that already in Japan, you can get it from lick-sang.com.
But I always get it whenever I hear that website, lick-sang, sounds like something in an Asian
porno.
Lick my sang.
No, but yeah, you can get it from there, and I guess that means they're releasing it here
if it was at E3.
That's pretty interesting.
You know one thing I saw at Network yesterday was the Game Boy Advance player for the GameCube.
I want me one of those.
It's pretty cool. It sits on the bottom of it though. It's kind of weird.
I think there's some comments wanting to be made in the corner that haven't been made yet.
Jamie and I are whirring it.
That's okay.
I think it's trapped in the corner.
Well, Brad, while we were still on that topic, and not trampling it flat, if you like your single-player, first-person, linear shooters, you can go to hell. You know what? I like them. I'll join you.
I don't think I get it. I can go to hell and you'll join me? What was your point? You like linear or you don't?
Ah, he's making it Doom.
I remember being in college, right after graduation, going to my friend Marcy's house and playing Doom, and we'd all be like,
hurt me plenty! Thinking we were all badass. We just thought we were awesome because we could play on Nightmare.
You know, I hate to bring this up again, but why is it that I did not know, I swear I did not know, any girls that played video games until after I was out of college, long after I was out of college.
I played video games all throughout when I was in high school.
How come I didn't have friends like you?
Because you suck.
I think I was just too preppy or something, and all my friends were in a band and cheerleading and stuff.
I worked in an arcade. I was the only girl who played Tekken 3. It was Namco Arcade, so we had Tekken 3 before everybody else.
And weren't you known as the girl who played Tekken 3 who kicked all our asses?
I was known as the girl who played Tekken 3 who kicked all their asses.
I went online on DDR Freak one day.
I was randomly IMing, PMing somebody because this was right before I was going to Alabama,
trying to see who all the people were to play so I could meet up with some of them.
Because all they had in my belt at the time was a dance maniacs machine, which is the Korean crappy one.
I go, I forgot who else I could tell.
I was like, yeah, I used to work at the Namco arcade.
Weren't you that girl who used to beat everybody at Tekken 3?
And this is five years later, no, four years later.
The legacy.
But the legend still burns.
Oh please.
I went back to that cyber station though and like proceeded to, it's funny seeing all these
people just sort of slapping at the dance maniacs machine and then I'm playing like,
you know, Miggle style.
It was funny.
And then so, we got a bunch of girl gamers in the room, that's cool.
How long have you been playing video games, Marron?
I've been playing video games since I was 10.
That's so cool. What was the first video game you remember playing?
Super Mario Brothers 2.
And then Legend of Zelda.
Very cool.
I know what my first one was.
What?
My first game was Pitfall.
on these hard choices hundred uh... i think about my neighbors across the
street were girls and they love that game they made a plan and um... kangaroo
kangaroo is shitty
uh... by me i don't think that
i played kangaroo in an arcadia godfather's pizza
so hot
i'm older
i remember playing a brand new donkey kong machine
i remember playing a cocktail machine and now and you i would expect to be
playing kongo bongo
never played it
because it's the Sega thing, but whatever. I figure maybe start a young age.
I played Space Fury and Gorf on my Colecovision.
I was going to ask Angel, since she's a girl gamer, too.
Yeah.
First one you remember playing.
Oh, God. It was either... Shit. What was it called?
The damn computer won.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The computer... No, it was Commodore. Fuck.
It was like between Commodore and Atari 2600
I've been playing since I was 3, so yeah, I've been geeky since I was 3.
Now this topic doesn't have to stay just for the girls, what about guys?
Now I'm in this reminiscing mode, what was the first video game you remember playing?
Another girl! I was born with a controller in my hand! I've been playing games forever!
I was either like 4 or 5 and it was either Super Mario Brothers or Metroid, I can't remember, it was like at my neighbor's house.
Then I got my Nintendo when I was in kindergarten, and I was a freak from then on.
I had a Nintendo jacket in the fourth grade.
I owned you.
Dork!
That's why the girls didn't talk to you.
It's not because...
But, did you ever get a hold of Super Mario Bros. cereal?
Yes, Super Mario Bros. cereal was the shit.
What is going on?
Why is it really me?
What is she saying here?
It's...
Put Jamie on a mic.
Put Jamie on the mic and explain what they're eating.
No.
Or he goes, ouch.
And then he flies away.
And see, it had that giant trackball thing.
So one could say I was attracted to balls at a young age.
Wha, wha, wha?
Oh, god, we just lost half our listeners.
What do you know?
And gained some new ones.
Ew, it looks like...
I'm not going to eat it. It's gross looking.
Give me some squid.
It smells like punani.
I'm gonna eat it live on the air.
Alright.
Uh, I think now's a good time to get into the-
Wait, does anybody want to reminisce first games?
Because we didn't get to everybody.
Dark Tetsuya?
It does smell like Tetsuya.
Well, you know, you just...
Actually, this kind of...
It kind of reminds me of beef jerky.
Got it.
My favorite is beef jerky.
As for games, oh god, I don't know.
Fast food.
2600.
Oh!
Was that the one where you're the little chef, and like, if you lost, then all the food
the food would get thrown at you for size? No, no, no. Your little purple mouth thingy.
Tappin'.
Oh. Ooh! Rob, did you see what he did?
You got me, you just got me and Brian confused, didn't you?
No, no, I said Rob, did you see what he did? Oh, what'd he do?
You better watch out or else there's some pussy at you.
Alright, let's finish up the others in the room.
Eat the squid!
Fine, I'll eat the squid, but you gotta give the mic to Angel and the others so they can
finish it.
You have to eat the squid before I do that.
Alright, it looks nasty.
You know what it looks like?
It looks like Big League 2.
This is horrible radio.
AHHH!
This is horrible radio!
Give the mic to somebody in the back.
Yup, leave.
Magus, first game.
Words could not express...
Words could not express what Rob is going through right now.
This is bad radio, tell me your first game.
Oh, it tastes like burning!
Burnination, yes.
I'm probably the youngest here, but I still remember playing kangaroo when I was three, and then moving on to burger time when I was five.
Then it was duck cut, and then it's all downhill from there.
Mokey, did you get to reminisce about your first video game you remember?
Smurfs, I used to love the Smurfs game, because that was easy.
The Smurfs game was weird.
I used to love to make the Smurfs fall, because they're stupid.
What else?
There was this one that, I can't remember.
I have a trackball.
But yeah, pretty much just Frenzy was cool.
Oh!
Ooh!
Jumpman!
I love Jumpman.
So Rob, now that you've had squid, do you feel like...
Okay, I'm going to share this real fast, and we're going to get into the nephews of the week.
I've had, what is it, calamari?
I love calamari, it's good. That, not good.
That's like beef jerky, but it's squid.
How can you, I'm just watching Mira and she's just like,
Um, nope, nope, she's just eating it, mmm, this is good shit.
It's nasty!
Mmm, beefy, but more like squid-y.
More like pussy!
I'm expecting it to, like, explode in my mouth or something. Anyway, I'm glad nobody caught that.
Alright, alright, let's settle down, children, because it's time for Jamie to burninate with the, uh, FUs of the week.
But the soul, the soul still burninates.
My mouth is full of squid.
Alright, you ready, Jamie?
No.
Since it's our season premiere, we should remind the listeners what the FUs of the week are all about.
It's where we take all the shit that pisses us off and say, fuck you.
Okay.
How was that?
The chat room is begging and pleading us to keep it under control this week and not go on for an hour, so.
So let's try and regulate ourselves, boys and girls.
If you hesitate, if you hesitate too much on your FUs, the mic goes on the next person.
Agreed?
All right.
Here we go.
Um, my thank you of the week goes to Rob.
Thank you.
It would make you more proud to know that I was talking on my cell phone when I parked.
Another fikey goes to Julie's car for smelling like dust and rotten milk and for having no working air conditioning. Or a radio that lets us change the station. Or a rear view mirror. So I had a rear view mirror and it was the side mirror. The passenger side mirror.
Thank you goes toward getting lost in San Francisco actually just toward the
whole street system in San Francisco and then toward like you know not being able
to get Final Fantasy 10 to network videos and also toward the city of
Milpitas for being weird for having like one entrance off of 101 and another one
off of 680 and had me turn around and have a nap. And then another one goes toward um
stuff. The end. And another, that's my hiccups. They're burpee hiccups, they hurt. Ew, are
you burping? Alright. That's it then? Uh huh. Okay, moving on to Loki. Oh wait, one more.
Triscuit, we're giving you the phantom taste of cheese, but not really being cheesed.
Pier 39 is a waste of time, it's just like expensive shit, and how many stores do you really need as souvenirs for San Francisco?
I can go to any store there and buy the same shit. It really sucks.
So after that, after you do my freaking cold, because, you know, I hate being sick, and all I smell is snot.
I've smelled snot for about four days now, and that's all I smell. It's like this nasty ammonia smell.
All day long, that's all I smell is goddamn snot. Okay?
After the stupid British chick that was performing up on the, like, uh, on the water stage, whatever that stupid stage was there, she was freaking stupid.
Her and her, like, gypsy child, I mean, freaking doing these acts up there, and people just didn't give a shit, they're just sitting there going, okay, what's the next thing on, what's the next thing on?
And then people were yelling for her to get off the stage and she's just like,
Oh, how do you like?
Oh, kid.
No, clap your whistle.
And it's just, it was annoying.
It was god-awful.
After using the refrigerator for having a stupid plug in the bottom there
and water being there, and I didn't know what the plug was for,
so I didn't want the water in the refrigerator,
so I pulled the plug, not thinking that the plug doesn't go anywhere
except down to the floor.
So now the floor is flooded with water from the stupid refrigerator and that sucks.
Um, F you to B3 for not giving me a freakin' badge.
I mean, God damn it, I fuckin' set up a bunch of shit for you guys.
Like the whole, like, you know, feed for that stupid camera and all that shit.
I got the damn CAT5 cable.
I just spent my own God damn money to buy 50 feet of CAT5 I'm never gonna ever use again.
And, God damn it, you couldn't even give me a fucking badge?
What is wrong with you people?
and seriously and after that oh give me a free t-shirt yeah sure i really saw
that one i had to go buy my goddamn t-shirt
i don't give a shit whatever so that was awful i had to
carry my goddamn stuff two blocks to your goddamn freaking arcade which
sucked because that overpriced shit all your games suck your stupid time
crisis games suck your stupid fucking um got it i can't
remember it's a stupid gun game that the goddamn
thing wasn't calibrated right i'm firing off the screen and saying dead center
That was, uh, yeah, House of the Dead, because I wanted to play that.
Yeah, House of the Dead fucking sucks.
By the way, though, your initial being a machine was the shit.
Yeah, but everything else was shit, okay?
Boy, there was that goddamn huge...
The roller coaster machine was the shit.
And what the hell is that? We're having, like, a stupid shooting rage right next to where we're frickin' performing for frickin' DDR.
So every now and then you hear this,
YEAH!
And people are like, what the hell's that screaming noise?
So that sucked.
And finally, the biggest one of them all, the biggest F.D. of the week, is going to PayPal.
PayPal overcharged my account by $600 fucking dollars.
Okay, beware of PayPal.
I wanted to pay for an auction that was $5.99 plus $4.25 shipping for a grand total of $10.24.
What did I get?
I had it instead charge me $599 and 425 shipping for a grand total of $603.25.
There's nothing that PayPal can do, so I had to end up contacting my guy, which made my account overdraft,
which also caused a bunch of my other auctions to overdraft my account even more, so now I have to pay finance charges of about $180.
I have to sell off my DVD collection to fix that. Thank you PayPal for ruining my whole fucking week.
And the thing is, if you're sick on a weekday, that's cool because you can miss work.
But being sick on a weekend, that just sucks because now you have to work and you have to waste your weekend lying in bed going,
I hate my life and I want to die.
But I do have a good point out of all this.
Coldies, whoever invented coldies, pure fucking genius.
I'm already on the other end of my cold and I was never like super duper ill.
Coldies are the bomb and I recommend everybody take them.
You should have been listening to me from day one, because I've always told you just take zinc and vitamin C and you'll feel better. That's exactly what's in that shit.
Yeah, I know.
But it's called coldies, and it tastes like cherries.
No, they do taste like butt. I'll agree.
It tastes like the shitty rear end of a SARS victim.
Yeah, F you to the taste of coldies. That's awful.
Alright, let's move on to the other folks in the room, starting off with Maren!
I would like to say F you to my car, since the alternator, like, exploded or something and we had to replace it.
F you to McCarran International Airport for making me take off my shoes so they could x-ray them.
And F you to guys who step on your feet and do not apologize and are rude.
And that's about it. Other than that, it was a good week.
Yeah, and the guys who step on your feet and smell bad and can't work the soft serve ice cream machine.
So yeah.
Let's move on. I'm going to move on and get Brad to go here.
Is this my song?
It's a different song every week.
Anyway, I have to go to sailors because, I mean, I love Varian's dad and all, but he wanted to play.
he was in the navy, you know, he's retired. He played, he had to do a drinking game, sailor style, like sailor rules, and you had 60 seconds to drink your shot, and he went in a round of three people. And I probably had somewhere around 11 or 12 shots in the round last night. And I didn't get sobered up until about 2 p.m. today. So, sailor stuff, there we go.
Yes.
Dead air!
Oh, sorry.
Ah.
My...
Okay, okay.
My FUD goes to not having that stupid DWI finish I wanted in the Season 3 premiere.
I was hoping to have it finished by then.
And F not being able to sleeve, because I had nowhere to sleeve, but that was probably
my fault.
So, yeah.
FUD to myself.
Okay.
Angel.
I'd like to say FUD to my boss again, because he almost said he was going to be dead.
I'd like to say F.U. to my boss again because she's almost in Gimmie the weekend off.
Ow.
I gave him that flash.
F.U. to the flash.
Um, yeah, okay.
Yeah, so I almost didn't get to come here, see?
That wasn't good.
So, F.U. to that.
Alright, moving on to Magus.
Yeah, first of all, F.U. to the Sacramento R.T. bus system.
They don't know how to run their bus throughout Arden. We were trying to get from my high school
To Arden for a mall go see like make some love and stuff
Apparently we make it to the light rail station and
well
Bus does a show for an hour and a half
so we took the long walk from Arden Fulton to
The mall
in the burning heat
Second of all, we leave on Thursday right before Memorial Day weekend. We expect no one to be on the road. We're an hour and a half late coming into the Bay Area.
Fuck those stupid drivers!
When again, we were one of the stupid drivers.
Math.
Naturalist.
He was.
A few of the Chinese food places that play Outbreak while you're trying to eat.
That's kind of funny.
I don't know if I give an FU, that's funny.
A Chinese food place that plays Outbreak, the movie Outbreak.
It happened to be Silver Garden, thank you very much.
Here we go.
cuz he forgot them cuz they were fucked up
Okay, let's move on to the chatroom FUs then.
Hey, not bad you guys, I only took 20 minutes to get through ours.
Usually it takes an hour.
Okay, Mandarin would like to say,
fuck the Orange Lounge radio host that don't wish me a happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Today's her birthday.
Well, FU for not being here to get spankings, girl.
Fuck stupid managers at Yardbirds that make my girlfriend work on my birthday.
fuck real radio stations like ninety four nine whoever played this song
whatever song that was
uh... let's see fuck people who say fuck too fucking much
uh...
but my roommates ex-girlfriend because she's a controlling bitch
who won't let my roommate be gay or at least trying as hard as she can
don't be gay
don't be gay sparky don't be gay
moving on
uh... justin b would like to say f you to rob and jamie at the beginning of the
show when Jamie was coughing up her lungs. Because the comment you made and Jamie coughing
made me spit soda slash hot dog out of my mouth. And now we just had a laugh at your
expense. That was the win. Ninst would like to say F56K connections who keep buffering
Orange Lounge Radio. Stupid kids who think they can play DDR when they can't pass beginner
their songs, moving out at the end of the college year, my professor from my coding
class, he didn't show up with a final until an hour after he should have, one more time
my modem and being a 56k connection, people who decide to take slow drives on country
roads on Sundays, you drive too slow and keep other people from where they need to be, people
who don't like Matrix Reloaded, they had to think somewhat because they had to think somewhat,
and to close it off my 56k connection to my ISP should die, oh one more, F you to my brother's
roommate, you are the laziest bastard I've ever seen, and F.U. to Radio Shack. They overcharge
on everything. Why can't there be a decent electronic shop around here?
That was two more. Yeah, that was like two or three more. God,
everybody's got a marathon today. Okay, DJ Tyrant would like to say, F.U.s to the internet
connection I'm on. Fox for not yet releasing 24 season 2 on DVD. They will this summer,
you know it. Women for only wanting to be my friend and nothing more. Aww. The city
the event or a for being an ass to the new arcade electric avenue and it's
taking forever for them to get their license f you to school for just sucking
i don't want to go
uh... and congrats
to j s p for winning james gains for yesterday
if you despise world
and black lab would like to say if you use
fuck horrible sleep cycles fuck boredom and laziness
i spent about ninety percent of this weekend thus far sitting on my computer
but the he writing a bike across town in ninety five degree heat is not fun
but the holiday for keeping the dining halls closed next today so i can't be the
decent meal a day longer than usual
like you get a decent meal in dorms anyway what's up with that
moving on
john fields would like to say
f u sony for making the p s two with such cheap parts
discrete error discrete error i'm so freaking tired of turning my playstation
2 upside down and spinning it all around to get it to read the disc. Also FU to server
ops to take their job way too seriously and let nothing go by and then lying about giving
warnings and thus ban someone without them realizing what they were doing was wrong despite
of how insignificant the problem was. Vandalus would like to say an FU. FU to my Cadillac
for having a leaky radiator.
Arkadian42 would like to say fuck you to the person who scraped my rear car door in the
Scandia parking lot and dented it in slightly.
Now the window of that door won't go down all the way anymore.
Fucking hit and run bitches.
And lastly, Muhimer would like to say fuck me for not being here and submitting late.
Fuck not having the internet for two weeks because of McGaffey Firewall.
Fuck homophobes.
But yay for 50 Cent DDR Extreme, 10 minutes away finally, oh, and thank God for acupuncture
curing my allergies.
Allergies.
Hooray, that's everybody's F.U. of the Week.
So, any last bits of bitterness?
Loki, you have something new that's going to be coming to the show that I see you just
got?
Do you want to share with our listeners what you just want?
Yeah, I actually found this when I was looking for Dance Sense Revolution stuff.
You know, normally I look for the arcade discs and stuff, and this just happened to be pulled up in an eBay auction.
So, I won a hentai cosplay, actually it's a cosplay porn featuring DDR characters.
So yes, we have DDR porn.
Will we get to play that on the show?
Of course.
Yay!
Oh, yay.
Don't sound too excited, Jamie.
No, I'm actually kind of curious.
Is it going to be like Final Fuck X?
I hope.
I hope it's not all blurred out and shit.
Will there be pantsless rage?
It'll be just like Final Fuck X.
Where did my afghan go?
That's why I'm curious.
It's like disappeared.
Oh, there it is.
It ran away from all the people!
By the way, I like these chairs because I can sit really sideways in them.
OK, we're gonna take a quick break, and we're gonna come back and do the cage match in a
little bit.
But first we're gonna hear some Kylie from the Euromega mix, and then we'll hear something
from Poppin' Music.
And last message, because Jamie wants to hear it, so we'll be right back boys and girls, you're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
Thought that I was going crazy
Just after one of those days, yeah
Didn't know what to do
Then there was you again
And everything went so wrong tonight
And the stars, they must get out this time
The music they were playing really blew my mind
Cause baby, when I heard you were in love first I knew you were meant to be in love
If you miss that beat
The king and the chef go marching
It's time to say goodbye to my fate
I want you to know
I'm ready to be happy
It's my time
I need to face that
Bad things for you
You don't have to let me get to see
I don't need you
Bad things for you
I can take you somewhere
I don't need you anymore
I'm running out of time, wait, where are you?
I don't know what I'm feeling
But I can feel it inside
I don't know what to say
I'm not living in reality
I'm a loser
Most of all, I've made up my mind
For this part of my life
To say that
That's it for you
You don't have to love me
Can't you see you're going to love me
That's it for you
I can't let you go
I don't want you anymore
That's it for you
You, you don't have to love me, can't you see I'm going to love you
I said, for you, I can make you go where I go
Anymore
Orange Lounge Radio, we put your thing down, flip it and reverse it.
your pick is pretty, well we'll see, you'll see what the songs are going to be in a little
bit.
But they're all pretty good.
I know which songs I've heard all these songs, they're all pretty good.
They're all the kind of music that our chat room seems to like, so those of you that yell
at us for peaking crap have nothing to complain about this week.
They said it picks show tunes.
Masquerade, Paper Faces, I'm very...
Anyway, I thought I'd open the floor up for story time, because I know a lot of people
had stories they wanted to tell tonight.
So Jamie, you want to kick it off, why don't you tell us about how you've been burninating
this weekend with Maren.
Oh God, where's Maren?
It starts off with me at work at 5.30 in the morning.
I work all day.
Do you want storytime music?
Sure.
Isao-kun.
Oh, yeah, I have to play the music that came to us from the Hamster Alliance because Loki
liked it.
I don't remember which one it is.
I think it's this one.
Okay.
Rob, do you have any cookies?
Do I have what?
I get off work and I go right over to Jessica's house and there's somebody waiting for me
there sitting on the couch which is still set up theater style seating for watching
movies on the wall so we went and what do we do we went out to the south sack
for boba then we went to roseville for sushi then we went back to my house and
decided to watch battle royale I got no I got my battle royale manga first
because we went to em a1 comics and then we watched battle royale and your
I think it would have been better if Dan wasn't doing, you know, director's commentary
during the last half of it, but it was pretty interesting.
Moving on.
Um, paper plate, okay?
This joke ends right now, okay?
The plate has been retired. I have a new weapon. It's called the smell of pussy. Or squid.
Janae, put your pants on.
We ended up crashing out.
I woke up at the ass crack of dawn, like 8.30 in the morning, and you were still asleep.
I went back to bed.
Got up around 9.30, we bummed around, and then tried to get out of the door, but I kept
forgetting stuff.
We finally get in Julie's car that smells like granny panties, the smell of dust and
rotten milk.
We had a really nice drive going into San Francisco and then I got lost because I forgot
to turn on Van Ness.
Through some direction and just some random turning, we make it to Gary and get there.
Go shopping, have good food, um, I almost bought Sara's mask, but decided against it.
And then we, um, we managed to get to a, to a network video with no problem, except for the guy behind me who wanted to kill me.
This guy had this big vehicle, I swear he was like the worst driver in the world.
But anyway, so the next thing, we get on the 101 South again to go to network.
And it turns out he gave us directions to Sunnyvale
because we were trying to get to Milpitas instead.
So I got directions from Shark's Girl, from my wifey-poo.
And we managed to get to Milpitas, Scotland, race to lead horses.
And then we came back and said, hey, we want some boba.
So we went to Davis, got...
What the fuck is this music?
It's story-type music!
Okay, this music needs to go away.
It's okay, but it doesn't fit my story.
Do you want the violins again?
This is some burninating music.
Okay.
And then we got back to my place.
And we were gonna have pizza, but we sort of just didn't make it.
We watched, um, we played some Soulcalibur 2.
And I got my ass handed to me repeatedly every time, um, Maran picked, um, Taki.
Of course, it turned out that I was, like, super cheap with-
Who was I super cheap with?
Uh, well, I was- I'm always cheap-
No, it was Seungmino when I pulled out Seungmino instead of Kilik.
I was really cheap.
And with, um, Eunseung.
I was, I sucked with Link. Then we watched from Shaman King, but she fell asleep.
So I was like, WAKE UP! Go upstairs, cause Dan wants the Goucher!
So, so she goes to sleep and I'm playing Ragnarok until 1.30 in the morning, and then the end.
And then there's today, where we just like, sat around the house like, most of the morning.
And then, um, what else happened?
We went to the mall, went to Fresh Choice, where the stupid man was who smelled funny and stuck on my foot, and then we went to see Rob- not Rob, we went to see Dan at work.
So I'm here just mumbling in the background. Mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble, mumble.
the orgy plans with more
and then uh...
and then
went back to my house
after
going to
the half of half of filtrid
and then the liberal right now
and then we can be
and tomorrow we're going to get
printed mongrel
as she made a horse and tried work
tells about trying to work
Chogdor is a man, Chogdor is a horse man, well really he's just a horse, but still he's
Chogdor.
That just got a jazz!
Anybody else have something they want to share for us on Storytime?
I know that they did over there.
First of all, I have pie.
You don't have cake pie, you have apple pie.
But I still have pie.
Whatever.
Music.
Get some Chinese music or something.
I didn't mean that in a bad way, but yeah.
Just tell your damn story.
It's the super garden thing.
I know.
And I think I pretty much said it.
Oh, because of the outbreak thing they were playing?
Well then why did you raise your hand?
I don't know.
Never mind.
I did a very, very obsessive thing last night.
What's that?
Friday night.
I watched Battle Royale and read the manga while watching the movie.
You're sick.
That's cool, Jamie.
Yay.
Does anybody have any interesting Bimani stories or Bimani accomplishments they want to name
for the week?
I passed another 2DX on.
Whoo!
Yay!
Which one?
Foundation something.
I thought you were going to say shades, dammit!
My only accomplishment this week is the fact that
there's the remix contest going on over on BomaniStyle
and uh...
I can't play DWR
can't play Semenya and talk at the same time
Anyways, there's a competition going on over at BomaniStyle.com. It's a remix contest, and both entries up, the Dark Black Forest, the Midnight Angel mix, and Legend of Trance are over there.
So, everybody is listening. What you need to go do is you need to go over to BomaniStyle.com. Go to their forums. If you're not a member, sign up. It'll only take a second.
You go down to the very bottom, and you'll see Bomani Cell Remixing Contest Volume 1.
What you want to do once you're there, is you want to find my entry.
There'll be a thread that says, Legend of Trance by Loki.
You go there, and you rate it a 10.
Go do that right now.
I'll give you a second.
Okay. Now that you've done that, I'll win.
Okay. No, but really, um, go there and listen to all the remixes.
remixes. There's a lot of them that really suck, but then there's some that are really
good. So, you'll know pretty much by looking at it which ones are pretty good. You've got,
there's one DJ Demon, I believe, did Max Resurrection. We played that a while back. It's, it's pretty
good, you know, but I still want to win. And, so go vote ten for mine, because there's just
not enough people voting on mine, and I need people to go vote ten, just because.
And don't just vote a ten. Vote everyone else a one. No, I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
But, um, post in the thread and talk about how, like, beautiful Loki's remixes are and how his remixes make you want to fuck him.
Just kidding, Nelly.
She's just like, alright.
Yeah, you can want.
It's nice to want.
But, um, yeah. There's some pretty good ones.
The one I like though there's a really good paranoia remix in there that's a hip-hop remix of paranoia
And we'll maybe get to play that later on in the show that's pretty good. There's a ghost one
That's kind of a piano ambience one. It's pretty good. There's a sodeep one that's a piano ambience one. That's pretty good
there's a long version like a trancy remix well a
Longer trance remix of uh sodeep thats. It's alright
I have a few remixes that I'd name that deserve ones, but I'm not going to name them on the
air.
Anyway, let's get on with the cage match, shall we?
I think our chat room has been kind of a little eager for this and and I am too. I'm moist with anticipation about this, so
Last week for two weeks ago. I should say in the orange lounge radio cage match. I got you. I got you
No you already you already had your one
Loki won with something that's kind of popular
He won with a pop culture buzz thing because it's the big thing right now, and he wrote. What are you laughing about?
Something in the chat room DJ Tyron fucks Loki
Anyway as I was saying
Last week in the cage match
Loki's pick one with this oh by the way the way the cage match works all the hosts the three of us myself Loki dark
Sakura we all pick one song and they all fight each other per your votes
So you vote for the song you like best, and you send those votes over to Sky in the chat room, but you can't vote until all three songs have played.
And then the song with the most votes goes into rotation on Orange Lounge Radio until the next cage match.
So, here was last week's winner and the first song you can vote for tonight is Don Davis and Juno Reactor with Mona Lisa Overdrive from the movie The Matrix Reloaded. Enjoy!
The first song you can vote for this week is Mona Lisa Overdrive, here in the Cajun
Match.
It's a very good scene in that movie, by the way, that was from the freeway chase scene.
Second song is going to be Dark Sakura's pick, so why don't you tell us all about it?
I don't even know if it's named right, it says it's from Final Fantasy X, but I don't
think so.
Some cool song, I don't even remember the name of it.
And you only heard a clip of the last song because it won last time, so you only get to hear a clip.
You get to hear the full one of this. So this is pick number two for this week. Set me free. Enjoy.
Oh
That was Set Me Free, which may or may not be Final Fantasy and may or may not be Paul Oakenfold, so go figure.
Anybody want to comment on that and give it something on a scale of 1 to 10?
Jamie?
10.
Loki, do you have anything you want to say about it?
It definitely wasn't Oakenfold. It could have been a lot better than that.
It was all right. I couldn't place it anywhere in Final Fantasy at all.
It was just kind of average to me. I've heard a lot of trance, second tracks. It was just average. So I'd give it a 7.
Yeah, I mean it's very trance in the fact that I see it as kind of like background music, but it's nothing I'd kind of be all,
Ooh, I gotta listen to this song, oh my god, I love this song. But like, you know, if it was planned, I'd be all,
Okay, yeah, I just kind of, you know, bob my head like the Roxbury guys. So, you know, I'd give it a 7.5. Cool.
Anybody else want to comment on Set Me Free?
I like it. It would probably make good background music to start from the net or something.
Seven and a half.
Anybody over here in this corner want to comment on Set Me Free?
Anybody? Anybody? Anybody?
It was okay, but...
Is it?
Yeah.
Um...
Do you want me to rate it?
Yeah.
Um...
No?
Okay, I won't.
You have to rate it.
Ugh!
I've been denied or something.
Okay, um...
Seven.
Alright.
Alright, so, any, oh, Magus?
Very transient, really good, like, working music if you're, like, working on some, like,
platform or anything like that. I'd probably give it an 8.
It's good burninating music.
Yeah, oh, hacking or burninating, yeah, there we go.
That's good music for decorating cakes, too.
Yeah, I like that.
Some, some cake decorating music, I like that.
I like driving to it.
Okay, any of, any other comments on Set Me Free?
Anybody, anybody. You could be influencing the votes.
Oh, oh, we have a hand.
Good music to refurbish cabinets, too.
Okay.
Alright, moving on.
The third and final song in tonight's cage match is my pick.
And I decided to go the slutty route, and I picked a former porno star.
I picked Tracy Lords.
Did I call it or did I?
And this this song is kind of a couple years old and a lot of people know the songs from the Mortal Kombat soundtrack
It's called control, but this is the version that has the vocals in it
So you could be really slutty so everybody get naked because this is the song to have some sex to
This is my pick for this week's cage match. It's Tracy Lawrence with control.
You're such a lonely, you're such a blue You're like your lover, let me control you
Can't surrender, you'll feel no pain
Cause I'm the master at this game
Let me kill you, and make you better
At this life, you will forget her
Let me get it and make it better
I'll be right here if you will forget
Oh no no no
Let me control it
Control it
Oh no no no
Let me control it
Come with me to the other side
Come with me, I need to die
Go with me to the other side
Go with me in the tide
Let me kiss it, I think you can make it better
I think tonight, you're up again
Up for Kenner
Kiss?
Lucky tooth
And lucky sada
debut
Out of the lights
You're up for Kenner
Up for Kenner
Kiss me lucky tooth
And lucky sada
debut
Out of the lights
You're up for Kenner
Up for Kenner
Kiss me lucky tooth
And lucky sada
debut
Out of the lights
You're up for Kenner
Let me control it, control, let me control it
Tracy Lourdes with Control.
It's cool, but I've had that version for a long time myself, so for me it's kind of old.
It still doesn't mean it's less of a good song, I'd give it a 7.5.
I love that song because it brings you back to Q's are days, where we used to play with the Mortal Kombat soundtrack all the time, and that movie, while being a really sucky movie overall, it was good at its time. I like that song even more.
Dark Tetsuya
I would agree with Nico Adachi in the chatroom who says it sounds like techno stripper music. Amen. Total stripper music. Yes, another comment?
That would be my cage dance music. Seriously, I love that. I'd give it a 10.
So how appropriate for the cage match.
That was really bad.
Yeah, I know. That joke gets a 2.
Anyway, anybody else? Any other comments on Tracy Boyer's control?
Yeah, mine is too.
What? Wait, what?
I like her pornography better than our music.
I had a really funny one though. It was like, I think, her first album that she did.
Just about like this girl who would like to introduce these guys and then like kick your ass.
I have to find that CD again.
Next time for your cage match, hit comment Alexa. Please, find some like comment Alexa and leave a comment.
Song number two is Set Me Free and song number three is Tracy Lords with
control
alright so those are the songs you can vote for send those
now
okay
so that's a cage match
everybody wake up cage match is over
cage match is usually a part of a show where people in the studio fall asleep
i kinda have to pee but i don't want to pee because we just played a bunch of music
so i don't want to go to break
low-key what do you
you're disgusting
low-key what's tells about some of the new vinyl you got this week
i think i got a lot of princes nineteen ninety nine
and they got
they had this other thing over here
buried they're almost
i got desert letting your mind go
and
i got
babies got a temper
by uh...
Prodigy
Ooh, it has an instrumental and acapella mix, you know what that means?
I can make a remix!
There were those other three from earlier in the week.
And I also got, um, what was it, I got, um, Heaven, you know, DJ Sammy, of course, Walk
Like an Egyptian, and, um, what else did I get, um, the Human League with, uh,
It's Don't You Want Me on the other side.
Yeah, it's Don't You Want Me and Love Action.
And also, we've got Kachigugu, Too Shy.
And I've got more stuff coming in.
Thank you, eBay.
I've got more stuff coming in.
I've got the whole Eddie Murphy album, including his song...
I forget what his song's called, but anyways, it's really funny.
And then I've got Frankie Goes Hollywood, Relax, and Two Tribes.
I've also got, well let's see here, pull up my list, let's see, I've got The Reflex, I've
I've got, oh shit, I'm trying to remember, just give me one second, stupid people, fucking,
god damn it, okay, here we go, I've got BT Dreamin', it's a pretty good song, we've got
the Culture Club, Color by Numbers, their album, Starship Knee Deep in Hoopla, you know
that song we built this city you've got the whole album for that and the
Ghostbusters soundtrack so yeah so when are you gonna start that mix show you've
promised for about the last three months well you know I should start actually
using my records first I need to set the other turntable second I need to learn
how to beat mix kind of an important part of the mix show no I seriously need
practice. I haven't practiced at all, period. You know, drama and stuff has prevented me
from doing so, so yeah.
Okay, um, any other, anybody else going to start a show on Orange Lounge?
Maybe I should start doing a Friday show.
You what?
I know, I've, uh, I think I'm going to start, I've, I've, I've tossed the idea around.
It's really inconvenient for me to do one during the week, but Fridays I could do a
show.
Don't also tie yourself down, because what you can do is you can pre-tape like four in a row and then play them later.
Why would I do that?
If you want.
That sort of defeats the purpose of me doing a live show.
Well, I mean, it's up to you. If you want to do a live show, do it. But, you know, just saying.
I'm thinking about doing a tape show about remixes and originals. Maybe. I'm kind of toying with that idea.
Well, mine's all random crap anyway.
Yours is going to be all random? That's cool.
I think maybe this Friday I might do another... If I can get the samples, I need to do another video game trivia.
you should call it to burn innate ha ha ha no I think the burn innate joke we
don't want we don't want to run around dating the burn innate jokes yes start
it so yeah you don't have to raise your hand you're not in school well he has to
get a mic though we need to get a third mic yeah we need to get espo back into
the chat room so I can get my title back from him good point get it while he's
not there yeah that's right you got to get it back when he's not there kick him
I'll tell you guys off-air what that cap is, but the rest of the people don't even know
So, we hope you're listening to Orange Launch Radio all day long because, you know, we play
good music.
Dammit.
Huh?
Okay, so, we're going to go to break now so I can pee and tally the votes for CAGEMATCH.
Maggish, your vote doesn't count because you're here.
Sorry.
I just see your name in red and I already know.
Jamie, any requests for this break?
Let's go with Little Red Corvette.
You want to hear little reg?
What does little reg corvette have to do with the money?
I don't care.
It's plants.
You're...
Okay.
No, I'm not reading that.
Why don't we go with some keyboard mania stuff?
Okay, some keyboard mania.
Let's go with least 100 seconds.
Okay, I can do that.
Let's go with clunk clunk.
Hold on, hold on.
Bing him, getting him, getting him.
We're going to hear clunk clunk.
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Move on now
Let your body be with me
Come on, wake up
Let it all get a change in me
I mean the back of your mind I smile
But I am not so blind
Just reach out, get off and out
You'll be the star tonight
Get with it
Finalize, you've got to tell me
You know it's too late when you're dead now, man
Pass it on and set me strong, man
You're the fucking sun to keep me warm
Hey, hey, hey
I just feel it
You got me feeling it, yeah, yeah
Wooooo
I'm just a part of love for you
I need to know, I need to know, I need to know how you feel
I need to know, I need to know, I need to know How it feels?
I got to know, I got to know, I got to know If it's real
I used to buy my love for you I'm giving all my heart to you, my love
I used to buy my love for you I'm giving you my heart, my soul, my love
I purify my love for you
I'm giving all my heart to you
My love
I purify my love for you
I'm giving you my heart, my soul, my love
I'm giving all my heart to you
My love
I purify my love for you
Easier to dance to than that freaking catch-up song, Orange Lounge Radio.
Alright, we're back.
You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, and we have the winner of this week's cage match,
boys and girls
and this is a very very close vote you guys
the winning song only had one vote more
than the other two songs
so like the other two songs were tied in the winning one only had one more
vote than them
so here it is your winning song
once again is Mona Lisa Overdrive
oh wait I'm sorry what did you say?
I say, of course, it's riding off the frickin' boom 6S and Jive or whatever, no, Pipe of
the Matrix, so...
What do you expect?
I mean...
What are you talkin', Jive?
Alright, Jive, I don't know, I guess it's because of Genaise.
Genaise?
Yes?
I hear hissing.
Anyway, uh, so there you go.
Um, so, what now?
i have nothing left to talk about what's just in the show
okay back
does anybody is in the happening to us are one of the
working shows a long time
we were
even in the approach of the world any part game shows taking shows there's
actually and i i'm really afraid to be asking visitors to make people here
so we just take you know if you have a target is for the this will do will do
will do match game
will be best humans for the celebrities for the celebrities
you you pick one
I have to give Jamie the computer, this is bad.
Here.
This is fucked up.
While you're waiting for him to do this stuff, go to ragnarokonline.com and download that game.
You don't want to do it now because they'll interrupt their stream for Orange Lost Radio.
We already just heard like a ton of music.
Doesn't everybody have like a T1 connection? Come on.
We'll get to your music later, don't worry.
shit well I took a big jump earlier no I'm kidding are you leaving oh yeah I
gotta go sorry guys that's you to having to leave early all right soul peace and
cheers to the third season thank you a drink drinks on the house as battle
Royale would say, one down, 13 to go.
I don't want any more freaking drinks.
All right.
So Maren, tell us about this book, this little manga
you're reading, the first volume of the English edition
of Battle Royale.
And Jamie handed it to me, so I am looking at it.
And hi, Smosh, because I know your name.
And the art is kind of interesting.
and there's a squirrel-faced guy in here that I really want to die, and hopefully he will
die soon.
That's about it.
Don't you think the battle royale thing is getting old?
Well, I had never seen battle royale until yesterday, so...
Oh, okay.
So it's still new for you.
I'm just teasing.
I'm just giving Jabin a hard time.
Oh, okay.
I get a long mic.
I'll come over here to the cuddling folks.
And since they wanted me to talk about marriage this episode and the people that are going
get married on this episode?
I'm just kidding.
Are you enjoying each other's company?
Yea.
It's cute.
Speaking of which we did play those two in Scandia yesterday.
How much time did you guys collectively spend at Scandia this weekend?
Let's see, wait. Friday and Saturday.
So yeah, probably, you know.
Any annoying scandia people stories you want to tell?
Kids running across the DDR machine while you're trying to play.
On stage, I mean.
We have a picture of it. We had this three year old up on the extreme
just jumping around on stage
H2, Rhythm and Police, Light. It was hilarious. We have two pictures that will be up on the
album.
You don't bring anything up, Rob.
set up
all i got to make a minute to keep me company this is nice anyway
i want to talk about uh... this kind of like controversy at the three or
whatever you want to call it okay
eight folks terms i think it's a poster so from seattle came down which i think
is really cool like travel really far for a term in and i met
i met like one or two of them they were very nice and that uh...
this uh...
girl goes by
d r four b online i think i hope it makes up the letters
she's very cool really close to work at least things are shoes which is awesome
But Seattle was kind of getting, I guess, knocked or jabbed at or poked fun at or whatever
for being big old bar-rapers.
Like they hold onto the bar when they play their songs, which kind of creates a little
bit of controversy.
Is that real P.A. or whatever, you know, is it real?
And to them, looking at us, like, the way they're kind of looking at, or I should say,
when I say us, I mean California, the way Seattle was kind of looking at California
was kind of like, what's a big fucking deal?
You know?
It's that the bars are there, so why not use them?
So what do you guys think?
I'm curious of people's opinions in here on bar raping, quote-unquote.
Um, I really don't give a shit, because I saw a guy AAA Max 300. Yes, he was raping the bar, but I'd like to see anybody else try that.
It doesn't really matter.
Exactly, we do have a bleeder, okay? Anyway, I mean, think about it. He doesn't want to fall on his ass, he doesn't want to break his leg like, whatever that guy's name was.
So, at least he's not freestyling and holding onto the bar, that's different, but PA-ing, whatever you can do.
The only thing I didn't like, and it had nothing to do with bar raping, was the constant spraying down of Windex on the thing to rub down the pads to make sure they were absolutely clear and free of dust.
Where, if I'm going to be putting all my weight in one foot, I won't fucking slip and die.
If I'm playing singles, whatever, you know, whatever the pads are, fine.
I don't know if they realize or even notice, but if you wash them, if you use some sort of solution to clean the pads, it makes it slippier, slipperier, slipperier, slipper, whatever.
ever
Because if holding on to the bar will make me that much better, I'm going to do it.
I don't care if there's this stigma like, ooh, you're not supposed to hold on to the
bar.
Fuck it.
If I can get scores that good, I'm going to hold on to the bar.
Sure enough, I go back, I play Legend of Max, I hold on to the bar this time, I got like
15 seconds further than I usually do.
Go figure.
Yes, thank you, my recent accomplishment.
I am two-fisting the mics.
Why did you give me a mic and Rob gave me a mic?
Okay, I've got both mics.
Okay, new topic, alright, we're gonna go with like, you know, this year and pretty much
last year.
This year I've noticed a lot of trends changing, you know, this is just like pop culture trends.
Example, you know, before I used to make all these AIDS jokes, like, you're gonna get AIDS.
SARS is the AIDS of 2003.
SARS is not a joke.
We laughed so hard just over making SARS jokes during the whole trip.
It was great.
Is there any other pop culture changes you want to address?
There was another one, but I can't remember it right now.
When you think of it, you bring it up, okay?
Okay.
In the meantime, Janae, how's the story?
Okay, I have this really weird story to tell, because just thinking of SARS, it's just when
you think of something.
I went to the mall the other day and I went to the store, and as soon as I walked in the
coughing really bad I was like oh my god what's going on I thought it was like
anthrax attack and walking through the store walking through everybody's
coughing. Anthrax was last year. Well anthrax was the year before last so
anyways but still I was like what the hell's going on come to find out this
kid that says cash register pepper sprayed his boss on accident because he
didn't know that the thing was full and he was messing around with it and it
infected the whole store with pepper spray so that was really interesting to
watch that and see the little like friend of cops come in and be like we've
got to confiscate your pepper spray everybody was they say it just like that
we've got to confiscate your pepper spray no no basically they have don't
Krispy Kreme in one hand is there we're going to complicate your pepper spray my
doughnut is peppery coughing go oh is is Jamie right do you want to just before
Before we get over to Mad Libs, do you want to introduce yourself to our listeners?
How do I introduce myself to your listeners?
Tell them your online name and give them a quick personal ad because we know you're available.
I don't know how true that is.
Okay, my name is Janae.
On the board, I'm pixie dust and I'm 20.
I'm too damn old is what I think.
I'm just looking at a picture of me holding up a McDonald's apple pie, so yeah, I'm sexy, okay?
Apple pie going straight to my thigh.
You know you want some of this Southern Fry Thigh, you know that already.
I'm a little stupid and wacko, so yeah.
I got a lip on me.
You had a quick thought, Lucky, before we get to Mad Lib?
I did.
Okay, you look like it.
Okay, Jamie, are we ready for Bomani Madlib?
Okay.
Oh yeah, I remember now.
What?
My friend was on TV because he was the only UC student to stay over in China during the
whole SARS thing while everyone else came home.
His name was Eric Fong.
If you're in the Sacramento area and you happened to be watching News 3 at 11 a couple days
ago, you probably saw him.
His name is Eric Fong.
He used to make fun of me all the time, but we were really good friends.
Aw, it's so precious.
Anyway, let's get to our Bemani mad lib.
How's this going to work, Jamie?
Give Jamie a mic.
Basically, I'm going to tell you whether or not to say a verb, noun, adjective, whatever.
Okay. And you suggest it and you go around the room, everyone's suggesting one.
Okay. One by one and then we'll read you the story and, by the way, this particular one,
I might even give you the title or anything of what it is, but you get to find
out what it is you're butchering after you put in the words.
So should they be Bhumani related words?
No, not necessarily.
Okay. Be creative.
Be creative. Okay. But I'm not even going to say that much. Here you go.
So let's let, um, why don't you go first?
Wait, you better hold on to a mic, Jamie, and we'll pass around the other one.
What do you want me to do? Hold the mic in my cleavage?
It's there.
Okay, first one is, um,
a verb.
A verb?
sorry
that's not a verb
okay um...
dropping
okay who's next?
marin
a noun
frying pan
beautiful
alright uh... next
a verb that ends in i n g
uh...
do i get to do it?
coming
a noun
next is a noun
monkey
the person with the laptop should read suggestions in the chatroom too
opium
uh... verb
uh... irene says jacking
yeah that's fine
an adjective from uh... maggots
sarsi
a noun from angel
thing
nobody would have been in a half
uh...
it is camp on that
tampon active
and they want to get an edge of anybody
uh... low-key
bloody
and a lot more active
one more active
smelly
right now
i would like to rock on line
where
the rug burn
rug burning
and fall
insult
cunt
descriptive term
how about
voluptuous
uh...
uh... active
uh... are raping
uh...
as it would describe something
pink purple
stupid, moronic, retarded, stinky. Gluttonous. What? I don't know, I don't care. Noun. Twin.
uh...
i would like to have a look at what
for the record
that's not a bird
jesus the down
now
d r extreme
active
what do you have to say that was on
this is a very it's not that both of them
ready dorothy
now
ottoman
uh... what did you say
at past tense of her
uh...
a past tense verb yeah
okay i think fuck fucked fine
oh ass fucked we want ass fucked
quote from the chat room
wait what did you say? i took ass fucked
DJ
nationality
national
Cambodian
i like black-a-pino
I like black-a-pino, too.
Black-a-pino.
Alright, noun.
A what?
Noun.
A noun.
Um.
Poll.
Poll?
P-O-L-E.
Okay, we're almost done.
Need a noun?
Okay, we're almost there.
A noun?
A noun.
Um.
Green.
Okay, green cheese.
Adverb.
uh...
fully uh...
craft fully
crap fully
combats
yeah bernie nationality
another nationality
honky
I need a number.
I'm sorry?
A number.
69.
No, 15.
59.
I'll take 59.
Adjective.
Excellent.
Metallic works.
Noun?
Shit.
Verb?
Okay.
A verb that ends in a word.
Shit.
a verb that ends in ing
burninating
past tense verb
erode
cosplayed
i'm going to go ahead and contribute one myself because i want to
sodomized
a verb that ends in ing
Boss playing.
Okay, a verb.
Sodomize.
Okay, adjective.
I don't want one.
We're almost done.
You get the next sound.
Adjective.
Homosexual.
Noun, Matt.
Chainsaw.
I don't want one.
We're almost done.
You get the next sound. Adjective. Adjective. Homosexual.
Noun, Matt. Chainsaw.
Adjective.
Sexual works. Erotic.
Insect
Butterfly no butterfly
All right you ready yes, okay, this is from an article taken from
Igm.com which I'm about to post the link to the article in the chat room so that you can do a comparison
3. Gameplay
You do not know how to drop Dance Friday Pad Revolution, yes? If not, you haven't been
coming much monkey to me, have you?
1. Opium go up on the screen
2. Jacking on arrows on Sarsie Padeff's dance tampon.
3. Bust bloody smelly maneuvers.
With a tampon that makes sense.
4. Sweat like a ragged rock online.
Okay, number four, sweat like a Ragnarok online rug burn like cunt.
Should I continue?
Okay, this sounds voluptuous, it is simple.
It may also sound gluttonous or odd, as the twin around here likes to put it.
Twatterific.
You can jizz that last one for yourself.
I guess, but from my DDR Extreme, the game, it is also a dirty amount of ottoman, and
there are a few million people out there who assfuck the many Black Rapinoe versions of
a poll to back me up.
Many frozen extra cream cheese are crapfully included to combust the basic gameplay concept.
The Hulky version has a full complement up to the import 59th mix, meaning metallic training,
free play, and the diet shit, where the other extras, oh, where the game shit the calories
you burn by burninating, but not the solo mode and the other extras that arrowed with
recently released number mix, released 4900 mix, whatever, okay, there's no cosplaying
that I can sodomize though, no homosexual chainsaw like the sexual centipede and such.
So, and how was that for our first big year of Mad Lib?
Beautiful.
I think, you know what?
I think the chat room fell asleep for the first half of that, but that was a good payoff
at the end, so it was worth it that you burninated.
Maybe we should, maybe we should like make one in advance and have the chat room vote
on words or send them by email and then we put it in to read during the show later.
We'll tweak that one.
Well, that was fun.
Yeah, I like that.
Shit the calories you've burned by burninating.
Oh, boy.
Hey, Irene, the chat room wants to see another Orange Crush segment.
When do we get to see one of those?
I could probably come up with one by the end of the night.
By the end of the night tonight?
Yeah, what time is it now?
You got 30 minutes?
Okay, I could probably get it in like 10 minutes.
Okay, what we'll do, we're going to go to a quick break and then we'll come back and
how about we do some Ask Orange Lounge?
Yeah, that's fine.
Does that sound fine?
Okay.
Orange Crush now.
Okay, so we're going to take a quick break and we're going to do some Ask Orange Lounge.
Okay.
Have a big light, mate.
Okay, so Loki's going to queue up something.
You can send in questions now for Ask Orange Lounge because we're going to do that when
we come back and then we're gonna move on to orange crush by the end of the
show okay look are you ready this is a VW actually it's a song that I found on
the money since it's a remix of air called the era grand blue era outs or
it's grand blue and the era outset mix and it's pretty sweet so check it out I
I think you guys will like it.
Okay, now we're also going to play something.
Loki, you want to introduce this, which you just told me to play?
Yeah, this is, I don't know if anyone, anyone who hasn't caught the fuck off shows we've
been doing, we've been playing a new remix that I did of Gravity, and this is Gravity
Reloaded.
And you want to talk about the fusion here?
Yeah, it's Gravity in a mix with a song off of the Matrix Reloaded soundtrack called Dread
Rock by Pollock and Fould.
Still accepting questions for Ask Orange Lounge via the chat room or our email orangeloungeradio
at yahoo.com.
So send those questions in and we'll be right back after this brand new Loki remix, Gravity
reloaded here on Orange Lounge Radio.
Hello? Hello, is this thing on testing? Testing 1-2?
I'm looking in the index, but I don't see anything for how to run a radio show.
Hello? I don't understand this. Does this thing work?
This thing reads like stereo instructions!
Is this on?
What the hell?
Orange Lounge Radio broke down Get Open Monty Radio.
What the f***?
Welcome back, everybody. It's time for everybody's favorite part of Orange Lounge.
It's the part where the chat room really gets to participate. It's Ask Orange Lounge!
Tonight you can ask Orange Lounge, that would be myself, DarkSakura, or Loki.
Or you could ask Maren. You could ask Pixie Dust. You could ask...
Well, Nelly's probably not going to talk to you, but you could try asking her.
You could ask Brad, Irene. You could ask Navi, but he probably won't talk to you either because he's setting up for Orange Crush.
Or you could ask DDR Angel and Magus.
Quite the cute couple over there.
All right, let's get to the first question, shall we?
Let's ask your ass, how are you feeling today?
That had a maturity level of like three.
All right, first question from DJ Tyrant
wants to know, when can I come up and be a guest on the show?
That's my question.
Well, when can you get in your car and drive?
Plus, you know, I don't know.
I feel weird about having strangers in the house. I mean, of course, it worked before because I didn't know Angel before she came up here to be on the show, so...
Tyrant's not the only one that said he wants to be on the show, though. Here's my recommendation to you. Come to a tournament...
Come to a tournament like, you know, we'll be... I'm sure at least one of the three of us will be at Cyber Beat Nation 2.
Or come, you know, come to us at a tournament, get to know us there, come be on a team...
Or just come.
And then, once we get to know you, okay, come on a show.
Because I can't come to the studio.
Come to a tournament and get warmed up to the show first, because that's an easy way
to be on the show.
You don't have to sit here and be bored in the studio like everyone else.
Let's get to the next question from Ninst.
Ninst would like to know, what is the meaning of life, the universe and everything?
42.
42 says Mary, 42 says Jamie.
69 says Skye.
37.
Janae might have a serious answer.
My ass. Your ass. That's wonderful. That's the second person.
The meaning of life really is 42. The earth was constructed to solve the riddle of the
meaning of life.
Unfortunately, it was destroyed before it could finish the computations, so it came up with 42.
Now the purpose of life is easy.
The purpose of life is not dying. The purpose of life,
Breathe in, breathe out. Repeat.
I have a serious answer to this question. Can you people handle it?
No.
Okay, I'm going to try a serious answer to this question.
The meaning of life
is to experience every possible emotion possible.
Aw, da da da.
That's not an aw, that's like, death can be one of those. I still think the answer is 42.
It's 42.
I feel deathly ill. I woke up the other day and I went, ah, I'm deathly ill.
Alright. That's, that's funny. You know what's funny?
I'm experiencing vomit from that.
You know what the meaning of life is? Well, actually, you'll never know because once you figure out the meaning of life, that's when you die.
See, so if you ever do figure out the meaning of life, you will die. That's why no one has ever figured it out.
The meaning of-
Hey, Shady.
Ah, shit. Dead.
Alright. Second-
Wait, what do you do? You just kind of like straddle the dryer?
Exactly. It's an industrial one, so I straddle the dryer.
It's Talbe? Does he know?
That's awful. I hope you get beat for that.
Alright, moving on.
Next question from John Fields.
Just how many people in California have SARS?
I want to be on the show when I visit California, but if SARS is a problem,
I may wait for next summer to visit.
That's gotta be the dumbest question I've ever heard.
Why is that? Because anyone who's been in America who's gotten SARS
has gotten treatment for it and are like, better.
I think it was a joke.
Just, you know what, we're not Toronto, so get over it.
Yeah, Toronto's just trying to be special because they're Canadian.
You know, and they're just like, look at us, we're Chinese.
Sort of.
We have SARS.
for sarsi
we got stars a alright
moving on
black lab all excellent excellent question from black lab referring to the
chat room earlier this week
okay we have to get an answer from everybody on this
have you ever been that point where you were just so hungry you are so deathly
hungry you would just do anything the question from black lab would you give a
blow job for a pizza
and i've done that
notice i don't have to
i wouldn't give a blowjob for any reason because it's nasty
i'm sorry but it's the whole concept of putting your mouth where someone pisses
from uh...
so i would probably say that what i would do instead is get in my car and go
buy one
let's say you don't have any money
then i would kill someone for pizza but i would never blow them
uh... anybody else want to comment
i agree with jamie thank you
Well, I'd receive one for pizza, then I'd have a blowjob for pizza.
Excuse me?
Here's an excellent plug for our forums right here.
Visit www.calibomani.com slash nbor3 where our forums are.
And Zero put an excellent answer to this question earlier this week, so go read it.
Let's change this show from Orange Lounge to Dick Haters, because...
I don't hate...
uh... uh... we can't
dictating feminized
hey really really really
i don't
it's not that i hate dick
it's like i don't think it's particularly appetite let me please let
me put it this way it's like
to jamie dick is like a teddy bear you know you can fluff it and play with it
and how to get squeezed it
you're not gonna eat it
you put it in your your couch
me dick is foreign it is so foreign it's like japan so i don't know where it is it's so foreign
let's revise this let's revise this what would you do for kondike bar
but that's chocolate that's different anyway moving on what would you do for oreo kondike
bar moving on i want to get through i want to get through these ask horse lounge questions
okay here we go here we go i just heard oh this is from crash override 003 as opposed to 0070s 003
I just heard that DDR Extreme is the last arcade game for the DDR series, oh that old
rumor. Is this true? If it is, the last will be complete BS.
Again, that old rumor.
You know what, this is my thought, again, there is no definitive answer. If we knew
the definitive answer, we'd tell you.
I have the definitive answer.
Who gives a shit?
This DDR sucks.
Shut up.
No, it's not the last one, the next one will be the last one, and they're going to continue
it on the console because DDR is not popular in Japan, popular music is.
Here's my thought on it.
As far as the USA is concerned, it's true.
There's probably not going to be any other USA machines.
It's pretty much a home only thing.
Japan, nobody really knows, but here's my thought.
It's probably the last version of DDR in its current form.
If they do another DDR, it's going to be like DDR or DX type thing.
That's my honest opinion on it.
So we can take no motion, I see.
Hopefully.
Not.
Anyway, let's see, also second part of this question, oh!
And when are they going to fire Naoki and replace him?
Some of his material is just plain shit now these days.
Don't you know that they clone Naoki every year and keep using his clones?
I don't know.
I do notice that Xtreme kind of had less Naoki tracks than usual, but I don't think.
He's still doing music for 2DX and all that, so he's still around.
From what I understand, isn't he also actually working on Gradius 5?
Yeah, he's got things to do.
Alright.
Okay, so I'm going to cut off the question submission now, so I've got four questions
left to burn through here and then we're going to get to Orange Crush.
would like to know what would Jesus do for a Klondike bar?
What would Jesus do for a Klondike bar?
He'd just, you know, hang around.
He'd pick up a piece of shit and turn it into a Klondike bar.
Jesus would blow the pizza man.
Anyway, okay.
Last question. Are you guys ready for Orange Crush? Good. Okay.
Puppy would like to know, do any of you, oh, and I know Jamie knows the answer to this, I'm almost positive.
Black Lab wants to know, do any of you know where the saying, this DDR sucks, came from?
It came from Fuzzy Half, from Drakona Staunter.
She was at a DDR tournament and said, this DDR sucks.
So there you go.
Was that at CVGL or was that at-
It was Lily.
I know it was Lily that said it, but was that CVGL or was that at the Mountain Mikes one?
Mountain Mikes.
I think it was the Mountain Mikes one.
I thought it was from, what was it, that huge-
No, it was CVGL.
I thought it was that huge SoCal tournament or whatever that they were competing for freestyle or whatever and it was for the solo machine.
That solo sucks anyway.
That's the other one.
But yeah, this DDR sucks.
It was TVGL because we did the Step Squad thing at Mount Likes.
The promo at Mount Likes.
Oh okay.
She didn't go, I went.
I thought it was the same day that you guys had done that promo, but it was TVGL.
No, it was before.
We tried to get her to say it again and she wouldn't.
Now, it's time for Orange Crush. Now, it's time for Orange Crush.
Okay, Irene, take it away. Do I need to leave the room then first? Tell them about the topic and stuff, and somebody else needs to time.
The theme for tonight is called Five Button Mode.
that means it's easy questions from Poppin Music 8 or you know the Poppin Music series
so that's why it's five button mode so we're just waiting for the time to queue up are
you ready there okay start did you already start okay start in three two one go okay
which song from Guitar Freaks 9 and Drum Minute 8 came from Poppin Music 8 kataka okay which
Which pop music artist is getting the newest artist collection CD?
In pop music 7, the song Platonic Love is done by Nard, who is better known by which
alias?
What are the names of the two star characters in pop music?
yummy and
oh no
I don't play pop music, why was I picked?
oh, I'm sorry
okay
you didn't get any of them right, so you got half of one right
but you didn't finish it
yeah
button munch, Neil and Bob
and um, yummy
okay Rob
it's your turn
Thank you for playing Jamie, thank you.
Rob's not going to do any better.
Oops, did I say that out loud?
We're just waiting for Rob.
So, go check out ragnarkonline.com.
I know.
Shameless plug, shameless plug.
I hope everyone likes all these pop music questions, because Garrett, I have to thank Garrett.
Garrett came up with these questions, because he's amazing. Garrett's the frickin' awesome, Navi.
I haven't been fucked like that since grade school.
Bye, Janae.
Thank you.
Okay.
My turn.
Who would like to play Orange Crush?
I'm so excited.
Are you ready, Andrew?
Yes.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Which song from Guitar Freaks 9 and Drum Mini 8 came from Popin' Music 8?
uh... seven seven seven which poppin' music artist is getting the newest artist
collection CD
no
i don't know, pass. In poppin' music seven the song platonic love is done by Nard, who is
better known by which alias?
Naoki
what are the names of the two star characters in poppin' music?
what are the names of the what?
the star characters in poppin' music
uh... the two star uh... uh...
pass
Yes, I've been glad one right how many did Jamie get a half of one?
I'd be Jamie. I'd be
Jamie since you're sitting right there. Okay. What's the fifth question?
I just want to get a question that neither of you got to was the vocalist from Sweden from the Swedish song did which song?
in eighth style
our shadow
Which song from Guitar Freaks 9 and Drum Mini 8 came from Poppin' Music 8?
Rob is right.
777.
You know how I knew that?
Because that's in rotation on Orange Line right now.
Question number two.
Which Poppin' Music artist is getting the newest artist collection CD?
Let me think about this one a little longer.
The pop and music artist getting a collection CD?
I'm just trying to think of the artist to have a lot of songs in pop and music.
I would...
The classic?
The classical ones?
It's either going to be A. Desrow, B. Hideo Suwa, or C. Parquettes?
I would actually say before I say Desrow, I would say Hideo Suwa.
No it's Parquettes.
No.
Haha.
Okay third...
3. In PAPA MUSIC 7, the song PLUTONIC LOVE is done by NARD, who is better known by which
alias?
4. What are the names of the two star characters in PAPA MUSIC, NIAMI and NIMI?
I was thinking of the other ones, I was trying to think of that chick from Dimanche that
looks like a hussy in the second one, yeah I know you, I know, and then I had the image
of them, oh that's what they're talking about and I had no idea.
Okay and the fifth question, the vocalist from the Swedish song did which song in 8th
style?
Murmur Twins.
Oh, I should have known because it's like Garrett's favorite 8th style song, or one
of them.
One of them, isn't it?
I love Murmur Twins.
And that concludes another episode of Orange Crush.
Thank you very much.
That was beautiful.
You're welcome.
Here you go.
Good job.
I hope the chowram enjoyed that.
Yeah.
Jamie and I making butts.
Jamie and I making butts out of ourselves with our lack of pop and music knowledge.
Because he made the questions.
I got yummy.
I like to give mad props to Garrett for his accomplishments.
You know, I got it because he was in YY Racing and he was like, hey.
I am so down with Garrett.
The only reason I knew like any of those or would have known it.
You know, I'm such good friends with Garrett, and I still didn't know.
Okay, so, can I get my chair back, please, please, alright.
What else do you guys want to talk about?
Do you want to say something about popin' music, because we never talk about popin'
music in the show.
You want to say something about it?
Want to say it, Navi?
Alright, I'll say something about popin' music.
It's apparently no one ever really plays it except for like me and then people in SoCal.
As demonstrated by that last quiz.
Yeah.
News.
Pop and Music 8 is coming out on July 3rd at home along with Silent Hill 3 is being
released on the same date.
The wonderful site Nifty slash Global Gate where you can translate all those fun Japanese
pages into English clearly demonstrated how confusing their sites are.
It's either that or the Japanese are weird with the way that they, I don't know.
In my Japanese class I learned all kinds of stuff about their culture and how, you know,
like an example, you don't say you don't want something, you just say, oh, I'll take a little
of it and that means you don't want it because it's too rude to say you don't want it.
Same kind of goes for when I was trying to translate these pages and read about the pre-orders
for the limited edition pop and music stuff, see what the hell they're all putting in it.
It looks like, from the way everything is worded and separated, they have the limited
edition package and then they have the privileged limited edition package, which I don't really
get what the hell is going on, but needless to say, they're loading this shit up.
I don't know why they don't do this for any other Bimani games, but Pop'n Music 7 had
tons and tons of stuff in it.
This one has just as much.
They're putting in long, besides the V-Rare CD.
They have a new sticker pack with all kinds of stickers of characters and stuff.
I didn't really read what it was.
I think it's actually a stuffed character from the fresh genre song from Papa Music
8.
It looks like this little cat thing with an owl nose or something.
I don't know.
There's going to be a big canvas tote bag that's all Papa Music-ified.
Japanese fan that's supposed to be designed from one of the ones that one
of the characters was holding in Popin' Music 8. There was some more stuff too I
can't remember it all but it's one big humongous package of goodies and there's
going to be well over a hundred songs in Popin' Music 8. There were 54 new songs
to begin with in 8 and usually with how they do the consumer stuff there'll
be another 10 to 15 consumer tracks that they add on to this. So it's going to be quite
a nice game. Yeah, I don't know what else to say.
I'm moist of anticipation.
That was so funny. One big humongous package of goodies.
Yeah, Pop Music 10 is being test located right now in Japan also.
I came up with a stupid thing that you could use.
What?
Now introducing Orange Lounge with a fresher scent.
Thank you. That's very clever.
Thank you very much for the pop music update, we appreciate that.
We'll have to bring you back to do it again, because none of us keep tabs on pop music.
The only person in the whole North State I think that plays it regularly.
Oh yeah, and then I'll really get to play it once I get my arcade style controller so
I can tell you how wonderful that is and then you guys can be jealous.
I'll get to play it, you better let me play it.
You have to bring it to an episode and then we'll just have an episode of Orange Lounge
And it's got, like, a bunch of bug fixes and stuff, so we're good to go and download that. It's pretty cool.
And, um, other than that, I don't think there's really anything going on.
Yep.
Oh.
Okay.
Okay, since we have such a long-ass fortune cookie message today, thanks to Jamie,
I'm gonna go around and collect everyone's final thought. It's that time, it's that time of the show, you guys. End of show.
So I guess since Irene's got the mic, we'll start with her. No? We're gonna start with Garrett?
No.
Care doesn't have a final thought.
No final thought.
Nellie have a final thought?
This show fucking sucks, says Nellie. Thank you, we agree.
Uh, Irene.
Brad, final thought.
Go to ragnarchonline.com and download the game.
That is all.
Play on Loki, that's where I am.
Play on Loki.
Play on KF Loki.
we all just get a life. I don't think Loki would appreciate you while playing on him.
Final thought, Irene? Garret's great. He did my hair and it looks so awesome. Yeah. Okay,
fine. Final thought, Pixie Dust? I just want to meet a cute boy. I'm right here. What happened?
I said a cute boy, not a Buddha boy. I am so offended. Get out of my house. Nigga, please.
she's it she is part black she can say that word
that's why i can say bad because i'm gay
angel
i'm so final thought
i'm just glad i got to spend the weekend with my best friends ever
all everybody all of you are a job
all
okay i don't know
nagas final thought
Well, haha, I'm still better than the Clippers, bitch.
Anyway...
Maren! Final thought.
Aw, she doesn't have a final thought. Thank you for coming, Maren. Everybody give Maren a hand.
Maren's great. So many new faces on tonight's show. It's nice. It's refreshing.
They can't see any of them.
Yeah, you can't see any of them because we were too lazy to set the webcam.
You want me to go to Loki for final thought here? Okay.
Richie, I love you.
Loki, final thought.
I hate you, PayPal.
Let me just make this clear.
A cute single boy.
Yeah, single, straight, not gay.
Because I have a lot of gay male friends.
No, as in, not, I don't know, just not seeing anybody.
I want the age range of 21 to 27.
Yeah, exactly.
I'll let Jamie have the final thought. My final thought is
me and Evil Naoki 2DX, our
Japanese schoolgirl love-love sugar routine is going to be the best thing ever.
Jamie, your turn.
My turn?
I turned. No, but none of them saw that. That was bad radio.
My final thought is... I just thought it. Bye.
Okay. I thought my thoughts.
And tonight... I'm... I'm tired.
The last word of tonight's show goes to...
You've had it before.
Maren, because she didn't say a final word. Last word.
Burna Nation.
You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio. Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Dark Sakura, Skye and Loki. We expect you a nice play again. And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
Inform the commander that Lord Vader's shuttle has arrived.
Lord Vader, this is an unexpected pleasure. We're honored by your presence.
Yo, G, I'll be here to see why your homies ain't working their booties off.
I assure you, Lord Vader, my men are working as fast as they can.
We be seeing if they get this ride going with six foot seven of black staring down him.
I tell you that this station will be operational as planned.
Well, the man don't think so, and he be cruising down here to check out this ride.
The Empress coming here?
Yeah, and he gonna put a cap in your white ass.
We shall double our efforts.
Damn straight. And remember, this be CNN.
Thanks for listening and we'll see you next week.
And... Fade to black.
The afterbirth of Orange Lounge Radio.
Not the stillbirth, the afterbirth.
Anybody have anything extra they wanted to add that they didn't get out
during the three hours? Something that they don't want in the archives?
Wow. You're really white, you know that?
I want to play that song at the very end.
I didn't know Brad was married, does he have a wife?
Are they in Utah?
I'd just like to add an extra plug for our Bamani Music & More program, which is always on when we're not here, because we love people that listen to Orange Lawn's radio all the time.
I'd like to add an extra plug to your ass, Ron.
How do you know it's not already plugged?
There's too many plugs in there.
Oh, an extra plug, I'm sorry.
You know, you remember that sex scene in The Matrix with all the plugs?
I think this has been an enlightening experience, and I know this, that I'm surrounded by dirty
mofos.
You fit right in.
I'm a dirty mofo too, so I fit just right in.
Beautiful.
Hey Rob.
Yes.
Hey Rob?
Yes?
Do I have a phone sex operator voice?
Kinda.
Why?
A lot of guys tell me that for some odd reason when I'm on the phone.
Why don't you give us your best phone sex operator voice right now?
Let's pretend I'm calling a 900 line.
Okay, here we go.
This is me and Pixie S. This is me calling a straight 900 number line.
Okay, ready?
Ring, ring, ring, ring, ring.
Hello.
Hi.
What's your name, little boy?
My name is Brad.
Hello Brad, what are you wearing right now?
I'm wearing a red shirt and khakis.
Why are you wearing so much clothing?
Take it off.
Okay.
Why should I take it off?
Because you're a naughty, naughty boy.
And you know you want some miracle whip.
What are you going to do to me, Miss Phone Lady?
My name is Bambi, and I want to ravage your cunt.
I don't have a cunt.
Well, pretend you do.
You all can ravage your cunts all later.
I can't take it anymore.
Okay.
I hope that was good enough for you, baby, as good as it was for me.
I came. That was so great.
Oh, thank you.
I imagine these phone sex operators are probably sitting back there, you know, knitting.
Or doing their laundry or playing with their Game Boy while they're on the line.
No, that would be you, Jamie. You'd bring a Game Boy to work.
Oh yeah, it's a DDR machine. Oh God. Oh God. It does that. On the third mix, if you triple A it, it'll go, oh God, oh God, like that.
You guys are horrible. Bag. Okay, we're gonna go now. Good night, everybody. Loki would like to play a quick remix for you that he really likes, and then we're gonna have a mini 2DX marathon. So you guys should enjoy that, shouldn't you?
And, um, that'll be it.
So, Loki, introduce this mix.
This is Max Wishful.
It's a remix of Max 300 and...