[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Rawr.
[SPEAKER_08]: Techmaster Loki, also joining us every week here on the program.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, would not be fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, also our chat room is always here chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you'd like to join it and say hello to us and of course we always like to interact with our chat room who right now is razzing me for a technical difficulty we had before tonight's show started but those of you on the podcast, it'll all be fixed by the time you hear it so yeah, if you want to hear all the good technical difficulties not that we usually edit a lot of things but most of this is very uncensored radio we don't really filter anything out but
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, should I call it a blog cast?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakra, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've, whoa, I played World of Warcraft today and Sims yesterday.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I downloaded another game that I'm going to try out that I've heard lots of good things about.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I have to pull it up on, actually I have to pull up iTunes so that I can find it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's a little shooting game, like a, like a Gradius type of shooter.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, you know, I just, I just downloaded it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'll find it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, meanwhile, Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: I honestly didn't play a lot, which is sad, because we had four days off.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I decided to go ahead and I played a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: I brought out the Wii when I went over to my sister's house, and we played a little bit of Excitebots and...
[SPEAKER_02]: Then also, of course, more Grand Theft Auto this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: But mainly, I've been busy doing other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that would be, for some reason, and I don't know why, during the day on Tuesday this week, I just said, hey, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to turn a PSP into a MAME cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's what I've been doing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been taking a PSP...
[SPEAKER_08]: You get the most random ass little inspirations.
[SPEAKER_08]: My favorite will always be when you walked in here, episode 300 last year, and you walked in here in your Sackboy costume like, Hey guys, I made a Sackboy costume!
[SPEAKER_08]: We're like, why?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's just like, and it's weird, because I had specific requirements I wanted to do.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had to be everything that I had in the house already, like just random crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's basically, you know, it's going to be small, like a bar top, but it'll be out of spare parts I had and cardboard boxes.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually burned my finger on the soldering iron, which kind of sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, assuming that my soldering isn't absolute crap, which it is, but it looked pretty good, then it will actually be done soon, because I actually finished soldering today, and what I'm actually going to be running on it is not MAME, because they do have MAME for it, but
[SPEAKER_02]: The way I soldered everything, I can't really solder the directional buttons because it's really hard to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I instead soldered the analog because it's really easy and you can actually use the analog stick in some of the games.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I can't select between which emulator I run, I just have to have it auto boot into that emulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the one I found that runs pretty well is actually the CPS2 emulator so I can play some Puzzle Fighter on there and Street Fighter and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, it's coming along, and hopefully it'll be done this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now there's some haters in our chatroom at chat.orangelandradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hitstun says, PSP MAME sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, PSP MAME does kind of suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: CPS2, not that bad, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It runs pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's just, you know, this PSP, I haven't used it in like years, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Amaze Satsuma in our chatroom, chat.orange.com says, Loki's real name isn't Matt, it's Richard Dean Anderson.
[SPEAKER_08]: Making a MacGyver reference there, which is somewhat true.
[SPEAKER_08]: And which Actdeft says, Loki Guyver.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if that has the same ring to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alpha Cananogram asks a question though, what version of the PSP is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it a 1000, 2000, 3000?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's my old 1000 because I bought a 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought about breaking the 2000 because the emulators run better on there, but I can't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're the LCD stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they weren't the actual game, but they were kind of like a step above Game & Watch where the lights would actually be in color.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they actually put them in a cabinet-looking thing, and I think these things were pretty expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were probably $50, $60, which back in 1980 was a lot of money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they were like $30 now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just... I have pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you have pictures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some pictures.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should upload some of these to our picture feed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't really show much, anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, right now, other than there's a spider of wires, but here's what I finished before I left.
[SPEAKER_02]: Real quick, you can see... Sadly, this is horrible radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, I know, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: You can see where it's going to be the actual control panel.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, I'm looking at a picture of Loki's cable modem, of which it almost looks like he has wired six buttons into the cable modem.
[SPEAKER_08]: The cable modem box.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the box.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, remember, it's all out of boxes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, are you going to paint over the box?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it's going to be a box.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be the most ghetto-looking thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly, that's the point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to send this to our picture blog.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I didn't... I told you it's everything I had in the house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have packaging tape to put this together, so I'm using duct tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's going to be duct tape all over this.
[SPEAKER_03]: You need to use chicken wire, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have any chicken wire, so it's just...
[SPEAKER_08]: You are making a PSP MAME cabinet out of a PSP, cardboard boxes, and duct tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, like, arcade spare parts I have laying in my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Amazing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, yeah, it's... HitStunts come around a little bit and says, this might be cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, now when you finish it, since it's mini, you're going to have to bring it in here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to have a handle on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the thing, I also... And this is assuming that this all works after it's done, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_02]: Hopefully it works once I power it back up again.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if it does, then it should be good to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bochikawa in our chatroom says, Hey, guess what I got Loki for Christmas?
[SPEAKER_08]: A box.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, at least it wasn't your you-know-what-in-a-box like Justin Timberlake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pywish, big fan of duct tape as a lot of our chatrooms are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chatroom is duct tape fixes everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't wait to see this.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's like the Force.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It has a light side, a dark side, and it holds the universe together.
[SPEAKER_08]: This thing is going to be awesomely bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't wait to see it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please, please post that picture to our picture blog or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a few, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or your Twitter at least.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know, somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll post them too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you know how to log into the ULR Twitter?
[SPEAKER_08]: You should post it there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you that info off air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because obviously I'm not going to give out the password on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's...
[SPEAKER_08]: Fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, did you find that Gradius game type game you were talking about earlier?
[SPEAKER_03]: I did.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's called AX Raven Elite.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I'm going to post a link to the chat room.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can go to RocketeerGames.com and give it a try.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually made by a local.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh wow, very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Brad from PodCulture in our chatroom says, Step 1, put the PSP in a box.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should do like a parody video building your PSP MAME cabinet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like called PSP in a box or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's something here.
[SPEAKER_02]: When I originally was going to do actually running MAME on there, I actually made a skin for the background that looked like
[SPEAKER_02]: MAME but built out of cardboard.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that was kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now this CPS2 emulator doesn't really have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I may also do a Neo Geo emulator.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't decided yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really depends on which buttons that I've wired work and which don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that's really what it's going to come down to.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because if I'm missing any of the buttons that I needed to work, it's just trash.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole thing is ruined.
[SPEAKER_08]: In which case, I do believe you should just set fire to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll make a little bonfire somewhere.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll make it work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe in DarkSakura's backyard.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll move all the equipment out in the backyard and burn the cabinet live on air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Doesn't that sound like fun?
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I would rather take a crowbar to an office space with some loud gangster rap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe if it was a PSP Go inside, but PSP 1000 is still kind of valuable.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I guess you bricked it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's not bricked.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just... Well, it could be fixed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: I just don't care because I have another PSP already and I wasn't using this.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the battery was dead.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yes to fire?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not going to burn it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes to grow bar?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It'll work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on so we can get to gaming news before, you know, midnight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, My Gaming Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not a whole lot of new stuff, but I will say that, you know, I've been very enticed by Steam's various deals that they've had this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: You might have seen it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know Deekman's been posting them to our Twitter every day.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Steam deals, and they're all over the game blogs, because there's just been some really cool deals there on Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: And one of them that I jumped on was Dragon Age Origins was on sale for 25% off, so I think I paid like $37 for it, which, you know, considering it's like $59.99 on 360 or whatever, getting that price on the PC wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I, you know, kind of got into the game and started playing it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I couldn't really get very far into it before I got highly irritated because my video card apparently kind of sucks and is behind the time and cannot run the game very well even on its lowest settings.
[SPEAKER_08]: Things I should have thought about before I plopped the money down for the game, although maybe it's just a sign I need a new video card.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought, since I just bought my computer new last year, that my video card would not suck that bad, but it was one of those, you know, gateway, everything's there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gateway, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I thought when I bought it, there was something about the video card.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was supposed to be better than normal, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, sadly, I can't give you a fair review of Dragon Age Origins just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: That wouldn't be a very fair thing of me to review it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say this, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was quickly immersed into the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did think they did a very good job.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Bioware is kind of well-known for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: But I did feel very immersed in the game and I thought the storytelling was done very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I did like the fact, you know, just like in Mass Effect that you can kind of direct the conversations and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, something that Bioware has done very well for.
[SPEAKER_08]: They do very well.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was immersed in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'll give you a longer review after I get a better video card, which is...
[SPEAKER_08]: One versus one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I went to Macy's yesterday and I bought something that was half off and I went to the outlets today and I bought clothes because they were all cheap.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was going to go to Old Navy for their whole 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_08]: rock band thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you do any Black Friday at all, Loki?
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to Radio Shack.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because I couldn't find a screwdriver.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I went and bought another screwdriver.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I wouldn't think Radio Shack was doing a huge Black Friday discount.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, there was no one in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a feeling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, so I went out and bought a bunch of clothes.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I noticed with all these deals, I keep thinking maybe it's just selfish or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: I keep thinking it's stuff for myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm also the type of person, I always do my Christmas shopping on Christmas Eve.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just a huge procrastinator like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I never know what to buy, like tons of people's.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking in the chat room and seeing the comments there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ricky GoMac says, Get a Mac, Rob!
[SPEAKER_08]: I wonder why he might be suggesting a Mac.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ricky, go Mac.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would love to get a Mac, but they're a little pricey.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're kind of the Mercedes-Benz of computers.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't hate on Macs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great for Apple.
[SPEAKER_08]: But my one Mac laptop I did have, unfortunately, didn't last.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was a little bit disappointed in that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't know how I feel about the desktop.
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw says, also be sure your graphics card is an NVIDIA card.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_08]: My one I have right now is an ATI Radeon.
[SPEAKER_02]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_02]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I apologize if I'm pronouncing this incorrectly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Vanis Lux in chat says, Screw Macy's.
[SPEAKER_08]: They made my children cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, now I kind of want to know that story.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know that might be traumatic, but I kind of want to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it Santa Claus that made your children cry?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or did they not want to take something back?
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: OrangeLoungeRadio.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if there's really anything after 100.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think maybe if you get to 1,000, you get more statistics stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't get to evolve anymore?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if there's any more evolving.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't really looked into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll have to ask Seg, my buddy Seg that was on the show a couple weeks ago promoting Umlaut, which is coming up, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: He knows more about that stuff than I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wouldn't have even known about the short URL if I didn't see him talk about it earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, let's get into some gaming news tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Daytel is kind of pissed because, you know, you may remember Microsoft blocked their memory cards, their max memory, from working with the last dashboard update.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, you know, dashboard update came, and the max memory cards went.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, unfortunately, they had a workaround, they said at one time, but...
[SPEAKER_02]: LUL
[SPEAKER_02]: They have accomplished their recent update by making a system change that will not recognize or allow the operation of a memory card with greater capacity than their own.
[SPEAKER_02]: We believe that with the power Microsoft enjoys in the market for Xbox accessories, this conduct is unlawful.
[SPEAKER_02]: So they're kind of going with the whole Monopoly thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't really know if they have grounds to stand there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, since it is Microsoft's hardware and I think that they pretty much can say who can make what for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I do agree, I wish they did have some other memory card options because the Microsoft memory cards and Microsoft hard drives are way too fucking overpriced.
[SPEAKER_02]: and what we're talking like 120 gigabyte hard drive for $200, $150.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, shit, you can get way bigger drives for a lot cheaper, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta admit, this is tricky for me and chat, I'm really curious what you guys think about this one because I'm really on the fence with this because I understand the whole Microsoft is evil and they always have monopolies on everything and they violated antitrust before and you know, all of this I totally understand that side of the argument and yeah, they do charge way too much for like, you know, considering that 120 gig hard drive is dirt cheap
[SPEAKER_02]: Or even like a 512 megabyte memory unit for 50 bucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, when you can buy like 4 gig thumb drives for like $10.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the part of it, though, where I'm kind of with Microsoft.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that is that these companies take huge losses when they put out these consoles.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you buy a console from Microsoft, Sony, not Nintendo this time, because we know the Wii was not quite...
[SPEAKER_08]: The same technological level, but in the past they've taken a loss on their systems too Maybe it was a small loss this time, I don't have the data on that, I don't think it was though But Microsoft and Sony take a loss on every console that they sell to you They've got to make that money back other places And that is usually through software, through licensed products, through the licenses and so forth That's how they make their money back
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can sort of see where they have the right to lock out the unauthorized products because my fear is, my ultimate fear is that let's say Datel wins this suit and it just opens the floodgates to all these unauthorized devices that are going to be out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: The next round of consoles are going to cost through the roof because companies are not going to want to take a loss on it.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't think that's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they had a ton of unlicensed products for the PlayStation 2 and the PlayStation 1 and, you know, hell, older consoles and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Never really affected their sales.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Sony also tried to charge out the ass for the PS3 when it first came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they were still claiming a loss, but we all laughed them off because we said, too damn much money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, but that's for other reasons entirely.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except the hardcore fans, of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's because, hey, let's throw in this really awesome cutting-edge cell processor.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, let's throw in some Blu-ray technology.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, let's throw in some other crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why it's so expensive, and to their benefit, they also have allowed their end user to upgrade the hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because it's just a normal hard drive.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Microsoft says, fuck you guys, we're just going to put that normal hard drive inside of a case and then charge you twice as much for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: What about the fact, though, that a lot of people, well, I shouldn't say a lot, but there was certainly a significant amount of people that were using these devices for the cheat functionalities that, you know, the SD cards, importing the saves, inflating gamer scores, cheating.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, Microsoft is trying to protect Xbox Live because, you know, they market it as, hey, you're paying $50 a year because we lock out this kind of shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you can't really lock it out permanently.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, they have all those game saves and everything are now... I mean, because originally they weren't all signed to the profile.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, you could download game saves and throw them onto your console and kind of save it at a point right before an achievement or something like that and boost your achievement scores.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now everything's signed to your user ID, so...
[SPEAKER_02]: Unless you're the actual user that made that save, you can't really use that save unless you re-sign it on your computer, which you can do that, and you don't really need this memory card to do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's really not an excuse.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just them being dicks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me ask this follow-up question very plainly because SalaciousPop asks this in chat, and I kind of want to know this too because I kind of agree with his thought here.
[SPEAKER_08]: He says, can't you put save games on like a thumb drive?
[SPEAKER_08]: It reads USB fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I'm missing something.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: I always assumed you could, because you could do MP3s and videos and all that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, if you could put it on a thumb drive, then it wouldn't fucking matter that they have their stupid little memory cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you can't, because obviously that'd be the easiest route.
[SPEAKER_02]: You wouldn't even buy the stupid little memory card.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it makes sense now that you're saying it, but I just kind of always thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then again, I've never tried to use it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not the type that wants to cheat in games and all this and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never really thought to use this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I never even owned a Game Genie back in the day, although I thought they were interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: They were awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's too bad we don't have anything like that anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_08]: Everything got too... Not anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all game saves now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, I always wondered how they found those codes for Game Genie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, did somebody have to sit there and actually go 00001?
[SPEAKER_08]: or was it because of the fact it was hexadecimal based, they could go into the programming and figure it out?
[SPEAKER_02]: They had cheat programs similar to that on the PC for cheating and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, it's memory searches.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I have five lives right now, do a memory search for five.
[SPEAKER_02]: I die once, do a memory search for four.
[SPEAKER_02]: I die again, do a memory search for three.
[SPEAKER_02]: What it does is it narrows down those memory addresses until you get the one that actually controls
[SPEAKER_02]: Curiosity, I don't even know if you know this, would a PS3 let you do it?
[SPEAKER_02]: PS3, yes, will let you put game saves on a thumb drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they don't sell memory cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all open.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all thumb drives.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can use whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony fanboys, if you haven't thought to add that to your arsenal of web forum...
[SPEAKER_08]: They're harassing.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's something for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Their memory cards are just USB drives, basically.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it's just signed different and they're shaped different.
[SPEAKER_02]: They've got, you know, but it's basically a UMD drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or not UMD, USB drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100Matt in chat asks, or says, basically, I was really hoping they were going to drop the price of the HDs this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, kind of surprising they didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: TigerClaw in chat says, do you mean a trainer?
[SPEAKER_08]: When you were talking about that memory scan software.
[SPEAKER_08]: For PC games, you used a program called a trainer.
[SPEAKER_08]: You load the PC game first, then load the trainer program, and it will modify what's in the memory so you can run some cheats.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's from TigerClaw.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not a trainer, but this is like predating all the trainers and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because a trainer usually is all the hard work's done for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's basically, okay, hit button one to have infinite ammo or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: And those are nice, but
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm talking about something, it was actually just a program I mean this is back
[SPEAKER_02]: Floppies and Shareware Days It was just a program that you'd run that basically would work with any PC titles because it's just a memory search function and you can do searches and stuff on different values and I think the registered version of it or whatever had an ability to figure something out with life bars because life bars are hard to determine since you don't know what the actual number is it's just kind of a percentage so
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, this was like years ago.
[SPEAKER_02]: But yeah, obviously now they have trainers for everything that come out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quickly to kind of wrap this up and move on with the show, and Jamie, I don't know if you have a thought on this either.
[SPEAKER_08]: How do you think this lawsuit's going to go?
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think Daytale's going to be shit out of luck, or do you think maybe they have something with this whole Monopoly thing?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they're going to be shit out of luck because they're going to be like... It's going to be... Well, you can make peripherals for us, but you just have to pay us a licensing fee and we have to approve it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think they're going to win.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jamie, agree?
[SPEAKER_03]: Disagree?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it could go either way.
[SPEAKER_03]: To be honest...
[SPEAKER_03]: It's not like we haven't had other peripherals be locked out before on certain systems.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, for example, I know that I couldn't use certain third-party controllers for certain games back in the day.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of look at it as being along the same lines.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, it would really have to be a situation of...
[SPEAKER_03]: and DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta say, for me, either way, this story sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if Datel wins, then I truly believe that's going to drive the price of the consoles up, and they're going to use that as justification.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if they lose, then all those people that spent money on that device lose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ultimately, the consumer loses.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let the buyer beware.
[SPEAKER_08]: Womp, womp, womp, womp
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: and they actually had a version of it in Super Nintendo that was pretty badass and it's one of the games that's going to be featured on my box cabinet because it's a Capcom system of course but for those of you that don't have the skill to build a cabinet out of boxes and duct tape you can also put it on any homebrew enabled PSP too so they work pretty well
[SPEAKER_08]: OMG Spoilers
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm more excited about Magic Sword than I am Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I did love that game too, I gotta say.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will say this about Final Fight, is that apparently some of the fighters and very familiar faces are making their way into Super Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I have to admit, from what I do remember and love about Final Fight, I think this is awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cody and Guy are making their way to Super Street Fighter 4 according to the latest issue of Famitsu Magazine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also making an appearance, Adon from Street Fighter Alpha So those were three new characters that were announced this week I believe Cody's been in a game before Yeah, Alpha 3, also he's going to be one of the characters coming up in Street Fighter 4
[SPEAKER_08]: Right, right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's very cool, I think.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I thought you were still talking about Final Fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this whole new crossover is kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of miss the whole Alpha series of Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: That all happened during that period of my life where I wasn't as into video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I never really played those games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I never realized that they had the crossover.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I do remember Hagar, the mayor, in Saturday Night Slammasters, which was also completely underrated Capcom classic.
[SPEAKER_08]: we had that at my arcade that I worked at that was the ultimate pizzeria arcade game I loved that game also on there shut up
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ranma asked in chat real quick before we get to another story here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyone remember Mighty Final Fight?
[SPEAKER_08]: I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't that the version that was on the NES as opposed to the Super Nintendo?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it wasn't like all kind of super deformed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was all the chibi characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was an 8-bit port, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, it wasn't as great because it was an 8-bit port.
[SPEAKER_08]: But DarkSakura, why don't you do one more story for us?
[SPEAKER_08]: Then we're going to get to our interview tonight.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We do have it coming up.
[SPEAKER_03]: But how about some PC news?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, Valve is basically sticking their tongue out and waggling it at all the people that are boycotting Steamworks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which I'm actually laughing.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're saying basically that any digital distributors who are boycotting PC games because they come with Steamworks services are missing out on an opportunity.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're actually saying that...
[SPEAKER_03]: and let's see different companies like Direct2Drive, Impulse and GamersGate that didn't want to sell Modern Warfare 2 because it had the Steamworks tools acting as a storefront for Steam.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're saying that if you make a good game it should be out through as many channels as possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: on my system.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not what I asked for.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whenever you download iTunes, it tries to install Safari on your system.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't ask for fucking Safari.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wanted iTunes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do find that kind of shit annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I realize maybe it's a little different because Steamworks directly does relate to the games, but I can kind of see their point.
[SPEAKER_08]: When you get these things you didn't ask for that even eat up 1K of memory, it's a bit of an annoyance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, what the word is is that they've actually based the inclusion of it on what customers have asked for and that they've actually sold the games as well through Steam as they have in the stores, especially Modern Warfare 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Redertainment in our chat room at chat.orangeleisure.com says, Sorry, I call for a boycott of the boycott.
[SPEAKER_08]: Perhaps that's something he needs to start.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: I say if people don't want it, don't get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: If people want it, get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_03]: You can uninstall the shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Vannis Lux in our chat says those distributors that didn't carry Modern Warfare 2 cut themselves out of a crap load of money and that's about all the effect it had.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Gold Anthro wants to point out not only Safari but also QuickTime.
[SPEAKER_08]: I give them a buy on that because the movies that play in iTunes when you download movies and TV shows which is an integral part of the system are in a QuickTime proprietary format.
[SPEAKER_03]: I however refuse to install Safari.
[SPEAKER_03]: Safari is ass on a PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate Chrome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm glad there's choices now, whereas it's not Internet Explorer seeming to dominate as much as they used to.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know they still are the number one, but not nearly the hold they used to have.
[SPEAKER_03]: Firefox actually is a lot more secure now in general than Internet Explorer is and has a lot more functionality.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of places are really starting to embrace it over Internet Explorer.
[SPEAKER_03]: You saw what happened to Netscape.
[SPEAKER_03]: Netscape's gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I could see that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, we got to move on because we actually have a rare live interview tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of times our interviews are pre-taped, but we actually have a live interview tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I have to ask you guys, especially here in studio, how many of you guys have seen this video that's floating around YouTube right now?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's this little...
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks to you and Megzi, I've seen both.
[SPEAKER_08]: So at the end, obviously, it's this little video that kind of parries using these Sackboy characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's kind of gone viral this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's very interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: The whole thing was created by this gentleman, Brian Moreno.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, his little big plan has been continuing to grow via the online co-op mode that you've heard about this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And after one year of release, the online community is still going.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think a lot of us kind of, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: continue to make good on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think this video going viral is just kind of an example of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this video, which you can find Little Bad Romance, YouTube user Brian RDM, it was on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then it got posted to NeoGAF, which is, you know, this huge, huge gaming forum.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure you've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then it spread through Twitters, through Facebooks.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's where I found it.
[SPEAKER_08]: An OLR member posted it on their Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it got coverage on Kotaku, other blogs, so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ironically, Lady Gaga, she's also big right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: She just started a big tour of hers last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: 50,000 views on YouTube tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just about 50,000.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just shy of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we want to get Brian Moreno here on the show to talk a little bit about this and about the LittleBigPlanet community.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're actually going to give him a call right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully he is standing by.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, is this Brian?
[SPEAKER_08]: This is Brian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey Brian, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Rob from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are doing great.
[SPEAKER_08]: We were just kind of checking out your video here in studio, looking at it, the little bad romance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Congratulations on the success.
[SPEAKER_08]: About 50,000 views now, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, it's pretty mind-blowing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you ever think that this was going to catch on as big as it did?
[SPEAKER_06]: Me and my friend were actually talking about this yesterday.
[SPEAKER_06]: We thought maybe 1,000, 2,000 modest views, a laugh between ourselves, and then
[SPEAKER_06]: all of a sudden the second day it was posted it was number three most viewed in its category in Russia and 95th most viewed on YouTube that day
[SPEAKER_06]: It was pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had no idea it was going to go that far.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got some questions for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, I got to know, Brian...
[SPEAKER_08]: Lady Gaga is huge.
[SPEAKER_08]: People love this new album.
[SPEAKER_08]: She has these super fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: People get on YouTube and they do karaoke, they dance, do whatever interpretive thing to bad romance.
[SPEAKER_08]: What made you decide, I'm going to do a tribute, but I'm going to do it in LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually a mixture of many things.
[SPEAKER_06]: I work, one of my steady gigs is a club photographer here in Orange County.
[SPEAKER_06]: and October last year, I actually had an opportunity to photograph and meet Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_06]: This was right before her career exploded.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she was the nicest person I've ever met.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was 2 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: The show was over.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fans were outside of her trailer and security was leaving.
[SPEAKER_06]: And she said it herself.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's like, I'm going to be here until I take a picture and take an autograph for everyone.
[SPEAKER_06]: Everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, she did something like that recently, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard it, like a Best Buy in L.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: that all these people came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: She said, I'm not leaving until I sign all your stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's great about her and her fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, I've thought she's the greatest person since I met her.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then with the release of The Fame Monster, I mean, I've been hooked on that album.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's so much better than her original release.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then when it came to LittleBigPlanet I had been a fan of it since it had been announced E3 how many years ago and just the ability to be able to create whatever you want and how accessible it was to everyone it just, me being a fan of those two it just seems like the perfect recipe for something that would go far that would have long legs So it just kind of worked out in your mind I like this, I like this, what happens when we throw them together?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, some could say that's the same way this show started.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Jamie, remember it was about, hey, I like video games and we do amateur radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's do a radio show about video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, to paraphrase the quote is, two great tastes that go great together.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a question for you, Brian.
[SPEAKER_08]: How long did this whole thing take?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I got to say, one thing that impressed me when I saw this video is I was thinking, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'll admit, anyone that's been listening to the show a long time, I'm a big old fan of Lady Gaga.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think she's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in fact, I'm not going to be here at the show on December 13th because I'm going to Monster Ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: Couldn't be more excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I was going to say, that video came out like Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this video seemed like it was on the internet not even 10 days later.
[SPEAKER_08]: How long did this whole thing take you to put together?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hours and hours and hours and hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was in fear of my 60 gigabyte PlayStation hitting the dirt.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was afraid of it dying how much I was on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Honestly, maybe a good 48, 64 hours total.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was just trial and error on making those costumes and matching it with the video and making the set pieces and doing what I could with the tools that I had provided.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was anyone helping you out with it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I noticed in a lot of the scenes, it seems like there were always three Sack Boys.
[SPEAKER_08]: So was that just you kind of coordinating three controllers?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or did you have a couple friends helping you?
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, in set pieces and costume design, it was just me and the PlayStation and me tweeting it to friends or Facebooking it to friends to see how well they thought it matched up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, you know, this is kind of a subjective question here, but would you say that the tools that Media Molecule gives you in LittleBigPlanet made this process easy?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I know you talked about it takes hours and hours, but it takes hours and hours to build a really good level in LittleBigPlanet, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think you have the tools you needed to produce this video good, or do you think there was something that Media Molecule could have given you that would have made this whole thing easier?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the process, it went well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did discover limitations that I did not know existed in the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of the issues was hair with me, because hair for me, I wanted to get the right colors and really differentiate from the Gaga Sat Girl.
[SPEAKER_06]: And one of the problems is, for a lot of the hairstyles, you can't actually change the hair color.
[SPEAKER_06]: So the way I had to go around that was using stickers and carefully putting colored stickers on the hair.
[SPEAKER_06]: but another limitation in that is it seems that items only have a maximum of three stickers that you can place on an object before it'll erase the first one put in and put in the new one.
[SPEAKER_06]: On top of that, it's a 2.5D perspective game and you couldn't get the camera in some ways that you could, especially in close-ups.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the way I found a way around that is
[SPEAKER_06]: When you go open the pop-it menu and go to the customize Sackboy option, it zooms in the camera to maximize the screen on your Sackboy.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you press circle and get out of that, the camera stays on that perspective.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that's how I was able to get a lot of the close-ups because the camera tools that they give you don't get that close.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there's a tip for other aspiring video makers out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking of which, was this really like the first thing you really did in LittleBigPlanet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or have you made levels before?
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you done other projects?
[SPEAKER_08]: And this is just the first one everybody seems to notice.
[SPEAKER_06]: I had fooled around with LittleBigPlanet back in the beta, and I had made a kind of inside joke level for one of the websites that I'm a forum member for, thenextlevel.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: But after that, it's just
[SPEAKER_06]: I really didn't have the time and so many other great games were coming out, but it was always in the back of my head that I always wanted to do something with LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that was just with the Gaga and the LittleBigPlanet and me wondering what would happen with those two.
[SPEAKER_06]: I went out and bought a capture device and I was like, I'm going to do this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to take my time and I'm going to make sure I make something great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you saying you bought the video capture device just for this project?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just for this project.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is dedication.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, since Lady Gaga is so generous to her fans and so forth, do you think there might be a chance she's seen it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I actually have no idea if she's seen it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I hope she does.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I spammed her Twitter every time I posted the link to that video.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do know for sure that some people in Media Molecule have seen it because if you go on their official YouTube page, it is one of their favorites.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope Media Molecule gets me on that, because I'll help anyone I need to to get those costumes done right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hey, you're kind of the perfect guy to ask about this because you said you were in the beta and all this too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we were just talking before you came on the air about how LittleBigPlanet, a lot of us didn't really believe Media Molecule a couple years ago, or I should say a year ago when this game first came out, that they weren't going to just jump right in and do LittleBigPlanet 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: They came out and said, no, we're going to continue to support LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they've really made good on that promise to a lot of our surprise, a very pleasant surprise.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think it is about the game that keeps this community going strong a year after the game is out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it all these constant updates?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it the fact that people keep building these pop culture references?
[SPEAKER_08]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think like overall it's very charming to look at and it's very peculiar to look at.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's nothing else really out there like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: But most of all I really feel that it's
[SPEAKER_06]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to just enjoy this and move on to other projects.
[SPEAKER_06]: What this video was, was a part of a whole of a project that I was doing actually for one of my college classes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm about to graduate finally.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was kind of about context and what would happen if I took something and put it in somewhere, something else.
[SPEAKER_06]: What would happen...
[SPEAKER_06]: The next part of the series, I guess I'll give you a little exclusive right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: My next video, using LittleBigPlanet and kind of going along with these puff references, is going to be remaking the New Moon trailer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, dear Lord.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which, you know, if there's anything bigger than Gaga, it's a new moon.
[SPEAKER_06]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, that's...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd love to continue doing stuff with LittleBigPlanet.
[SPEAKER_06]: With NeoGAF, I promised them that if this made it on any gaming blogs that I would go along and do some of their music video requests.
[SPEAKER_06]: So some of them that they've requested are Thriller and White Wedding.
[SPEAKER_06]: So really going to have to see if those are possible because I did stretch the limits and really got really creative with what I was given to be able to get the costumes as close as they could look.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I gotta say, it's getting a lot of mixed feedback in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're getting some LOLs and XDs, and then of course the Do Not Wants and so forth for the new Moon trailer.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I like this from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_08]: How are they going to make a Sackboy turn into a wolf?
[SPEAKER_08]: And Bochikawa says, roll full, sparkly, and wolf Sackboys.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I guess we'll see, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll figure it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: If this whole thing was for school, I hope to hell you get an A. I hope so.
[SPEAKER_08]: You got robbed.
[SPEAKER_08]: You play this for your professor.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give Brian an A. He earned it.
[SPEAKER_06]: This will actually be part of the package that I turn into him.
[SPEAKER_06]: This will be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome, awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, you know, Brian, one thing we like to ask everybody we have on the show, you know, just a standard question for all the guests because we always ask it to ourselves at the top of every show.
[SPEAKER_08]: What video games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, besides LittleBigPlanet, of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: The matter is, is what haven't I been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been playing Dizzidia, Final Fantasy on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not too sure about that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I played it at E3 earlier this year, I was kind of
[SPEAKER_06]: I had no idea what was going on, but I'm getting used to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a really big fan service.
[SPEAKER_06]: On top of that, playing the original Left 4 Dead because I already bought Left 4 Dead 2 on Black Friday and haven't even finished the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me and a friend also went to the 3 a.m.
[SPEAKER_06]: Old Navy Black Friday opening and we got ourselves a copy of Lego Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_06]: We've been rocking out with that with Elton John and Vampire Weekend.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was debating doing that, but I was like, I don't want to fight all those people at 3 in the morning, so props to you for doing that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very interesting, too, because LEGO Rock Band is another game with very cute-looking avatars.
[SPEAKER_08]: You think you might have something there with LEGO Rock Band and making fan videos?
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing with LEGO Rock Band is...
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, for me, I really need those tools.
[SPEAKER_06]: And as far as I've seen, Lego Rock Band doesn't give me anywhere close to what LittleBigPlanet does.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_06]: In terms of being able to create and being able to have some control.
[SPEAKER_06]: Besides LittleBigPlanet, I am going to start looking into Uncharted 2 because I remember hearing there's a movie-making mode where you can do all kinds of camera tricks and lip-syncing, I believe, is in there.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see what I can do with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really...
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really trying to get into these electronic format and electronic creative ways to continue this project beyond just the school project and the assignment requirements.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Brian, it sounds like you're going to be able to use this as kind of a launch for future Mashima and types of movies based around video games, so props to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where can the listeners keep tabs on you and your future projects?
[SPEAKER_06]: The easiest way is going onto my website, www.brianmoreno.com
[SPEAKER_06]: You can find me on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's youtube.com slash BrianRDM.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those will be the quickest and easy ways to keep up on any of the work I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, and stay tuned there for the soon-to-come LittleBigPlanet New Moon trailer, which you heard about here on OLR First.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you so much, Brian.
[SPEAKER_08]: Appreciate that exclusive and everything else.
[SPEAKER_08]: And best of luck to you in your future endeavors.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys, I want to thank you guys, Kotaku, NeoGaf, The Next Level, all the listeners on Orange Lounge Radio, everyone on YouTube, Lady Gaga, everything because without all of you guys this wouldn't be anywhere close to what it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm glad we can kind of make your day with all of this and you know what, I really smiled and got a good laugh in a really positive way out of the video when I first saw it so I'm glad we can kind of turn it around back to you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent, thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, take care Brian, have a good one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care guys, bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: He definitely sounds like he's going to kind of use this to kind of start something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: And although, you know, this may be the one that's really big and maybe the other ones, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that one was so good and he's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was very well done.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I was quite impressed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Whether I like it or not, you know, I like Gaga, but I don't like Twilight nearly as much.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually looking forward to seeing how that pans out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love...
[SPEAKER_08]: He's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: The only thing bigger than Gaga is Twilight, so why the hell not?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, yeah, you're totally right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who doesn't love a good Weird Al song no matter what it is he's parodying, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, he should do a Weird Al video.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hopefully he's listening.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, a Weird Al one, that would be good.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that was fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got some more news here before we get to our classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, Part B tonight, 7 o'clock here in California.
[SPEAKER_08]: 10 o'clock for those folks on the East Coast, but plenty more show to come.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Loki, what's up next?
[SPEAKER_02]: As we alluded to in our intro, although the podcast won't be privy to that, New York State apparently now has teamed up with Microsoft to issue emergency alerts via Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of similar to, I guess, the Amber Alerts that we have and other emergency broadcast system stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're going to let you know if there's a natural disaster, terrorist attack, disaster.
[SPEAKER_02]: You name it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Whatever requires them to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just hope they don't do the tests with that, and I also hope they don't have that annoying beep that goes with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, a message to me might be fine, but man, I hate watching TV and all of a sudden there's like an Amber Alert thing going on and all the audio cuts out, and it's like, dude, I'm inside my house.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not gonna see some guy driving around with his stolen child in my house, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: So you really have to use a device like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're using Amber Alert.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that the type of thing they're talking about here?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kidnap kids?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's mainly emergency broadcast system stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mainly, I think it's because New York and the whole 9-11 thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I'm sure other states are probably looking into something like this too.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if the gaming consoles are exactly a good platform for that because most people would be like, God damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who's messaging me now?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to go finish this game first.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Terror, Terror Alert, you know, Death Inimitator.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, ah!
[SPEAKER_08]: The Vs have arrived, get out of town.
[SPEAKER_08]: The bomb has gone off already.
[SPEAKER_03]: That bothers me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_03]: I, no, I don't like using, okay, that was, that's like seriously my big pet peeve with that show is I'm calling them the Vs that, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: The whole point of the V in the original series was the reference to World War II.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know in the new one they got the whole... I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's retarded.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, regardless, all joking aside, I gotta say, though, you know, when they originally incorporated the emergency broadcast system, wasn't it kind of a similar deal?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, people use their free time playing TV, or playing TV, watching TV, and so the emergency broadcast system would alert those people who aren't glued to the radio or going outside.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, this kind of makes sense in a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that they use this tastefully, like, hey, there's a fucking fire right by you right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, it might be a good idea to get the fuck out and stop playing your game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually don't think it's a bad idea, but again, it's just about how much they use it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if it's an Amber Alert every other hour, people are going to get pissed off.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if it's for big stuff, like you need to leave your home, you need to evacuate or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: If it's an absolute emergency like that, they have a way to call all the phones and have an automated message play so you can pick up your phone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because most people might not be playing a game console.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, what's that crackling, rumbling sound?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh hey, it's fire!
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome!
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to play it over level, it's far enough away.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's just a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just interesting to see how it's implemented.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it's going to be just about as effective as it is on TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which is, if you're like me, that's the time that I go get a snack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because that noise is... Oh god, I hate it.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt in our chat took the words right out of my mouth.
[SPEAKER_08]: The next step would be announcements in WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then again, those people won't leave their homes anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
[SPEAKER_08]: I resemble that remark, thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Janayan Chat, yes, it just goes in the next time.
[SPEAKER_08]: We interrupt this WoW raid for this important Amber Alert.
[SPEAKER_08]: And again, guys, I'm not trying to belittle Amber Alerts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Obviously, it's an important thing, but I think that type of thing works best, you know, on the highway, where the cars are, you know, on the signs on the highway, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, how would you feel if you were playing a game and then suddenly...
[SPEAKER_08]: Fire, Get Out
[SPEAKER_08]: Fire in Bakersfield Do not give a crap.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, sucks to be people in Bakersfield, but don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would want to have it be my specific zip code, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be more appropriate.
[SPEAKER_08]: The chatroom collectively, I'm just kind of attributing this to several people in the chatroom, seem to think that the iPhone is a good idea for these types of alerts.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've heard that talk before too, is alerts through text message.
[SPEAKER_08]: which I think could be very effective.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I get charged text messaging.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not if you have an iPhone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, and your carrier doesn't charge.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know even when I had Sprint and I got charged for every message on my plan, they didn't charge for messages they sent.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and I wouldn't think those you'd get charged for.
[SPEAKER_03]: But a lot of times, though, it's built into your iPhone plan to have a certain number.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or even if a little app you could download that's like an alert app or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: It might not have the same impact, though, that just sending everybody text messages.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just send it to your email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Just have stuff that goes to your email.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, SJ100Matt makes the joke, Nintendo will send their Amber Alerts through friend codes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So an Amber Alert will look like 012463.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, hey, speaking of WoW came up in that last story and WoW is the attention this week of a lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: One million dollars in a complaint against Activision Blizzard over the design of World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: This complaint says the publisher maintains a quote harmful virtual environment to many of its customers by forcing them to follow the game's sneaky and deceitful practices.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well now, what would you think about this lawsuit if I told you it was filed by Eric Estavio?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, the guy who filed the lawsuit against Sony.
[SPEAKER_08]: And the judge basically laughed it out of court.
[SPEAKER_08]: So he went and sued Microsoft and Nintendo, which we reported on last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this week, now he sued Activision Blizzard over this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, by the way, as part of this case, Estavio has subpoenaed actress Winona Ryder...
[SPEAKER_08]: and Depeche Mode's Martin Lee Gore to testify on his behalf.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because apparently, I don't even want to get into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just as ridiculous as it sounds.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that mean they have to actually show up?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think he just wanted to meet them.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm reminded of that scene from Clerks the Animated Series where they subpoenaed George Lucas into the courtroom, which didn't this whole topic... I want my money back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't this topic come up on the show like just two weeks ago?
[SPEAKER_08]: Last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, here it is again, probably for the same fucking guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, it was.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's just exactly what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want my $8 back.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's exactly what it sounds like.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone sue him.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, let's have a class action lawsuit against that guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: for ruining all of the news sites for having such an impact on the gaming culture and the game blogs for mental anguish that someone could be that stupid
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch out or we might get sued next.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, you can't get blood out of a turnip.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't have any money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd take him to court.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd fight it all the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Check this out.
[SPEAKER_03]: If he sued us, then we could actually petition for damages for cost if this would win.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'd counter-sue.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we'd have money to advertise the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: We would.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's my thought.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'd buy a studio.
[SPEAKER_08]: In all seriousness, though, like, okay, this is the point where you relate.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, last week we were asking this, but now you really have to ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: Money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: That we call him Lord Voldemort here on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: A few folks invoking that name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, this guy is starting to make Lord Voldemort look good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, at least you kind of knew what Lord Voldemort was thinking.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, it's not like you could hire him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just so weird.
[SPEAKER_03]: I really would like to find this guy and shoot him with a water gun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to admit, I kind of want him on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Has this guy made a comment publicly?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think he's made any type of comment publicly.
[SPEAKER_08]: All these blogs are reporting on it when really he should just be banned.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you pay the town fool no mind, he will just go away and entertain himself in his house.
[SPEAKER_02]: Everybody likes the town fool that jumps around and makes an ass of himself.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: I love that movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, totally off topic and I don't care.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you hear that there's going to be a stage play soon with Nathan Lane as Gomez and Bebe Neuwirth as Morticia?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Epic epicness.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nathan Lane?
[SPEAKER_02]: I can't see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little weird, but let's face it, Raul Julia ain't here no more.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if they're going to go with this comic Broadway angle, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's a little chubby for a... You know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe he's worked out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, look.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ricky GoMac says about this guy, he just wants to get on Oprah before she's gone.
[SPEAKER_08]: This might be the way to do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then who was it that said that we should go settle this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, here it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maysatsuma.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky, sue him so you can be on the people's court.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if this guy does, for whatever reason, sue us, even though we're totally under our rights to comment on what is a public news story, for whatever wacky reason...
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember the People's Court back in the day when it was Judge Wapner
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, I remember that too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Back in the day.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: You always waited for the day he was going to send somebody to the electorate chair, but it never happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think they can.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_02]: They make an exception.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not the way TV court works, but you know, sometimes there were just those people on the show that you wish would get the death penalty.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, sir, you can't do that.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to make this exception this one time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I vote for hanging.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Part of me just wants to ban this guy from the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: Are we going to report on this guy ever again?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, you know what I want to do?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I want to publicly humiliate him.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, isn't he kind of doing that for himself?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I didn't mean it like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I meant mock, apart from just what we're doing on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, is there anything additional we could lend to the rest of the internet?
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll get Brian to help us make a little big planet level.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got $10 with your name on it because we have no money.
[SPEAKER_08]: It could be a level in LittleBigPlanet where OLR goes to the people's court with Eric.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's about our adventures of traveling to Judge Leon.
[SPEAKER_03]: We will provide a voice talent with Judge Mr. Spanky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Seriously, that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm in the mood to do something silly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm tired of making lol sims.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I want to do something funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll have to brainstorm off air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe if the chatters have an idea, you can email us at mailbagorangelinger.com, especially if you have LittleBigPlanet skills, because I'm loving this idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, ActDeft has the perfect name for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: LittleBigLawSuit.
[SPEAKER_08]: How perfect.
[SPEAKER_08]: What a perfect name for this whole story.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Castlevania, Lords of Shadow
[SPEAKER_03]: and saying that it's a big departure.
[SPEAKER_03]: So they're a little nervous about how it's going to be received.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be...
[SPEAKER_03]: A free sort of game as in you have a free roaming world.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can move through different areas.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's also supposed to be a pretty A-list voice credits added in there too.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they're a little nervous because it's going to be a different kind of Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't this the one that had Patrick Stewart in it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Ian McClellan.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: The mic's not on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turn the mic on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mic is on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: You weren't picking up for some reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, weird.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the ghost.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently.
[SPEAKER_02]: You read, I'm sorry, go back to the last story.
[SPEAKER_02]: You read what the lawsuit was about, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: about the whole fact that it takes over people's lives.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it doesn't take over people's lives.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's complaining that because the speed of which you walk or run in the game is too slow, and therefore it takes you longer to finish quests, therefore causing you to have to pay longer and longer subscriptions in order to finish the quests in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was his complaint.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's even dumber than, you know, it being addicting.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would almost not be, like, so pointing and laughing at this guy again if it weren't for the Winona Ryder and Depeche Mode subpoenas because that's where you went from just petty to batshit crazy, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Ivorite state my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I want to go back to Castlevania because I'm nervous about this new Castlevania game too because let's face it, there hasn't been, in my opinion, a really, really, really memorable, keyword memorable, Castlevania game since Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't belong in this world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Big hurrah before the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_02]: So first thing first, we've got Avatar coming out on pretty much everything on PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, Wii, and PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this PC as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I be honest with you for a minute?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: is it just me or I am so not interested in Avatar it just doesn't look good to me I'll be fair and say I realize that I'm not always into the same type of movies everybody else is but I like Terminator I like Titanic
[SPEAKER_08]: I like, you know, all these movies that James Cameron's done.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course I cried.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm looking at... I cheered.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking for... Shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at Avatar, and I'm just kind of like, oh boy.
[SPEAKER_08]: This just... It just looks bloated, long, pompous, and it doesn't look like it's going to be good to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to go see it just because it's going to be in 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be really awesome, but then if, you know, it sucks, I'll be sure to shout it to the world that it sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: The game itself is supposed to be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have been working on it for a few years at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's supposed to be good and not sucky.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see though.
[SPEAKER_08]: If my friends all come back and say it was freaking awesome, then I will go see it and maybe I'm wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll just blame the marketing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kind of with you on that because it does look kind of like it could be lame.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura just exclaimed, I love salacious pop, referring to one of our chatters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Avatar looks like Starship Troopers plus Warcraft plus The Spirits Within plus corny diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a pretty good way to sum up.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, this is my take on Avatar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, I am a big fan of Fantech.
[SPEAKER_03]: and looking into how they make it, the behind the scenes stuff, the technology going into it, the innovations that are actually being made
[SPEAKER_03]: in the CG process, in the motion capture.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's really, really interesting to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_03]: A lot of times I'll go see a movie, even if it's supposed to be the corn and crap, I will see it to see how the final product looks.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I do like a lot of movies that people hate.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love bad movies.
[SPEAKER_03]: I loved Hypercube.
[SPEAKER_03]: I loved Xanadu I love Showgirls I love Showgirls too and you got me into that movie you don't know shit but no in the end but you also know that I don't really go for the stuff that's overhyped I really avoid stuff that's overhyped but I think I'll see this one I won't see it opening week because honestly I don't want to see it that bad
[SPEAKER_03]: But I will see it after it's been in the theater for a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't mean to turn this into Avatar hate.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm so sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I had to get that out there because there was just something about it that just wasn't sitting well with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: And again, maybe it's going to be an awesome movie and I'm totally wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I love some of the comments from chat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku says, Avatar equals dances with Smurfs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dances with Smurfs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's from South Park.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I didn't see this week's episode.
[SPEAKER_08]: That must be what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then SSJ100Matt saying, I heard it's getting terrible pre-screening reviews.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, this is the time for them to fine-tune it and tailor it and what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I hope for their sake they can pull it off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, I will say this, though, at the same time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I still want to go see The Princess and the Frog because I am all about Disney going back to the way they did movies back in the 90s with Beauty and the Beast and Aladdin and all this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just because a movie is overhyped doesn't mean it's necessarily going to be bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's been zero hype for that movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: maybe it's just because I'm a Disney fan and I'll fully admit obviously I'm biased in that regard it looks good but I'm just saying there's been no hype whereas Avatar they were just like fucking your eyeballs in 2009 I don't think so you don't have kids though and I think they've been aiming this at the kids I think it'll do decent I don't think it's going to be like their huge movie but I think it'll do decent enough that they'll get back into doing 2D movies we'll see I think it'll make more than Avatar does
[SPEAKER_08]: No, it won't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Care to make a wager?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I don't, but I can tell you right now it's not gonna.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tried.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Derailed the show, my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Totally.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so other things coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rogue Warrior coming out on PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: MX vs. ATV Reflex on the DS, PSP, Wii, PC, PlayStation 3, and Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: And God, I forgot that this movie was coming out, and I really don't want to see this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alvin and the Chipmunks' Squeakquel on the Wii and DS this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why, God?
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got the Chipettes this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd rather... I would rather watch, like, Avatar...
[SPEAKER_08]: for 24 hours straight, or any... Oh, I know what I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I saw the trailer for Avatar, it looked like an M. Night Shyamalan movie to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was what didn't sit well with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I would rather than watch the new Alvin and the Chipmunks movie, I would rather watch, what was it called, The Happening, or whatever that latest... It was so horrible.
[SPEAKER_02]: You sure you weren't watching The Last Airbender, which is an M. Night Shyamalan movie?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I would rather watch The Happening five times in a row than watch the new Alvin Chipmunks movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: For the record, this is actually going back to what you're saying about The Princess and the Frog.
[SPEAKER_03]: This is from Becky.
[SPEAKER_03]: Tell Rob that I do have a kid and I actually haven't seen much about Princess and the Frog on Disney Channel yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: She's got a two-year-old who watches Phineas and Ferb, Rob.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember, I showed you some of that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: And it's great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fair enough, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess, I guess, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Once it does come out, and it hasn't come out yet, or it did come out last Friday.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Princess and Frog.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's in only New York and L.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's everywhere the 11th.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dirt 2 on PC, the very first DirectX 11 game making its way out Might and Magic Clash of Heroes on the DS this week
[SPEAKER_02]: Wreck Room, a generic party game for the Wii Storybook Workshop, the latest schlock from Konami coming out on the Wii Seven Wonders 2 on the DS for your casual game fans Safecracker, also casual game fans
[SPEAKER_02]: World Party Games, yet another generic party game out on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, next week we're going to have some really awesome stuff with Legend of Zelda Spirit Tracks and Saboteur.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: for the most part it's going to be pretty quiet the rest of the year but I will say on the PlayStation 3 they also get Assassin's Creed 2 over there and Fallout 3 again they're also getting some discounts on folklore moving into the PlayStation 3 the best or as they call it their folks soul and Ratchet and Clank's future as well as Resistance Fall of Man those are all going into the best series over in Japan
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey!
[SPEAKER_08]: They're getting it this week, though, on December 3rd.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sengoku Musou 3 comes out on the Wii as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's from Koei Entertainment.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is, I believe, another one of their strategy-type games.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's one of the... I think Romance of the Three Kingdoms?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Koei did all of those games, and I'm pretty sure this is right in that same vein.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those games are...
[SPEAKER_08]: Way more popular over there than they are here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, I will say, the game certainly is not without its fans over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the Nintendo DS, Cross Treasures.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get that out there from Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also coming out, Kaiju Busters.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_08]: And then lastly, going over to the PSP, seeing if there's anything to look forward to there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, LittleBigPlanet Portable gets its release in Japan this week, as well as Mobile Suit Gundam, Gundam vs. Gundam Next Plus.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, that sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, this one might be worth importing to some people, Phantasy Star Portable 2 comes out this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, and Jamie?
[SPEAKER_03]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Tokimeki Memorial 4 on the PSP this week.
[SPEAKER_03]: No Tokimemo for me, please.
[SPEAKER_03]: Someone in Japan send me President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about the UK?
[SPEAKER_03]: Not really a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: On the fourth we have Colin McRae, Dirt 2, like anyone cares.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have Easy Piano for DS.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then we have Avatar The Game and The Saboteur.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Tony Hawk Ride, but who plays Tony Hawk anymore?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't care how unrealistic it is, I want to grind on the moon or something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a comment from chat, did we miss Final Fantasy XIII in the release dates?
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what, it's very possible because I believe that's releasing on a day all its own, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: And I was only looking at the December 3rd dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: When is Final Fantasy XIII out in Japan?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know it's out in December.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me look up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking up its release date real quick to see if I did miss it for this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why don't we get into the next story?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll come back to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, so... December 17th.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we still have a couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why you'd play this game other than for charity, and that's what's been done.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Desert Bus for Charity, an annual event where they play the horrible, horrible game that's part of the Penn & Teller game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have raised over $100,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: In fact, they have raised $132,568.94, which is 88% over last year's total.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess a comedy troupe load-ready run.
[SPEAKER_02]: And of course, this benefits the Child's Play charity.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And apparently... 88 hours...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of driving, booked by the pre-event donations.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now it's not just one guy that has to do the whole thing, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like a comedy, people do the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to admit, I didn't get a chance to tune into the whole thing, although I read about it and I thought it was cool, but there's lots and lots of child play events going on, including Umlaut's coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had Seg on the show a couple weeks ago, and that's coming up.
[SPEAKER_08]: God, it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: Charity Marathon
[SPEAKER_03]: When we have a day off that isn't... I'm not playing that game, though, that's for sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, we won't play that game, but we've got to do our own spin on Charity Marathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Find a good charity.
[SPEAKER_03]: We still need to do the classic game stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dan and I were talking about busting out the Master System today.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I'm saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to do our classic game marathon for charity, where we let donators pick the games or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, here's what I think we should do for that, is I pick...
[SPEAKER_03]: 6 or 7 of my systems it'll be easy to shift out or whatever and then put up a list of like 12 games each so someone can say spin a wheel you get like a twister wheel okay you get this system and then spin a wheel again for the number on the list and then oh you get this game make it all completely random and go
[SPEAKER_03]: New game, move, next seat, move down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so you're kind of like musical chairs, but with games.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, like, you know, the Mad Hatter.
[SPEAKER_03]: New cup, move down.
[SPEAKER_03]: New game, move down.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, you know, usually what would be a great weekend for me is Martin Luther King weekend, because I have a holiday there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you guys do.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Jamie works for a bank, so she has everything off.
[SPEAKER_08]: But sadly, I'm going to Seattle that weekend.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have Arbor Day off.
[SPEAKER_03]: Arbor Day?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can go out and plant a tree like John Denver told us to?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, is that what you're doing?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, John Denver also, you know, flew a plane.
[SPEAKER_08]: Said he was leaving on a jet plane, and he did.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was so awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, I love it, but it was really awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was definitely, like when they say tragic irony, I think that's exactly what they meant.
[SPEAKER_03]: It wasn't really a jet plane.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a little prop plane, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: If he had been leaving on a jet plane, he probably wouldn't have crashed.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we're making John Denver jokes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: You started it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, every week here on the show, we like to do a little segment here pretty regularly.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've done it for, gosh, over a year now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It used to be like the website of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then it turned into like the DarkSakura's advice column.
[SPEAKER_08]: And now it's the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of miss doing the website of the week, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do kind of miss it, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is really fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: If I was going to do another one, though, I'd do Weebles again and make that a third time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love Weebles.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, moving on, it's now the classic video game of the week where DarkSakura digs through the classic game archive she was previously speaking of and picks out the game that she says, you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: The kids need to play this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: They need to respect their elders and they need to dust off their NESs or whatever it happens to be and go play this game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, DarkSakura, what is the game that is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_03]: A game that pisses me off sometimes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little Nemo Dream Master.
[SPEAKER_03]: Play a little bit of the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Isn't that good music?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little bit quiet, but it's very Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: One thing about Junko Tamiya is that she also did the music in Bionic Commando and in Strider, actually.
[SPEAKER_03]: So those are two notable games that had fantastic music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, and Gunsmoke.
[SPEAKER_03]: But...
[SPEAKER_03]: Back to Little Nemo.
[SPEAKER_03]: In Japan, it was called Pajama Hero Nemo.
[SPEAKER_03]: Which is pretty cute.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it's actually based off of the Little Nemo Adventures in Slumberland.
[SPEAKER_03]: The animated movie, actually, that came out based off of the comic strip from the early... I believe the original comic strip came out in, I want to say, the 1920s?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've seen, actually, an original compilation of the Little Nemo books.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, no, sorry, I take that back.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1905 was when the...
[SPEAKER_03]: The comic series first started in 1905 and then went on through 1914.
[SPEAKER_03]: The books that I saw were published in the 1920s.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you know me and book publishing, I'm all into that.
[SPEAKER_03]: So going back to this, it's about a little boy who goes into his magical dream world called Slumberland.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he can...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to be honest, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember hearing about this game when I was a kid.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I think I saw the commercials, but I never played it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So now that I'm kind of watching the video here that the music's coming off of, you know, it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, it definitely has that whole, like, the different suits of Mario, but it's...
[SPEAKER_08]: I can't explain it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just kind of have to play it yourself, I guess, or check out one of the videos of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, right now he's kind of riding a dinosaur, which kind of reminds me of something in Adventure Island.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love the dinosaur, but see, now you, for certain abilities that you get with some suits or some animals, you lose other, like, for example, you see he could, like, for example, the frog or, I think it's either a frog or a dragon or something, but he can do like a belly slap, like a belly splash move and land on them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um, and he, if his belly lands on the creatures, then he can actually knock them out of the sky, you know, to damage, um, I think that's the creature on the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it looks like a little, like, kind of gecko-looking thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, but he can, he can pop them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, but, like, you can get a mole, and you can dig, or you can get a gorilla and punch them, or climb up the walls.
[SPEAKER_03]: The purple little lizard thing, I think it's like a salamander or something, but it can walk up walls, you know, like a lizard can.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, good lord.
[SPEAKER_03]: and as you were watching some of this they actually are hidden like you had to actually in the first level if you get the mole you actually have to go all the way over as far as you can through the dirt to the left and then go down through the floor to where two little blocks of of area that you can dig through to get underneath to another place where you get the key and a one up and some other crap um so uh
[SPEAKER_03]: You have to have the right animals to get to some places, but if you don't really have everything, and on top of that, your animals have different lifeforms than Nemo does, so sometimes you have to really be judicious with what you have to make it through.
[SPEAKER_03]: So actually, I'd have to say it's one of the harder NES games there are, and it's a cute game.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I would go that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, again, like you said, it was released by Capcom.
[SPEAKER_03]: The year that it came out was in 1990, so I was actually just starting high school.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, no, I was in 8th grade.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, no, you were in 8th grade.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I remember...
[SPEAKER_03]: Having a fit over this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had it when it came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I would just... I don't think... I think this is actually one game to this day I haven't beaten.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, that's an indication.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I've beaten a lot of games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Once again, Jamie, a very popular pick in our chatroom, at least those that have played it, but a lot of folks agreeing with you on the difficulty that it was a bitch.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree with Ricky GoMac that the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles game on NES, that game was freaking difficult too.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game pissed me off to the point that I wanted to throw it down the stairs and I did and actually it lived through it and I can still play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was actually one game I had that was duct taped.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_08]: She'll have to do that another week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a different game altogether.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, that game is not going to make it on my list.
[SPEAKER_03]: That game is not going to make it on my list because to this day, I'm still angry.
Angry, Rob, angry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm thinking one day we need to do the anti-classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game that DarkSakura says, do not play this game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's terrible.
[SPEAKER_03]: I could tell you what that is right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: In fact, I'll go ahead and mention it right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess we're done with Little Nemo then?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, Little Nemo, the Dream Master, your classic game of the week on the NES.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a game that is so bad that Dan and I rented it from Blockbuster because we were really into renting games every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was about right before the Dreamcast came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, around 98, 99.
[SPEAKER_03]: We rented... We were also into wrestling games at the time because the WrestleMania 2000 came out on the Nintendo 64, which was rad.
[SPEAKER_03]: We...
[SPEAKER_03]: got NWO Thunder and we got it home we played it for about 10 minutes and called Blockbuster and said we just rented this game about 30 minutes ago because we had to drive back we want our money back or can we change it out for something else and we went in there and the guy was like oh yeah I remember you if it's that bad then yeah we'll change it out it was so bad that Blockbuster let us change out our rental
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that's just good customer service, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was... It probably wasn't the first time they got out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kept Spice World longer than that game, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I loved Spice World.
[SPEAKER_03]: And yes, I rented Spice World.
[SPEAKER_08]: There were some lulzy moments in Spice World.
[SPEAKER_08]: You just make Baby Spice do backflips over and over.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've bought games that are arguably bad games, and I liked them better than that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's probably the worst game I've ever rented.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say the worst video game experience I ever had was when I got Tetris Plus on the PlayStation 1.
[SPEAKER_08]: What a colossal letdown that game was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tetris was so huge at the time, you know, especially on the NES, and I think everybody very fondly remembers that game, and it's been done very well on many platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: The DS has an awesome version of Tetris.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even Tengen Tetris is pretty good and kind of reminiscent of the arcade version, but I'll tell you what, Tetris Plus, which was by, and I remember to this day, Jellico, did it on the PlayStation 1, and it is horrific.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is bad, it is terrible, because they changed the game mechanic of Tetris, and it was one of those things where I spent, like, I bought it, because I was like, oh, it's Tetris, how can it be bad?
[SPEAKER_08]: I hated it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played it once and I said, how can you fuck with the main game mechanic of Tetris?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because what they did is they changed it so it was like a little professor that would walk along the top and you didn't want him to hit the- I remember that!
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh my god, that was awful!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a terrible, terrible game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was hideous!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not alone.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: That deserves- Wah, wah, wah, wah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I need to fire up the Price is Right losing horn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're idyllic.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that game is an enemy of the Daleks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, traumatically bad video game experience?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything you can remember?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, there's not really anything horribly bad that I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: I always used to find some sort of good out of it, I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, aren't you just like the Mother Teresa of video games?
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Ball GT Final Battle, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: What was so terrible about that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, keep in mind, it was like the first Dragon Ball game that came out in the U.S., unless you want to count the Dragon Ball RPG that they made into something else over here, which doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_03]: It had the awful, awful American voice acting, and it was just...
[SPEAKER_03]: I still don't regret the trade I loved Blue Stinger
[SPEAKER_03]: Isn't that Twinbee or something?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, Stinger was Twinbee.
[SPEAKER_03]: Blue Stinger was the game that came out.
[SPEAKER_03]: The Japanese version of that one was sort of lauded because it had a movie director directing the cameras and cinematics in the movie.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not in the movie, in the game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But when it came out over here, they butchered the camera.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because people were like, oh, we can't control it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was like, I did just fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was a little kind of survival horror type of game.
[SPEAKER_03]: But it was a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, we're going to take a break, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to rest our voices here a minute and refill our waters and run to the restroom and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But when we come back on Orange Lounge Radio, we're going to get into Part B. We've got plenty more news for you guys tonight, a lot of rapid-fire news, including some updates on Red Dead Redemption, Uncharted 2, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we're going to get into some other stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to talk Tron in Part B.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, so definitely stay tuned for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, when we start Part B, I can just go greetings programs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, if you really want to.
[SPEAKER_08]: And at the end, you can say end of line.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, end of line.
[SPEAKER_08]: At the very end of tonight's show, I want you to say end of line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, can we do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like after the credits and everything?
[SPEAKER_08]: End of line.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should do it before the credits.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll do it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: And a proper sequel to Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not Galactrix, but something else.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to talk all that in Part B. So stay tuned, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll be back in just a little bit with more of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_08]: by the way we do tape live of course every Sunday night at All Games Radio www.allgames.com where there's lots of great programming all throughout the week check out the buffet of great game programming they have here and you know what and I always say if OLR you're finding this show just isn't your taste hey no harm done but there might be a show that is more your taste throughout the various independent podcasters that broadcast over there at All Games Radio so check it out
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to move on and get into some of the rapid-fire news tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we'll move into Twitter topics right after that for those of you guys who asked us questions on Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then we got some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Loki, why don't you start us off with some rapid-fire news?
[SPEAKER_02]: Red Dead Redemption Red Dead Redemption Red Dead Redemption Red Dead Redemption Red Dead Redemption
[SPEAKER_02]: Uncharted 2 The Fort
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's a Fortress multiplayer map from Chapter of Drake's Fortune.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, may the fort be with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, and it's free, so you can't beat free.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then finally, Valve is selling some Team Fortress 2 and Left 4 Dead themed greeting cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: Those look kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if those are actual greeting cards or if they're like e-cards or something like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, they are real cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can actually pick those up at the Valve Software Store at store.valvesoftware.com and check them out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They are a little pricey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looks like $16.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm not sure how many you get in that, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: How many portal jokes in the Christmas cards?
[SPEAKER_02]: None.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Zero portal jokes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, moving on to some other rapid fire news I have for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a whole lot of Rock Band news going on, as there usually is, because every week they try to add something new, and this week there's more Nirvana coming to the 360 Wii and PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Come As You Are, the MTV Unplugged version, which I think is kind of interesting, is coming out for Rock Band, as well as Lithium and Smells Like Teen Spirit, finally!
[SPEAKER_08]: All in Nirvana Pack 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also the band Night Ranger.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can still rock in America.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't tell me you love me, and you're going to hear it from me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Night Ranger!
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I'm laughing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, a member of Night Ranger was in Damn Yankees with Ted Nugent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Rock Band platform, by the way, now has over 1,000 songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: 390 different musical artists.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, we have collectively downloaded over 60 million songs from the Rock Band store.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody's making a shitload of money.
[SPEAKER_08]: 105 consecutive weeks of new additions to the store.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, that's pretty impressive.
[SPEAKER_08]: And they actually did some math and figured out that if you wanted to play through the entire catalog, that would take two days...
[SPEAKER_08]: 18 hours and 40 minutes to play through the entire catalog, which I think I wanted to read some.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought I read somewhere some guy was doing for charity.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Good luck to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, back when they were really good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, by the way, the games you can play there on Atari, you can play Asteroids, Adventure, Battlezone, Crystal Castles, Lunar Lander, and yes, Yars' Revenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: By the way, I used to love Crystal Castles.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't like the Atari 2600 version, though, nearly as much as the arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think you'll like it, for one thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a trackball.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's the way it's meant to be played.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've got a 2600 trackball.
[SPEAKER_08]: Lastly, some game controller Christmas tree ornaments are available and I guess they're making their way around the different game blogs and you can get them, it looks like, at ponoko.com P-O-N-O-K-O dot com.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's $25 plus $10 for shipping or more if it's somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can get some various game controller themed.
[SPEAKER_08]: It looks like there's an old school NES controller and a Wiimote
[SPEAKER_08]: Dreamcast Controller, Gettin' the Love, and of course, Where Would You Be Without a DualShock Controller.
[SPEAKER_08]: So all of that is there in the Game Controller Christmas tree for those of you that are going to be decorating.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what do you have for us tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, I've got good stuff.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, kind of good stuff, because...
[SPEAKER_03]: There actually is a statement by Harada Katsuhiro, who is the producer behind Tekken 6, say that there's going to have more content on its way via download content, but that they're not going to charge for it or they don't intend to charge for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: There could be, there's a, and this is a quote, strong possibility of additional download content.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, you know, then again, they've said that before and have kind of lied.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: Didn't they say like, oh no, we didn't put Darth Vader in the Xbox Soul Calibur.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no, we didn't do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then like, psych.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, also, about the Games Convention Online, you remember that?
[SPEAKER_03]: They're doing another one.
[SPEAKER_03]: and it will be from July 8th through 11th, 2010 at the Leipziger Messe in Germany.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope I pronounced that right.
[SPEAKER_03]: I took German for two weeks, sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But they got 43,000 attendees last year, so they're hoping that with another day they can get more.
[SPEAKER_03]: So hey, good for them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And lastly, and this is something I'm pretty happy about, Bayonetta demo.
[SPEAKER_03]: We should be getting it in Europe and North America on December 3rd.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that will be freaking fantastic.
[SPEAKER_08]: LittleBirdie told me you can get it early if you know where to look.
[SPEAKER_03]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was through GameSpot.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're like a member over there, you can get a code generated, something like that, for the demo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't had a chance to check it out myself because, again, I got a Bork 360 that I've been too lazy to replace.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, this, folks, is why you need to create a Japanese region account so that you can download these region-free demos to your 360 or PlayStation 3 way early.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have one for every region on the PlayStation 3 and I have one for Japanese and US and my 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just putting it out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, let's move on to some Twitter topics and some things that you guys are asking us on the Twitter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, if you don't already have us on Twitter, you should really consider adding us.
[SPEAKER_08]: www.twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: We always take messages before every show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Starting off with Spazinator tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: How about a discussion of some of the better PC exclusives out there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Must-owns.
[SPEAKER_08]: For example, recommendations.
[SPEAKER_08]: With me getting a PC not too long from now, I'd like to know what to get above and beyond WoW.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bummer, because WoW would have been the first thing I suggested it would be.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, a lot of MMOs.
[SPEAKER_08]: We haven't really seen console MMOs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Granted, Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know the PS3 has some in development.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, there's going to be a lot of stuff in the spring.
[SPEAKER_08]: Supposedly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unless it, you know, gets...
[SPEAKER_08]: But right now, you know, the Guild Wars, the City of Heroes, the Aion, the Champions, the Star Trek Online, none of those are on the console, nor are they going to be on the console.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, all those types of MMOs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a lot of stuff in the pipes, just not quite out yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, anything you can think of as far as PC games go?
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as PC MMOs?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, just PC games in general that are exclusive that you can't get on the console.
[SPEAKER_02]: Command & Conquer 4 is going to be exclusively on PC at first at least.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not positive on that, but I know that's coming out in the fall and I haven't heard about a console version yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: X-Link suggests Civilization 4 and I give that a hell yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Civilization series is outstanding and they did do like kind of a dumbed down version of Civilization called Civ Revolution for the Xbox 360 and PS3 although I will say Civ Revolution I liked.
[SPEAKER_08]: It kind of reminded me of the very first Civilization game so when I say dumbed down I don't mean that in a negative way.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you like that game definitely Civ 4.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a great suggestion from X-Link in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on to some other questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like this one from Fernando on Twitter and this is a good one for Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will there ever be an installment of Grand Theft Auto where you play a female and would it sell?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it would, and I hope there is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, hell, they've done it with Saints Row, where you can play as a female character throughout that game, and it works pretty well.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may remember before when people were putting out fake screenshots for Grand Theft Auto 4, it had a female wheeling a mace, and that looked pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why it couldn't happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Red Dead Redemption Red Dead Redemption
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to see that, dude, I would say email them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you know what I got to say?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think Rockstar has been pretty decent about, you know, kind of an equal opportunity, if you will.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I'm sure they're about the story and the art they're trying to go for first.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if they can work it in for a female protagonist, they will.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, let's see...
[SPEAKER_08]: Looking at this one from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nathan Drake gets supersized for Thanksgiving weekend and sends us this over.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently the Uncharted developers...
[SPEAKER_08]: made Nathan Drake look fat during Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: They made him gain a few pounds there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that something that was actually in the game, or is that just screenshots?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I guess that's just something they rendered, those screenshots.
[SPEAKER_08]: That wasn't actually in the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be funny if you played it on Thanksgiving.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be kind of funny, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: So Obama and apparently the LittleBigPlanet team are teaming up for kids.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the White House, they basically announced that they're going to have a program to improve science and math education with a variety of different entertainment software association-backed initiatives, including a program to put LittleBigPlanet in libraries, as well as $300,000 in game design challenges.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I mean, hell, LittleBigPlanet,
[SPEAKER_02]: Very flexible with what you can do with it, and it's supposedly pretty easy to learn.
[SPEAKER_02]: I still haven't actually sat down to try and make a level, even though I really wanted to.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's fucking hard!
[SPEAKER_08]: It takes a lot of dedication.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just because we're older, that's why.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe, maybe, but that's why I invited the gentleman on the show earlier tonight, because I know it's not easy to have that kind of dedication.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was kind of awesome, and then to have it all take off, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, they said, you know, the Sony LittleBigPlanet initiative, Game Changers, is part of a $2 million 2010 digital media and learning competition funded by the MacArthur Foundation and involves Sony donating 1,000 PlayStation 3s and copies of the LittleBigPlanet to libraries and committee organizations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Participants will strive to create levels that involve science, technology, engineering, and math.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, engineering, health, physics, and...
[SPEAKER_02]: The second program is called the STEM Nation Video Game Competition.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a three-pronged $300,000 contest encouraging entrants to create the best browser video games that teach the STEM disciplines for a trio of ages 4-8, 8-12, and 12-16.
[SPEAKER_02]: The competitions intend to reach historically underserved populations including girls and minority students according to the ESA press release.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's kind of neat
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of interesting, especially the whole fact that video games usually get a bad rap.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, ironically, and I swear I didn't plan this, I'm wearing my ECA shirt today with the controllers on it that says, contrary to popular opinion, these do not make me a killer.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, video games get such a bad rap usually out there that games like Manhunt 2 are going to turn us all into murderers and all this garbage.
[SPEAKER_02]: And if I remember correctly, the unedited, unrated...
[SPEAKER_02]: PC version came out and the world did not end.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it really didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so it's kind of neat to see video games being embraced in this regard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think this is something that people will actually really get into and it will be a successful program?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't see why it can't be.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, hell, we grew up on Oregon Trail and number munchers and shit like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just kind of an evolved version of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember we had...
[SPEAKER_02]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: They wouldn't do something like this where, you know, challenge people to kind of learn how to use computers and learn how to, you know, build stuff in video games and whatnot to kind of help promote education and, you know, their agendas with the science and math programs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it sounds like a good idea to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a way to reach children at a level that they're, you know, going to be interested in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_08]: Logo, the programming language, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Forward 30, right 90, forward 30, right 90, to draw a square and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey Jamie, Tron.
Tron!
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, if you want to see more information about Tron, you're going to have to watch the VGAs.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, the Spike Video Game Awards apparently is going to have some new Tron information here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess this is not about the movie, this is about the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: The game based on the movie?
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, yeah, the game that's based on the new movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's actually a little teaser that went up, and it looks like the game might actually just be called Tron.
[SPEAKER_08]: You might remember...
[SPEAKER_08]: They tried relaunching Tron a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a Tron 2.0 video game I remember that came out.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was pretty cool, but it didn't do very well at all, which is kind of unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, there's movie sequels coming out called Tron Legacy, and apparently more information is going to come out at the Spike Video Game Awards.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that'll be on Saturday, December 12th.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, very, very brief teaser that's hit the internet recently.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if Jamie's seen it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to pull it up here in studio so she can kind of get a peek here at what it looks like.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if it's going to play very well here.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you just see somebody... Virus detected.
[SPEAKER_08]: Motorbikes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And remember...
[SPEAKER_08]: Light Cycles, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, Light Cycles.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember the Spike TV Video Game Awards.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's also your chance to vote for the most anticipated game where you get to write in your own choice and perhaps President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, we did try to start something on the Facebook and Twitter to get everybody to write in President Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we do hope it makes a clip package.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what we're hoping for, is that when they introduce who wins this award, they do some type of clip package for all the anticipated things.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't think it'll win, realistically.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not on the ballot.
[SPEAKER_08]: But maybe it'll make the clip package, and that's really all we ask.
[SPEAKER_08]: We want it's 15 frames of fame on Spike TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't you want to be the one to send that tweet over to Rina Wee and let them know, hey, did you know your video game was on TV in America?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've still been spamming it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, how about some stuff about another game?
[SPEAKER_03]: Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: I never played Puzzle Quest, so I couldn't really tell you anything about the sequel.
[SPEAKER_03]: But there is...
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually don't really know much about Puzzle Quest Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought you had played this before, the Puzzle Quest game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Huh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I played Peggle.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was Galactrix that came out that was supposed to be some type of sequel to Puzzle Quest, but it wasn't really because it had this whole, it was based around hexagons.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, I was looking at the screen capture going, what am I looking at?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Bejeweled, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Ye Olde Bejeweled, basically.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then, that also isn't 100% fair, because especially Puzzle Quest had all these different other elements in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, when you first play it, you're kind of like, oh, it's Bejeweled with attacks, but then you have to get into...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: My wife did too.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your wife was into this too, huh?
[SPEAKER_03]: I think I was also busy playing Marvel Ultimate Alliance.
[SPEAKER_08]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Puzzle Quest 2, I guess, is now going to be a proper sequel to the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I don't know exactly what type of stuff is going to be in it, but there's an early screenshot that's leaked out there, and apparently the game is in development for the 360, it looks like?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it looks like colors and some ogres and some guy with a sword.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now it's interesting though because there's some new icons here I haven't seen before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like there's these different colored skulls, although one of them says plus three, so maybe they just changed the color.
[SPEAKER_08]: But then there's these fists, and I don't know what that's all about.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's no more gold icons either.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maybe it means a hand comes out of the screen and punches a player in the face.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Puzzle Quest is a fun game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Galactrix couldn't get into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was just a whole different way of thinking.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, there you go.
[SPEAKER_03]: I saw there was a Neopets one, and I just wanted to laugh.
[SPEAKER_03]: People still play Neopets?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me rephrase.
[SPEAKER_08]: People over 13 still play Neopets?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: No one plays Neopets.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's all... It's all Gaia.
[SPEAKER_02]: All a hoax.
[SPEAKER_03]: Everyone's using Gaia now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, it has been confirmed that the trailer for Mercs Inc., the brand new game, is actually legit.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's being developed now, not by Pandemic, since, well, they kind of closed.
[SPEAKER_02]: And EA Los Angeles is actually going to be working on that game, and it will be a multiplayer, or at least have multiplayer in it, release.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: because it was so buggy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'd like to exploit those buggy games, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say as much shit as you give a game like Driver 3 here on the show, you'd love to play that game because it was so bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And same with Mercenaries 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just so buggy, but it's hilarious because you'll just be watching and feel like, what just happened there, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt says, I've gotten more non-gamers hooked on Peggle than Puzzle Quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: Peggle for the win.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Peggle.
[SPEAKER_08]: I liked Puzzle Quest too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Peggle is my number one I'm stuck somewhere board game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like Peggle because it reminds me of Plinko.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's why I like Peggle.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, that's actually the same thought that I had about it, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who didn't want to play Plinko whenever you watched that on The Price is Right?
[SPEAKER_03]: But Peggle is so fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like, I'm actually working on the challenge modes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've beaten one of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, the extra orange.
[SPEAKER_08]: You gotta beat more than one.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Keep trying.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I've been doing them.
[SPEAKER_08]: After Burner Climax
[SPEAKER_08]: Both systems, 360 and PSN.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, don't know if this game will hit both platforms.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would assume it would.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exclusives are very few and far between these days.
[SPEAKER_03]: If they're going to bring After Burner Climax, which, by the way, they had it at John's Incredibly Sucky Pizza.
[SPEAKER_03]: I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_03]: That was so fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I would wish that they would bring out Planet Harrier.
[SPEAKER_08]: And by the way, for those that don't know, After Burner Climax is an arcade cabinet that's like old school After Burner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Except better!
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but, you know, now it was modernized, basically.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, yeah, it has like a full hydraulic seat in it that moves and turns and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which, sadly, you won't be able to install in your chair.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, if you're Loki, he'll make one out of duct tape and cardboard boxes somehow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will not make any chairs.
[SPEAKER_03]: And ballpoint pens.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because you have to use the little springs of the ballpoint pen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_03]: But, like, if they can bring this out, why can't they bring out Planet Harrier?
[SPEAKER_03]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: They hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Planet Harry or Sega?
[SPEAKER_08]: So check for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be coming soon if the ratings boards are to believed, which they usually are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just so you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are those things ever wrong?
[SPEAKER_03]: Red Entertainment's funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why?
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: To quote, After Burner Climax, is that what happens when Maverick ejaculates?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what's in the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, speaking of Redertainment, dear OLR, first of all, thank you for updating the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_03]: Between these episodes, the other podcasts I listen to, the music I've recently pirated, I have enough entertainment to last me for the rest of the year at work.
[SPEAKER_03]: What, a whole month?
[SPEAKER_03]: Second, can you send me the link for the article from last week about the guy marrying the DS character?
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I call bullshit.
[SPEAKER_03]: A guy marrying a character from a DS game in Guam.
[SPEAKER_03]: The part about Guam alone screams bullshit to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now, on to the reason I'm emailing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Recently, many of us have been sick, including SkyDarkSakura and myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: When you are sick at home, you need things to entertain you.
[SPEAKER_03]: These things can include video games.
[SPEAKER_03]: What video games do you suggest for someone who is sick at home?
[SPEAKER_03]: This game should preferably need little input, doesn't agitate you much, and can be frequently paused...
[SPEAKER_03]: to enable you to visit the bathroom slash sickness... sick room on a frequent basis.
[SPEAKER_03]: My suggestion is to get to ride on the Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_03]: Little input is required.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's entertaining without being agitating and can be paused at any time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I say peggle on the iPhone because you can take it with you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I gotta be honest, when I was home for a week with swine flu and all that, I wasn't really playing video games at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, because I didn't want to think.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched movies.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was more my time to catch up on movies and TV shows.
[SPEAKER_03]: When I'm sick, really, I watch The Muppet Show.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_02]: Diapers!
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_03]: By the present... Eating, shitting, crying, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And trying to figure out what this big blur in front of its face is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do a favor.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buy diapers.
[SPEAKER_03]: For mommy.
[SPEAKER_03]: For baby.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because diapers are expensive and you need a lot of them.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I only know this because I know mommies.
[SPEAKER_03]: Buy diapers.
[SPEAKER_03]: And butt paste, just because it's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ha ha ha!
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously, whenever I go to a baby shower, I make sure that I do like a care basket and put butt paste in it because I just want an excuse to buy something called butt paste.
[SPEAKER_08]: It makes it sound like it's going to glue it shut.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's for diaper rash.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know what it's for, but it's just funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: The name is hilarious, butt paste.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, just the way it rolls off the tongue.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you say it anymore on the show tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Rob, give it a try.
[SPEAKER_07]: Butt paste.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, isn't that great?
[SPEAKER_07]: Knock, knock.
[SPEAKER_03]: Who's there?
[SPEAKER_03]: But Paste.
[SPEAKER_03]: See, that's funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's not funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just not.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_03]: But Paste.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: This was brought to you by Stay Care Redertainment.
[SPEAKER_03]: This message has been brought to you by Prayer, the preferred birth control method of the state of Utah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now that is hilarious.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh, a long one from Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi folks!
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi Spazinator!
[SPEAKER_03]: I just thought I'd send you three this email just in case I accidentally fall asleep like I did last week, dammit, and end up not calling as a result.
[SPEAKER_03]: I initially intended to pass the following information along to other listeners out there who have been following my situation for the past two weeks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just thought I'd give a little detailed information.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, the Monday afternoon after OLR's episode 244 aired live two weeks ago, I placed two phone calls to Sony's customer service number.
[SPEAKER_03]: The initial call, as you may have suspected, didn't go well.
[SPEAKER_03]: I had explained my situation as clearly and calmly as I could after put...
[SPEAKER_03]: After being put on hold for an insanely long time, I was told that they couldn't do anything for me.
[SPEAKER_03]: It goes without saying that this tidbit of info did not sit well with me, and I was not about to let it just drop.
[SPEAKER_03]: If need be, I was prepared to be a major thorn in their sides until something was done.
[SPEAKER_03]: Short while later, I had placed a second call to Sony and had asked to speak with a supervisor.
[SPEAKER_03]: The customer service rep that initially answered the call took down some basic info and connected me with a supervisor who, if I remember correctly, was named Gerald.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I just interview real quick and say, usually when you get put on hold for a long length of time, and you would know this too, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you worked in a call center for a while, and I trained for one and have for many years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually it's not because they just want to sit there and not do anything while they have you on hold.
[SPEAKER_08]: Usually they don't know the answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're trying to find out.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's usually why you're on hold for so long.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not all the time, but usually.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, well, I'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Where I worked, we actually would have, and reps would be marked down for this, that they'd have a two-minute hold time maximum.
[SPEAKER_03]: And...
[SPEAKER_03]: www.DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: to our reps on the phone.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or we would also take the escalated calls, you know, the pissed off people, which I loved.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was good at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: But anyway, we... But we'd always go back and say, hey, you've had this person on hold for this long.
[SPEAKER_03]: Go let them know that you're still talking to somebody.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, and any call center I've been in contact with has a very similar policy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony probably doesn't need one because customer service probably isn't their top priority.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate to say it, but, you know, they don't need it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sadly, they're the only people to make the PS3.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, customer service is not probably their forte.
[SPEAKER_03]: Although... But in some cases, too, like when I was actually on the floor doing calls, I would actually run and go to the source of something, which we weren't technically supposed to do, but I knew everybody in the other department.
[SPEAKER_03]: So sometimes you may have just someone who's in the know and knows where to go to find out what you need.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, give them the benefit of the doubt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_03]: However, moving forward, again, for what seemed like the trillionth time, I explained as clearly as I could in detail what the situation was and conveyed how upset I was that I no longer was able to use the content that I had paid tons of money for.
[SPEAKER_03]: I also mentioned how aggravated I was due to how previous calls went.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimately, the supervisor agreed to allow me to re-download my paid content again as a one-time deal.
[SPEAKER_03]: He also made a point to mention that it would take a few days for everything to fully show up on my download queue due to two factors-
[SPEAKER_03]: 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bought a lot of stuff and 2.
[SPEAKER_03]: They had to go through it all and reauthorize it manually so needless to say it was going to take some time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Considering all that I had profusely thanked the supervisor and told him that I was thankful for this.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ultimately everything started showing up on my list late Tuesday night which I started downloading.
[SPEAKER_03]: The first wave basically took all day to fully download.
[SPEAKER_03]: The second wave occurred roughly at the same time the following night and again took a considerable amount of time even with high speed cable.
[SPEAKER_03]: Needless to say two weeks later I now have all my content back.
[SPEAKER_03]: I looked out this time, but if, God forbid, next time I may not necessarily be so lucky.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this email is just a little on the long side.
[SPEAKER_03]: Considering that as of late the mailbag has been a little light, I figured you three wouldn't necessarily mind too much.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks again for your input and help in the whole situation.
[SPEAKER_03]: Believe me, it's greatly appreciated.
[SPEAKER_03]: And that's from Spazinator.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, he typed this whole thing, I think, on the PlayStation browser.
[SPEAKER_03]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's impressive.
[SPEAKER_03]: So yeah, very good, very few errors.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm quite proud of you.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: My graphics card from my computer is coming soon and I'm sure everyone will want to see the room you guys broadcast from.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: You do not want to see the disaster this room is right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say I did take a picture of the mixing board and I took a picture of
[SPEAKER_02]: I also uploaded my photos of the cardboard slash cabinet Oh really, you got those up there?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh sweet It doesn't look like much yet because I just took a few quick pictures and they're probably not even I don't know, I just took a few in case I ever wanted to explain how I made it Oh god, there it is, your cardboard box with buttons Amazing Sorry Jamie No it's fine Better in person
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you should color it with magic marker.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know, really.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or a paint pen or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: That'd be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I originally wanted to just do it just in plain cardboard.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: Electrical tape.
[SPEAKER_03]: Get that cool vinyl look to it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have duct tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking of wrapping some of it in duct tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Use colored duct tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's going to look very ghetto when it's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's going to be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anyway, actually this room is ready for a complete cleanup because I have these storage bins that have been sitting here on the floor forever and I'm ready to start using them.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, to let anyone know too, this is sort of related, I'm getting rid of a whole bunch of manga and different books, including a few, I think I'm going to get rid of my Gothic and Lolita magazines, so if anyone wants them, let me know, we'll work something out.
[SPEAKER_03]: But back to the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, also when Loki's arcade cabinet works, maybe we could see Loki drunk playing Daytona USA.
[SPEAKER_03]: Haha, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm writing this from my Blackberry at Christmas party, so I better go.
[SPEAKER_03]: But before I go, and this is by the way halfway through the email.
[SPEAKER_03]: Before I go, I hope you guys check out Fallout 3 or even Fallout 1.
[SPEAKER_03]: I recommend that you guys play Fallout 1 first since the third one is in first person and I know how DarkSakura gets motion sick.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aw, thank you, that's so sweet.
[SPEAKER_03]: Also, I think it's free to play on GameTap.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um,
[SPEAKER_03]: The third one has a game of the year edition now with all five downloaded content packs that I highly recommend anyone who hasn't played a Fallout game.
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, Becky's husband has Fallout 3 and I saw him play some of it and it looked really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: Like I said, I wouldn't be able to do too much of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Not to mention how much of a deal it is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I hope you guys check those out now.
[SPEAKER_03]: If you'll excuse me, I've got gifts to open.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sent from my Verizon Wireless Blackberry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got regular email, a Crackberry, and a PSP all tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm going to double check and see if we've got any more just because I'm nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: Clank.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to send in an email, mailbag at orangelaunchradio.com is the place to send them.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for now, it's time for us to get a little bit angsty here on the program because, you know, sometimes things piss us off.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so a special holiday edition of the FUs of the Week.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what's on your mind tonight that you want to get off your chest?
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact that I still need to, um, F you to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I still need to do the faceplate that we were going to autograph.
[SPEAKER_08]: F you!
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_03]: And you know, I had it set out.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll get it.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, but still, I feel bad about myself because I just remembered it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And also, um, a secondary F you to me for not actually cleaning my room today.
[SPEAKER_03]: Or yesterday.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: I came home very intoxicated last night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_03]: My car is over at Becky's house.
[SPEAKER_03]: She will be bringing it to me and I will be taking her home.
[SPEAKER_03]: So F you to me and Boddington's Ale.
[SPEAKER_08]: But bless you for doing the right thing and not driving home drunk.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the right thing to do.
[SPEAKER_03]: Because I'm amazing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: F you to burning myself on my finger with a soldering iron.
[SPEAKER_02]: I decided for some reason to grab the tip of the soldering iron to move it to the side.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not smart.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why I did that and was like, ow, as it sizzled.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, maybe I'm the only one not giving an FU to myself tonight, although it does have to kind of do with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU to my back, because I don't know what I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I might have slept on it wrong or something, but it's been hurting me for like a week, and it sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Back pain's never any fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just makes me remember that I'm getting old.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU to getting old.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know a lot of you people listening to this show are like, I'm 21 now, I'm old.
[SPEAKER_08]: FU!
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait about 10 years, then I'll tell you.
[SPEAKER_08]: of course then again a lot of my friends that are in their 40s would say I'm being just as big of a whiner so what can you do age is just a number Loki, why don't you give us another story and then just a couple more stories here we're going to make our way to the Skype line where you guys can give us a call at 1-877-GAME-OLR or of course our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio so we'll have that open very soon just after a couple more stories
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, apparently not to delay themselves from jumping on the bandwagon too late, Microsoft has decided to go ahead and patent their own Xbox 360 hint system, very similar to what we saw with the Super Guide on the Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: You may remember that the first game that had that was New Super Mario Bros.,
[SPEAKER_02]: This new patent, though, it doesn't really say what they're going to do exactly, but it's going to have some more guides and digital brief audio commentaries or stuff that adds portions of the screen that give you hints and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's just kind of a generic system that maybe they're going to include in some games going forward to make them more approachable for casual gamers.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have I heard this before?
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's a neat idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: We kind of gave the whole hint system crap for the Wii and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was going to be the staple CC button.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was so behind the scenes stuff, it really shouldn't have been even brought up.
[SPEAKER_08]: In other words, people were reading way too much into the trademark and the patent documents.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, to be fair, we've also only seen it implemented in one game.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't know what it's going to look like in the next Zelda game or some other games that Nintendo might have in the future, just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, maybe a lot of us jumped the gun and that's what happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I don't know, do you think Xbox 360 is just like, hey, Nintendo's got a good idea, let's copy it, or do you think they're really going in a different direction with this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think they're just trying to kind of...
[SPEAKER_02]: Take the same approach, not necessarily just because Nintendo did it, but maybe had the same ideas.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, to be fair, Microsoft kind of does this sort of thing very well where somebody's got an idea, they sort of take it and make it better.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, they're trying to kind of broaden themselves out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They kind of have the opposite problem as Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Nintendo, they're really trying to broaden the audience so much so that they don't really have any core games for the core gamer, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: But
[SPEAKER_08]: Alienware computers are coming now pre-loaded with Steam
[SPEAKER_08]: Alienware is now actually bundling with their all-powerful systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: These actually, I gotta admit, they're kind of cool looking, the whole black and red thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, if you're gonna pay that much money for a system, it might as well look kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so if you buy one of these all-powerful systems, they're actually shipping with Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: Steam comes on these systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: Part of the reason why is because Portal is a free game that's included, which of course was a Valve game that they did release through Steam.
[SPEAKER_08]: I actually bought, that was the very first game I ever bought through Steam was Portal.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, no, second game because I bought AudioSurf too.
[SPEAKER_08]: But regardless, Steam is now coming in bundled with these systems.
[SPEAKER_08]: Which for these box systems is not really new news.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know I talked about earlier, and it's funny kind of to bring this full circle because Jamie had a story earlier about Steamworks and I was saying like, aren't those like Google Toolbars and all that other crap that tries to install with the program kind of annoying?
[SPEAKER_08]: But this, you sort of grow to expect that when you buy these computers in a box, they come preloaded with tons of crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bloatware.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's... What do they call that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I've never heard of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bloatware.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a good term for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, you know, the antivirus demo is installed and the trial of Microsoft Office is already on the computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: So this honestly just seems like another logical step to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is kind of a kick in the groin to the competitors like, you know, direct-to-drive and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: But what are you going to do?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess you could say the Microsoft Office has its competitors too.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, you know, they get to jump up on some of these...
[SPEAKER_08]: and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our chat room for some comments at chat.orangelongerator.com Salacious Pop says Alienware has a build your own shopping cart a la the Apple site where you can build a system for $7,000 without really trying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku says Skyid is hella cheaper to build your own PC than to buy from Alienware.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can they be as pretty though?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I gotta say those systems are very nice looking.
[SPEAKER_02]: You'd be surprised what you can find in cases nowadays.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although I've got to say, the new computer we've got for the show is pretty sleek looking.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a nice looking little box.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that wasn't even trying.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't light up pretty, but it looks nicer than the one I've got for myself.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nowadays, it's almost hard to find a case that doesn't light up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Seriously, my computer at the time, I think, cost me $1,700.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I put in...
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: I really don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm looking at some of the other comments here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft says, the general consumer doesn't know how to build a computer and will go for something that's already built.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's clearly where they're making their money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tigerclaw says, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is more important, the way the case looks or the performance of the system?
[SPEAKER_08]: I choose the latter.
[SPEAKER_08]: And no, in all seriousness, and for myself and not playing devil's advocate here, obviously, you're not staring at the box the whole time.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're staring at what's on the monitor.
[SPEAKER_08]: The box is just for impressing people at LAN parties.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: My computer lights up.
[SPEAKER_02]: My power supply lights up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mine lights up like a bluish color, but it's nothing special.
[SPEAKER_03]: My favorite, I think, computer that anyone ever built was one built into a tall tackle box.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, a tall metal toolbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I gotta say, maybe lesson learned here, I didn't build my own computer the last time I bought a computer because, you know, I'm not quite as talented as Loki or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I thought maybe I was getting a really good deal because I bought my computer for, you know, a certain price that was kind of low to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now I'm learning, should have got a better video card and, you know, some of these other things I should have considered better at the time.
[SPEAKER_02]: But lesson learned.
[SPEAKER_02]: One thing I would change if I were to go back and actually make my computer again is I would not buy another graphics card to run SLI.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I have two graphics cards in mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're both EVGA, GTS, 8800 graphics cards with half gig RAM in each one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, in the games that run SLI, it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: But most stuff out there does not support SLI.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_02]: I did it for Crysis, but Crysis got boring really fast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bummer.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we're going to open up the Skype line now.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR, or our username on Skype, is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to take your calls live here for a little bit, and then we'll start to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Meanwhile, while we wait for the calls to come in, because there's a little bit of a delay from studio to encoding to the all-game server to you guys hearing it, let's see if there's any last-minute stories.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a rumor that there's going to be some exclusive characters for Sonic Sega Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sonic and Sega All-Star Racing, including for the Xbox 360 that Banjo-Kazooie might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's from some work-in-progress box shots that are appearing, I guess, on their UK site.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there's a fun little website I was looking at earlier that you can...
[SPEAKER_02]: Create your own Zelda scenes with the Zelda 2 text generator And if you go check it out, it's at ZeldaPower.com And it's under their features The Adventures of Link text box toy You can make all sorts of weird scenes But you can't actually put them in the game, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it's just to make little webpages or stuff for forums and stuff like that So it's kind of neat
[SPEAKER_08]: Great, more forum macros, just what we needed.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, there is a rumor that apparently you're going to be able to attend some of these gaming conferences through your Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: One of the new things they're talking about is imagine an interactive online version of E3, BlizzCon, Gamescom, Comic-Con, and every other major video game convention were made available through Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's something that is being put out there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I guess it's coming from some guy who works in the game industry, VG Market, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a, looks like it's another survey, a market research survey.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we know about those market research surveys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes they end up coming true.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot of comments there in chat about the SLI.
[SPEAKER_08]: DangerSkew in our chat says, I agree with the SLI argument.
[SPEAKER_08]: You should never build a computer with SLI from the beginning, only if you need more power later.
[SPEAKER_08]: And TigerClaw says, you only need SLI if you have a huge-ass monitor.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's meant to handle graphics to higher resolutions.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you have a 19-inch widescreen monitor and only one NVIDIA card, you're good to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, those comments coming from chat.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is Skype all fucked up today?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that what's going on?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had something awful linked to me, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Skype was acting weird earlier, but yeah, what's that?
[SPEAKER_03]: A trailer for Nuking a Fighter's movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a real movie?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and it has Ray Park in it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I watched some of it and I wanted to cry because I'm like, where's Kyo?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is it an American movie or is it something that's been made overseas?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's American.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_03]: I didn't know they were making that.
[SPEAKER_08]: You would have thought I would have heard about this sooner.
[SPEAKER_03]: Why don't I send you the link?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we can play how awful it is on the air.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on, we're getting a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Islands Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, hi, Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just trying to get over this whole Thanksgiving ordeal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a bummer we all have to go back to work tomorrow, but such is life.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, yeah, basically, I know we barely covered the DDR and Belmonte scene, but...
[SPEAKER_01]: I figured you already know by now that DDRX2 has an arcade release.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's going to be released in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll mention it once in a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't mention every little story like we used to, but any of the big things will come up.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we mentioned the location test last week, and I did read something on the internet this week that somebody out there in Japan was bringing back reports of what was in the location test, which was a lot of...
[SPEAKER_08]: your Beatmania 2DX style artists and a lot of the Konami House originals which I think is DDR's biggest problem right now in cracking the mainstream is that I realize people love their Konami originals I do too, there's a lot of talented artists it's never going to break into the mainstream unless they start Well, I mean, that all depends on what licenses they end up including in the final version but right now, apparently a lot of the community from the consensus I'm hearing right now is that they actually
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually hearing good consensus from them.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm actually hearing a lot of good things in terms of the song selections.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: They may be skeptical as to whether or not they can execute the same Japanese version to America, which we already know how much of a disaster DRX was.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't really, I have to admit, you know, I haven't been following DDRs closely.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, the fucked up pads and the countless number of, you know, fixes afterwards.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even my pads, even my David Busters managed to get a DDRX CAD that couldn't even last a month.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was not even playable.
[SPEAKER_01]: The fact that there's, yeah, there's not that many machines around.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, and the fact that they killed off upgrade kits made it even worse.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I pretty much consider that a failure.
[SPEAKER_01]: The way I see it is that I use Supernova as a baseline because that manages to have good coverage all around.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just about most of the places I can think of off the top of my head that had Supernova at one point.
[SPEAKER_01]: But then when I try to do the same thing for DDRX, I can't.
[SPEAKER_01]: I can only think of one place.
[SPEAKER_01]: and another place that wasn't Coney Island that no longer has the machine.
[SPEAKER_01]: But that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Honestly, Zaku, I just want to play 4th Mix Plus.
[SPEAKER_01]: I already had that chance.
[SPEAKER_01]: I've already played that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Last summer, back on 8 on the break, we basically...
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, I've played it before, but I'm just saying, like, with all these fancy new mixes and all that stuff going on, I miss 4th Plus.
[SPEAKER_08]: 4th Plus was the bomb.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was the best mix they ever did.
[SPEAKER_01]: Apparently they're doing, they have, like,
[SPEAKER_01]: They've been throwing fourth and fifth mix around pretty recently.
[SPEAKER_01]: I don't know if they're still doing it now, but that's what they were doing a couple of months ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: 5th Mix was pretty badass, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where else can you play Moonlight Shadow?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_02]: 5th Mix was awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there anything else on your mind this week besides just the DDRX2?
[SPEAKER_01]: Basically, going on what you said about Alienware, you can build yourself a PC for less than $1,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: A really good gaming rate for less than $1,000.
[SPEAKER_01]: You just have to look hard and deep and you just gotta...
[SPEAKER_01]: You gotta really consider what you prioritize.
[SPEAKER_01]: Graphics, sound, or both.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, that's pretty much it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I've managed to get mine for $1,700 and change when I bought them, you know, when I built it.
[SPEAKER_01]: But it still runs pretty good as of today.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, obviously it can't do 60 frames of a crisis, but it can play stuff like Left 4 Dead, Team Fortress 2 pretty well.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's just a matter of how much you're willing to spend on something like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's important, too, is prioritizing.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you really want out of your machine?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because if you buy a cheapo graphics card but buy a big monitor, it's not going to do a lot of good.
[SPEAKER_01]: Right, you've got to get at least something.
[SPEAKER_01]: At least GeForce 9 or better right now.
[SPEAKER_01]: That should do you good for another year or two before you have to refresh it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, well, Zaku, we're going to let you go so we can get some more calls, see if anybody else is trying to call tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: But have a good one, okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, later, buddy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, 1877-GAME-OLR if you'd like to give us a call, or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Either way will do it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll keep the phone lines open a little bit longer to see if anyone wants to get through.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know some people told me earlier they wanted to call in.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure if they're going to try to get through or what.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do we have any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_03]: I sent you the link.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I forgot about... Oh, and of course we're getting another call.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll bring up the link for after this though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, this is X-Link.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hi, X-Link.
[SPEAKER_00]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_00]: Hey, doing good.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was playing a game recently that I'd like to talk a little bit about if it's okay with you.
[SPEAKER_00]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_00]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing the full version, and the full version is not that much different than the demo.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just you can level up your monsters a lot more.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I've been playing just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't gone through the whole game exactly yet.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been playing during downtime for a while, so...
[SPEAKER_00]: PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_08]: What are your thoughts on it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like because I'm a big Blitz, Bejeweled and Bejeweled Blitz fan and I think they're taking more after Bejeweled Blitz because the fact you have to rotate the pieces to make the lines to sum around.
[SPEAKER_00]: I like it a lot more.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a lot more difficult than going, okay, well I'm going to take this and switch these two around.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not like two pieces.
[SPEAKER_00]: You have to switch actually four around in a counterclockwise position.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: in gyromancer your twists do not have to cause three to line up you'll get higher scores and even penalized you know if it doesn't and higher scores if they do but I just had such a hard time kind of getting used to that idea I mean it didn't ruin the game for me I still think it's kind of interesting but I just think I'm going to suck at it because I always play Bejeweled Blitz because I want my epine to have me at the top of the leaderboard even though that never happens
[SPEAKER_00]: Most definitely.
[SPEAKER_00]: You get more points by doing that, but also at the same time though, if you do a move and you don't make three, it will cause the enemy's power to grow a little bit each time.
[SPEAKER_00]: So you want to make those lines, you want to make the ones, because for each of your characters you get a certain color, so you want to make those lines with the color that you're...
[SPEAKER_00]: Creature Represents, so that way you can use your powers and take more.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's cool because it has a life.
[SPEAKER_00]: It added more of a role-playing element to it with the hit points, so you do certain moves and it'll take away hit points away from the other enemy depending on how many was chained or what was happening.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has a lot of the element to Puzzle Quest to it, but it's a lot of fun, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Puzzle Quest Puzzle Quest Puzzle Quest
[SPEAKER_00]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It has a lot of the puzzle quest type feel to it, but it's more storyline driven and a little more interaction that I would say than that.
[SPEAKER_00]: But like I said before, for a puzzle game, $15, it was Pop Game and Square Enix.
[SPEAKER_00]: You can't really go too wrong with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_00]: It is a damn good price.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty cool how there's been all this puzzle game resurgence in the past couple of years, especially these very, very fleshed out type of puzzle games between what Q Entertainment has been giving us with Luminous and so forth, and now these RPG meets PopCap games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty fascinating.
[SPEAKER_00]: I just use it mostly, like I said before, as a time killer.
[SPEAKER_00]: If I want something to fill in in 15 minutes, I usually just load it up and then play it, you know, play or maybe play like one level a day or something, so that way I don't get an overkill of it, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised this game hasn't shown up on every platform.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure it's just a matter of time before it's on the iPhone.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, right now I know it's for the Xbox and PC, but I don't know if they're going to expand it over that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they're trying to wait to see what happens first beforehand, so.
[SPEAKER_00]: Right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Very interesting.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, anything else on your mind tonight, X-Link?
[SPEAKER_00]: Night of the Old Republic 250
[SPEAKER_08]: and they're just getting people to install Steam to get these hella good deals and maybe even, you know, kind of the idea behind the consoles they're taking a little bit of a loss
[SPEAKER_08]: over these games, you know, especially a game like Knights of the Old Republic that hasn't really generated buzz.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I mean, I guess I shouldn't put it that way.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, it's years old.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's years old.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, you have to think about it this way.
[SPEAKER_00]: If someone was sitting around, like, say, for, like, example, even in the video store, a game was sitting around, they wasn't doing anything, and they're going, they put a price tag of $250 on there, and they know it's going to hit, then they, you know, at least they're making something out of nothing.
[SPEAKER_00]: So, I mean, they're making money somehow.
[SPEAKER_00]: True.
[SPEAKER_08]: True.
[SPEAKER_08]: So maybe it's a range of these companies.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm holding out hope that Torchlight is in tomorrow's deals because I really wanted to pick that up.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, well, you know, you get what you pay for.
[SPEAKER_00]: Kind of like I kind of kicked myself in the ass for picking up F.A.W.
[SPEAKER_00]: 3 and then two months down the road they're like, oh, by the way, Game of Year Edition, same price.
[SPEAKER_00]: And you get all the downloadable content to go with it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, bummer.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I did pick up Civ 4 also from GoGamer when they're doing their Black Friday deals for $10, which was the complete edition.
[SPEAKER_00]: So that was very nice compared to that of $5 from Best Buy.
[SPEAKER_00]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, X-Link, we're going to let you go so we can try and get maybe one more call in.
[SPEAKER_08]: But have a great night, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thanks for the review on Gyromancer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anytime.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did get that video brought up here that DarkSakura was talking about earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me look at a little bit of a clip here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It does look like an actual, like... I just never knew they were making a movie out of King of Fighters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or maybe... Is that mine?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, this definitely looks direct-to-video.
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Maggie Q, Sean Ferris, and Rick Park.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be fun for fan of martial arts movies and stuff, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Part of my soul cried.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I don't know what else to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll make this brief because since you guys were talking about DDR and so forth, a funny little anecdote popped up at Anime USA that I have to share with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the funniest thing I've ever heard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not sure if you guys covered this about the whole... I think you guys did the whole Konami DDR tournament that they were having.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I came up on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: People emailed us about it and we were kind of giving our spin on it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not enough notice on it, I think, for it to be taken as seriously as they wanted it to be.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, if I'm not mistaken, I believe there was also a cutoff point for the tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had to be under a certain age to compete.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_08]: So officially DDR has turned its back on me, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, from what I understand, they're saying the cutoff date was like 31 or 32, which I call shenanigans on.
[SPEAKER_04]: But one of the people I know in the DDR fandom community...
[SPEAKER_04]: I believe it was DDR Darryl Bill, he told me how it was crazy that they were having this, and I ran into another friend of mine, Jim DaFly, at Anime USA.
[SPEAKER_04]: He told me that the guy that was hosting the tournament, who more or less put the rules together, he himself had a heart attack.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait, the guy who, wait, like a heart attack, like literally had a heart attack?
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_04]: Caram is kind of fucked up, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, yeah, hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would never, you know, even if it was, let's say it's just like the worst of the worst bottom of the barrel video game personality.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, for instance, this guy who's suing all the companies for these ludicrous reasons.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would not wish a heart attack upon them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would wish.
[SPEAKER_04]: Neither would I, but I just find this just odd.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like he's talking about you can't be over a certain age to compete.
[SPEAKER_04]: This, this, and this.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then, boom, he has a heart attack.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm like, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know, I think it's just an unfortunate coincidence.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, people get sick as they get older.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have to be the stage to compete, because this is what?
[SPEAKER_03]: How about you have to have a blood pressure under a certain, you know,
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I think it's sad, and I don't want to make jokes about it, you know, and I don't care if you all hate the fucking rules or whatever, but I just don't think we would ever want to wish that upon somebody, and I hope it gets better soon, but I think what I can speak to is the tournament itself, and, you know, the rules and the tournament itself seemed a little silly, and was hastily thrown together, and I think that's why it didn't get probably the type of coverage that hopefully Konami was going for.
[SPEAKER_04]: but you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I think I'm going to host my own national DDR tournament and you can be up to whatever age you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you need to bring your walker, your wheelchair, your cane to compete, that's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just don't bar me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hold on though because then I'll bring a cane and use it to hit the arrows and so forth.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would be cheating.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was the guy though who played on crutches.
[SPEAKER_08]: Freestyle's different.
[SPEAKER_03]: And he mostly PA'd too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did he?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is playing with crutches like holding the bar, though?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, he had one leg.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did he really?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: There's a video up on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're not thinking of the same guy, then.
[SPEAKER_03]: And if I might, I think he's actually from New York.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does Ranma know him?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Probably not no, but Zaku might.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Ranma, we're going to let you go and, you know, be safe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Us 30-year-olds.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just have my Geritol shake.
[SPEAKER_04]: I saved some for you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I use Ensure, but thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, that, I mean, that's unfortunate.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, I don't care what fucked up tournament he planned.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, heart attacks suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, that's just, that's, that's, I hope he's okay, for God's sake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, that's going to do it for the Skype line tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you guys didn't get through, please, you can always feel free to leave us a message at mailbag at orangelaundry.com or of course the Twitter and of course the Facebook and all those social networks we interact with.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have eyes and ears everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for now, it's about time to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But in order to do that, we have to go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll start tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: My final thought is I need Advil or something that will make my back feel better because it sucks.
[SPEAKER_03]: I have some.
[SPEAKER_08]: I might take you up on that or just do it when I get home.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not like killing me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Otherwise, I'd be going to a doctor tomorrow, but it's just annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's annoying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, what's your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final thought is this Doom with Mega Man looks kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Doom mod.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it Mega Doom?
[SPEAKER_02]: With Mega Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got all the 8-bit sprites and everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kind of amazing, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm so downloading that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that out?
[SPEAKER_08]: Released publicly?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Deathmatch mod.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure if it's out yet to download.
[SPEAKER_02]: The official website looks like cutstuff.net slash blog slash question mark P equals 1677.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll pull it up for you and you can check it out.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, your final thought tonight?
[SPEAKER_08]: End of line.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my final thought tonight would be... Oh no, I already said my final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, wait, I already said something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was last for a reason.
[SPEAKER_08]: Clearly it's old age.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you want the direct download, because that URL is kind of hard to find, it'd be cutstuff.net slash file slash megadmalpha.zip and that'll get you the zip file for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And for the record, I used to play Gatchaman Doom.
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: And I also need to say, as I do every week, thank you guys very much for tuning in to Orange Launch Radio and supporting independent radio and independent podcasting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Without you guys, this would not be possible.
[SPEAKER_08]: Remember, we don't have any fancy website, multi-million dollar magazine or game company backing us up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just three of us do this because we love you and we love doing this broadcasting thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So all we ask, tell a friend or two about the show.
[SPEAKER_03]: And get us pizza.
[SPEAKER_08]: And pizza would be nice too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Order us pizza for next show.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: I like vegetarian, just letting you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see if that happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, we'll be here to do it all again next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, I'm Rob, she's Jamie, he's Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're out, but Jamie has to say...
[SPEAKER_03]: End of line.
[SPEAKER_05]: See you next week!