Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
We're an hour earlier and yet somehow still exactly the same time
We hope you're well rested with the extra hour you gained last night because tonight you'll need that brain working
We have news to catch up on, report, and make and it all starts right now in the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio live tonight, episode number 706 of our show for this November the 5th of 2017
I almost said November the 2017 of the 5th
Yes, remember the 5th of November or whatever that is, I never even saw that movie, I just heard about it through everybody else
You don't know about the actual Guy Fawkes day?
Whatever I read on Wikipedia and then promptly forgot
Girl
Hi DarkSakura, or Jamie Summers, how are you?
I'm your resident history nerd
And enjoying some decaf coffee tonight
My face is burnt now
I decided to punish DarkSakura tonight for what I don't know
But I said you're going to drink this out of the DC Comics Justice League mug that I have because she's not a big fan of DC
But then Loki, Techmaster Loki over there suggested DC is decaf
Decaf coffee
This DC decaf mug
Yes
Perfect
And for the record, remember remember the 5th of November the gunpowder treason and plot
I know of no reason why the gunpowder treason should ever be forgot
Okay
That's how it goes, so whatever
Alright, props to you
And I could not in a train
Y'all need culture
Y'all wouldn't know culture if you got smacked in the face with yogurt
Remember remember, one fish, two fish, red fish, blue fish
Y'all bitches need culture
Listen to the muffins child, listen to the don'ts
Don't let the cat in the hat in your house because you'll fuck shit up
And you know what? Fucking banana muffin
Alright anyway, hi everybody, we got a busy week
So first I want to say sorry we weren't here last week and that was totally my fault
I had no voice at all last week
When I woke up Saturday morning I had hosted Rocky the night before
And I guess I was a little more extra than usual because it was Halloween after all
And so when I woke up on Saturday
It was literally like this
And I didn't know it
Like you should have asked Alan about how I sounded, it wasn't pretty
And so I have to make a judgement call on if there's going to be a show or no show
Because there's not going to be a show, Dark Soccer and Loki should get their evening back
So around 2 o'clock I was still sounding like this
So I was like alright we're not doing a show because I have to rest my voice because I need it for my job
So sorry guys but shit happens
So that's what happened last week
Sadly we won't be here next week
That was the pre-planned week off because of the long Veterans Day weekend
I'm actually going to be out of town
I'm going to Seattle so hoping to hit up some gaming related fun places while I'm up there
I just found out today
I'm going to go visit an old friend
I'm going to visit an old friend from LiveJournal who I've never met before
She lives in Bellevue so I get to go over there which I haven't been to before
I think that's just a stone's throw away from where
Where's Nintendo and Microsoft? Redmond?
Yeah I gotta travel there just to look at an office building
Because that's what they are, office buildings
There's nothing that exciting but at least I can say I went
You have to go to the Pinball Museum in Seattle
Is there a Pinball Museum in Seattle?
There is, I'll have to find out where
I'll send you the address
Yeah tell me where it is, I wouldn't mind hitting that up
Because we did all the big touristy stuff last time we were there
So we've done the Space Needle, we did the EMP, we did all that stuff
So I mean we'll probably do some of it again
But I wouldn't mind seeing other parts of Seattle too
So we'll see
Anyhow so we've got to make this show really good
Because it's got to last for a few weeks for people
So sorry about that
You can also of course join us live
We do tape live every Sunday night at the Voice Geeks Network
vognetwork.com
6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Usually right after our pal Bobby Black Wolf
But we're not the only one that's been having issues lately
Bobby's been having internet drama
That's been keeping him offline
He doesn't have enough bandwidth at home I guess
Something in his neighborhood has screwed something up
And here's my thought Bobby
Maybe it's somebody's Xbox
Because I want to talk about this
So this is some drama that is like unfolding on Twitter as we speak
Because I had a pretty serious problem today
And it's my Xbox's fault
Now let me tell you what's going on
So I get online today and I'm setting up for the show tonight by logging on to vognetwork.com
But I get a new pop-up window that I don't usually get on vognetwork.com
And it's Xfinity
And I was like wow I've never seen that before
And Xfinity actually popped, which is Comcast
They popped up a thing that said you are at 90% of your bandwidth for the month
You have used 900 and something gigs out of your 1024 that are available
Because everybody has a terabyte of data a month now
It used to be like 250 and then it's been slowly climbing up
Well I was like the fuck?
And they were like for the calendar month
And I'm like it is the 5th of November
And I've used a terabyte of data this month
I'm like what the fuck's going on?
So I log into the Comcast website
And sure enough most months we use about maybe 380 gigs
I think last month there was 410 gigs
But I downloaded Destiny 2 PC last month right?
So it's going to be a little more
But usually we use between 300 and 400 gigs
Which is pretty impressive considering there's two tech nerds in this house
Myself and my husband
I do this radio show on Sunday Night from here
And I've been doing live streaming
And you probably watch Netflix and all that
Yeah I binge watch Stranger Things 2 when that first came out
So we use a lot of technology
But sure enough it was like
At this point it said I'd use something like
1050 gigs or something like that
I was like what the hell is going on?
Well luckily my pal Xtifer
Who you guys remember from Guys on a Show
He bought me as a Christmas present this last year
A Google Wifi
And the reason why this helps right now is because
On Google Wifi you can with the phone app
Go in and it shows you which devices are connected
What's using bandwidth right now
And you can pull a report for the last 7 days
The last 30 days
So I was like alright well I remember that
So I was like I want to see is it on my computer
Is it on Alan's computer
Is there an unknown device that's figured out our Wifi password
That's downloading all of the porn
Like what's going on?
So I go onto the Google
The Google Wifi and I pull the report and it says
My Xbox has pulled down
I think it's 940 gigabytes
In the past 7 days
By itself
The Xbox
I have a 1 terabyte drive on the Xbox One
So I started
Obviously I did what anybody does
And I wrote passive aggressive tweets about the situation
Tagging Xfinity and tagging
Xbox because I'm sitting here going
The Xfinity website is like you get charged
$10 for every 50 gigs you go over
And I'm like fuck that
I didn't do anything
So I called and
They told me that you get like
2 courtesy months
Or something
Like you get months where you're allowed to go over
And they don't penalize you
So this month is going to end up being a courtesy month
I guess for me
I'm going to download all the porn now
Might as well at this point right
But I'm still kind of shocked
Like what the hell happened
So obviously one thing that's on my mind
That I think a lot of people are suggesting on Twitter
Because now one of my buddies
Who runs another podcast that's more popular than this one
Retweeted like all my tweets
I don't know if he was having the same problems or what
But now I've got all these people that are giving me suggestions
And everybody is kind of saying
Well do you have an Xbox One X
That's the first question I get
The answer is no
I have not changed my Xbox One
Since Forza Horizon 2 was new
And that was the game that convinced me to get a new Xbox
I bought my Xbox when they just released
That one terabyte model
So I do have a one terabyte Xbox One
But still
Why is my Xbox trying to download
940 gigs to my one terabyte Xbox One
So I unplugged the fucker
I was like you're done
I unplugged it
The one thing the Comcast guy suggested I do
Which I was like oh yeah that's kind of obvious
He said change your Wi-Fi pass
Or just make sure nobody else has it
He's like cause I can't see on my end
What devices are using your bandwidth
And I'm sitting here going
I just fucking told you it's my Xbox
But I'm like don't get mad at the call center people
They're just doing their job
So I was like alright you know what
Why not
Is changing your Wi-Fi password a bad idea
No it's not
So I went ahead and did that
So now I plug back in the Xbox
I'm just not going to give the Xbox the new password
Trying to figure out what's going on
And I do notice it's trying to download
A 43 gigabyte update for Quantum Break
And I'd heard that Quantum Break was getting a big update
But I don't have a 4K TV
I don't have an Xbox One X
I don't understand why
Was it attempted to download it like 20 times
That's what I think is happening
That it's been attempted
Now I can't prove this yet
But I don't have a lot of space left on my Xbox One
I filled that thing to the brim
That terabyte
I mean because I don't usually delete things
Because why should I
So it's like 92% full
So I'm wondering if
Is it trying to download
The Quantum Break update
Failing and starting over
Over and over again
Possibly
So here's
It should be smart to see that it can't fit on there
So it can't update it
That's what it does on the PlayStation
That's
And that
Geez Microsoft learn
But here's the weird thing you guys
I can't
Like nobody else on Twitter is complaining about this
So I can't sit here and go
Microsoft's got a big problem
This is widespread
Where's the news story on Kotaku
Alerting everybody about this
Because it does seem like
I'm the only guy that this is happening to
But here's my first question everybody
Would you go look at your bandwidth report
For the month
And especially if you have Google Wi-Fi
Or something similar that will tell you
What your Xbox is doing
And would you let me know
If anybody else out there
Is having this extreme problem
That I'm having
Just makes me glad I never bought one
I guess but I mean
I don't know what to think
Like I want to say I feel bad for Microsoft
But I don't
But it's weird that this is isolated
Like that's the
And so it makes me wonder did I do something wrong
But I haven't done anything outside the norm
I barely use my Xbox One for gaming
It's just a Microsoft device
It likes updating on the fly
Here's a thought
That maybe you have enough
Because you know there's a difference between
Actual size and virtual space right
Right
So it could mean that you have enough in one aspect
But the moment that it's filling up the cache
It's hitting that point where it can't
But it's still reading that you've got room for it
Yeah I don't know
So you just might be at a sweet spot for that
Interesting
Or in this case a sour spot
Well I'm gonna go look at some comments in chat
Because everybody's playing armchair IT
Which when you get a bunch of nerds together
That's what's going to happen
Not me I'm not at work
So in our chat room
Over at live.vognetwork.com
Because again we do tape live
Six o'clock Pacific
Nine o'clock Eastern
Oh and Bobby, thank you very much
Bobby Blackwolf did make it to chat tonight
And he says he fixed the web chat
So if live.vognetwork.com wasn't working for you before
It might now
Because he changed the web app
So hopefully it'll work again
Thanks Bobby
Speaking of armchair IT
Let's see
I'm looking in chat
Tigerclaw says
When you leave your Xbox One in an instant on mode
Whenever you get one of those free Xbox One games
It'll automatically download them too
So it's best to have power saving mode enabled
I've never had a game download that I didn't tell it to
Like I will go into the Xbox gold membership thing
And download what I
But I've never had the Xbox just say
Surprise we delivered you a game
So I don't have that setting on
I have had it update games
But that's
I mean
Usually you want that right
Isn't that what PlayStation Plus had as a feature
When it first launched was auto updating games
Yeah I mean that's what PlayStation does now
But like if I don't have space for the update
It knows it's like well this isn't gonna fit
So we're not updating
Bobby Blockwolf says
I think the Xbox One actually has a thing in settings
That shows its data usage
A I can't find it
But probably B because
For it to do anything it wants to go online
And I'm sure as you all can sympathize right now
I don't want to put my Xbox One back online
Although I guess if this month is gonna be a wash anyway
Maybe now's the time to do it
When I can sit there and watch it
But I'd prefer to know at least a little bit about what I'm doing
Before I put it back online if that makes sense
Maybe I can tell
I bet through Google Wi-Fi
I bet I can let it go online
But like throttle it
I think Google Wi-Fi lets you do that
I think you can say
This device can use no more than X amount of data per second or something
So maybe that's what I'll do
I gotta say
The winner in this whole scenario is Google Wi-Fi
So props to that
Because that helped me figure out what it is
So that when people on the internet are like
Are you sure you didn't get hacked
Or how do you know it's your Xbox
It's like I got the receipts
Receipts, I has them
Here they are
Korkay in our chatroom over at live.vognetwork.com says
Go for the high score
Why not?
Even though I kind of promised him I wasn't gonna do that
But there you go
Alright
So yeah some folks in chat
SSU100Matt says I'm only seeing I use 15 gigs
Tigerclass says I'm only using 49 gigs
Well good for y'all
Yeah I know
But that's the weird
Those guys have Xbox ones
And so what is unique about my situation
I don't know
I can't figure it out
But I can tell you it's trying to download an update for Quantum Break and Forza
And I put all the screenshots on my Twitter
Twitter.com slash Skye S-K-I-E
If you wanna continue to play Armchair Warrior
I tagged Xbox in all these posts so maybe Xbox support will fire me back something
But I don't
Like
Here's the thing at the end of the day
I don't particularly care if my Xbox is gonna download all of this data
I care that I'm gonna get charged for it
So
And especially if this isn't just happening to me
You know what I'm saying?
Really just fuck Comcast
Cause that's really the problem
Cause if you had unlimited bandwidth as we should all
It wouldn't even be an issue
That's true
So there's you know
But I also think the system
The Xbox should be smart enough
That like
There should be some type of internal trigger
That when it's used a hundred gigabytes in a month
Or two hundred gigabytes in a month
It should pop up a window going
I'm eating a lot of data and this is why
Do you wanna continue?
Like at least give me the option to put
Cause I would have never known this was happening
If that pop up
From Xfinity
So to Comcast credit
If they hadn't put a pop up
That said you've used ninety percent
Hey it looks like that you've used a lot of data
Would you like me to download some more data for you?
Says Clippy
There you go
So that's the drama I've been dealing with
So stay tuned for potentially an update in two weeks
But for right now the Xbox One is sitting in the corner
It is not allowed to have the new Wi-Fi password
That is the punishment
Grounded dammit
You're grounded and you're not getting the Wi-Fi password
That is what's happening
Loki and DarkSakura got the new Wi-Fi password
But the Xbox did not get the Wi-Fi password
Now that I know that I can download as much as I want
I'm downloading all the porn right now so it's fine
Like Corky said earlier in chat
Go for the high score
Why not?
Come on Nolgus in chat says
Does Xbox have a beta thing
Xbox Insider or something?
You know what for the sake of transparency
Yes they do
And I'm in it
So is that
Is the problem because my console is doing something
In a beta mode
Which I understand
Microsoft's gonna wash your hands of liability
If that thing happened or whatever
No that's just usually
It just means it downloads more frequent
System updates
980 gigs of updates
Good
I mean but I doubt it would
I doubt it would keep doing that though
Yeah
Because usually it would just download
You know the latest one
Brad from Paw Culture says
You have the Xbox on Wi-Fi
That has to be rough on gaming
No
I actually
Right now because the PlayStation 4
Moved into my office
So I could do streaming from the PlayStation 4
My Xbox One has become the CBS
So I can watch Star Trek Discovery device
Netflix for when I binge watched
Stranger Things 2
When we weren't here last week
Device
So it's been kind of my main media device
Maybe it's Star Trek Discovery's fault
Did Star Trek Discovery break my Xbox
Maybe it did
Perhaps I don't know
But all those things have been running fine
And great quality
I don't have 4K
My television isn't 4K
So I wasn't downloading like 4K Stranger Things
But still
And again that was all technically October
Because I watched that Stranger Things
Like in the first three days
You guys it is so good
It is so good
Stranger Things in 4K
Except for Episode 7
Fuck Episode 7
But The Resident's fine
Which one was Episode 7?
The one that was
Without spoiling
The Back Door Pilot
Oh yeah
That little
I don't know
I liked the main person in that one
Yeah me too
Me too
A lot
Plus I liked the makeover
Yeah
We have to keep it
Plus it was all MTV
Some people are very hyper about spoilers
I know
That's all I'm saying
When do we get to spoil the shit out of Stranger Things?
I guess we have to give it a good 60 days
Huh?
2018?
I don't know
Too soon
Anyway
I guess also that's kind of the department of critical myth
Pod culture
The more TV based shows on our network to get into
We're usually here to talk about games
I do want to talk about games
So the kickoff topic I did want to talk about
Was I wanted to talk a little bit about
Digital distribution
Now this is a topic that's come up on our show before
But
I don't know if you guys heard about this this week
But there were some major earnings calls
That happened in this past week
Activision, EA
They do their quarterly stockholder calls
Because at the end of the day
Companies like EA, Activision
They exist
What?
To make money
To make who money?
To make their shareholders money
And that's why people talk about investing in the stock market
Right?
America 101
There you go
Okay
So every quarter
These companies have to basically produce
You know
They have to update their shareholders on what they're doing
So Activision did an earnings call this past week
Where they said
50% of Destiny 2's sales on consoles came via download
Rather than a retail disc
Now
I would have believed that
If we were talking the PC numbers only
Because I would have thought
Oh there's a ton of people
That probably just do digital on PC
Because of storefronts like Battle.net and so forth
And that there's people that are buying Destiny with Warcraft gold
Because you can do that
The way things are set up on Battle.net
But no
That factor is for
I guess all of it
Or for the consoles
I buy everything digitally
For the most part
Yeah
And I guess this is getting bigger and bigger
Earlier this year
EA said
They expect 40% of their console game sales to come from downloads in 2017
That is a jump up 10% from where they were at
30% of sales in 2016
EA has gone on record before saying
Quote
They're gonna be 100% digital company period
It's going to be there someday
It's inevitable
No
And I don't think that's gonna be the case
Because here's the problem
Yes
It's a nice idea to have it all digital and everything
But if everybody goes all digital
Remember there's that wonderful company
Comcast
That has those wonderful bandwidth caps
That will fuck you over
Right
If you try to download everything
So that's why it will never be that way
Because fucking net neutrality and all that shit is
Not in the picture because
Those companies want to make money too
So
Because you have that
And also because
And this is very important
These same fucking companies
Keep pushing these stupid
Collectors editions
And shit with giant statue editions
You can't digitally download those
You can't digitally download a statue
You wouldn't want to digitally download a statue
Correct
Okay
So you think there's still going to be a market
For physical stuff
But it's gonna be kind of limited
It's gonna be like
They do it now
They can still do digital distribution
But they do it now where they have editions
It's collectors editions that don't include the game
Why?
I know
Why would you do that?
So
Well is it because they expect that people are gonna
Download to play hour zero digitally
So this is just literally a box of shit
With the games branding on it
I mean like for me like if I'm gonna
If I'm looking forward to a game
And I want to play it day one
I'm not gonna pre-order
Because that means I gotta drive out to the store
To go pick it up and do all that nonsense
Whereas I can
Digitally pre-order it or download it
Fuck I'm not pre-ordering shit
But I'll digitally order it like
The day before or something like that
And it'll unlock at 9pm the night before it comes out
That's what I did with Destiny 2 on PC
Is that I bought it like two days before it launched
So it would be all loaded and ready to go
But with Destiny 2 I knew
If I walked into a store and bought it on a box
All I was gonna get
Maybe I was gonna get a Blu-ray or DVD with the game
But it was likely gonna be a code
And a game like that is so much online anyway
You're gonna get some code for your online access
So there's no reason to really have the physical edition
Whereas here's my thing
I guess I've had the hardest time buying into this digital stuff
Because I'm still this big believer of
Well when you buy a game on a disc or on a cartridge
Let's say Mario Odyssey on the flip side of things
I have a cartridge for that
And if someday I decide I'm sick of Mario Odyssey
Which I doubt is gonna happen
But we'll get into that later
I could sell that cartridge
Or I could loan that
What happened to that?
It's because I'm lazy
Two things
One, I'm lazy
So I don't wanna have to worry about selling that cartridge
Or whatever
And it depends on the system
Like if I had a Switch
There's not a lot of onboard storage for that
Then yes, physical copies are gonna be more appealing to me
Whereas I've got 500GB of space on my Playstation 4
So I can download a bunch of games at once
And I don't have to worry about swapping discs out and stuff like that
Not to say that I don't buy disc versions of games
I do sometimes
It's just not all the time
Usually I'm getting stuff on sale
But with that
There's also another factor
GameStop is not gonna really be happy with them going all digital
They've tried to do it in the past
They've tried to say that they're gonna go all digital
Never gonna happen
Because it's such a big monster
And they control the industry
So they're not gonna
It's not gonna happen
They're never gonna be fully digital
Because there's people that want physical versions of the game
There's gonna be GameStop
And other big retailers that that's a big chunk of their money
Well GameStop, it's most of their money
So they're not gonna just give that up quietly
And bandwidth caps
You're not gonna be able to do that
Plus internet speeds
Because as these games get bigger and bigger
The 4K content
That's more data that you're dumping down the tubes
And it's gonna take a lot longer to download
Especially with all these internet companies fighting to upgrade their service
I wanted to get to DarkSakura's perspective
But real quick
I wanted to mention
I was noticing a lot of parallels maybe with the music industry
You know 10 years ago with the invention of the iPod or whatever
And you know just the fact that a lot of people were pirating their music
With things like Napster or whatever
Apple kind of came up with this method to legitimize it
A lot of other people kind of went on that as well
But anyway my point is
A lot of record stores are gone because of it
Tower Records
Gone
The Warehouse
All these big record stores I remember from my youth they're gone
Now that's left are indie niche places
You know like we have a local chain here, Dimple
You know they seem to do pretty well because
They also expand the books and movies
Yeah that's true
They've also expanded to books and movies
And I noticed
What's the music that people seem to be buying these days?
Vinyl
Exactly
And it's kind of that collector's edition stuff
I found a place downtown
Because I was when I had to get my window replaced on my Fiat
And I was at this little place like 16th and E
And walked around down E to go have breakfast at this little place called Shine
Have you ever been there?
No
But on the way there there's like this little like thrift store
But it was all full of fucking vinyl
Nothing but vinyl in a thrift store
Yeah and speaking of I'm going on this trip to Seattle
And I remember one of the things I bought on my last trip to Seattle
This is like seriously one of my prized possessions
This is my copy of Abba's The Visitors
My favorite album from one of my favorite bands
I bought you one
Probably my favorite band ever
You did
I got you Super Trooper
You got me Super Trooper
But this is the one that I got in Seattle at Pike Place Market
At a very similar store
It was like a thrift store but it was all vinyl
And I was like do they have Abba, Abba, Abba, Abba
And then they had the visitors
What's that place in San Francisco on Market near Castro?
Is that Rasputin?
Yeah I think it's Rasputin
Because that's used to where I would go to buy laser discs
Like I found my Wizard of Oz laser disc there
It's like two places down from like the Brody salon
But it's like right there at Market in Castro
J.D. has regrets to inform us they closed
Sad
Bobby Blackwolf in chat saying
I buy new albums on vinyl now and get the free MP3 download for the USB stick in my car
So
I have one
I only have a handful of albums
I have a copy of Rubber Soul because that was my favorite Beatles album
I have Gorillaz Demon Days which I have it unopened
So if I need a quick 500 bones I could sell it
Because it's a first printing
I have two Rodale albums
I have Even Worse and then I have Mandatory Fun
Because we got them to sign it
Yeah I mean I don't even own a record player
So the only reason I own that Abba on vinyl
Is because it is a relic of the time period from which that album came out
And that record was likely used to play that music
You know what I mean like it's more the collector thrift store kind of atmosphere of it
It's very hard to explain but I bet a lot of you that have bought vinyls
Probably understand
It's more the fact that you know I own something of that time period that is that album
I almost bought a Panasonic record player at that place
Well the record player is coming back
You know why?
Anyway let me
Wait it had an 8 track player
We've been too far into music which you know I know a lot of us love music
But Jamie what are your thoughts quickly on the digital versus
Especially because you've been a big collector
But I don't know how much you guys have embraced digital
But what's kind of your thoughts when you hear EA saying
We're going to be a 100% digital company
Okay
I kind of don't care
Okay if it wasn't EA saying it what about Activision?
Still don't care
Still don't care because then
Probably even less so
I mean like look at all of the like World of Warcraft
Look at Overwatch
Look at all that
Right
Those are already digital only pretty much
I mean you used to be able to get discs for them
But computers aren't even built with DVD drives anymore
You know
I'm like this
My thought is that if I download a game
That I want to keep badly enough
I'm going to copy those files off to external media
And have an archive
I do that anyway with my stuff
You know my um
For example I mean my iTunes directory right
It's all housed on an external drive
I manage that shit myself
My games are exactly the same way
I have two internal drives one of them that's for all of my games
And it's marked so that I can take it out and put it in enclosure if I want to
And I have my 3 terabyte drive that I save all of my save files to
So
And the point of all this
Is that the PSP Go is just ahead of its time
Really wasn't it
No
I mean
It was ahead of something
I don't think it had a lot of storage
And the problem with the PSP Go is their stupid proprietary memory stick shit
That's also the other thing that kind of hurt the Vita
Is because they want to charge extra for their proprietary memory stick formats
So that
They can make more money
It's all about greed
That's the other thing about these companies saying oh we're going 100% digital
Do you really want them to be the only source of being able to purchase those files
Because if they go all digital
That means that there's no competition anymore
Because they're selling their game on one store front
And that's it
And there's not a chance that you're going to get it on sale
I mean they do sales every now and then
But you know it's a lot more prevalent with physical versions
So it just
And plus they're fucking lame
But they're fucking you know
Microtransaction bullshit that they're piecing shit apart
That's where they're making most of their money digitally
Is from that shit
And not necessarily I don't think selling digital copies
So Orange Dontradio we do like to say we are the show where every gamer has a voice
In an effort to kind of expand that and get more voices on our show
Tried something new this week and went to our Discord with this topic
Again you can join us on Discord over at vognetwork.com slash Discord
That will get you the invite you need to get on there
You don't need a special code outside of that
Just go to vognetwork.com slash Discord
And I asked our members on Discord their opinions on this
Let me read you some of the answers from Discord
Corky said I buy digital games when they're cheaper
Or when they're PC games that are just a code in a box
I've never owned a current gen console
So paying $60 for a game and trading it in after isn't something I've been able to do
I do sell old games on eBay to pay for my gaming habit
But it's a fairly rare occurrence
Evil G will probably be a general geek culture store
Like it's slowly transitioning to
My local one is probably one third ugly Funko Pops and clothing
I think you know what speaking of the Funko Pops
And look I own a few of them myself admittedly
I have the Golden Girls Funko Pops
I have a Winston from Overwatch sitting there
We really need to draw the line on those things
Like those fuckers are everywhere
I found them at a thrift store
I'm kinda over it you guys
Like we need something new
Like Funko Pops are losing cool points
Let people love what they love
You're right, you're right
You spend your hard earned money on whatever you want
But it's crazy going into like half the stores in the mall have an entire wall dedicated to it
And it's like do we need that many Funko Pops?
You haven't seen my cube
How many Funko Pops do you have in your cube at work?
Too many to count
No I know what I have
I have a baby group
I have a regular group
I don't need the whole inventory just a number
No I'm actually going through it
That's five on that one
Alright while you count
Dark Tetsuya talking about
Eleven in my cube
I'm not super into mainstream AAA titles
But I definitely prefer physical whenever I can
A lot of indie publishers are doing physical releases for their upcoming Switch titles
Like I believe Limited Run Games is starting to do that
Maybe I'm old school but I just like seeing my game collection on the shelf
And with physical releases sometimes you get extras
Like Mighty No. 9 came with a poster, an art book
It's just not the same as a downloadable PDF in my opinion
But also Mighty No. 9 came with Mighty No. 9
So you know you have that too
Stop
Yeah you know the thing with the physical releases on Switch though
As cool as that is
A lot of them are coming way after the game is released
And it's not like I don't ever buy digital games
Like sure I buy $20 indie games on Switch
On PlayStation and so forth
Sure I buy those but that's because they're $20 games
They're not $60 games that I might want to sell
And try to get like $15 of it back someday
I don't know
Other comments
JD in our Discord saying
I prefer digital but I'll buy whatever's cheaper
Unless there's a strong reason for one or the other
I like digital because you can't lose the cartridge
And stuff tied to your account is good for data recovery
But now that we have two Switches
Being able to pass a cartridge back and forth
Means my husband can play games without buying a second copy
And Tigerclaw over on Discord said
Most people prefer physical
Well that's
That may not be what EA's telling us but anyway
Because digital has its limitations
Such as you running out of hard drive space
Or when a digital game is removed from the store
Which would prevent you from ever buying it
Oh that's true
Bringing up the point of delisting of games
Like the PT demo
You can't
I mean that's different because you didn't buy that
But I bet a lot of people would have bought that
But anyway you can't get that anymore
Right
So you know there's certain things that get delisted
You know Microsoft has this a lot
Rock band songs get delisted
You know and that's just part of the rights
Or whatever goes with that
Anyway thanks you guys over on Discord
vognetwork.com slash Discord
Let's see going to some other comments in our chat
Over at live.vognetwork.com
Ragenator says
With me being a PC gamer for five years now
I'm pretty damn good at finding all the sales and deals
Right Rob?
Yeah I mean obviously you call into the show a lot with those deals
But again and I've said this a lot
I don't mean to sound like a broken record
But this is my perspective on this
Is that when you buy a cartridge or something
Now you have something that has value
And sometimes that value goes way up
Like Dark Sakura's copy of what is it?
Like Symphony of the Night on Saturn or something
What's one of those games that goes up in value?
Yeah that one might be it
The more you own it
Right
Or like you just mentioned your Gorillaz album
You know went up to so much money
You know sometimes the value may go up
If you are lucky enough to own a copy of
Fucking what is it like Chrono Trigger on a cartridge still
That's still worth a lot of money right?
So there's that
Or Final Fight Guy
There's the value in your game
Ninja Gaiden Trilogy
But if the game is cheap enough
Where you're like
Eh I don't need any return on this investment
I'm good spending five bucks to get a copy of Civ IV
And all the expansions on a Steam sale
Then for that that's kind of worth it to most people
Because you know you're getting a game
That's probably worth much more than that
So you're not looking at the resale value
It's a big reason why I think humble bundles
Have done so well right?
So
Probably
Anyway thank you
Dungeon Buster naming some of the big collector's items
I'm trying to think of
Panzer Dragoon Saga
Have it
Silver Gun
Black Label Final Fantasy VII
Have it
So
And I actually traded my original US Dragon Ball GT Final Bout
For
What was that game?
Blue Stinger
And you know what?
It really isn't worth all that much money anymore
Magical Chase is worth some money
Because it was the last US Turbo Duo game
And just to be fair
Kaijuto in chat says
I don't collect Funko but I still love them
I love watching how happy people get on YouTube
When they find their pops fine
I didn't mean to crap on your fandom
If you love your Funko Pops and more power to you
Just
Every store you guys
Have you been to them all lately?
They're in like every store
They have a whole bunch half off at Barnes and Noble
Yeah I guess that's true
I guess people are buying them for reasons
SSJ 100 Matt pointed it out
Dragon Ball GT Final Bout went down way when they re-released it
So it's
I mean
One of the games that never lost any value
Was Rondo of Blood
Uh
Dracula X Rondo of Blood
Didn't Sweet Coat and Two kind of fall in value
When they finally put it out on Playstation 3?
I think maybe a little bit
But um
A little but not a lot
But I mean um
You know
If anyone wants to give me $500
By the way you can have a copy of Ninja Gaiden Trilogy
Just saying
In the box
You've been trying to get rid of that for like a year
We just didn't put it on eBay again
Alright
We could probably get money for it
I mean we could at least get $350 for it I'm sure
Alright
Well ok we've had enough talk about the digital distribution
Is that
Well let me just quickly
Let me just quickly kind of ask this question
Cause I asked this to Discord
In five years
Where are we at with digital distribution
Is it 100% of the industry
Is it 80% of the industry
Just quickly let me go around the room
Where is this industry at in five years of digital distribution
Loki?
60%
That seems very conservative
Yeah
Ok
I'm gonna go with 75
75%
Uh I
That's not accounting then for the 25%
That'll be pretty much all collector's items
Collector's editions
This is not where I want it to be
But I'm gonna say 90%
With the 10% being collector's edition
The vinyls of video games basically
I think that we're gonna though see
A good number of like actual
Brick and mortar stores going
Because it's all gonna be online
I think GameStop's in big trouble
I really do
GameStop is gonna go the way
If they don't change their business model
They're gonna go exactly the way that like our blockbusters did
And all that
Because digital really is
And on top of that you know it's really
I think
What's a good word
Attractive for the manufacturers
Because that's less in materials they have to pay
Less labor they have to pay
Less in shipping
They can put that money into advertising
And for digital content instead
And actually throttle
The sales of it if they run
You know hit a particular license number
All they have to do is just
Generate more licenses for it
So they're not the supply
Will always be there to meet the demand
Alright
Alright we'll
We'll probably dive into this topic again
I think this is something that is gonna be following
Our industry for a little while if you want to say something
And if you want to no longer participate at
Orangelaunchradio.com
In the meantime we're gonna talk about our gaming weeks
Because really it's been two weeks since we've been here
So let's talk a little bit about some of the games we've been
Playing this week
Some of the notable highlights
DarkSakura what have you been playing this week?
Idol Poring
Pokemon Go
You know
Me Tomo
I started Dragon Age Inquisition again
Because I fucking love that game
In fact my
Dragon Age fire got lit under me
By a dragon
Also
Crap what else was I playing
A little bit of Ragnarok online
And then I
I got a Switch
And three games
I acquired it
Now this is interesting because when I saw this on your Facebook
Which by the way I still need to like add you on Switch
I figured you would have just found me through the 3DS connection
Dan played it more than me already
Well I had each other eventually but
I assumed you bought one
My assumption was
Oh Mario Odyssey broke them
They finally got a Switch but you won it
I wasn't really supposed to say much about that
Oh sorry
But since no one knows where I work
So I did win it in a raffle
I was keeping it off
Social media for a reason
Oh sorry about that
Because some people do know where I work
I was in the raffle
They were doing cupcakes
At work
And I said you know what
I don't want a cupcake
Well I wanted a cupcake but I was being good
And I put my name in the raffle
One ticket in the raffle
Next thing I know look what you got
Wow
So I have a Switch
I had a Joy-Con with it in three games
There's no shame in that for the record
This is very common for any corporation to do
So you know this is common
But I still
Fair enough
So yeah
I have Arms, I have Breath of the Wild
And I have Mario Kart 8
And we are gonna put in our order
For Odyssey
Coming up
And it's been fun
But Dan decided he was gonna
Take over and play through Mario Kart 8
And then he got the demo for
Puyo Puyo Tetris
Because one of the things is that
I still
I read Japanese like maybe a semi-literate
Five year old
So going through Puyo Puyo Tetris
On PS4 was an adventure
And we eventually
Figured it out to where we could play against each other
And all that but Dan's like I can play it in English
Now meh
So here's the beauty of
A cartridge based world do you wanna just borrow my
Copy cause I rarely play it
Yeah if you guys really wanna play it just borrow my copy
Bring it back
This is like totally Playstation 4 type stuff here
You mean I can swap games without having to switch
Codes and being part of my family network
O M G
Yeah thank you
You're welcome
That'll be my makeup for Blabbing
Okay
But at any rate
It's been
It's been fun, the setup was super easy
I actually
I forgot my password but I could change it through Miitomo
Because it's linked to my Nintendo account
So it was pretty cool
I just put the picture up
Got requests already and I was like hey
This is sweet
So I've been having
We played a little bit of it but that means that I'm gonna start Breath of the Wild on my own
And not play over Dan's game which is on Wii U
Nice
So we have two copies of the same game on different systems
But it'll be interesting
Now you kind of spot those little differences maybe
Probably won't be much in the way of differences
Cause I don't think the Switch
Is that much more graphically
Advanced than the Wii U was
I don't think so either
I think
Everything looked really pretty though on our TV
Cause we have a 4K TV
And it was all clean and pretty
But Switch is only outputting
A 1080 top
It's all about using the emulator
To play that game
Cause then you can output some really good graphics
I did however
Look into the Breath of the Wild emulator
That they've got out there
Basically it's a Wii U emulator
But tweaked for Breath of the Wild
And so I've seen
I've actually gone on this kind of thing
For looking to see how the world was built
Cause I'm very interested in stuff like that
I mean you remember me in World of Warcraft
When we'd go do something and I'd stay in the instance
To just explore
You like to go do screenshots and stuff
You were big on that I remember
Well I haven't figured out how to do anything like that
In Final Fantasy XIV
I actually got my account fixed
Once I decide if I want to get the collector's edition
For Stormblood
Cause that's still $60
And I've got drag queens coming up
Hey
I'm buying both mine and Becky's tickets
I've got to pay her back for them
That's coming up in like two weeks
It is
And that weekend will be after
I have
Oh I'm not talking about that on the show either
More secrets
This one's a big secret but you know what it is
I think so yeah
Anything else for your gaming week?
I like
Cheese
Loki how was your gaming week?
I didn't play anything that I said I was going to play
What?
I know I got lazy
Oh well
I did end up playing a little bit of Minecraft
On Windows 10 the other day
Just to check out I really haven't played that in a long time
So it was a little bit different
And then
What else
I played some more of the stupid
Idol clicker game
For office space
Just because it's the thing to do
And
I
Don't think there's
Much else it was mostly updates
I had got everything cause I was gonna
I wanted to play VR and I was actually gonna go do that
The other day I had everything set up
And then all my controllers
Were dead
So I was like god dammit
So I finally charged everything but I still never
Got around to actually playing it again
But I have everything ready to go now
So I can bust out some VR games
From the PlayStation VR
Hopefully very soon and get all that stuff out of the way
Cause I have like 4 or 5 games that I've purchased
That I've been meaning to actually get to
But I haven't gotten to yet
So there's that and then
What else
Just reinstall some games on Steam
Cause it's gonna go play through some of that
Backlog stuff finally cause there's stuff on there
I'm like oh shit I forgot I have that
So yeah that's it
Alright my gaming week I have a lot
To catch up on so I was
A bit of a sheep I guess some of you want to call me
And I got an iPhone 10
But before you bring the sheep
Emojis at me here's the thing
I use my phone more than any other device
And the phone I was using
Was 3 years old so you know what
I'm worth it I earned it
Treat yo self
Exactly treat yo self
And it is a nice piece of hardware
So I'm a fan so far
I think the animojis are kinda dumb
But Jamie did laugh
When I sent her the unicorn talking
I finally listened to it when I got home
Cause I was at work
But it popped up on
You know I'm looking at my messenger right now
And it pops up on my
Mac
And it actually saves them as little movies
So I can quite literally drag
It out to my desktop
Like I could with all of those Retsuko stickers I got
That's how I put one on Twitter
I sent it to
Alan even though he doesn't have an iPhone
I sent it to him and it just sent him a video
But I saved it to my own phone
And then I posted it to Twitter
I posted something stupid on Twitter
Why can't you just directly share those
To social media
Apple?
You might be able to I just didn't look into it
But the animoji isn't a separate program
It's built into the messenger
But if you're using SMS
It converts it to a video format
I did not buy the phone to be a talking unicorn
And yes I picked the unicorn
Because everybody else is picking the poop
Which is stupid
So I'm the unicorn which is awesome
And the first thing that comes out of this unicorn
Hey girl
I'm like
Oh Rob
Eyes detected
So anyway I've been playing more
Pokemon Go on that
Because it runs so good
And as a congratulations on your
Dumb new phone gift
Alan got me a gotcha
Which is like the Pokemon Go Plus
But you don't even have to push the fucking button
You just walk
And it plays the game for you
Which is awesome
Yes it's so easy
It's just you know
My Apple Watch will do that
But you don't even
Like do you have to tap the Apple Watch
I haven't honestly played with my Apple Watch
You used to have to tap it
But I think you can do a setting on it now
But the thing that I like about having Pokemon Go
On my Apple Watch though
Is that I don't have to have my phone out
You know just walk around
Kossin in chat over at live.vognetwork.com says
My computer is over 9 years old
Guess that means I should buy an AMD Vega
Sure go for it
If you can afford it do it
Slay mama
Like
If you're surprised that that's my answer
Then maybe you don't understand why I got the phone
Enabler, enabler
SSG100 Matt says
I was gonna ask how fast does Pogo
Play on the X
I feel like it's the way it's supposed to be
I can't help but say X
Anyway, Mortal Kombat
Mortal Kombat ruined it for me
All right fancy ruined it for you
You can help it
All right anyway
So anyway other stuff I've been playing
Not just on the new phone
I have been playing
More Heroes of the Storm
Like that is like my online game right now
I am still playing a crap ton of Heroes of the Storm
I'll play it with you, I love that game
I suck at it
Like 90% of what I play is AI
Just to do my quest
But I will say I finally
Just like sucked it up
And I was like okay I'm getting pretty good with
Morales who's a healer character
I'm feeling like I got a good energy
With her, I got MVP in a game
So I was like I'm gonna try a real game with Morales
And I did and I went in the real game
And we won and
The toxic Heroes of the Storm community
Even complimented me on my healing
So now my ego is like
Woo I can do this
I'm gonna be a Heroes of the Storm champion
Cause I'm the Morales king
So now I'm playing more online
So yeah
I'm playing a little bit more
I'll do the quest to kind of screw around
With other characters and stuff
But then if I'm gonna play a hero I'm really comfortable with
I have been doing more quick matches
So that's been a little bit of that
But I wanna talk about new games I've been playing
So I didn't get to talk about them last week
So now I can talk about them this week after I've played them more
I've been playing Destiny 2 on PC
So I bought that
And I started playing that when it came out
And I gotta tell you guys
The game is gorgeous
It looks so good
Now I'm not able to play 4K's
I didn't buy the AMD Vega
That I just told Casa to go buy
So I have a video card that's a couple years old
So I can't play in 4K
But I can play in
Some resolution that's like 1440
So it's a little higher than 1080p
Just ever so slightly
But like
Isn't that like 2K?
I think it might be 2K
So yeah
And just
Like the environments in Destiny 2
Are a lot more varied than they were in the first game
So I just, yeah
The game looks awesome
But it's fun to play too
I'm not usually huge on first person shooters
But with Destiny being a little bit more like
I don't wanna say RPG-ish
But that's kinda how it feels when you have quests
And the fact that people can drop in and out
Like your buddy Crystal
Has been playing matches with me on PC
And Crystal will join matches
And we'll just go do stuff
And then it's like, okay we did a quest
I gotta go
I like that whole drop in and out
That you can help other people type of thing
That's really cool
And then my buddy Delvin, shout out Video Game Realness
My pal over there who hosts that show
He was playing with me on some matches as well
And we were both swooning over Sniper Daddy
So there it is
So Destiny, I'm
Liking way more than I thought I would
And again the visuals
At least on PC
I haven't been playing it on console so I couldn't tell you how it compares
But it looks
So good on PC
But again you wanna make sure you have a video card
That can at least handle it
But mine's a couple years old and is doing okay
And if you're gonna be that guy that goes get that brand new AMD card
Then hey, I bet 4K is gonna look gorgeous
So there you go
Dungeon Buster in Chat says
I've heard a lot of good things about Destiny 2's
Optimization from PC people
Yeah, there's no frame rate cap
So
I probably could play on 4K
But my frame rate would be like 20
So by dipping it down a little bit
I'm able to have a really smooth experience
And I really really like it
So JD says
Sniper Daddy, yes
I don't wanna give too many spoileries away
But in the first area
The guy that you kinda turn Quest into
Is a Sniper Daddy
And he's voiced by, here's the thing
He's voiced by Gideon Emery
Who
Balthier, Fenris
Yeah, Fenris
And the thing is that Gideon Emery
Never changes his voice
For the characters, but there's a reason for that
Everybody is just fine with the voice
That God gave him
So there's that
Just give me a character name so I can Google fan art
I don't remember the character's name
I've been calling him nothing but Sniper Daddy
Somebody in chat knows
The name
Help JD and I out
I don't remember the name of the character
That's kind of embarrassing
One other game that I've been playing
An awful lot of is
Not as much as some of my friends
Cause I haven't beat it yet
But I feel like I'm getting really close
Super Mario Odyssey on the Nintendo Switch
I bought that game when it came out
And I've been playing quite a bit of Super Mario Odyssey
And you guys, I love it
It's just like
If you don't like Super Mario Odyssey
I would really want to know the why
Because I just feel like
There's just so much fun
And Super Mario Odyssey
Just makes me smile
Now I don't want to spoil too bad
But there was one part in the game in particular
Like everybody knows from the trailers
New Donk City, right?
So those that have played the game will know
That there's a certain moment in the new Donk City
When you're playing it
A celebration of sorts
And everybody that's played the game is going to know what I'm talking about here
So like when I was going through that whole sequence
I was like
This is just
This is fucking awesome
Like there's just
This is how playing video games should feel
All the time, every time
This is a fucking delight
What I'm doing right now
And I wish every video game felt like this
And that's where I'm at with Super Mario Odyssey
Are there small nitpicky imperfections
I could maybe get into about the game?
Sure, it looks a little
I think it looks cheaper when it's off the dock
Than it does in the dock
Like I noticed some of the problems and some of the frame rate issue
But honestly, it's so fucking minor
It doesn't matter because the game
Is extraordinarily fucking fun
And that is like
I just love that when I go into a new level
Like all of a sudden there'll be some
Dippy new mini game that's so adorable
That I'll have to play
Like I just went to Snow World
And the only racing thing you have to do
Is these fat little walruses
That you have to like bounce
Because you're a fat fucking walrus
And you have to bounce around
It's so adorable
You do like your test cars
I do
Mario Odyssey kind of has their version of that
And it's super adorable
Dark Tetsuya in chat over at live.vognetwork.com says
Like Breath of the Wild did
For the Zelda games
Yeah, actually Mario Odyssey
Is a lot like Breath of the Wild
In some ways
Not totally, I mean there's a little more structure to it
You go from zone to zone
But like the freedom to do whatever you want
In those zones
Or let's look behind this wall
Because there might be a moon
It's just like Mario 64
It is, and honestly it's the most Mario 64
It's probably the best Mario game since Mario 64
And I even thought
At the time Mario 64
Was kind of overrated
And that's because I had a very hard time
Shifting from 3D to 2D
And I think a lot of gamers of a certain age
Kind of went through this
So Mario 3D was a little harder for me to get into at the time
And believe me guys
I loved Mario Sunshine
I loved Mario Galaxy
I think Mario Galaxy was my game of the year
The year that game came out
Odyssey is even better
Like this is Mario at the top of his game
And I couldn't be happier
If you own a Switch
You're getting this game done
Like there's no, is there a debate
Why would you own a Switch
And not own Mario Odyssey
I just, I don't know
You would have to hate platformers
Or really only be into it for a certain game or something
But just like
If you even remotely enjoy Mario games
Mario Odyssey is fucking great
And I would say
Go for it
So orange right in chat says
My entire gaming week was Mario Odyssey
Are there bushes to hide in in the desert?
Well that was a question
For Dungeon Buster
I guess about, oh, hiding
Being Assassin's Creed-ing across Egypt
There are some different kind of
Mechanics where you can kind of hide in things
And parts where 3D turns
Into 2D and it's really cool
And guess what I got today
In the mail that I'm really excited to play
Well in the mail, UPS from Amazon
I got my Princess Peach wedding emoji
So you know what that means guys
Mario wedding dress time
Woohoo
Dark Sakura
It's like rolling her eyes
Mario drag
Have you seen the pictures of Mario
It's just like
How can you hate it
It's so funny
Like cute
It's just great
Those pictures of Mario in a wedding dress
Running away from a Goomba
It's everything that Mario Odyssey
I love it
Alright
Anyway, Dungeon Buster in chat says
I own a Switch but don't have Odyssey
Yet, well yeah
But it's on your agenda
Like obviously there's gonna be people that are like
I don't have the finances for 60 bucks right now
But I will by the holidays
It's on everybody's radar for sure
So there you go
Alright
So yeah, Mario Odyssey
My highest recommendation of that game
I'm loving it
I've had a very good gaming week
These are all good games that I'm talking about
Heroes of the Storm, Destiny 2
It's a great fucking time to be a gamer
Housekeeping
I already mentioned we won't be here next week
That's a pre-planned night off
Sorry about that
Follow us on Twitter
You can also do Facebook
And Discord
So I'll tell you this now
Stay tuned tonight
I thought what a nice apology
would be tonight
Let's do something, and I looked, do you know it's been over
a year since we've done this on our show
We're gonna bring back a segment
that I know you guys love
We're gonna have ourselves a list list tonight
So stay tuned
List list coming up in part B
I'll tell you the topic later
But it has to do with one of our news stories tonight
So I think we need to get into the news
So we can get to the list list topic
Right, Loki? Let's get into
the news
So let's talk a little bit about it on Paris
Games Week
So they have that big
I don't know if you call it a press conference
trailer sizzle reel I guess
Where they showed off a bunch of new things
from Sony
One of the big IPs they were showing off
was actually a game called
Ghosts of Tsushima
Which is a brand new game
from Sucker Punch
And it kind of looks like
a Ninja Gaiden just based off the
small bit of gameplay that they had
But it basically takes place in feudal
Japan with
Samurais
So it looks pretty cool
So that's something I'm definitely wanting to check out
whenever that comes out
They also showed off
some other stuff including
Let's see
They had this game called Erica
Which is gonna be using that
The
PlayStation integration, the play link
with your phone
So basically you can kind of
pick, it almost looks like a choose
your own adventure type thing
Where she's trying to figure out some sort of mystery
that's going on, try to piece together
like a puzzle or something
Kind of have that quantum
or not quantum break, the
quadratic dream
type look to it
but you know, live action and everything
Interesting
I guess, I don't know, not my type of game
but it is a neat
neat idea to use the phones and everything
Plus I guess one of the gimmicks of it
is you're gonna be able to draw in the world
or touch the world, they said
So it's gonna be using your touch screen
Touch the world
This game actually looked pretty awesome
I feel like that should be a commercial
that airs during the Jerry Springer
show
Pick up the phone, touch
my world
So there's
another game called Onrush
which is like this off-road
racing kind of
cross with like
burnout type of game
So it's a very fast paced, you know
smashing the cars and stuff like that
games gonna be coming out from Ubisoft
on the Playstation 4 and it looks pretty awesome
so definitely
one I'm willing to pick up since
I love me some burnout
and then
one of the things that they also announced
that with the new Monster Hunter World
you're actually gonna be able to play as Aloy
from Horizon Zero Dawn
with the Playstation 4 version
so that's kind of neat for fans of that
of course they also talked about the expansion
that they have for that game
then they've gotta
please buy Monster Hunter World
cause our company's in a lot of trouble
we need this game to be a success
well
I guess, yeah
and then of course
there's some new Playstation VR titles
they had one that kind of looked
a little bit like a spinoff of the
gangster, like a London gangster
thing that they had in Playstation World
but it's this
game called Blood and Truth
and I guess it's just
you know, kind of throwing you into like
some sort of modern
like, I don't even really say it's like
gangster, more
it might even be like a Mission Impossible type thing
or something like that
so lots of gunplay and stuff
and then
what else
they had another game that was kind of lame looking
though that I was not interested in
but lots of VR stuff that they were announcing
so that was kind of cool
and then finally the last thing they had a game called
Ore
and it came out actually
that day when they announced it
and it kind of resembles like
a
game company game
they couldn't say made by that game
company or anything like that but they could say
in the style of Journey and
Flow brings this new adventure
and I heard the reviews were only mediocre
I didn't play it myself
I hear it didn't play that well but it looks similar
to that, you know the same kind of art style
which I mean
Journey was
hands down like one of the greatest
video gaming experiences of the past
ten years, like no question
Journey is up there, so it's
like it's no surprise we're seeing
games inspired by Journey
because it deserves that
It did look kind of neat though because it almost
reminded me of a shooter almost
it seemed like a lot of bullet dodging and stuff like that
so there was that, it's about this boy
kind of can transform into this dragon
like a Chinese dragon
so it was neat
I don't know, I would just check out the trailer
see if something that you might be interested in
check them out but
that's pretty much the major stuff that they announced
during Paris Game Week
Interesting that they announced a lot here because
Sony still has PSX
coming up in the early December
now I thought I saw some tweet
and I don't know if this is you know
take tweets with a grain of salt
but I heard that Sony shifted
some of what they were going to announce at PSX
to this
so some people are saying lower your expectations
for PSX but that
seems strange
the stuff that we kind of mentioned
was just the new stuff but they also had
more trailers for different
games that have already been announced
like God of War had a gameplay trailer
they looked alright, they showed
the redone intro for
Shadow of the Colossus
that remake
which looked pretty gorgeous
so do you think PSX is going to focus on
here's an update on Final Fantasy 7 remake
well they have that
they have that other zombie game that's supposed to be
coming up that they kind of showed a little bit of
before
there's still they can do another
I think they showed the Last of Us 2
trailer as well
so they could always do more of that
they could show hopefully
I'm hoping at this point you know especially since
you know their chummy
and everything we'll see a new Death Stranding
trailer so
yeah so maybe I guess you're right all those things they could
kind of quote unquote get away with
honestly the PSX
conference could be three minutes
long and a win and all they have
to do is come out and say well we know
you've been asking for it so we finally
changed our mind of backwards compatibility
PS1, 2 and 3 games available
today have fun like that could be it
and everybody would be like fuck yeah PSX
was the best year ever
old shit is new again
they're never going to do that though they're not going to do that until they're in
second place it's just frustrating when you're watching
like Microsoft over here going
we're going to take original Xbox games
and make them in 4K and like
meanwhile Sony's like
they're not thinking they're like thinking well PlayStation 4
is so fucking strong and everything
right this generation
but then you look at like when the new consoles
come out and you think hmm you know the PlayStation
4 didn't really have all that mod support
that I liked that the other one had oh hey
you know what those exclusives weren't so great
that was it you know
those games that I was really like banking
on that were going to be really great games maybe
I will go back over there and you know
do Microsoft instead and that's kind of where
it was like this time around because
I don't know PlayStation 4 looked like
it had some really great exclusives but then some of
those games just turn out to be kind of garbage
well yeah SSU100Matt in chat says yeah
I'm not expecting any blockbuster stuff from PSX
show but they like well you
you mentioned that Loki Street Fighter
5 was a PSX announcement
now at the time that was a pretty
fucking big deal now obviously the game came
out and it's
controversial we'll leave it at that they're
trying to salvage what they can with that
but at the time still the fact that
Street Fighter 5 was coming and it's
PlayStation and PC only
and not none for you
Xbox go home that was a pretty big
deal that's the thing about those both those conferences
and stuff and like especially these major game
announcements are like this console and
PC exclusives like fuck yeah
I'm a winner on PC woo I can get all of
this you know that's kind
of like what that's that was that was
me Microsoft E3 yeah exactly
it's really kind of the big thing that's kind of
kept me away from an Xbox one because
I don't feel that I need to have a system
for these games like man I
really want to play Forza wait I have a PC
that can run that and they have it on PC
so I don't need the buyer console
but yeah I you know hope that there's
other games that'd be worthwhile but
there really is not a lot of
exclusives that's why I kind of been just like eh
I'm not really jumping in you know
to getting multiple consoles right now of course
a Switch later because Nintendo's never gonna put stuff
on PC although they do
be fucking awesome come on
emulators eventually
well anyway
yeah I'm gonna temper my expectations
for PSX but I still
there'll be a surprise or two there's gonna
be some big game they're gonna unveil to get
the fans hyped because this is their chance
to get things in front of the fans I don't think it's out
of the question that maybe we'll get something
playable
for Final Fantasy 7 remake
or for Kingdom Hearts 3
like something out of the Square Enix camp
Kingdom Hearts 3 has got to fucking
come out at some point right?
yeah I'm like these games are supposed to be coming out
some day
like I
one of those games has to come out 2018
Crackdown's gotta come out some
day I know it's not
Sony but Jesus Christ man
that was gonna be the game that was gonna
sell me on that console and now I'm like
eh I would think Final Fantasy
remake part 1 is coming 2018
like because again they split that game
into parts and we've already seen
the trailers that show that game in motion
in Midgar
you know some of the opening scenes was like
and that was a year ago so
I would think we're closer than
I mean again
I'm not gonna get my hopes that high up
but I would think Final Fantasy 7 remake part 1
is close
I still have to play through 15
15 was a game I was really excited for
well if you play 15 that's gonna be the same engine
that Final Fantasy 7 remake is running in
so you'll get an idea what to expect
alright
S.H.O.N. and Matt in chat says to be clear
I'm not expecting any sort of Kingdom Hearts 3
Shenmue or Final Fantasy 7
remake news alright that's
don't go in expecting
any of that that way if it does show up
you'll be pleasantly surprised
all C-Man
go expecting
nothing but C-Man
one publisher
that won't be showing up at a Nintendo conference
anytime soon likely is EA
cause EA has mentioned this week
you know we're not really in a rush
to make more video games for the Nintendo
Switch you might remember that EA
kind of has tested the Nintendo Switch
with FIFA 18 being out there
on the platform I would assume
this game's doing alright but in a
recent I guess this was an interview
with the Wall Street Journal since we are talking about
finances the finance chief
Blake Jorgensen said
that basically
they want to wait
for the Switch to be on the market a full
year before deciding whether
to release more games besides
just FIFA 18
they want to wait to quote
fully understand what the demand is
for Switch before committing more
resources to it
it's just cost versus return
on creating another engine because
Frostbite doesn't run on it that's really what it
comes down to and I'm guessing that they probably just
converted because I still think
that they have legacy versions coming out
on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360 still
for FIFA it's one of the few games that they
have that still because in certain regions
they don't have the newer systems or they're
not readily available so that's probably why
they converted FIFA is because they have
the older engine that they're adapting to
it but they're not going to
that's why they're waiting it's got to be a
runaway success before they want to sink money
into it I'm going to tell you what it is cause
my husband hit the nail on the head with this
first thing out of his mouth he said
oh this is because Nintendo is challenged
when it comes to online
and EA wants that sweet loot box
money that's and I was like
you're right you're absolutely right
Nintendo still hasn't unveiled
what their full plan for online is
that's what's holding EA back
I don't think so I think they could still implement
loot boxes if they wanted to they have
does FIFA 18 have loot boxes? yes
they've got the ready
they've got the
what do they call it?
it's like the team thing that they have
they've had those loot boxes for FIFA for a long time
the player cards or whatever they call them
I forget the something team
I don't remember what it's called
well that's been around forever that's why everybody got their accounts on their Xbox 360
or something like that yeah
so it's been around forever so they've had
they had loot boxes and that type of stuff
for the longest time
JD in chat says
to be honest if EA had any sense
they would port Bejeweled to
Switch yeah I mean
EA has that PopCap kind of casual
arm is PopCap still open or did
EA close it? I think they closed it
fuck EA if they did that but I remember
PopCap did a lot more of those
no because they're still making Plants vs. Zombies
and Pagle games
I think they're still around but
they're not kind of what they used to be
under EA which you know
but anyway
but still I mean
you would think that those types of more
casual games would do very
well on something like Switch
oh by the way in a related
update the Nintendo Switch
has sold 7.6
million units
doomed for failure
total failure
7.6 million Switch units
as of September 2017
already more than half the
sales of the Wii U in its
entire lifetime
this includes 4.7
million Zelda Breath of the Wild
4.4 Mario Kart 8
3.6
Splatoon 2
and speaking of
sales Super Mario
Odyssey 2
million copies in 3 days
that's per Nintendo's estimate
that includes bundles
digital sales but
still 2 million copies in 3 days
there ain't a lot of games pushing
numbers like that so it does
put an interesting sort of
when you put that next to EA's
we're gonna wait and see how the Switch does
uh ya boners
the Switch is doing just fine
if you would just figure
out what you are gonna put on this system
EA doesn't make games like Mario
Odyssey they don't make good
games like that anymore
honestly
if
well no cause they'd have to convert
the engine so I guess there's no
Mass Effect to be had on it
what about the original trilogy that could
happen you know because there's been tweets
out there the N7 day is next
week right so and I guess it's the
it's 10 years of Mass Effect this year
and EA I'm still mad I know
well here's my punchline EA put out
a tweet that said come join us to celebrate
10 years of Mass Effect on November 7
so what if they show another
trailer for Anthem that day
I am gonna riot
my reply was
if it's not Cory and Arc DLC which we know
it's not cause they're putting it on a book
or a remaster of the trilogy
go party by yourself which is my nice way
of saying go fuck yourself
after what you did to that franchise
so if you're not gonna invest like
at least if you're gonna say
Andromeda done fucked it all up
if you're not gonna at least then go back and do
the trilogy and remaster that
and put that out you know which
could hypothetically be on the Switch
then you know what
that's a party I ain't going to
have fun
anyhow let's move on to happier news
Dark Sakura what do you have for us
well
you know I love my Animal Crossing
and I'm looking forward to Animal Crossing Pocket Camp
even though I am not going to
you know be an idiot and make an
Australian account just to play it early
when I'm going to have it
soon anyway
but anyway
of course it's already
been data mined for information
put up by CriticalGG
and
there are
I mean it's interesting but not surprising
so as a
campsite manager you will be able to grow your
own plants in the garden
and you have to water them
I mean that's just mainstays
of Animal Crossing
really
but then you also like buy fertilizer
which if I remember correctly came
up in New Leaf
and then you have
soil states normal to dry
to withered
your other
animals can hang out in your gardens
and then there's like plant breeding which again
they also had with the different you know
colors of roses and other
plants in New Leaf
and then you also
are going to have like winter themed locations
different things for different seasons
different facilities
like a school, a shop, a hospital
restaurant, office and hotel
and that's like more of the stuff from
New Leaf so this is really
just like it seems to me
just like normal
Animal Crossing but
updated for
mobile
and of course it doesn't necessarily mean that these
items are going to be
implemented in the game
but the thing that's interesting is that there's costumes
that are found which again there were costumes
in New Leaf and other Animal
Crossing games but it includes Mario
Link and Samus
so you can get those
assets already existed in the other Animal Crossing
games I just think it's cool that
this is really going to look like it's more
like an actual Animal
Crossing so I'm pretty happy
I got to admit
like I don't know what it is I don't know if it's just because
Animal Crossing has not
been about collecting virtual console
games since the original GameCube release
but I'm having a hard time getting
excited about it I mean
of course I'm going to download it because
it's free and of course I'm going to try it
and play it and who knows maybe I'll have a good time
but like when I watched the
Nintendo Direct at the end of it I was just
kind of meh
oh yeah
how about something really
truly different for Animal Crossing I mean
granted they're going to save that for the Switch
probably, hopefully, but I just
I wasn't that excited
I don't know
I'm going to play it and I want one for Switch
I love my Animal Crossing
that's cool
with my Switch I can take it to work
and play it during my lunch
SSJ100Matt says in chat
my girlfriend is all over this Animal Crossing mobile game
which means I will have to be but I'm like Rob
I'm not really feeling it after watching the Direct
Kaijuto though says Animal Crossing
is fun times and JD saying
I'm looking forward to the Animal Crossing game
it's like the Funko dolls
I'm not going to knock you for spending money on
Animal Crossing have fun with it
I like Animal Crossing
but for me it's a little
stale so maybe
the change in setting or maybe some of this other
stuff maybe it will make the mobile version
more interesting but I'm just
I'm not really excited about it
although I did have a laugh
at the whole Tom Nook on the Cash Money Store
because there was a picture
like there's pictures of Tom Nook
selling the different amounts and the highest
amount of like the paper tickets you can buy
is like 50 bucks and it shows
a picture of Tom Nook swimming in a
bathtub full of money and that
cracked me up so at least I was like
well at least there's a sense of humor about
what a disgusting amount of money Nintendo
stands to make off this game
I like that his icon is one you can have
on your Switch
oh yeah that's right it is huh
I have a little version of my Mii
I think doing a little pose
that's like hey
I want to try my amiibos on it
now all my Animal Crossing ones and see if
any of them bring anything up
in certain games
I'm talking about on the actual system
where you can use it to make your avatar
I don't think the system will do no the system won't do anything
but the games will like you can use
any amiibo in Breath of the Wild
only Zelda related ones do
very specific things but the other
amiibos will give you coins, random items
and Mario Odyssey is a very
similar thing like every amiibo
will give you something but only certain
ones like Bridal Peach will give you
something like very specific I wonder if the
Tom Nook one will take your money
it might or if the Resetti one will actually
yell at you that would be
cool alright
let's move on with some more stories
Loki another big event this past weekend
right yes I forgot that BlizzCon was even
this weekend but apparently there is
lots of announcements from that oh you don't
follow the same people I do on Twitter I
couldn't avoid it but it's
you know what I had a lot of fun when I went in
2014 I would love I was
a little pissy that Diablo
was nowhere to be found and
they said it was gonna really not be
a BlizzCon I was a little pissy about that but
you know I was still
I was still living vicariously for my friends
who were there it's really about the community
at these meetups so
they did announce that their
Overwatch is getting another hero
so they have Moira
and or Moira
I guess Moira
Moira I believe is correct
okay she is
a healer and
I guess from
of course Blackwatch
and then they also
showed off a new
map as well which is kind of neat
it's like Blizzard World which I guess
is a tribute to different Blizzard games
it's like Disneyland
it's that China theme park that
ripped it all off that was when I was first looking
I was like oh they got the last laugh on that
didn't they remember the stories about the China
theme park that they built around World of Warcraft
and shit like that's what it is
so I had a good laugh about
that I'll just quickly say
with the Moira thing too
she was completely unexpected because they
haven't really dropped any hints about who the character
would be so
Moira kind of came out of nowhere
so to speak but they also showed
during one of the development panels which I thought was really interesting
they showed a ton
of concept art for like all
these different characters
yeah I thought there was a jet pack cat or something
there was an
it's an illusion to an old
kung fu movie but there was an old
Asian lady with curlers in her hair smoking
a cigarette oh yeah from kung fu
hustle is that yeah there was a character
in Overwatch that looked like that old lady
that was awesome
that would have been fucking rad
jet pack cat in there
yeah jet pack cat would be awesome but who knows
maybe some of these characters will come out
in the future who knows
especially if they get good feedback on it because remember the whole
Pandarian thing remember that was a big old
April Fools joke thing and then all of a sudden
that's true
this expansion you know because people were fans of it
so that was kind of neat and then
in non-Overwatch news of course
this was something that they've
alluded to in the past with shutting down
those servers but
World of Warcraft classic is finally
announced which is going to be basically
the vanilla World of Warcraft
before you know they added
all the expansions ugh all those people are welcome
to that shit go
have fun everybody
I don't miss having to elementally
do my weapons
or training with my weapon
I don't miss that shit
they can have it I know everybody that's like
back in the day World of Warcraft actually
used to be hard you know when they first
announced the news I was like why the fuck did
Blizzard give in to those people why did they give them those
people they're going to do all this work
building those servers then people are going to be like
oh yeah this game sucks
what's it's fuck outside Orgrimmar
were it was like
they divided it into two areas now
I've come around on my
perspective if that's
go build the classic zone
get those fucking people out
of the game all those people that are like
back in my day fine go
be here go have fun go have fun
in your playground that is not
going to be as good as you remember
have a blast going to level 40 to get your
mount have a great time
maybe I'll come back to wow who knows
but I wasn't really feeling
the rest of the news that they announced Loki
yeah so um
yeah along with that of course
they did announce that if you are
you know like most people that do
enjoy the expansions they have another
expansion coming so they have
a horde versus alliance expansion
called the battle for
Azeroth which has a new
continent uh Zandalar
and new dungeon raids
and uncharted
islands and
I guess um you also have
uh you know basically
um supporting
the you know different alliances
in this alliance versus horde war
how long
have people been talking about having
the Zandalar stuff like
since vanilla at least
Lich King when that was really front and center
in one particular zone there right
so why are they announcing
this shit after I've decided to move on
that's why they're doing it but I
gotta say my I was not
I didn't
again I was kind of meh at the expansion
news I wasn't really feeling it like when they were talking
this whole line about we're going back to
the war in Warcraft and going back to our roots
I'm like you say the same thing every
expansion when you introduce
Mists of Pandaria you said
we're going back to horde versus alliance
and we all saw how that turned out
so forgive
me if I give a little side eye to this whole
we're going back to our roots uh huh
sure Jan honestly I'm
tired of the whole horde versus alliance thing
I would rather like have
a neutral faction
horde an alliance fuck party is that
something you'd play it'll be called
the whoreliance
and then
finally last but not least they
said that Starcraft 2 is going free to play
so you can actually
on November 14th it will download
Wings of Liberty
the campaign without paying anything
and you get access to both single and
multiplayer for free
that's a pretty big deal for a lot of
people that Starcraft will be free but it
sounds like it's free but
it sounds kinda limited
it sounds like you have to buy the expansions if you want
those they're just not selling the base game anymore and then
apparently if you just have Wings of Liberty
they'll also give you the first expansion
that's me I only have
Wings of Liberty but never really play the game after that
so you'll get that at least
so that's cool I guess if you want to
try it out and of course they have the
Starcraft
remaster that you can check that out too so
that's also free
you did miss the news for the current Blizzard game I'm all
about which is Heroes of the Storm
oh yeah so they have more Overwatch characters
coming to it? Just one Hanzo
which is like the worst Overwatch
character I'm sorry but people are gonna disagree
with me on that but
actually he makes
as much as I kinda give him shit in Overwatch
he makes a lot of sense for Heroes of the Storm
like his abilities especially the dragon
thing for a lane game are gonna be great
so alright whatever and then Alex
Straza looks pretty cool I guess but you know
here's the thing with
all that Blizzard kind of announces
new heroes throughout the year all
the time like we just got
within the past six weeks
Ana and Junkrat from Overwatch
so the whole reveal
of Hanzo and Alex Straza
at Blizzcon didn't feel
exactly like oooh
you know so it's like oh okay this is
the next months and they're just doing it on stage at
Blizzcon so oh
and there's another game Hearthstone
they have a new expansion too
something about the Hoggers and a silly
little theme song that goes with it because there's always
some silly little theme song that goes with it
so but I don't play a lot of Hearthstone
sorry guys but I know some people are super into that
so your requisite
Blizzcon announcement of a Hearthstone
expansion did indeed occur done
alright
going to chat
over at live.vognetwork.com
SHO100Matt says wow Hanzo
shade you know what
let's see Ragenator says if Hanzo was in a valley
would he be Hanzo low
and shoot first?
oh god
yes he would
no no no because
I quit I'm done with this show
I quit here's my letter of resignation
no no no no Han didn't shoot first
Han shot only
alright
but Han's taking medication to fix that
problem so
moving on just for that
next story oh it's my story god dammit
alright
just for that we're doing sad
news first off for sad news
and actually I don't mean to make light of this because
this news really does suck runic
games has been closed if you don't know them
by name you probably know the games they made
does EA own them? no
actually perfect world owns runic
games does EA own them? no
torchlight and torchlight 2
were the big games that runic made which
coming off this news of no diablo
news we've seen these other games that
kind of come in and you know pick up the slack
what was it Grim Dawn's another one that's
pretty good I mean that's not runic but you know there's
other like diablo clones out there
oh path of exiles the other
huge one right but anyway sadly
torchlight which was pretty good I
really enjoyed it runic games has been
closed that fucking sucks
they also were making a MOBA
called gigantic but
sadly they have closed
runic games which was located in
Seattle perfect world
in a statement said that that gigantic
will quote continue to be available on all
our platforms and runic will
remain a part of perfect world entertainment's portfolio
of studios
they also went to say for those
that love the torchlight series
there will be some news coming that's from
runic studio head Marsh Leffler
and for all our fans our
community and multiplayer services will keep running
even after the studio's lights go off
you haven't heard the last of us
so it makes me think that another developer
will be taking the reins for torchlight 3
or whatever is next in torchlight's
future but sadly a moment
of silence for our pals at runic games
that's not fun news to talk about
also not fun to talk about is
house mark apparently says
they're no longer going to make arcade games
and that means like arcade style games
this was in a blog
from CEO Larry
Quintonen sorry
I'm totally mispronouncing that but in this open
letter said despite critical success
and numerous awards our games just
haven't sold in significant numbers
are they the ones that did super stardust or something?
they are the ones that did super stardust as
well as rezogun which were huge
titles here's the thing
I was like wait a minute didn't house mark
have a game that I really wanted to play coming out
they did it's next
Mashina was the other
game that they were doing
and actually did you
know that next Mashina came out
that was that game they showed at E3 that was
the big trailer they had with it
and Eugene Jarvis was a part
of this game which is a pretty big deal he was
back in the day was he Robotron
Defender, Defender was the game that Eugene
Jarvis did so
it was a big deal that he was partnering up
that game came out over the summer
I had no
idea and I wanted to play that game
so
I need to go back on my Playstation 4 and
get it but can I just say that
like you know now granted look
this podcast thing is a
hobby Twitter isn't everything
although it's a lot but I'm just saying like
I really liked what I saw at E3
I had no
idea this game came out already
I think
that should say something about why the game wasn't selling
did
you guys know that it came out because
I missed it it's also to the Sony
storefront that they have their Playstation
stores kind of crap I would
I would agree with that it's time for it to evolve
it needs an evolution it needs a fresh coat of
paint I'll give you that
because there will be games that I know
like are coming out like for example there was
that Megaton Rainfall game
that I was looking forward to
and it was supposed to come out on a certain day
and it was like only a couple days away from it and it wasn't on the storefront
anywhere I was like okay well shit you know I was
gonna market for download or pre-purchase or something
like that and it wasn't there and all of a sudden like
oh yeah it's up now and it's like
okay well there's the store page but like
all these other games have like coming soon pages
and everything where's all this shit
well now and I do want to clarify Housemark
hasn't announced that they're closing they're just
announcing that they're making different games
now so that's fine I mean well that's
fine if a company wants to branch out and do different games but
honestly the shocking part
of that story honest to god for me and maybe
I was just in the dark or playing something else
the most shocking part of that story was that that game came out
and I had no idea
oops I guess I'm part of the problem
Kaijuto said it was
all over the PSVR store page it was a
PSVR game?
I had no idea
it was a VR game?
I didn't know that
I figured since they kept talking about
Robotron and name checking Eugene Jarvis
I figured it was kind of like a modern version of Robotron
with some awesome Tron
looking music and stages and stuff
that's and I was here for that so
I had no idea it was a VR game
oh boy
alright well good luck to Housemark
with their future development and
promotion of the things that they put out
that's for sure so
anyway and Dark Tetsuya confirming
yeah it is oh I mean it's like
Robotron alright well Dark Tetsuya
Dark Tetsuya figured out that that
game came out I somehow missed that
sorry about that oops I killed
that franchise sorry guys
Dark Sakura what do you have for us?
treasure
buried treasure? no my favorite
no treasure like Radiant Silver Gun
and Ikaruga well that's pretty cool too
Gunstar Heroes
so there was a rumor
that treasure was going to stop making new
games but
no
the last new game that they
did was Geist Crusher God that came out in
anyway
the rumor was that
they were going to go as an IP holding company
but their president
Mayagawa Masato said
that they have an announcement
coming out in 2018 and
that treasure is not going to make social
games as long as he lives
the quote I'll never work on
social games for as long as I live
I'll have something to share next
year somebody's taking
a stand somebody has had it officially
right?
but anyway he also
was complaining
about the lack of communication
at Sega when they were working
on Mega Drive games especially when they were working
on Yu Yu Hakusho and
they said Gunstar Heroes shipped
70,000 units in Japan and
200,000 abroad and that the
the
first run of it in
Japan ran out really quickly he also wishes
that Sega would do a
Mega Drive mini like what Nintendo
is doing and not licensed out by a third
party so that it actually is the right
you know
hardware to run the games
so
anyway
we've got some things
here from Treasure from next year that's going to be pretty
exciting I love Treasure
would you like a Dreamcast mini
or like a... Dude a Dreamcast
mini would be rad
of course how
many you know
burned GD-ROMs
do we have
in existence?
how many times how many of us
own
have a copy of
Mario Brothers or Super Mario Brothers
and ROMs and stuff everybody does but it doesn't mean
they're not going to buy the system
I'd buy a Dreamcast mini
oh hell yeah I'd buy a Dreamcast mini
especially if they put PSO
again on it you know I don't know
how that would work but I would be here for that
who cares this is fantasy world that we're talking
fantasy zone
I don't think it's in our
show role at all but PSO2
is getting like some neat skins
like I tend to leave
that stuff out because it just causes me pain
well I mean there's
but like they're supposed to be getting
um
oh god what was it like
one of the Shining games
skins for that
and uh virtual on
so that may be enough
to make me re-download it
alright just a few more stories
before we get to the classic system of the month
but first Loki
yes so Call of Duty World War 2
finally came out and
there's of course
controversy
uh well first off
you know they have the controversy that
for some stupid reason
they have Trevor T. Martin
actually
promoting the game
and he was best known
for violating
Federal Trade Commission regulations
by owning a
Counter Strike skin gambling
site and not
disclosing that so
he's apparently doing I guess
a race of prestige
fundraiser type thing
I don't know I think it's
dumb but all the more reason
not to really give a shit about this
um one of the big things
though that's kind of annoying though and remember
we talked about this whole
um patent that
Activision had done
and they said no we're not using this patent
in Destiny 2 or whatever about
loot boxes and basically
finding ways to get people you know
oh exposed to loot boxes
and you know manipulating people
in certain ways guess what
Call of Duty World War 2 has
it's not in Destiny
it's not in Destiny but guess what it has
it has fucking loot boxes
because I know when people are in
World War 2 loot boxes fell from the
fucking heavens and you know
there's literally like achievements
and goals in the game to watch people because
when people get there's like a social area
first off so the beach of Normandy is a
social area so many things are wrong
with that in the first place wow
so wow there's that
and then apparently as
you're doing that when you get loot boxes
other players can see them drop from
the sky and see what cool shit you
got as like some sort of
subliminal way to say oh maybe you should
purchase some fucking loot boxes
like a certain patent that a certain company
made that said oh don't worry
it's not evil we're just thinking
about ideas except we're totally gonna do this
in the next Call of Duty what you're describing
is like a parody
of what gaming has become
but it's fucking real
yes so
on top the social zone
of the beach of Normandy
yes so yeah
they have these socializations
what other cool things do they have in
there as well well apparently
you can also
uhhhh
play Pitfall
well I do like Pitfall
who doesn't like Pitfall but yes you can play
Pitfall 2 even
better I love Pitfall 2 I think you actually
have to purchase some of these so
yeah they have a rest and relaxation thing
so they have
it's a fucking loot box isn't it you have to purchase
them with in game money or whatever
but they've got and I don't know
if it's per play
but apparently you can go to
an R&R tent and they have Pitfall 2
Grand Prix, Fishing Derby
Enduro, Kaboom
River Raid
okay so all the old 2600 Activision
yes all the old Activision
games which is all on those
Flashback consoles because Flashbacks
are on version 8 this year
and the big thing that they got was
Activision licenses so like all those
exact same games you just named are on those
Flashback 8 consoles
yeah just except
I don't think Pitfall 2 is in it but Pitfall 1
is
so it's just
something that they have in this part of this hub
now
alrighty
to register participation for this
week's episode of Orange Island Radio at
vognetwork.com use the passphrase
home
so yeah well look I'm all for
classic games being available and all this stuff
but if they charge you per play
that's a little silly I don't think
I don't think they're charging probably per play
doesn't specifically state that that would be
kind of lame because who would do that
but they're like you know it
doesn't look like it's that much currency it's like
10 currency or something like that
10 whatever loot
I don't know what the fuck they're
10 lootie points
10 looties
are
you found the lootie
alright and one more story
for you before we get to the classic game of the week
and it's about the video game
Just Dance have you played Just Dance
recently? no not for several
years it's a
a franchise I've kind of fallen out of
taking the world by storm
well apparently it is I mean they still
they're still putting them out
Just Dance 2018 is out there
yeah because they don't have to update their
engine or anything they spit them out
every year because they still have it coming out on the original Wii
so apparently
these games are so popular that
it's justifying the existence of
Just Dance Live
that's right
4 places in North America
if you are one of the lucky residents of
Miami, Chicago
Houston or Los Angeles
guess what Just Dance Live
is coming to your town
what is Just Dance Live?
I don't fucking know because I can't
figure it out from the trailer it looks like
it's just a kid friendly
rave meaning
all the glow sticks and none of the ecstasy
I think that's what it is
um
apparently there will be dancers
and by the way Just Dance has like
degrees as dancers too
you can't actually be playing Just Dance without having
like a panda bear like a character
doing the dances
yeah they said there's characters on stage
that you follow they're iconic
once again Ubisoft misusing
the word iconic
Just Dance moves
girl that panda dance
iconic
like I'm sure that like you know the
iconic moves of like
no
any of the moves that they do in the game
which is iconic I guess
colorful characters dancing live on stage
you follow along share the thrill
with your friends and family
pricing from $45
to $99
for the VIP experience
okay to be fair
it does sound to me like this is an event
for kids like when I say kid friendly
rave like there's a half truth
to that so
Loki this begs the question
take your kids to the Just Dance
live first off
my kids don't know what Just Dance is
um so no
I would not do that and I was
just curious oh my god
fucking hell is wrong with these people
are you watching the trailer
it's pretty late though I mean they've got
like you know
8.30 it starts at 8.30
there's two shows
one is late and one is
matinee okay so the matinee
whatever but like
no no
no no no alright for the
VIP experience
for that $99 you get glow up
glasses an exclusive
drawstring bag and VIP
glow laminate and you get an
in-game reward for Just Dance and a meet
and greet with the cast after the show
although I should point out
although it's been in many of her music videos
Katy Perry is not going to be there
at the Just Dance event in fact
no actual
recording artist that you know from
these games except unless there's like an
in-house band or something will not
be there so you are meeting
people
that are just dressed up
you're meeting costume
characters
that
it's awfully bold of
them to assume
that this is so big that
I
I just can't
you can't
you can't literally
let's put this back okay so they have like dancing
with the stars and they do live stage
performances of that but that you're watching an
actual skilled person that like
knows how to ballroom dance and that's like
that's actually kind of entertaining because you
know what C-list celebrities which are
you know so you know what you're going
into that but this is like
it's just people playing
the fucking game basically
you're watching them and doing the same
shit why would I pay
$45 to go to an arena
to do that
even if I was a kid I could think of
way better things I'd spend my money on
how about a copy of Just Dance
come on Noel Gustin our chat
over at live.vognetwork.com says
Rob if they had an ABBA themed
one you'd be there
how dare you drag me and
read me so accurately in front of our
dozens and dozens of listeners how very
would you though would you would you seriously
go pay they wouldn't be ABBA
singing it would just be pre-recorded ABBA music
with some dumbasses on stage
dancing to it would you pay
$45 to watch
people dancing to ABBA
well see here's the thing here's the thing
like I want to say I want
to have my pride I want to
say no Loki I would not
but the reality is
I'm pretty sure there actually is a show
in Reno where drag queens
do ABBA songs but that's drag queens
okay that's some talented people this
is fucking
did our token straight person
here on Orange Lounge Radio just
say drag queens are more talented
than the Just Dance live crew yes because it's
fucking this panda bear that I
see on my screen I am the
proudest gay I am the proudest
seriously like there's this the
picture that they have of the Just Dance live
interactive experience that's
quite a bold statement right there
you know they have this
and sorry
for using this word because they use
it quite often but sorry fucking
retarded looking panda bear it is
the most stupid derpy
panda bear I have ever seen
and don't get me wrong like
this would be different if it was like a
character that people know but no one's like
oh my god I love panda
bear from
Just Dance yeah I'm totally dressing up
on Halloween as panda bear the well
known iconic character
nobody does that
nobody is that into
just it's a casual game the only
hardcore into a casual game like this
the only Just Dance I care about is Lady Gaga
uh JD in chat says
uh they also have an Abba Just
Dance game yeah I'm aware
Dark Sakura may have seen me play that
I thought that was Singstar Abba no
there's both and I may own both there's
there's a Singstar Abba Tiara was here for
that yes okay so I'm gonna
I don't want to talk
you love Just Dance
the game and showing stupid
people dancing at home now experience
dumb asses on
stage okay I'll
tell you what this is okay think
think back really gonna rant about
no no no no no hold on hold on think back
to the last few
E3s okay think back to
E3s and think back to the Ubisoft
conferences okay what is seriously
the best part of every Ubisoft title
is it I'm surprised
you didn't say it's the Just Dance
performances because I know every time I see those
Just Dance performances on any of those
Ubisoft conferences like holy
fuck this is stupid and cringy as
shit this is what people are paying
money to go see why
why would you say that
well if they say Aisha Tyler's
gonna be there now I haven't said I'll
tell you what I'm sure that these people
that listen to these songs like the artists
that sing these songs how about you put that
$25 towards a ticket and actually see the real
artist go
on stage and perform because that's fucking
worth spending money on not watching
a bunch of nobodies dance to a
song that's why you have Just Dance
so you can be a bunch of nobodies dancing to
a song you don't need to pay money to
go to an event to do that calm down
Marissa Congusto our
our pal we love her in our chat saying
dumb asses on stage was rejected
by the marketing team
alright
look we have got to move on
but maybe we'll revisit
this topic a little later Wink
in the meantime we need to get to
a segment we do here on the show quite
regularly called the classic
game of the week except
plot twist dark soccer
sometimes like it's really a plot
11 months and once
a month she does the classic system
of the month this is the next to last one
it is and it's actually not one
that wasn't on our original list you
changed it I did
because this one's pretty fucking awesome
alright well that's alright it's your segment you can do whatever the hell
you want it's the classic game of the week
or this week the classic system of the month
as it was known in
Japan the
X Rokuman Hasen which just sounds
so cool this thing allowed
the X68000
which is a home computer that was made
by Sharp it was first released in
1987 only in
Japan it had
first model of 10 megahertz
Motorola 68000 CPU
one whole meg of ram
and no hard drive
the last one that came
out which was in 1993 had a
25 megahertz Motorola
30 CPU
4 meg of ram
and an
optional 80 megabyte
SCSI hard drive it was so SCSI
at any rate
this was
pretty much the thing to have if
you liked your Capcom games
basically most of the
and also you could expand the ram to
12 megabytes but it didn't really
need more than two for most of the games
so anyway it's
operating system was called human
86000 which was developed
by Sharp and
actually developed for Sharp by Hudson
soft and we know Hudson was
actually really big in bed with
with
NEC at the time
oh a lot of questions
were just answered this video just got to a segment
from Parodius Da
which I know is one of your favorites
yeah
it had really a lot of great games on it
it looks really, he said this is
93 as he just ended
yeah 87 to 93
this looks really good for a system of that time
well and I picked just basically
you know like some of the top 10
or top 30 games for my video on it
but it also
was like a tall tower
it was white because
apparently I guess light colored
systems do well in Japan
maybe anyway
it also
had
it would also function as
with a cable ready
TV set with composite video input
it also
could
the display that came with it I'm sorry
would also work for JAMA
arcade boards because it had RGB input
and a
standard resolution refresh timing
so pretty good
it used
a hard disk interface
which was the
SASI sassy
I want to call it
that basically
the later versions though went with the
which was pretty much a standard
for a long time and then I guess
it got
you know replaced by something better
it did not support
the vfat file name
standard that went with windows systems
it had an 18.3
character file name instead of the 8.3
allowed in the fat system
so yeah just some
background on it but the thing that made this the best
the thing that made this the best is
because the
2000 had very
similar hardware
to what arcade machines
ran at the time and it also
was the Capcom CPS
system development machine
it had different text
it could support separate text ram graphic ram
and hardware sprites as well
it also had Yamaha's
basically best synthesizer at the time
and it was
the thing I mean basically
games that were made
for this system were
Parodius Da as we saw
Ghouls and Ghosts, Strider, Final Fight, Alien
Syndrome, Street Fighter 2
Dash and
actually one of the best Castlevania
versions the original
Akumajo Dracula
that was later on ported
to Playstation with Castlevania Chronicles
Chorensha 68000
which basically was
ported to Windows later
and it
really just allowed for
beautiful graphics and
I mean arcade perfect sound
was amazing on it again
everything that the system
that basically came out on the system
was like having an arcade
version in your home
it really was the one to have
I would love to have one if I could find
one I mean
it'd be fun to hook
that up and play different
things you know I think it would be
the Legend of the Valkyrie we're looking at
is it? I missed the name sorry
oh well but anyway
just to go over
a list of a few more of the games that came out
on it a couple of little things
that people might
might recognize is
we had After Burner
came out on it Alien Syndrome
like I said
we had
Asuka 120% Burning Festival
we had Atomic Robo Kid
Battle Chess
I fucking love Battle Chess by the way
a game called Blodia
several Bomberman games
Bubble Bobble
Chase HQ
Columns
it's a cotton game
Cotton Fantastic Night Dreams
this system has your name written all over it
it's like all your favorite games
I'm really surprised you don't have one of these
well they're pretty expensive
I mean like I said Daimakemura
is Ghost and Goblins
Daytona Twinbee
several Dragon Knight games
I'm just going through the list here
you don't have to read the whole list
Emerald Dragon came out on this
Emerald Dragon which I
which is kind of like one of the
golden games to have for
the PC Engine
that came out on this
we had Final Fight, Fantasy Zone
all the stuff that I fucking love
Galaga 98
and several of the Garo Densetsu
games which was Fatal Fury
so
hey
this is the thing to have
yeah so if you
have one to give away Dark Sakura would like to talk to you
honestly
even if you could find one just for a good
affordable price I'd be down for it
I would give someone else's right
arm for this
alright anything else to say about this?
no I know this system looks
this is like Dark Sakura's like somebody made
this just for you if you actually
want to see really good comparisons
for how well this ran everything
in comparison to its
uh
what's the word, contemporaries
look for
oh shit Salamander which was Life Force
but look for
the channel that does Battle of
the Ports and
he's really good
I mean a lot of them are played emulated but it
really does showcase how
great this system is compared
to its contemporaries that were out at the time
especially like the ZX Spectrum
I mean that was just kind of sad
but it's worth a shot I mean
really really really if
on my
holy grail of systems to have
this would be at the top of it followed by
the Mardi or the FM Towns
Mardi and then
probably after that well I'd still really
like a duo RX
so
there it is your classic system of the month
the Sharp X68000
good pick Dark Sakura
I didn't really know a lot about that system
but it looks really
I mean just looking at the video it's looking
like arcade versions it would be
just it's on my list
I would need you underwear for that system
alright we're gonna take
a break but when we come back we have plenty more show
we're gonna get into rapid fire news your email
and I promise a list list tonight so
we're already two hours in so we're gonna
we're gonna try to get
through our break here and get back to part B
so we can give you some more show here to hold you
over since this has gotta last you two weeks
so we'll be back after a quick break with more
of Orange Lounge Radio right
after this
Music
Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio
live here on November 5th with
episode number 706 of our show
already in progress probably gonna be a little
bit of a longer show tonight but seeing as we
didn't have a show last week we don't have one next week I guess
we gotta give you a nice long show we're making up for it
hold you over make up for it a little bit
quickly before we get into rapid fire
news did I hear you right Loki
during the break or before the break you picked up
the Animal Crossing ape like I guess
did you go on the dark web and figure out how to get
Animal Crossing yes the dark web
of Google yes oh is that all
okay yeah you just do a search for
Animal Crossing pocket
whatever APK and
there it is it's just that easy so you
are you checking it out now what do you think it's
Animal Crossing
there it is
I mean it looks nice
alright
I don't know if I'd play it very
long you haven't had enough time
to really it looks okay yeah fair
enough alright let's get into some rapid
fire news Loki
alright so um
PlayStation Plus they announced what games are
coming out in November I am sorely
disappointed because I actually own all these
uh at least the VR
games um but you get
Worms battleground on PlayStation
4 I guess I don't have that bound
which is an alright
PlayStation VR PlayStation
4 game uh the one though I do recommend
and really there's no reason you shouldn't
have this if you have a PlayStation VR
but Until Dawn Rush of Blood
is free and that's just seriously one of
the best games on the on the platform
um so definitely check that out
that's you it's on
Playlink and then of course on
PlayStation 3 R-Type Dimensions
on PlayStation 3 and Ragdoll
Kung Fu Fists of Plastic on
PS3 then they have um
Fravita Dungeon Punks
uh which is also cross platform with
PlayStation 4 and Broken Sword 5
The Serpent's Curse episode 1 and 2
which is on Vita and
those should be available shortly
um and then of course
another thing coming to the PlayStation
VR um platform
as well sorry I was giving
Loki theme music there sorry
um is Stranger Things
the VR experience now
I'm not sure what exactly this is
um they kinda showed a little bit
of a teaser but it
sorta resembles the
I don't know if it was a VR experience
or like a 360
video that I watched for Stranger Things
um they had something that was kinda
tied in with like the first season of
of the show
it was in like Will's house and stuff
and it was alright
if that's the same thing I hope it's
more to that because I would like
something a little bit more elaborate but
I'm thinking it may just be that because
that was available on the mobile VR
platforms not too long ago
but we'll see hopefully it's something
more exciting
alright well guess what the modders are
up to recently they're still playing with
Super Mario 64 this time it's not about that
multiplayer thing that uh
got the uh the other
uh Mario thing shut down but this time it looks like
somebody's put a portal gun
into Super Mario 64
this was by modder
Kaze Emanuar
who did a video called Portal
Mario 64 which of course you can download
right now before Nintendo shuts it down
and you can do the portal mechanic from Portal
with Super Mario 64
I mean need I say more about that
sounds awesome
yeah it does sound awesome
why not both
yes why not both
I think we talked about this console
not that long ago but it's the super
retro bit micro console
I think they had a regular version of this that was
kind of amped but now they have a new one coming out
and it was going to be Capcom and Data East
titles like Strider, Final Fight, Joe
and Mac well they
also kind of teased it with and more
to come right well now we figured out
what the more is Technos
is the next publisher
from the classic days that it's
going to be contributing to this which means
Double Dragon will be coming
to this as well as
Combat Tribes and Renegade
so there it is 60 bucks for the
console which I guess is coming out later
this year that's kind of neat Dark
Sakura what do you have for us
well I guess kind of sadness
except he's doing it on
why didn't it open
sorry I just had a slight technical
difficulty because it tried to open the
RSS version yay
anyway the
producer of Danganronpa
Saito Yuichiro is leaving
Spike Chunsoft
basically
he said as of
the end of October he's resigned
and
they did a Danganronpa
surprise farewell party for him
and he's going to be doing
console games for
a different world
he said and he's also
wearing
in this
he's wearing Doraemon pajamas because
he's also a big Doraemon fan which
I think is funny because the
original voice actor for
Monokuma was also
Doraemon back in the day so
pretty cool although
he or she's not doing very well so very
sad and then an easter egg
an ass creed sorry
assassin's creed
because they like the ass
is
the TARDIS so basically if
you're in Letopolis
going through ancient
Egypt under the
water you will see a
stone TARDIS it is very
clearly the TARDIS as well
so the
doctor was here
and that's it
alright let's travel around
and check out what is in stores
this week at a store near you
starting with Loki so this week we have
Farming Simulator the Nintendo
Switch edition coming to
of course the Nintendo Switch
Neo on
PC Sonic Forces
on PC PlayStation
4 Xbox One and the Switch
hopefully that doesn't suck
but I'm afraid it might
Super Lucky's Tales on
PC and Xbox
One Ace of
Seafood on PlayStation 4
Doom on the
Nintendo Switch
Football Manager on PC Mac and
Linux Mario Party
the Top 100 on 3DS
and Need for
Speed Payback on
PC PlayStation 4
and Xbox One that's
it alright well let's travel
to Japan everybody in the plane right now
and check out the releases over there
including on November 9th
hey that DJ Max
Respect gets its Japanese
release I was wondering when that was going to happen
so DJ Max Respect gets its release in
Japan on November 9th I wonder if we'll get that in the
US at some point on the PlayStation 4
also coming out in Japan Sonic Forces
Occultic 9
in regular and limited edition as well
as Sudden Strike 4
and lastly
Taihei no Arashi
Shijo Saitai no
Gekisen Normandy Kobusen
comes out from System Soft
and that is some type of
tanks and war
sim type games I think that's kind of in the
vein of Nobunaga's ambition
let's see if there's anything on the Vita
this week yeah that Occultic 9
is in a regular and limited edition
on the Vita as well this week
and checking out the Switch this week
Sonic Forces gets
its Japanese release as well on the 9th
Shin Sangokumusou 7
Empires as well on the 9th
and Musou Orochi 2 Ultimate
and Monopoly
for the Nintendo Switch also coming out in Japan
lastly on the 3DS
this week some new Amiibo
makes its way out to Japan
but I don't think we really have
any major releases in Japan this week
one minor one
Cake Yasen Monogatari
Oishi Sweet
wo su koru comes out
this week oh my god I want to play a cake
game it's a cake game it's a cake baking
game it's
it's like Legend of Cake
or something like that yeah
maybe it's like Iron Chef
but with cakes
I want to be the ultimate patissier
I want to be the ultimate cake eater
anyway it's probably quiet this week because
next week there's a little game coming out in Japan
called oh it's actually two of them Pokemon
Ultra Sun and Ultra Moon
and I think there'll be a lot of people excited about
that on the 3DS
alright how about the UK Dark Sakura
we have on the 7th
Super Lucky's Tale
on PC and the bone
sorry the X bone and god
dammit it's doing it again okay
and then on the 10th Football Manager 2018
and that's it
it
all over
but we have to go to the mail bag
we're not done hearing from Dark Sakura
just yet
every week you guys email us
participate at orangelaungeradio.com
and Dark Sakura dives in the mail bag
head first and finds some emails
worth our time reading on the show
although with the weeks and weeks
and weeks of no show
I'm sure we've been flooded with emails
one
stinkin' email let's get to it
hello LR
hi YYR you're the only one who starts it that way
after the
continued discussion last week on
free-to-play style monetizations
and loot boxes being present in AAA games
nowadays
and about the potential reasons why I felt
a need to chime in because something about
this seems a bit familiar to me
throughout my life I've spent a lot of time
in arcades but I started talking to
owners and operators when I was in college
back then in 1999
I remember the operator
of an Aladdin's castle asking me
what do you think the biggest earning
game in this place is? Tekken Tag Tournament
was hugely popular upon its
release I was
one of probably at least a dozen players
who played it every weekend
so that was my guess but that wasn't the
answer I was shocked when
this man said to me it's that coin pusher
over there
just a few years ago I owned a DJMax Technica
cabinet and made a deal with the owner
of an arcade in Queens to host it there
and split the revenues I love
the fact that he also had several other
fantastic hardcore games such as
DDRX2
the latest
Beatmania 2DX and Popin' Music
plus an Initial D, Maximum Tune
Tekken 6 and others being conveyed
to me a sad truth the loyal crowd of
hardcore players the ones that kept coming
back to play these games over and over again
were not nearly enough to keep his doors open
the casual players that fed his ticket
redemption and prized games were a far greater
source of income
backing up this theory even
further is the story of
Nanowet Arcade
which opened in Fall 2014
and was filled to the brim with over 50 arcade games
spanning all eras and genre
plus a number of pinball tables
but absolutely no ticket redemption at all
when I visited it felt like someone's dream
arcade but with no redemption I wondered about its
long term viability as it turned out
it closed forever just a few days before its first
birthday so what does this
have to do with loot boxes and console games
here it is think back
to a generation or two every time
a movie came out there were console
and handheld games to match
you had games for kids
games based on Disney properties
games for casuals games for families
this is all because you had
millions upon millions of casual
console gamers where are they now
the answer is simple poking away at
phones and tablets
according to a statistics site
around 69 million of the most popular game
consoles and handhelds were sold worldwide
in 2011 by 2016
this figure shrank to around 27 million
that's a drop of more than 50%
the same sites claim that within the
US overall dollar sales of consoles
and handheld video games dropped about
50% between 2009 and 2015
with spending on social media
based and mobile games more than doubling
over that same period
over the last few years our hardware has progressed
AAA games look better than ever
budgets have fattened
development team sizes have increased and even
worse market competition has exploded
and yet the casual audience who used to
generate half the revenue has all but
vanished from the arcade of the modern gaming market
how can the hardcore
keep the doors open
since we don't have real
redemption games we substitute the next best thing
loot boxes quite honestly
I think we're seeing the beginning of a huge
market shake up one that we'll see the
larger game developers and publishers needing to
make massive changes just to keep their doors open
except for Nintendo because they're Nintendo
I guess we'll see keeping the
discussion going
at home started getting better and better
right when we were talking about the classic system of the week
of the month this week we talked you were
mentioning that the games looked as
good as they did in the arcades and that was the early
90s that was kind of the beginning of the
end which is why we don't have things like Flynn's
arcade anymore because
you can get a lot of those similar experiences
at home but that also kind
of goes I think for the arcades to kind of do
a soul searching a little bit you know what
does seem to be doing well in arcades right now
well shit it's kind of come full circle
they're stealing a lot of the ideas from
mobile these loyalty cards
that unlock new characters or new cards
or new songs in Bimani games
through EMUs or you know the similar
stuff in
Square Enix's theater
in those types of games you know that's
I see a lot of that stuff kind of selling at
round one so it is kind of interesting
how a lot of that stuff does seem to be coming full circle
in a way but round one is also
I mean for all the fucking import games
we talk about and how it feels great
to be in an arcade that really feels like the arcades
that we used to go to in our twenties like
round one is also well
over half redemption games
there's so many
freaking crane games well and on top of that
too you know I think that
the arcades that are
really the ones that are thriving
are the ones that have the right balance
between the redemption like
remember when we went to round one
I think half the time was spent
on the Bimani and the other half was
spent on those claws not me
that's you that was me well okay
that was me you're the claw addict but
you know I love those things and I got a
really crappy looking no
I got the blooper and I got a Yoshi
you can spend your money on whatever the fuck you
like but I think that it's also
I think the concept that the
average person who
people like to get something
that's another thought that I have about it
people like to have
either some kind of tangible
or quantifiable result
for the time that they've spent doing
something it's not just the joy
of playing anymore
they want something for it people have this
competitive nature and
they want to see something for their efforts
as Joe and her map points out
bark aid seem to be doing well
that's true all you have to clean up just
add booze you know every city's
got one of these at this point
but that's that strikes to me
more as like games aren't the
feature at these places I'm sorry to say
games are the niche
for the bar some bars
have music certain types of music
some bars have really
lush seating or food
some bars have arcade machines
those are the best ones yeah
those are the ones we like but maybe
there's some people that like to go to this other bar
because they do sports
uh every single
Sacramento Kings game is on all the time at this
bar you know maybe that's another
niche who knows anyway
so uh
alright well thank you for the email yyr
it is it is an interesting perspective I don't know
if I would directly relate redemption
games to loot boxes but I do
see where you're going and I do kind of think
the industry is a bit of a
a circle in that regard so there is
that it's like gambling I guess so
it's similar to
kind of the whole
coin pusher games and stuff I mean
because that's really what the loot boxes are you're
gambling to see if you're going to get more
out of that than you put into it
and I guess even with the redemption stuff
on top of that you're kind of earning tickets
to purchase
something that you want which of course all
the things that they have in the redemption case
are worth like nothing so
unless of course it's Dave and Busters
when I worked at an Aladdin's castle
I would save all the little
tickets that kids would leave in the machines
and I would put them in I had this
secret pouch in my purse and I
turned them in before I left and
got a polaroid camera
and several Tekken 3
shirts that were like
only the ones they gave at the Namco arcades
so you can get some good stuff
if you take your time
alright you know
you guys have been very well behaved
and we feel bad for missing last week's
show so you know what I think tonight
we need to bring back a segment that we haven't
done in a very long time and that
segment is listless
but I do have one small change
you see the old theme song we used
to use for listless that now gets
our episodes flagged on YouTube for copyright
infringement so I'm going to have to change the
song that we use so I'm very sorry to Crystal Waters
but blame your music label
people for content IDing at the drop
of a hat so I accidentally let
this sneak out a little bit earlier but I thought a new
theme we could use for listless is
listless, listless, listless, listless, listless
should this one get us flagged either?
what?
eh it might but it would be worth it
ok
so here we go
tonight's list I'm sure you're all dying
to know the topic since we haven't done this in forever
well since we had that news
story about Just Dance
becoming a live experience
to which Loki at quite
some length discussed here on the show
we thought well then if that's the case
which video game
should become a live
experience so tonight
we will be building the definitive list
here which video game
needs a live
experience alright so
you can participate with us over at
live.vognetwork.com and
god I haven't done this segment in forever so I hope
the list works right
but you should see the question pop
up there on the page as well
as our four contestants tonight so we
haven't done listless in a while so this is how it works
ok by the way it's not list
list it's listless
Elliot it's a little play on words but anyway
so with listless
what's gonna happen is that we're gonna
put together the definitive list it's a very
scientific process there's no argument
so each host and a special guest
will bring a list of three to
the table and then one by one we're
gonna go around and determine which item
is not worthy of the list
so we'll take a list of twelve items and bring it down to a list
of eight items at which point you
guys will vote in our chat you're gonna click on
your number one and your two answers in that order
submit them in over at live.vognetwork.com
and we will build the definitive list
to which there is no arguing
it's done and of course
you know we should talk about you know the whole
elimination part of that as well
oh yeah the whole twist where
we made it so that if a host has
two answers eliminated from their list
the third gets immunity and cannot be eliminated
cause unfortunately we had some issues
in the past where somebody's
list just totally got eliminated
and that was sad so
anyway joining us tonight a very
special guest who you hear sometimes on the show
Alan is joining us tonight
hi Alan hello how are you doing
fine quickly what games have you been
playing lately
Elder Scrolls Morrowind
like OG not the online one
the expansion lots of
Overwatch a lot of Overwatch
and then this phone game
we don't care about phone games
alright
what would you say Alan if I
came to you and I said Alan I want
to spend $45 to go to a Just
Dance live concert
I'd be like
who's headlining and don't you know
someone that can get you in just because of your hookups
oh yeah oh yeah I'm so
sure don't you know yeah you know how you know what
how long have you known me Alan
has this show ever got me anything for free
free tater tots at
Arby's I'll
take it hey tater tots
are awesome alright
so here we go
which and by the way if you guys have
some answers you can yell them out in chat they're
already doing it which video game needs
a live experience I already see some really good answers
there in our chat room so let's get to it
let's start building
the list Alan we're gonna
let our guests go first tonight what is your number
three answer for which video game needs
to be a live experience showering
with your dad
shower with your dad
simulator I
believe it's the name of the game
and why did you pick this
because it's fucking funny
alright
there it is it has been added to the list
Dark Sakura
what is gonna be your number three pick
I was thinking in terms of games
so I think Farmville
Farmville real life where you get just
like regular casual people who've
never been to a farm and they have to
fucking farm
so Farmville is your answer
essentially is the game that needs to be
Farmville IRL ok Farmville IRL
and you said Farmville
well it's almost in a way
it sounds like kind of like a sick dystopian
future where like there are no more
it's like being Zsa Zsa Gabor
in Green Acres I was trying
to go with like that futuristic like
sad approach no I'm thinking Zsa Zsa Gabor
who has no concept of what to do on a fucking farm
ok what
was it Zsa Zsa or Ava it was Ava
ok one of them
it was a Gabor
alright my number
three answer what item am I
gonna pick for my number three answer
I decided that the experience that needed
a live event was civilization
yes
civilization would be a live event and you
can actually rule the world
and uh
and nuke Gandhi right back
there you go civilization it's on the list
Loki your number three answer
for what video game needs a live experience
um I see
like the problem I have with like the Just Dance
one was there's really no point to it because
you're basically going to watch
people dressed up like artists
that's you know perform
songs but they aren't the artists that perform
the songs and they're not really performing the songs
dancing so an actual
game that would be like performing music
that I thought was pretty awesome is DJ Heroes
so I would totally see a live
performance of DJ Heroes
stuff with actual DJs
mashing songs together
so basically Activision's
E3 press conference from that year
like touring the country
kinda
but you have like Daft Punk
and you know Dead
Mouse and stuff like that I mean it'd be pretty awesome
no I get it that would be awesome that would be awesome
alright some answers well I'll get to
the answers before the last answer we'll get to
our answers from chat but uh let's see
maybe some of us will steal them and put them on the list
for now the number two answer
from Allen
Hotline Miami
and why are you picking Hotline Miami
cause that is the dystopian
future listen to this awesome music
you're gonna fucking die
oh shotgun to the face you're dead
are you actually killing people
at the Hotline Miami live experience
no it would be like the um
one of those the Universal
Studios things that's like super
realistic where it's
like don't pay $50
to have us jump at you and then punch us in the fucking face
or don't go in if you have a heart condition one of those
okay like the scare
events or some Fright Night
something like that alright
Hotline Miami you're at
did I marry you for real your answers are kinda
disturbing
the number two answer
is Hotline Miami
Dark Soccer your number two answer
I was going to say
actually something along the lines of
Call of Duty where it's
basically either like a laser tag or paintball
but they set up like
recreations of like maps
and then you pay to get in and play the maps
they actually have that but you know do they really
they do they did it for uh one of
the Call of Duty's yeah they actually set up a map
and they did it was Airsoft
but does it tour
no there you go
so
what am I calling this Call of Duty
IRL
just like your Farm Bill
which I need to add Farm Bill IRL
Call of Duty in real life
I would hope most of this would be IRL
alright Dark Tetsuya says
that would be kinda cool so you have at least
one paying customer there you go
alright my number two answer is
just make Blizzard World
real just
everybody lost their shit
at that press conference
when Blizzard showed that as
the new Overwatch map so my answer is
just make Blizzard World real just
if you build it they will come just do it
but not in China do it
here no offense to China but
we need one
here for the US income
and all that good stuff or at least our
friends in Canada alright just build
Blizzard World IRL
Loki your turn your number
two answer
Splatoon
oh that's a good answer why did you
say Splatoon because it's just like paintball
except you're shooting on the walls and everything
and it would be really messy and I
at least see people playing that people like
doing was it like the Tough Mudder stuff
where they covered in mud so what about paint
Splatoon 5k
or you could do like
the Splatfest or something like that
no
I'm not going to go there because I was going to say
covered in ketchup
no
alright here is the list
as it stands so far Shower With Your Dad
Simulator, Hotline Miami, Farmville
IRL, Call of Duty IRL
Civilization, Just Make Blizzard
World Real, DJ Hero
and Splatoon here we go
it's time for our number
one answers and then we get to the hard
part where we eliminate answers
so here we go over to Allen what is your number
one answer for
video game that they need to make
a live experience
Valve Studio presents the number
three
and what would
happen at Valve Studio presents
the number three
they would have a Half-Life
episode 3 area
and they would have a Half-Life 3 area and they would have a
Left 4 Dead 3 area and this would be the only place
you could actually ever play these games
yeah and they would have three
Gabe Newell's you give them
your money and he just fucking laughs
three of them just laughs
big belly laughs
alright Valve presents
the number three not live
alright it's on the list
for now DarkSakura what is your
number one answer
Sims The Tour
where basically
you have to be in
a Sims environment and
can't do anything until someone
controlling you tells you you can't
I'm gonna get out of this pool
I'm gonna drown in here
I really need to use the bathroom
if they don't let you pee then you have to pee your pants
that's not fun and wear really horrible clothing
and you can only speak Simlish
me me me wah bweeb wah boo boo
and
Katy Perry's there doing a concert in
Simlish because she had that
song that was in Simlish which was ridiculous
but it was funny
we're almost there to the end of the list
here JD in chat says
so the power exchange I don't know if that's
that or one of the chat answers but anyway
my number one answer
on top of the list I'm gonna go
you know here at OLR
we have to respect the classics
right so I'm gonna go with one of the
all time classics here at Orange
Lounge Radio in fact I would
I would bet many of you don't even fucking
know this game if it wasn't for Orange
Lounge Radio but at one time
it was so noteworthy it was our classic game
of the week and I think it's time to bring back
the 21 anniversary
21 year anniversary tour of
Miss Nude World 96
Lord
everybody move your body
isn't like Miss Nude World
like an actual event though I mean
but does it tour
I
maybe I don't know
will it be in your city
alright we are just
about to the final answer
on the list but first
let's hear from our chat room
let's see some of the chatter answers
that we have here let's see
uh
Sjoan Hunter Matt says Pixel Shits
Brad from Pod Culture says BMX triple X
Rage Nator says C-Man
Dungeon Buster says Night
Trap
Hataful Boyfriend
Katamari Damacy
Rage Nator says Pixel Shits
Sjoan Hunter Matt says Custer's Revenge
Seek Therapy
Dungeon Buster says Streets of Rage 3
Someone Gets to be the Kangaroo
Who the fuck said Custer's Revenge
Rage
Sjoan Hunter Matt
No that's not fucking cool
That's why I said Seek Therapy. Smack
You hit enter without thinking
Rage Nator says
My number one is Genital Jousting
And Dark Tetsuya said
was it Rabbids or Rayman?
I think it was on the list so there you go
Alright
Those are what the chatters said
Loki, what did you say?
You know I was gonna go with
Dead or Alive
Extreme Beach Volleyball but
being that we have Mr. New World on there
I probably won't do that so
Nah I'm still gonna go with
Dead or Alive Extreme Beach Volleyball
Cause
of all the obvious reasons
Say No More
Say No More, that's just the Olympics
Alright
It's like the Olympics
Like the
XFL of the Olympics
Here is the list as it stands
Shower with your dad
Simulator, Hotline Miami
Valve presents the number three live
Farmville IRL, Call of Duty IRL
Sims The Tour, Civilization
Just Make Blizzard World Real
Miss Nude World 96, DJ Hero
Splatoon, DOA
Extreme Beach Volleyball
Now it's tough but it's
part of the process
Alan, you gotta go first. Which of these
is not worthy of the list?
I don't wanna be mean
and get rid of anyone's
I feel that
God dammit
Can I do one of my own?
I don't know if we've ever had that happen before
Can a host take one of their own off the list?
Alright, why not? Sure
Yes, a host can take their own item off the list
Half Life or the Valve 3 thing
Dammit, that's what I was gonna pick
Alright, why are we eliminating
Valve the number three?
Cause it's not a game, it was just me making fun of Valve
I was gonna say cause you could go there
and there'd be nothing there cause they
don't produce the number three of anything
Alright, so in an OLR
first, Alan has taken
his own item off the list
Valve presents the number three
is stricken from the list
Dark Sakura
Which of these is not worthy of the list?
Sorry Alan, I'm taking off shower with your dad
Ah, shower with your dad
simulator. Poor
Alan. First, well of course he did it to
himself, so there it is
That's right, Hotline Miami
The Hotline Miami was pretty rad
Now has immunity, but shower with your dad
has been stricken from the list
Ooh, my turn, what am I gonna eliminate from the list?
Um
These are, like
yeah, this is a pretty good roundup of answers
Um
I'm gonna, I'm gonna
Sorry Jamie, I'm gonna take one of yours
I'm doing Farm Bill
Just because, like, I think you and I
have a different vision of what that would be
and I wasn't jealous
I just think it would be hilarious
to have, like, regular people have to actually do a farm
Eh, fair enough
But unfortunately, I've already clicked the button
It's gone, so, sorry Jamie
Alright, Loki, last but not least
the last one, which of these is not worthy
of the list?
Um, I'm just gonna have to take Miss Nude World
96 off there
Oh, you bastard! Oh, why would you
eliminate Miss Nude World?
I mean, it's old, it's just
Oh, I see, you're afraid
that now it's about
Although, I think that folks
in their 50s can be just as fabulous
that maybe, maybe
we, you know, these folks that were in their
prime at one point, or maybe
maybe they shouldn't be touring
It's just, it's gonna be weird with demons
and, like, and just, like
old Bikini models
and porn stars, I just
it's just, it's gonna be, like, weird
Oh, the mic, sorry
Yeah, I mean, superficially
it's naked ladies, but if you've actually
played Miss Nude World, if any
college kids tried to go to that high
Mm-mm, no, like what
Loki is saying, that's a bad time
Alright, well
rules are rules, so that is it
It has been removed from
the list, but the list is now
clickable, and you guys can vote
over at live.vognetwork.com
for your two favorite
answers, so just click your number one
your number two, and then you click the answer button
if you screw up, you're gonna have to reload the page
cause I don't think you can undo unless
we have that fixed, anyway, here's the list as
it stands, Hotline Miami
Call of Duty IRL
Sims the Tour, Civilization
Just Make Blizzard World Real
DJ Hero, Splatoon
and DOA Extreme
Beach Volleyball
There it is, which video game needs a live experience?
I'm really confident
of one, possibly both
that are gonna win, and I could've been a dick
and I was like, that's a really good thing, so I'm gonna be a dick
and get rid of it, and I didn't, and I took
one in the knee for myself
You took an arrow to the knee, as appropriate for him
It's too bad, cause I would've voted for the same one
that you took away, so you could've
Alright, well
there it is, yes, you do have to be logged in with
a VoG account, then you can click on the
purple squares, we don't sell your information
we just like to be able to tell people
um, when we're registering for events
that we do have so many registered listeners
that's live.vognetwork.com
you do have plenty of time to vote, so if you don't get in right
this second, you can vote
soon in the
list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list list
this
satisfied
dual they have stereo speakers in the front and for her mod lithium ion
battery so it looks alright I mean considering what phones go for nowadays
you know that price range is actually not so bad so that's on on Verizon
because that's what I have but who says I'm gonna stick with Verizon so there's
a gaming phone and 120 FPS you know what that would be really good for and I
don't know if it supports it though VR VR content but is there any is this phone
compatible with any of the VR platforms that are on Android I would be very
interested to find out because if it is and hell yes I'm on board
Brad from pop culture says the razor phone looks kind of cool
corky says 120 Hertz isn't a new thing in portable devices the iPad Pro has one
so but you know those iPad pros are probably a little more expensive than
this device so yeah 700 for a phone mean look at the Samsung Galaxy s8 and the
node 8 and I mean that 700 is not that ridiculous as far as phone prices go
yeah it's actually kind of a little bit on the lower end all right
raising your wants to know will the phone play Miss nude world 96 yes
probably would I think of a 486 PC can play this new world 96 to be fair all
right let's talk about Niantic the company behind Pokemon go and ingress
which you know we don't know what else they're working on but we do know they
have acquired a company named Evertune that's right Evertune was acquired by
Niantic this week and John Hanke the CEO of Niantic announced this Evertune
is a recently established mobile animation app and they're doing this to
expand the social media functionality of the games Evertune was founded in 2016
and the startup raised 1.7 million today from a variety of publishers for their
film sharing app for social networks like YouTube or Twitter so one could
imagine that maybe there will be something where Pokemon are animated or
something in a later version of Pokemon go but really this could be anything
Pokemon animated emojis it could be something for a future game Niantic is
planning that we just don't know yet ingress animated emojis who knows who
knows you know speaking of this whole like Pokemon go and all this stuff I
didn't get into this during my gaming week but did you know there's a knock
off game in the App Store and usually usually knock off no game all right
tell me there's Garfield game on there at some point too but here's the thing
so the latest knockoff game is called Draconius go which is like dragons and
stuff and they don't have the same like logical layout of gyms and stuff like
Pokemon go has when you first look at the game you'd be like this game is a
complete flippin ripoff of Pokemon go and like because it looks like imagine
what Pokemon go looked like in February before they announced gen 2 before they
did the gyms this is what Draconius go kind of looks like at first glance like
it's all the same stuff to look there's a little dragon thingy I don't think I
have this one yet on the house so I'm gonna capture that yes Alan with the
exception of the critters it really looks like they downloaded the AP get
AP gay ha APK and like just unzipped it with like a dash tar well it's all
unity so they could just reverse engineer so when we say it's a knock
off it it really has a lot of the actual original layout gooey and everything is
all but here's the reason why I bring it up so yes at first glance when you
play it for the first five minutes right this is a complete fucking ripoff of
Pokemon go but then you start to see they added more there's PvP in it
there's different types of ways to retrain your monsters in it there's like
these other features the Pokemon go doesn't have and you know what Niantic
is pissed and I think they're going after this developer for infringement
basically but it also kind of goes to show like hey these guys have added
these features to the game that you guys have been kind of sitting on for
months so it's just interesting I'm not saying if it's right or wrong or
anything but it's just an interesting development well they don't own the
copyright to that type of gameplay granted it looks very similar but change
up that that's fine a lawsuit that you come up with that just change the way
your game looks enough and you know put it as your own thing I mean I don't know
there's a lot of games to come out that are that people think are knockoffs
everything like remember everything is they oh it's a street fire clone or oh
that's you know just a clone of this game that's a minecraft clone and then
it all becomes its own thing now I want to catch this creature because I don't
have one yet there's the one of the creatures is called a potty and that
made me laugh because it's an actual little fire pot oh I was thinking it was
a potty and I know but that's well I laughed because the name it does make
you think of that anyway there you go so I don't want to give this game too much
credit but I thought it was interesting that they've kind of taken the template
for Pokemon go and added a ton of shit to it and I'm sure Niantic ain't happy
about it so there you go who fucking who add some fucking features to it and maybe
fix some of the hacking problems yeah little little competition may help who
knows we'll see all right let's move on we have some more news Stark Sakura well
I'm still super excited about Dragon Ball fighter Z even though the story
mode is gonna be fucking bizarre basically you're playing quantum leap
you are showing up in the bodies of these different Dragon Ball characters
let's try to go through the story and you've got this other artificial human
who is talking about eating you like like legit food like she says that
everyone's tasty but like at the the start of the trailer it's like you wake
up and you're in Goku's body and it's really bizarre so I don't know it's
gonna be fun the trailer looks really neat though it's such a pretty game I'm
so excited and honestly enough it it is rendered in game but it looks like real
animation and that's what I'm super impressed by so super excited it needs to
oh and it's gonna be of course out I think January 2018 yeah yeah I was
about to say how long is the wait for this game because sorry January 26th
okay that's not too bad yeah it's not bad excitement don't kill spiders die
have to it was trying to it was looking at me catch it and take it outside
sizing me up to eat me up just take it I got one out of my bed and took it
outside it was a cute little wolf spider Rob gross they eat mosquitoes yeah
anyway let's go to a couple more stories for you guys we're gonna open up the
skype line briefly we're running a little long time so we can't take too
many calls we'll open up the skype line briefly but first Loki all right so this
is a game that I've you know been interested to see a localization forward
they've never done it so captain rainbow has a fan translation for the game
because it was originally only released in Japan and that's kind of where it
ended there but you can actually check it out now so they have it's a patch
made by a guy goes by mark ass that's right and he basically combines the
works of his translation group kirameki along with his stuff as well so now
it's almost 100% complete but there's still a few things missing but it should
be enough to at least play the game nice that's kind of cool enough to get you
through all right this is the last chance to submit listless votes it will
be closing shortly so if you have not submitted your listless votes tonight
make sure you get to live dot vog network comm and get those votes in last
call meanwhile one more story for you guys tonight and that is that something's
going on with Konami because they're acting kind of shitty to their composer
teams that create the music in Bamani games obviously things like beat mania
DDR and even the newer stuff like music and you know sound voltix and stuff
would be nothing if it wasn't for the actual music in the games but what's
interesting about it is that now these songs in the game are being attributed
to Bamani sound team that's right so we don't see you know the actual creator of
the songs anymore it's just attributed to Bamani sound team so yeah some folks
are theorizing that this could go back to a dispute about how there's a record
label called beat nation records that came out about a decade ago and this has
led to live concerts and soundtrack CDs and so on and Konami may actually be a
little bit afraid of this so they want to control their artists very well hmm I
don't know it sounds like a very BuzzFeed thing to do well and it's it's
just kind of just add that to the list of grievances we have with Konami and
ask Atari how well that went back in the 2600 days with not crediting your
creators and what happened is the cause of that the answer is we got Activision
which made better games for Atari's own platform mm-hmm so anyway uh there you
go I don't know if you guys have anything to say about that but just I'm
not surprised considering the source yeah add add this to the list of Konami
grievances shall we all right before we get those bastards before we get to the
skype line which we are about ready to open up dark soccer has requested that
we bring back another segment we haven't done in a while and it's something we
can do on demand but it's CF use of the week
you
my SU goes to people who don't respect the word stop especially when the person
who is requesting that you stop happens to be autistic usually we're gonna tell
you to stop something if it's necessary or else if we don't see anything it's
going to be very ugly so when someone says I don't want to do this anymore
fucking respect them I'm in a pass because I'll sub tweet something and put
my foot in my mouth so low do you want to say anything yeah we say that if you
do the people that are driving in front of me on the way this show today they
were driving 20 miles an hour in a 35 what the hell come on people I get it
you're old but Jesus Christ man you close to this be long a good old-fashioned
fu2 bad drivers it's a slow driver they are there's bad drivers everywhere
all right I think it's time to close up the list and see what the ants actual
results were here which I think I'd have to keep this answerable but not live I
think was the way I do this I have to remember this here it's a tricky thing
here all right so here it is the actual results from the list the scientific
process you ready the number three answer a video game that most needs to
be a live experience dead or alive extreme beach volleyball is the number
three answer the number two answer tonight this is the one I thought would
win Splatoon was the number two answer tonight I thought that would be the
winner Splatoon is the number two and last but not least the number one thing
you want to see a live experience of just make Blizzard world real just make
it happen make it in a tour it could if you built it modularly you could be like
a giant techno Jerome of blizzard just narrowly missing the list Sims the tour
people were into that but fourth place for Sims the tour and hotline Miami I
think only got a couple votes poor Alan so there you go there it is your extreme
splat Blizzard world list there it is all right what do you say we open up the
phones take some calls orange lounge radio all one word on Skype if you want
to get in for tonight otherwise let me check in real quick with my co-host to
see if there's any last-minute stories while we wait to see if anyone co-op
there it is it's lighting up and again it's lighting up on the computer when my
I don't get it anyway hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hello
you're on orange launch radio if you can hear us we can't hear you I thought I
heard hello I thought I heard a little Russell or something all right well I
don't think it works so you have to try calling back test your connection with
echo one two three that's somebody who calls a lot though so I'm surprised not
working I wonder if it's something about my computer but I thought I heard like a
little Russell in the background or something so I only had a computer for
you then dumbass me had to instead of Microsoft in their confusing language
system refresh your system restore so it is system restore back to factory
settings which dropped it from Windows 10 and Windows 8 don't if I did a system
refresher would have kept Windows 10 I actually I thanks to a very good friend
I have a code for Windows 10 actually sitting in my repository because it was
supposed to be for if a new computer oh well then perfect so there I might have
to look into that I could still play with Windows 8 on that laptop though for
the record you can get a code under their accessibility plan still oh really
still going on if you have a legit install of Windows 7 you can upgrade it
to Windows 10 under the accessibility plan huh all right I'm gonna look into
that we'll see all right meanwhile I'm gonna see if anybody else wants to call
us orange lounge radio all one word on Skype let me check in any last-minute
stories no not really I guess we have had a lot of stories tonight but let's
see okay that person's calling back let's see if it'll work this time trying
to get in here on the skype line hi you're on orange house radio who's this
hello I can hear the chair hello that's so weird
okay hmm I don't know what's going on sky being stupid I guess wait let me
check here okay so we're gonna try this and I'm gonna call out this way good old
radio welcome to Skype call testing sir yeah that works fine so no I just can't
well you have a last-minute story since we were taking some time good so there
is a mod that someone's big area should say like an actual game it's called
Castlevania Simon's destiny it is a first-person shooter Castlevania game
done in the style of the old SNES Castlevania games built on top of the
doom engine and it looks awesome interesting because that first point you
go Castlevania first-person I go oh great Castlevania six no it's got like
all that like you know 16-bit looking stuff and it's out now for the great
price of free because it's so yeah the great price of free if you want to
download it you can go to the Z doom form yes it's yeah form that Z doom
org and you'll need GZ doom to be able to play it all right we're gonna give
this one more call that sent me a private message saying it's fixed hi
you're on orange on its radio who's this what was my bad I muted my entire sound
system while I was gone for the whole weekend it did not realize I was trying
to call you guys that's okay it's just you know the joys of live radio what's
on your mind my friend okay first of all hi I'm Ron well y'all probably know
me by now but um I would hope so yeah as I'm coming back from my amazing trip
this weekend and listening to you guys are tuning radio I want to call an
objection on one of the titles on listless yes DJ hero okay why are we
objecting to DJ hero you don't need to make that a live experience that's what
a rave is for they still have those well isn't that isn't that kind of what we
were joking that the Just Dance thing basically is is that the Just Dance is
gonna be a rave for kids more or less I think it's gonna be more like the Just
Dance is gonna be on stage dancing and the kids will be watching it out like a
special VIP area where you can dance so like we go to a weird Al concert but
you're still like the performing music though like actual DJs mixing actual
songs together not just like playing one track to the next but like actually
doing live mashups and stuff that's actually talent versus some dumbasses
dressed up like the artists that originally sang those tracks but not
quite and then dancing to pre-recorded music so so what Jason did on the good
place for a short time not to spoil anything but basically that right so you
could I think and I think Ramos point is that that does I mean to be fair it does
kind of exist some club I do love Janet's rebound I know I know don't
spoil all right anyway JD and chat points out there's an event called booty
NSF that's really what it's called I've heard of this it's a mashup party yeah
I've always wanted to go to that I've heard of that oh yeah they always they
talk about that so I I can kind of see where I miss coming from saying that
event sort of already exists but to be fair to Loki's there is nothing under
that video game brand perhaps there could be some of that triple-a talent
that comes in although fat chance but you never know I mean there was that
there was that legendary press conference here what what year was it
was 2010 so whenever those games were announced like they had some that's a
major talent at the staple yeah it was like all these like Eminem and many on
and all these people like under one roof performing for these games I mean
Activision probably paid a ton of money for it but didn't go to that I know some
people I knew went to that I can't remember if Bobby was one of them or not
I didn't it was one of the years I didn't go so but there you go Rama I
guess that's our our rebuttal although it's it's a fair perspective you're
right some of that same stuff kind of already exists out there yeah on the
plus side um they don't have to worry about the cops coming in to break up the
rave that is true that is true I hey Rama before we let you go you said you
were on a great trip this weekend is that something for anime jam session
this week was it a convention or no this is something more like me Persil's
me just getting away for a while just kind of like my time to relax and
recharge and get back into the game eat pray beer oh yeah Oh works what Loki I
just got another the last minute all right well Rama we're gonna let you go
then I'm glad to hear you had a good trip and we'll check in with you again
awesome take care of y'all fight all right what'd you have for us Loki last
chance to get in last chance so there's gonna be a new rewards thing for Sony
rewards now through the PlayStation Network so guess what now those trophies
that you're earning they're actually worth something oh so basically you can
earn some of the PlayStation points they can be redeemed for like PlayStation
Network vouchers and other things so here's how it works so you get one you
have 100 silver trophies you can get 100 points or one point per trophy 25
gold trophies for 250 points or 10 platinum trophies for 1,000 points huh
so and you can like earn those I guess that's available through the service so
go in there if you've got some trophies you can get some free points all right
interesting how that stuff is making rewards in the real world I wonder if
we'll hear more about that at PSX that would be very interesting but anyway I
notice our phone is not lighting up so I think that's gonna do it for the
skype line tonight which means our show has about come to an end how sad but I
want to thank you guys for listening to our show tonight and helping it be a
success if you guys enjoyed what you heard here at orange launch rated
tonight don't forget to tell a friend or two about the show help us spread the
word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice but we can't put those
voices out there if they're not here to call in and send us emails and
participate on discord and chat and all the places where we try to get your
voices in on the show and vote in listless they were not a part of that
scientific process maybe something else maybe hotline Miami would have won if
more of you would have voted for it so anyway tell a friend or two about the
show a nice five-star review or ever you heard about this show especially iTunes
places like that those go a long long way I really can't underestimate that so
please please consider leaving us a nice review especially the kinds that have
words with it too that are like you know yay
olr is great Jamie is rad Rob is cool like those are Loki's okay like those
reviews are great too so anyway uh that's it we got to go around and get
everybody's final thoughts I suppose we will not be here next week it's a
pre-planned absence thank you to everyone who has served in the Armed
Forces it is Veterans Day coming up after all which is why we have a long
weekend so thank you to everyone who has served who lets us have the right to
have this show and say whatever the fuck we want on it
appreciate that so thank you but we will be off next weekend we'll be back in two
weeks on 19 November to do this all over again in the meantime final thoughts
dark soccer I will start with you ladies first things things are happening I'm
not going to tell anybody what these things are unless you talk to me so talk
to me what's happening just kidding things all right I got you all right my
final thought tonight is pizza and oh I want to say kudos to everybody that's
been streaming for extra life this weekend we didn't really talk about that
on tonight's show but I know a lot of that's still going on but I had friends
and folks that were participating in that so I just wanted to give snaps to
all you that were participating donating and making that a thing Loki your final
thought tonight my final thought is I'm hopefully gonna actually play some games
this week you say that every week I know I do but I got two weeks I've got the
controllers charged now so oh shit that's gonna make all the difference
like you know there's stranger things that was you know no it's it's why I
didn't touch Mario Odyssey right away and why I still haven't beat I would
love to get Mario Odyssey just don't have the money drop on the system at the
moment you can't justify it all right we'll be back in 14 days on 19 November
to do it all again until then support indie podcasting go check out some of
our friends here at the voice geeks Network if you miss gaming shows next
week try try Bobby Bobby black wolf try game buoy electric sisterhood I was
listening to their recent episode they're always a delight to listen to
so or any of our great podcast here at the voice geeks Network or anywhere on
any Network or non Network just support indie podcasting because we love you
have a good night everybody we'll see you next time you've been listening to
orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is a production of OLR studios to join
us for a live show tune into fog network calm Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific 9
p.m. Eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not
necessarily reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio or fog Network
but you know they were all still true
see you next week
you