Orange Lounge Radio
Who's your hosts? DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
It's here! It's here! Blizzard has finally announced their don't call it a MOBA hero battler
Also, Sony released the Playstation 4 and the player media has been at a fever pitch
What have people been saying? What's gone wrong? Find out all this and so much more right now
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio episode number 527 for this November the 17th of 2013
My name is Rob Roberts joining over the next few hours to talk about video games and gaming culture and gaming lolz
And thank you for being here by the way after a week off
But I'm joined this week in studio as I am every single stinking week except last week when we were off
By the one and only DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
How are you doing? Did you have a good week off last week?
What did you end up doing?
I was in a car the whole time but you know like it's about a 6 or 6 and a half hour drive back from L.A.
So I'm in the car the whole time and Alan's there too but there's only so much talking you can do and at some point
And playing what game am I thinking of?
Yeah that kind of thing
We did listen to Bobby's show I will say that we were somewhere in the middle of I don't freaking know
Probably about an hour south of Santa Nella probably Harris Ranch
You California people that know your I5 was around Harris Ranch when Bobby's show came on
So that entertained us a little ways but then the whole way home I'm just going
And this is where OLR will be starting
And here's where Jamie will be doing the Classic Game of the Week
And here's where she'd be throwing a fit about reading emails
I don't throw a fit
But just kind of going through that whole like you know after so many years of doing something
It's kind of like I should be doing this right now but I'm not
We know when we're behind and we know when we're ahead
That's right
Well I hope you had a good week off it was restful and all that stuff
I slept
That is a great way to spend the time
Sleep is good
That's what Sundays are for
Also say hello to Tech Master Loki
Hi
Hi Loki how are you?
Fine
You sound like you might need to be doing a little more sleeping yourself
What happened? Did you catch a cold?
Uh yeah
Did you bring disease to the show tonight?
I've been staying up late at night
Oh is that because of Josh or just you're just doing projects?
Yes it's because of Josh
And totally not because I was playing Cookie Clicker last night
Wait a minute
Cookie Clicker? Really Loki?
I got bored I got bored last night
I got bored last night because
Nellie was messing around with Reddit
And so I was talking with her
And I was like I don't want to browse Reddit anymore
I remember hearing about Cookie Clicker
Or reading about Cookie Clicker
And then I'm like let's see what this thing is
So I tried it out
And yeah
You kind of missed the train Loki
Because Cookie Clicker was all the rage on my other show
Horde House about two months ago
And I think we're all over it now but
You're late to the party that's alright
It's alright I just need to finish it and it'll be done
I didn't realize there was an end to Cookie Clicker
Oh
I played the iPhone knock off one
That's not the same
It isn't the same they really need to put out an official one
For the record?
It's addicting none the less
No
You're not going to get into Cookie Clicker?
Hell no
What about the other iPhone game I've been playing
I can't believe I got sucked into this garbage all over again
I really want to thank Kethervis if she's out there listening
I don't think she listens to OLR but if she is
Like I'm doing that whole warning shots at you right now
She got me addicted to Tiny Death Star
Have you seen this?
Yes and I'm not playing it either
It's Tiny Tower with the LucasArts franchise
With all the Vader and Palpatine and all the characters
And cute little midi style Death Star music
While it's playing
I still refuse
You refuse?
I refuse
It's probably for the best
The only thing that makes me upset about Tiny Death Star
We'll get into real games in a minute I promise
Is that you can't rename all the stores
Because that was the best part of Tiny Tower
Which is based off his renaming the stores
Because Allen would always rename his stores to these hilarious things
Of course I can't even remember any of them off the top of my head
Allen what were some of your funny stores
You remember any of them on Tiny Tower
He's shaking his head I wish I could bring it up and see
I know I had a restaurant called Poops R Us
Yeah
Just because I was thinking that it gave people diarrhea
Well there was a
The apartment complex I built in the Death Star
The Death Star was
Let me look I'm trying to
I'm actually pulling it up as we are live here
You can pull up our chat room if you're listening live
Oh you named it Ewok Shits
You can't participate with this show live every Sunday night
At 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
At the Voice of Geeks Network
Vognetwork.com
And if you are listening live come join us and chat
Live.vognetwork.com
Ah here it is the Felucia apartments
Is one of the apartments I have
So I was going to rename it to by Felucia
But I couldn't rename it
Very sad
Sad trombone
Womp womp
Alright anyhow
We're going to get into our gaming weeks and all that good stuff
We'll talk about all that
And what we've been doing with the week
But we got a lot of stuff to catch up on too
After being gone last week
Oh Alan came and he brought in his Tiny Tower
Let me read
What? It's still loading
Live radio everybody
I think I deleted it like
Yeah I finally deleted mine off the phone too
Let me look at our chat room
Live.vognetwork.com
Tim Tripp in chat says
I actually played Tiny Death Star for about 30 minutes
Which is 25 more minutes
Than I usually spend with an iPhone game
Dungeon Buster says
I'm playing Tiny Death Star
Never played Tiny Towers before so this is new to me
So I guess if it hasn't worn off yet
Then that's good
Sandy Ball Gym is called Sandy Balls
The Glassworks is called Here Blow This
The Breakfast Place is called Enough Fucking Pancakes
The Greenhouse
Florist is called Dankweed 420
So yeah
And I see your computer lab is called Sierra Online
In a nod
There you go
Those weren't even his funniest ones but that's alright
There's some funny ones in there
We have to settle a few things
From when we were gone last week
We weren't here last week
I was in Anaheim
Sort of at Blizzcon
Meaning I didn't go to actual Blizzcon
I just went to all the parties and then I went to Disneyland
Which is right next door
That was the way to do it
I had a great time
I met a lot of awesome people
I'll talk more about Blizzcon later in the show
When we get to some of that news
One of the cliffhangers we left last week
Or excuse me, two weeks ago
Was that we were talking about the end
Of the last generation with PlayStation 3
And so forth
And the start of the new one
And I mentioned that I was waffling on the PlayStation 4
And I wasn't sure if I was going to get one
And I had my pre-order through Amazon
Was I going to keep it, was I going to cancel it
Wii U, you might remember a year ago
I never bothered pre-ordering a Wii U
I said I'm not going to get it
The day the Wii U comes out, what did I do?
I got one at Target
So what happened with the PlayStation 4?
I did not buy the PlayStation 4
I cancelled my pre-order
When I got back from Disneyland
You were a wise, wise fellow
Well, here's the thing
A part of me actually feels kind of bad
Because at Disney
I had a great time at Disney
Alan and I had a great time on Friday
And the park wasn't very crowded
But then Saturday, randomly
An old friend of mine
A few years ago
Who actually works for Sony now
Was hanging out with me at the park
And we were talking, of course we have to talk
I don't want to bug him with work
But we have to talk a little bit about PlayStation 4
And he was telling me all the good stuff
And I was leaving Saturday feeling really jazzed
About PlayStation 4, like, okay
I gotta get one when I get home, I gotta get one when I get home
But then I'll tell you what
Swamee was that drive home Sunday
And I don't know what it was
I don't know if it was kind of listening to Bobby's show
You know, it's
A video game system is only as good as the games that are on it
Or what have you
But I really realized, guys
There's just nothing I really, really want to get
On PlayStation 4 right now
Now, early next year
Absolutely
Diablo 3 on PlayStation 4 looks great
Even though I already played it on PC
I enjoy the controls on PlayStation 3's demo
And I will give the game another try on PlayStation 4
Absolutely
Final Fantasy 14 will be in beta
In the PlayStation 4
And then
I do want to get the Need for Speed game at some point
But next year, some other things to look forward to
Infamous Second Son, obviously
And Destiny
I mean, that's all in the first half next year
So I'm sure between now and then
I will end up buying a PlayStation 4
But I'm gonna be perfectly honest with you guys
Despite all this, like, console wars
And whether you're cheering me or booing me
For my decision
Money played a big part of it, too
Might have gone over budget a little bit
When we were in Anaheim, so
Whoops, womp, womp
Going to the chat room
At live.vognetwork.com
RawstealUT says
So the Wii U is worth more at launch
Than the PlayStation 4?
I'm
This is not gonna be a popular answer
Yes
And the reason why I say yes
Is at least
On the Wii U
And you can call me fanboy all you want
I don't give a fuck
But on the Wii U at least, there was the Mario Brothers
Which I really wanted to play, the Super Mario Brothers Wii U
And there was Zombie U
And yeah, I wanted to play Nintendo Land, too
I mean, that was three games
At launch that I said, I really want to play these games
I couldn't do that with PlayStation 4
I couldn't sit there and go
These are four games I have to play
Right now
I couldn't do that
And honestly, we all know that Wii U lost a lot of steam
Over its first year release
And I'm not gonna try and defend that
You know, there should have been more in the pipeline
Or what have you
I think that's where PlayStation 4 will outpace Wii U
Is because I'm looking at the first half of next year
Going, this looks very exciting
For PlayStation 4
With all those games I just named
So in that regard
Which I would argue
Is more crucial
To the system
In the future than the launch
The next six months look very good for PlayStation 4
So
Let's see, also going to the chat room
I didn't get one either
Yeah, neither did Loki
You guys had already kind of locked that in a couple weeks ago
But I know I was waffling
It just has to do with the bullshit of system launches
The way they go these days
If there aren't the games that are gonna be out
Let me rephrase that
Because I can't apparently speak proper English today
If the games that I want to play
Are not out when the system launches
Then buying the system is buying a giant paperweight
I would rather wait
Till the issues get worked out
I would rather wait until there's a library that's worth me
Actually putting some money on
And my $100 gift card will last me a while
Yeah
I am still planning on
And this again
Probably won't be a popular statement
But I don't care
I am still planning on getting that Zelda 3DS I want
And Mario 3D World next week
You know when Fire Emblem's out?
It didn't Fire Emblem already
It did?
Yeah, it came out a while ago
Unless there's a new one I'm not aware of
But that's
Yes, I am still planning on keeping that
But the good news is I can actually sell my old 3DS
To recoup some of the money
That's what I plan on doing
Yep, yep
Let's see
Going to our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
RawsteelUT says
There's never been a system that had a five star launch lineup
I'm really trying to think that through
Oh, the Xbox 360 I thought had a pretty great launch
360 wasn't bad
360 wasn't bad at all
Dreamcast had good games when it came out
Dreamcast was decent, yeah
Sonic Adventure by itself
Was a great game
I remember
Super Nintendo was really weak
But it had Mario World
Nobody cared there's Mario World
There's another one I'm trying to think through
Genesis launch was really crappy as far as games go
Because it was just the standard Sega fare
There was no Sonic
Was it like an Alex Kidd game?
Yeah
Altered Beast I'm pretty sure was the launch title
columns
Alan's here
I was trying to think pop quiz wise
There were five or six launch week Super Nintendo games
It was SimCity, Pilotwings
Super Mario World
I want to say Final Fantasy 2
But no that came out a couple months later
It was Launch Window
Within like six months of it
There were just like the four or five
There was also the Super Scope games
No, Super Scope games way later
Actually, Alan, I think those ones you named
I don't remember
Was F-Zero at launch?
But I think the ones you named
I think first party were the only ones
There was Pilotwings
The Nintendo
The Green Hair Professor port
Of SimCity
And Mario World
Those were the big three from Nintendo
I thought that first week there were five
I'm trying to think of what the other two were
Someone Wikipedia it in chat
Now I'm trying to
I'm getting asked some questions about the Xbox One
And where my head's at with that
I'm going to be honest guys
I kind of counted that out a while ago
Because the $100 price tag gets a little more up there
And the launch games to me
Didn't counter balance that
Yes, I know it's getting Killer Instinct
But I'm kind of eh on that
I think the launch games sound a little bit better
Four to five sounds pretty awesome
And Dead Rising 3
It's just like the whole series
Dead Rising, I bought it
I have fun with it for about
A week and then I get bored with it
Really fast
The same thing happened
I got Dead Rising 2 and Dead Rising 2 off the record
And I got bored with it so fast
You'd think that would be impossible
Being that it's a sandbox zombie game
But Dead Rising 3 I think I'd just get bored with
Really fast
Just so you know Alan, looking at chat
Bobby Blackwolf went and looked it up for you
Super Nintendo launch titles were indeed
Mario World F-Zero was a launch title
Pilotwings, SimCity, Gradius 3
Was the only other one that was there the day it launched
Yeah, that was the one you were missing
So yeah, here's the thing
I actually kind of agree that I think
The Xbox One lineup and those things you just said
Forza, The Crimson Dragon, not so much Rise
In fact, very much not so much Rise
Yeah, Rise is kind of...
But a lot of those other games you're talking about
Actually, I think the Xbox lineup out the gate
Sounds a little stronger than Playstation 4
But do I want to pay another $100 for the privilege
Of playing those games?
Is it that much a must-have title?
Not for me, and not the stuff I play
So
I still think it's weird seeing
I saw a TV commercial again today
They had some football on at Chili's
And it was talking about
How to watch TV with the Xbox One
And how that's a selling feature
I'm like, I just don't get
I guess if you're really hardcore into
Fancy football, cool
But other than that, why the hell
Would you purchase that system to watch
TV on it? It just doesn't seem like
That makes sense
I will say this now
Now that it's been a week
Do I regret my decision to not get a
Playstation 4?
It's
It is really
Taking a lot of willpower
To make me not go
Isn't there something we could sell to get the money
Don't we have hidden money somewhere
That I could dig up and help pay for the
Playstation 4? Do I have a rewards card
Or an unspent gift certificate?
Watching other people
On their Twitch streams
I've been watching Exeter was streaming
Some stuff, and that was fun, and Bobby was streaming
Some stuff, and it was neat to watch
It kind of made me go, oh
That's right, I could have played like DC Universe
Online with all the new textures would have been really cool
And flowers really pretty
And all that
And the Twitch stuff looks great
So there is that whole like, I want to be in the cool kids club
Type of thing going on
But I'm doing alright
I'm pretty sure I'm going to make it till
2014 without breaking down
And buying a Playstation 4
We'll see
Alright, so yeah, that's it
No Playstation 4 for me
For now, but I am still going to
Of course be following it as are we all
And doing the news and all that
And I'll get one eventually
Just so you know guys
Just to kind of put it in perspective
I did not buy an Xbox 360
At launch either, nor did I buy a
Playstation 3 at launch
I actually bought the Xbox 360 first
I bought that about 4 months after it launched
They were still really hard to find
When I bought it, like I had to
And when they got the new
Shipments, and I remember I had to get
The not fancy 360
And had to buy the extra stuff
Separately
Excuse me, they were still hard to come by
And my Xbox 360 died within a week
Of me buying it, and that pissed me off
But whatever, it's old news now
Playstation 3 I didn't buy
For like a year, I didn't buy Playstation 3
Until LittleBigPlanet I think had been announced
Or came out or something
Was when I finally got the Playstation 3
So, just because I don't buy a console at launch
Doesn't mean I won't love the system eventually
Like I said before, if Killzone
Wasn't Killzone, if it was a new
Resistance game, next gen
I would buy that
Because, well, I would want that game
But
I just, I don't like Killzone
I really don't like Killzone
And looking at like, you know, what the next gen
Games, I guess, you know, like Call of Duty
And Battlefield and stuff, I mean, Call of Duty
Just, first off, Call of Duty I'm not excited about
At all
I had actually gotten a copy and I'm like
Fuck this, I'm not opening this, I'm selling it
And so I did
But I still have another copy
But, you know, it's just
I haven't even bothered to want to play that
And, you know, it just didn't look that
Great on
It just doesn't show off
The power of that system at all
It just kind of, you know, okay
This looks like a Playstation 3 game
I don't know
Alright, well, let's see
What else should I talk about here? I want to get into our gaming weeks
But I should mention BlizzCon real quick
I did talk a little more in depth about this
Over on Horde House, my other show, which is on Wednesdays
With Xtavor, Shana Linko
And Grandpa Matt
That is on Wednesdays
And the latest episode, which is called
Outworld is Mortal Combat
The name of it, long story
You'll figure it out when you listen
I talked a little more about BlizzCon, but I just want to reiterate
I did have a good time at the parties
I met all the people
There was this fun little event called World of Podcasts
They did Thursday night where they tried to get all the podcasters
Together to kind of like do these panels and things
And that was neat for networking
And just getting to meet different people
So yeah, I had a good time at the event
And, you know, you definitely feel that buzz
In the air, all the excitement for the new products
You know, obviously
A big Warcraft expansion was announced
We'll get into some of the details a little later on when we get to the news
But there was a lot of buzz about that
And the many other things that they announced
But, you know, remember guys
BlizzCon costs $175 to go to
And I just, I got to be honest
I think the way I did it was great
Where we went to Disneyland
And I got to go to the parties, so I got to do all the networking
Yeah, I didn't get to play the new stuff
But that's okay
I'll play it eventually, it'll come out
$175, hmm
I don't know about that
Alright, let's get into our gaming weeks
What types of video games have we been playing this week
On the consoles we do own?
Dark Sakura, how was your gaming week?
I'm actually defending RossTLUT
Give me a second
Oh, chat stuff going on right now
At live.hugnetwork.com
If he wants attention, then don't give attention
Let me, go ahead
No, my point is that he left the room
He's not there to defend himself
I don't see any point in talking about him behind his back
The end
Let's get into our gaming weeks
Dark Sakura, how was your gaming week?
Um, my gaming week
Was nice
I
I actually
Have twice finished the Stanley Parable
Sorry, I didn't mean to kick you
Then I'll kick you harder
I finished the Stanley Parable
Which you play it through once the way you're told to play it
And then you do different things that keep you
From actually finishing the game
So it's a very interesting kind of twist
On the walk through
First person adventure
I really like it
It was very well done
I don't know that it was worth the full charge price
Of it, but it was definitely worth the sale price
It was a very good game
And I haven't finished exploring it
It's pretty neat
I hear the game has a funny sense of humor
It does, it has a really funny sense of humor
Compared to GLaDOS from Portal a lot
Yeah, the narrator is just Mr. Snark
As long as you don't do
What Mr. Narrator says
So you can rebel against the narrator
It's encouraged
That you do so from time to time
I also
Have been playing
Mass Effect 2
And Mass Effect 3
Because I have
I'm actually trying once again to get textures
Imported on my Mass Effect 3
By doing mods myself from scratch
Using textures and meshes that other people
Have made and I've got
Meshes working just fine
Not textures and I do not want to use text mod
Because that means it would be a pain in the ass
So, moving on from that
I also played Final Fantasy 14
And I'm taking my sweet time with it
But I finally got Thaumaturge leveled up
Once someone reminded me
That I could actually
Pick some of my Arcana stability
And use them with my Thaumaturge
The class became less shitty
I'm sorry, physic is like
Thaumaturges are like
Squish, squish, squish, squish
No mana, squish, squish
And then I was like
Oh yeah, physic
Being able to heal yourself is a great little perk
But now I'm back to
Arcanist and I'm going to
Work up to 34 and then do that stupid quest again
That one that I'm trying to finish
So I'm just wandering around doing fates
Right now anyway, so
Kind of boring, but...
Are you excited about the content patch coming in December?
Yeah, I did enjoy the lightning
Thing
I got the quest
And I actually hung out
Basically you just find
Where all the people are camping and that's where lightning
Is going to show up eventually
In one of the little random
Fates that pop up in that area
So I actually got the lightning
Thing, her showing there and being all kind of
Broody to herself and
Is this my fate?
I'm lightning angst
I just liked how all the fonts turned to Final Fantasy
13 and the music
I gotta be honest
I sat there waiting for the fate to pop
And I was like, this is so boring I didn't even
See it through
I was like, fuck this I'll do it later
I was a little bit late because I was trying to get a good
View to screen capper
You know because
They turned it off, regular screen caps
But I use steam for it
So I was going to turn off all my stuff in screen capper
But I didn't get it done
I did like though that you can get
Some of the outfits and armor
And that's what I'm kind of working on right now
Because I like pretty stuff
I've been playing Animal Crossing
I am going to be probably playing
Animal Crossing because I have one
Lone left
For my second character
And then there's Julian's but I'm using his as bribery
So that he actually behaves in
He's a good boy but he doesn't listen
Another one of your animals moved to my village
Really?
Agnes I think it was?
Oh the pig? Yeah
I know Portia just moved too so I don't know who she moved to
I don't think she came to mine, I got Agnes
I got Mitzi finally
The white cat with the blue face
That was on the cover of the first game
I have Mitzi now
And I like her better than Ed
And I want Ed to leave because he's fucking creepy
It's like they're real people
I was actually
I started listening
To the Night Vale podcast
Which is fun
But I was thinking about doing an Animal Crossing
Parody with Night Vale type
Stuff that's called Welcome to Normandy
Or something
A particular person at VOG has
Openly voiced the fact that they would love to have
Some type of fiction based podcast
Thing here, it would be a lot of fun
Well you know I've
I've been working on stories already so
Make it happen
Make it work
I actually have a very extreme story I'm already working on
For a webcomic but it would tie in very nicely with the podcast
Talk to me, talk to me person
Alright
Crap I played other shit
But I don't remember what the fuck it was
It's kind of hard though I've noticed
To play MMOs
When you have a very needy cat
Midna has now taken
To climbing up my side
And patting me on the shoulder when she wants me to play with her
Not just you know
The climbing up part
But she pats me on the shoulder and waits till I look at her
And then she goes
And then she hops up in my lap
And tries to eat my mouse so whatever
Not an actual mouse
Like your computer mouse
Cat and mouse
You know what's stupid about my mouse by the way
Because Microsoft doesn't make that thumb track ball anymore
People on Amazon sell them for 200 bucks
And I own two of them
They don't make thumb track balls anymore?
Not the wired Microsoft thumb track ball
Oh like different brands
Logitech makes one like it
But people are actually spending the 200 bucks
And it makes me think maybe I should sell one of mine
But then again I wouldn't be able to get another
Loki how was your gaming week?
I played a lot of Grand Theft Auto
Of course you did
So I played more of online
I think I'm like level 28 now
On PS3
I didn't play any online on 360
But I did 100% 360
So I'm all done with that
And actually I'm kind of
I was trying to black out everything on 360
As far as the 100% checklist
Because there's more stuff you can do
Than actually get 100% for
Doesn't make any sense but
That's the way they have it
So what did I do?
I did all the
Epsilon tracks the other day
And
I don't know just messing around
I'll probably play more online
Because they're gonna have a content patch
Coming out
This week
And
Then
Then I played Cookie Clicker
I started that last night
It's only been a few hours
I can hear you over there clicking while you're talking by the way
Of course
You got an intervention
It'll be over soon don't worry
There is an end
Alright
How many cookies do you have right now?
Well I'm producing
Looks like just under
30 million per second
It's not enough
Alright anything else?
Um
No that's it
Alright my gaming wheel
Real quick actually
A little bit of Forza Horizon but I wasn't actually playing it
My son was playing it
I saw the stuff on Facebook
With the pictures and everything
Yeah he likes playing with my Microsoft
Racing wheel
He likes pretending it's a steering wheel
And goes and plays around that
So I'm like hey what about the
Then he wants to sit in my car and stuff
And tell him how the car works
And I'm like yeah you push the pedals to go
And stuff and well I'll tell you what I can set up
A game for you and you can go drive a car in that
And so
He had trouble at first because I had the
Force feedback on and stuff
It's hella hard to drive that stupid steering wheel
With the force feedback on so I turned it all off
And then I finally
Switched him into a Honda Fit
Because the car I picked for him
Because it was a class C car
Just was all over the road but for some reason
The Fit doesn't
It's more stable I guess or something
And so he
He was doing alright
He got it up to like 35
And he was staying on the road
But there was like a turn
It was like an S turn and he was able to stay on the road
So it was pretty cool
Let's see look at our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
Dark Tetsuya saw the video
And said that was a great video Loki
Ciao wants to know
Sorry I always mispronounce your name
Says what's the subscription fee
For the Final Fantasy MMO
I believe it's $12.95 a month for the basic
Which gives you 1 character a server
Think $14.95 for the advanced
Which is 8 characters a server
I only had 1 plan
And that was the $14.99 plan
Go take a look
Because I think there's a $12.95 plan
I didn't see any of it but I don't care
Because I wanted all the stuff and whatever
It's what I was paying for a while anyway so it's fine
It's not that big a difference
Anything else Loki? Or do I get to go?
Alright my gaming week
Honestly not a whole lot of
Different stuff because I was out of town for a few days
But you know the typical Final Fantasy 14
I'm addicted to that
And also played some World of Warcraft
I think the whole BlizzCon thing might have energized
Me a little bit to at least log in and check out my character
And go yep still
Still got no friends left playing this game that's too bad
But I did play
Some actual new stuff
I did play a little more of the Midway Arcade
Because I was trophy hunting in that game
And I talked about that a couple weeks ago on the show
But another game I played
On Playstation 3, you ready for this?
While all you guys were busy with your
Newfangled Playstation 4's
Playing one of the big launch titles, Assassin's Creed 4
I played Assassin's Creed 3
On Playstation 3
Which by the way is my first
Assassin's Creed game I've ever played
To which everybody is telling me
You're doing it wrong!
I want two, I actually have two for PC
Do you?
But I hated playing it without a controller
I like
I've been playing Assassin's Creed 3
I like it well enough
I've only gotten through that first little chapter
Where you're in the Opera House, then the boat and everything
I liked the way that it was telling
A story and I thought the environments were really
Kind of neat, like I really liked that
Opera House was really pretty
To be scaling all around and jumping all around
So I was kind of having fun with that
But did you fight Ultros?
No, I did not fight Ultros
But I did
I did have to walk in the
Rafters and all that stuff
The way the sequence was done was really
Neat, like you would hop over to this stage
Piece that would fall because of your weight
But not all the way onto the stage
Yeah, I was
Having fun with it
I want to play a little more of it
I probably will, I didn't get to play a lot a lot this week
But I played enough to get through that first
Chapter, it was exciting enough
Considering it was a series
I never really, I've had a lot of people
Tell me like, Rob, you should play Assassin's Creed
Why don't you talk about Assassin's Creed on your show?
Why aren't you playing this game?
I tried Assassin's Creed 1, nah
It was just kind of not for me
I just wanted to play 2
Simply because it was Renaissance Italy
And you get to kill
Dometicis and that's always fun
Because when they weren't busy
Being Pope or killing each other off
They're a very interesting family
But yeah, all those same people telling me to play Assassin's Creed
I'm sure when they hear I started with a third game
They're gonna be like, what are you doing?
Don't do that one
But too late, and I'm enjoying it well enough
So, hey, the good news is if 3
Is like the worst one, then
That gives me incentive to go play 1 and 2 again
I don't think 3 was the worst one
It sold way better than 4 did
Well, wait a minute though
4's only been out, what, since Friday?
I'm talking the first 4 days
Oh wait, that's right, 4 was out on the other consoles
Well, but could that be because
Of the spread where some people are waiting for
PlayStation 4 and Xbox One and all that?
It's funny because actually for work
I was doing some comparisons
Between launch
Basically from that Tuesday to
The Saturday launch
Week
Versus their previous
Iterations and stuff
Just a little bit
Of a spoiler here
Call of Duty and Ghost did not sell
Every 1 billion copies, they sold
Into retail 1 billion copies
They sold through maybe about
177 million dollars
Worth of that, not 1 billion dollars
And then
Assassin's Creed 4
I don't remember what it was, but it was about
It was less than half
Of Assassin's Creed 3
Assassin's Creed 3 sold really well
My idea with that is because they changed
Up the locale and it was a little bit of a different
Type of game, so it was a lot more interesting
Warriors 4 is very similar
To Assassin's Creed 3 except now it's
Pirates and there's more of the ship
Stuff in there, but
I don't know, no one cares about
Call of Duty for some reason this year
Looking at our chatroom at
Live.vognetwork.com, Tim Tripp
Says, I'm loving Assassin's Creed 4
Sexy pirate adventure time
Assassin's Creed 3, the part
I played, didn't have pirates, but it had a little bit
Of the boat
I don't know if you've been
Marking yourself for download for all those free
Xbox games
Right? No, I don't think I have
They had Assassin's Creed 2 on there
Did they? Yeah
Stupid me
Other comments on Assassin's Creed
DKB says I couldn't get through the first one
But the rest were great
Let's see
Burr says the Assassin's Creed 2 trilogy is good
Or you could go right into Assassin's Creed 4
And
Let's see
Well they had it out on PS3
And now it's out on 360 as well
Gene in our chatroom at Live.vognetwork.com says
Maybe the second one, it's cheap
Easily sets up how to play
So here you go
Some comments and suggestions from our chatroom at Live.vognetwork.com
That's pretty much it for my gaming week
I have some other Playstation Network things to get into
But I didn't play them enough
So I'll get into them a little later on next week
So let's
Move into gaming news
But first we'll do some housekeeping
So I should say one other thing
And this kind of goes to housekeeping too
Cheat plug time, you ready? Ready for cheat plug?
Yay
So one other game I played this week
Was the retro-tastic Jumpman Jr.
On Commodore 64
Which is one of my earliest gaming memories
And I played it because I'm toying around with this new project
For my YouTube channel
So if you want to see me playing
A good 20-25 minutes of Jumpman Jr.
Go check out my YouTube channel
My username over there is RobRobertsPlays
All one word
You will get my YouTube page to come right up
Because I have some other newer stuff
Like I did some streaming and typing in the dead
That old Slenderman video from a few months ago
That's all there
But you can check out my Let's Remember series with Jumpman Jr.
First video is up
I started to do a second video tonight
But I couldn't use it because
Get this, I was trying to do
I don't want to say the game because I'll probably end up doing it later
But it was an Atari 2600 game, I'll say that much
And when I was recording
Because the old Atari 2600 games
When there was too much on the screen
It would have the flicker
So when it was recorded
It recorded at just the right frames a second
That when I was doing one part of the game
My character just disappears in the video
So you can't even see it
Because of the flicker
I'm starting to learn about all that fun stuff
But the Jumpman Jr. one looks great
So check that out over at YouTube
And I will be adding more videos to it
I had a really nice response to that first video
There are classic games
Both mainstream stuff and neglected stuff
I'm kind of starting with a bunch of games
That don't get talked enough about
But I have a shit ton of Commodore 64 stuff
I want to play
And even older stuff, Atari 2600 and so on
Alright
Let's get into some other housekeeping
Twitter. Twitter.com slash O-L-R
Is where you can follow the show
And we're also on Facebook
Facebook.com slash OrangeLoungeRadio
We crossed 600 likes this week
Thank you guys very much
Nice little milestone on Facebook
But we could use more
So please give us your likes over on Facebook
You can also listen to this program
Not just via iTunes
And the app store and all that
But we are also available on streaming sites
So just tune in and Stitcher Radio
And that's an opportunity for me to say
That Stitcher Radio does have reviews now
And those really help with exposure
They do have a direct impact on that
So please, if you enjoy the show
We really, really appreciate it
Alright, let's get into
Some gaming news now
It's been a very busy week with the launch of a system
And everything, right Loki?
Yeah, so
As with any console launching
There's sometimes hiccups with things
One of which is people encountering
The blinking blue light
Which is a
Error indicator
It can mean a bunch of different things
Including
An issue with TV compatibility
An issue with the power supply
The hard drive, or something else
So
Yeah, and they kind of
Go through some of the things to try
Of course, you know
Turn it off, turn it back on
Number one thing that you do with anything
That's mechanical
Is reboot
Of course, there's
One of the things I know that people
Are mentioning is sometimes there's an issue
Where the HDMI port that they have on there
That part of the metal shielding
On there is popped up
And you have to push it down because your
HDMI cable might not go all the way
Into the port and make a bad connection
Then that
You know, causes that wonderful light
To pop up as well
Or, your hard drive might not be seated properly
And you need to go pop that out
And maybe put it back in
And see if that works
So they have a lot of stuff
Obviously through Sony's support site
You can check it out
If you have a problem
Or just fucking complain and say
Hey, my shit's not working, I just bought this system
What the fuck
And they'll send you a coffin to
Send your system back and fix it
But don't do what everybody else does
Which is just write an angry post on the internet
Because that's not really going to fix anything
No
So what do you think? I don't know
Is it doom and gloom for Sony?
No, because they were saying
That it's a lot of these issues
So far that they've charted
As far as people calling it
It's only been about
You know, was it
0.04%
Or something like that
Of the systems that are out there
So that's about like
I think we're going to get the numbers later on
But it's only a few thousand systems out of
About a million systems launched
So
Yeah, obviously
Those people are very vocal
So it's making it sound like a larger issue
But until
It becomes a larger issue
Like the Xbox 360 launch
That's actually well within
Usual
Hardware tolerances
Here's the thing though
Just to play devil's advocate a little bit
Didn't the 360 and Microsoft and all that
Grossly understate the amount of 360
Consoles that were having problems
Because I think they said what
I don't know, the number was really low
And then at one point they said it was 30%
Like they went as high as it was
But just the people I know
It's more like 75%
Of those things had problems
For real
Considering how many consoles I went through
On the Xbox 360 and how
My Playstation systems
1, 2, and 3
Not a problem at all
I actually took apart my Playstation 3
A couple weeks ago
When I thought
Oh it's pretty hot
I'm sure there's a ton of fucking cat hair
In there
Surprisingly there's no cat hair in there
How the fuck did that happen?
My computer is full of cat hair
But that system for some reason
Nothing
I don't know what they did to it
It's a magic cat hair repellent
I've never had a problem with any of the
Microsoft would be the one I'd be very wary about
Because like I said I went through about 12 systems
With them so
Yeah I'm a little bit more skeptical
With Microsoft hardware
But
It's not to say that it's
Not possible that there is
A widespread thing but
So far it doesn't seem to be that
With the Xbox 360 at launch
Everybody was being affected by it
You knew someone that had
Something go wrong with their system
It's very obvious
But we'll see
Once they just went through
And sold a ton of systems
We'll see if we start hearing more about this
If it's going to be a widespread thing
But I don't think it is
At the moment
Yet another reason I avoid launch
Well you know what though
I bought my 360 like 4 months after launch
And it still wasn't fixed
So I worry that if there is a problem
It's not going to get fixed overnight
Go into our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
ShadowNextGen says Loki was
One of the lucky ones not to have a Playstation 1
Or Playstation 2 without problems
Very nice I have a launch 20 gig PS3
And it works just fine
I'm just hoping that it doesn't crap out someday
Because that would suck I've never had a problem
With any of my systems except the 360
My Playstation 1
And Japanese Playstation 2 and American
One were fine Well my
JPS2 is a launch one too
And it's been working just fine perfectly
And my PS3 was a launch PS3
And it's zero problems
You know how apt those were
To having issues
But we did
One of our Xboxes red ringed
But we haven't had the problem since
And they were still making them under those same specs
So
I think they've learned their lesson a lot
Especially with the red ring thing
Was the whole overheating of those chips
And technology has gotten so much better
In the years now that they're not using
30 nanometer chips anymore
They're using 20, 30 nanometer chips
That are way cooler, way more
Energy efficient
So running into
Heating problems nowadays isn't
As much of an issue anymore
Because technology has improved
So much in the years
I think unless
Of course you're shoving your system
Into a closed look area
The red light of doom was one of the ones
That people were saying on the
PlayStation 4, that's from overheating
But
I just don't think right now we haven't heard enough
To where
I think it's widespread yet
We'll see, I mean if we hear that there's a ton of people being affected
By it or if it's something that
It's fine now
But like you know
Two weeks down the road all of a sudden everyone's systems start dying
Then that's something different
Alright well
Moving on to more talk about
PlayStation 4
When they released that giant FAQ on Sony's side
A few weeks ago
Some people were very upset to hear that there was not going to be
Any type of playback in the games
And that the PlayStation 4 for some weird reason
Won't even play CDs
I guess CDs are a dying thing
Which is ironic because this is Sony
Like didn't Sony start the CD player stuff?
Like it's kind of weird
That their own device wouldn't even play CDs
But whatever
Anyhow
So Sony is hearing the
Loud vocal internet people
That are bitching a lot about the MP3s
Being missing in the CDs and so forth
It was in the form of a response
From the president of Sony Worldwide Studios
Shuhei Yoshida
Who said the biggest surprise for us
All internally at Sony was that there are so many
People who passionately reacted
To our announcements that there's no MP3
Support or CD support on day one
It's not like we actively decided
Let's not do this feature so people
Will have to subscribe to Music Unlimited
Except that's the way I saw it
It's interesting that
He fires that direct shot
There's a lot of people saying that
Whether you want
I'm just saying believe him or not
But he did come out and say we did not
Do it because of this
Let me finish the quote
The focus has been more on the game features
Some of the features we wanted
But couldn't get in on day one
I would like to explain why he did put it out
If they said
You guys could have had CD MP3 playback
But then we wouldn't have had game streaming
Or something like that
It just sounds
Odd
That they would just omit this stuff
Yet
Hey that Music Unlimited service works just fine
It's just a little odd
Is it working though?
Have any of the PlayStation 4 adopters
Signed up for Music Unlimited just because
They had to hear their Lady Gaga
While they're playing?
There's a lot of detail in there
With all the launch systems
One of the things I did like
Just kind of reminded me based off that picture
Is
One of the things I don't even know if they've really been talking about
Those controllers have a headphone out on them
For game audio
Like actual game audio from
Your TV
Before
About a month ago or so
I didn't have a wireless headset for my PlayStation 3
I just had headphones
And that would work fantastic
Just being able to
Have that audio without having to bug anybody
But I thought that was kind of a neat feature
That I wish all consoles had
It's neat to see that on there
But yeah it would be cool
If I could play MP3's back
Or put MP4's
On a jump drive or something
And watch them on my system like I can
On my PlayStation 3
It's kind of dumb that they don't have that
But hey if it's something that
They can get this out on time
And so they just focus on game related features
Now and then they're going to add that all in
Quarter one next year or something
Ok I'm fine with that
Yeah he did go on to say
As we speak the people in Japan
The system guys are discussing
When we can put these features in
Ok well then it sounds like that's what it is
But you know
It is a little
Perplexing that oh hey Music Unlimited
Works
You know we couldn't
Possibly squeeze out
The one programmer
That's going to take to implement MP3
Playback on
I mean come on how fucking hard is it
Going to be to implement MP3 Playback
On a goddamn PS4
I don't think it's going to be that hard to write
An MP3 Playback
App
It just doesn't seem like it would be that difficult
I don't know
Alright by the way some folks in chat
ActDef says
Philips did the CD but Sony jumped on the CD quickly too
Rama says it was a joint venture
Between Philips and Sony
I do remember that Philips was heavily involved
And Philips had the CDI back in the day
So they got into gaming at one point
You remember that Sony worked on the
Super Nintendo's processor and I believe was supposed to make
A CD unit
And then like no let's do our own thing
I think it was Nintendo didn't want to do it
Something to that effect
But at any rate Sony took what they
Had from having worked with Nintendo
And jumped on their own little
Bit of the wagon
Gaming history y'all
Alright well so you'll get
To have your or as
What is it sg100matt in chat says
If I can't listen to Kesha while I'm gaming
Then that's a deal breaker
You'll get your
We are who we are
Or whatever songs it is she does
You'll get those to play those songs
In Need for Speed or whatever soon enough
Help because I like Kesha
I blame you for showing me that video
Oh now the video
She did with James Van Der Beek
That was great
You know I checked out the directors other videos
And they are equally as brilliant
But I blame you
To register participation for this weeks episode of
Orange Lounge Radio at vognetwork.com
Use the pass phrase hate
Let's move on
Chakra you're next actually
Well how about some wank
Wank wank and more wank
God damn you blizzard
During the show it's gross
Blizzard is a bunch of fuckers
Why? Because they put out an expansion
I'm actually interested in
Warlords of Draenor
Blah blah blah level 90 blah blah blah
I mean actually level 100
But they're doing an instant level 90 now
With the expansion which I think is stupid
But I'll talk about that in a minute
So basically you get to go into the past
And learn more stuff about the space goats
And explore the land of the space goats
And hang out with the space goats
And hopefully play more space goats
Because that was my favorite race
I'm glad to hear the Draenei aren't getting
Fucked over in this expansion
Because in the last couple of expansions
They've just been absent
Like straight up not a part of it
Fuck your pandas
Fuck all these other people
We're gonna go here and be Russian
Or at least sound
Like
Eastern European accent
And honestly I actually
They're my favorite race
In the entire anything
Having to do with Warcraft
My first character
When I actually decided to play
Longer than level 20
Was Erisa remember?
My arcane mage
And I had so much fun with it
I played through all of Cataclysm
Without any help practically
Except for just being in the guild
I didn't do dungeons, I didn't craft
I didn't discover crafting until like
I had already started raiding I think
So it was kind of funny
But yeah they're boosting level cap to 100
And you can instantly upgrade
One character to level 90
So that you can start
Playing the new content
Which I would like to see
If there are other restrictions
On this just because keep in mind
People
Part of the reason that you level
Is to not just
Gain the experience and the
Abilities of your character in game
But so that you learn the mechanics
Of your character in game
And by learning those mechanics
It makes you an overall
Better rounded player
You know how you fit in
Should you decide to do instances
Which some are fun, some are not
You know but
And people will give you unwanted tips
On how to play your class
Even when you don't give a shit
Which assholes
We were talking a little bit about this on Horde House
Just at that point
There's supposed to be some type of like
Scenarios or something that help you
Like if you're a brand new level one
That boosts to 90
You get some type of scenario
But that's still I don't think gonna be good enough
It's an interesting
Band-aid
You know like even
I always kind of like approach that
Because I don't play World of Warcraft
And I don't know too much about it
And this announcement just
Nothing, I feel nothing
Jumped out and saying hey that looks really cool
I just like kind of eh whatever
They didn't really do anything to attract
New players to be honest
Which kind of sounds like a mistake to me
And this is the crappy thing because I really
Want to play it for the lore
You know I really want to
See what the new stuff is
It's very interesting to me
But I just completely dropped
World of Warcraft for Final Fantasy
And I'm really enjoying Final Fantasy
I enjoy not having to rep grind
I don't care about doing all the what is it the
Titan crap or
What's the other stuff that you guys have been doing
The primal fights basically
I can get those later
I haven't had this wild urge
To like massively level I've been
Able to sit back and enjoy the game
And that's kind of what I dug about playing through Cataclysm
The first time but then when I got to all the
Panda shit I was like it really
Was literally steaming piles of panda shit
That's all it was
Rep grinding, the rep grinding got worse
With the freaking pandas
And I hated the arena
And I hated the Pokemon battle
Because it was fine for like a week
And I got sick of it
But yeah along with this too there of course will be new
Zones, dungeons, new raids, scenarios
Battlegrounds
There's supposed to be improvements like a
Reskinned character models
And new animation
But I hope that they never change the night elf
Dance because that shit's funny
So you can watch the trailer online it's pretty
I
Part of me just does not want to give a shit
The other part of me is like
Goats
You know I'm not super into
World war class lore I never have been
Which is funny you know with the podcast and everything
But I was always more about the social aspect
And the garrison sounds really neat
The whole player cities
Or whatever sound really neat
Well it almost sounds like they're trying to give a nod back to
The original Warcraft games
Because you pretty much had your
Own towns and your defensible areas
You know when you did places
That's a good point
The other thing that's just really
I'm wondering
The updates I think
As far as characters and animation
Are necessary
They are long overdue
And I realize they've been trying to cater to people
On older systems that might not be able to
Keep up with it but at the same
Time I think that keeping like
A window of about maybe
Five years worth of
Computer
What's the word I'm trying to think of
Being friendly to older systems
Is a safe bet rather than
How long has the game been out now like what
Oh nine years almost
And they were still catering to people
From computers still on
I mean I was playing
Whatever you had
Installed on your
Macbook
I was playing that stuff on your
Macbook and it was still
Just fine
So I mean
I don't know I really
Really really really
Want to see the new stuff
It's just I don't know if it's so
Worth it to me I've been well you know I read
All the books that came out during
Cataclysm I got all of those books
I love the freaking thrall book I didn't read the Jaina
Book though because I'm just pissed off about what they did to her
I mean I hate how her
Character has become she used to be like one of my favorites
Even though I made fun of her
But because I do have a character named
Jaina
Who I made look like her
But other than that
I can
Get the lore stuff from my friends or I can
Get it on YouTube I watched the whole ending
Of the Garrosh bullshit
On YouTube
Yeah oh there's two versions right? I've watched both of them
No I'm
Mildly surprised but not
Majorly I just like Jaina shut up
Your trauma's showing
Granted
It's well earned trauma but still
I don't want to repeat myself too much
From Wednesday's word house but some of my co-hosts
Really got into how they
Feel that this is being charged for a patch
That a lot of this stuff should have been
Taken care of in a patch
But I said that you know I'm
Really looking forward to five man's coming back
Thank god because I've been really pissed
Off that Pandaria neglected them
And that's probably the reason I'm not playing right now
It's because I really can't fucking stand LFR
And but
Five man's you can tolerate it's much easier
When it's five people versus twenty five
It's something about that social dynamic
But I am really jazzed to hear about these
Rating changes where now you can
LFR with eleven people
So if you can put a group together and
You know when I say eleven that's an arbitrary
Number between ten and twenty five
You can now do LFR difficulty with
A pre-established group of like eleven twelve people
Everything flexes now
And for the hardcore players they're getting a new
Difficulty called mythic rating
That's all twenty man that's it no more tens and
Twenty fives twenty man
That part's cool
I do actually miss the rating but you know
The big crappy part of it was at the end
Was that I like to
Chat with all my friends you know
In the guild
And it just sort of got to be a ghost
Town sort of I mean I was fine doing all the
Stuff by myself it's a you can easily
Play through anything in
World of Warcraft as a solo game
Right and it's the actually
That's one advantage it has over Final Fantasy
Fourteen to me because you have to
Have other people to do the
The duty
Things like what's
The like the dungeons
The dungeons yeah you have to do those yeah
I like the better that they're four people
And not five but still it's
I liked having the option of
Me being able to do this shit by myself and
Then going back and doing
Dungeons alone
So that I could see what they were like because you know
That's how I was farming for
And you can't do that
In Final Fantasy Fourteen because it level sinks you
Exactly which is you know
It's good and bad
So yeah pluses and minuses
I don't know for right now there's
As much as I
Really really want to see the new content
I can't justify it so
Well we don't even know the date anyway so you have a long time
To make up your mind
So if Final Fantasy Fourteen turns crusty and old then maybe I'll be back
Which it might and Blizzard's probably
Banking on that a little bit so we'll see
Alright moving on
Loki
So let's talk a little bit
About the
Let's go back and talk about gold
As I mentioned before
You know there's the Xbox Live
Games with Gold thing that you get
Some free games and originally
It was oh hey we're gonna like
Stop it you know once
Xbox One comes out and everyone's like
Why the fuck aren't you just continuing
That well now they're like well hey we're gonna
We're gonna do it again and uh
We're gonna keep it going through
2014 and we're gonna include
Xbox One games on a monthly basis
Which makes me
Believe that that's
Probably gonna be digital games
Cause I don't see them
Giving away
Well I could see them giving away
Rise cause that game looks like crap but
There's no way they're giving away retail games for the first year
Or for at least six months
Probably a lot of download stuff
So yeah it'll be a while
But um hey
Still though it's good to see that that's gonna be continuing
On I would not be surprised
Though even if they did retail games
That that doesn't change to be more like
The Playstation Network program where
You have to continue being a live member
In order to I mean cause come on they
Put everything else behind the fucking paywall
What makes you think that they're all of a sudden gonna just
Continue on with oh sure are we generous
To give you free games that you can have forever
Nah nah this is Microsoft
Sony's doing it and people
Are happy with it they're gonna do it too
Um I guess
Yeah I'm excited to go
In there and see what they're gonna give away on 360
And maybe flag some of the
Games but at the same time my
Account's coming up for renewal
Soon I don't know if I'm gonna do it
Cause I'm just like there's really nothing
I'm playing online on 360 anymore
I've been playing Mass Effect 3 pretty heavily for a while
But now most of the people I play with are on PC
And we haven't really done
Forzen forever and
There's really not a lot to play on 360 right now
Even on PS to be fair on Playstation 3
There's not a lot I play online either it's all PC
Or really nothing
It's all free now so I mean it's free
True
Mine's renewing soon too but I do
Play quite a bit on 360
So I'll probably keep mine but
You know it
The free games aren't really
A benefit right now it's just kinda like
Oh cool old ass shit I don't
Want anyways but I'll take it
Because you're giving it to me for free
You know it's like I already have Halo
Or I already have Crackdown but
Now I have a digital version of it
Fable 3 another one
Oh fantastic
Fable 3 was kinda crap anyway
Alright let's move on
Nintendo put out a bit of news
This week they did another one of their
Nintendo Directs which is how they get the news out
These days taking their case
Directly to their fans and
Cutting out all the skeptics in between
This is the news that came out
On their Direct on November 13th
A release date for Mario Party Island Tour
In Europe that will be January even though we're
Getting that next week right? Sorry Europe
You gotta wait till the new year
The 3DS will be getting YouTube
Which is kinda one of those things they announced it and I went
It's not already there and I
Oh yeah it's really not already there so
Finally YouTube on the 3DS
Grasping the internet
Which by the way let me throw this out there
See what the live chatters think I was gonna keep this a
Secret but what the hell
I'm thinking about putting OLR episodes up in full
On YouTube and no this will not involve
Video but just like a static picture
While you have because now you don't have to break
Things up into 15 minutes anymore so you just do 3 hours
And my
Big problem right now I can't get in the Orange
Zaun's radio account so I need Jason's help
Getting me back in there I don't remember how to get in
They switched YouTube so many times now
With the integration I can't log into the account
So hopefully Jason can figure it out or he might be
Screwed I'm gonna have to get a new name but I am thinking about
Putting up episodes in full on
YouTube which when I hear things like
This like oh YouTube on the 3DS
I go oh that would be really cool
Because people can't like
Download MP3's on their
DS or at least I don't think they can right
That's not really a thing you can't like do podcasts
On a 3DS otherwise yeah I think it does have a
Sound player but I'm not sure if it's
MP3's or if it's like
MPA or that
iTunes format or whatever it is
Regardless you can't do podcasts we know that
Even though the PSP did that website on the
PSP that did it you can't really do it easy
So that is something we're toying with
So that's really cool to hear that YouTube
Will be on the 3DS so that you know
For whatever it is on YouTube you want to look at
And YouTube on the 3DS
I believe that there is a YouTube
Player for the Playstation 4 as well
So there you go
Hey it's all over the place there you go
Alright um other things
3DS and Wii U
There's going to be a system update for both
And finally the eShops will be
Combined thank god it's about
Time right they're going to combine the
eShops not the games
Sorry but the account balances
Will be one and the same so the good news
Is if you have like 23 cents sitting
In your wallet on 3DS and like you know
23 cents on your all that leftover
Change you'll be able to combine it
Yay buy something
And not have that leftover change anymore
DLC coming to
Pikmin 3
DLC worked out pretty well for Mario Wii U
Last year with the Super Luigi Brothers
So it will be interesting to see what comes to the
Pikmin 3 DLC
Bravely Default comes to the US on
February 7th
Professor Layton and the Azran Legacy
Comes out in North America on February 28th
And there is a new
Hero mode in Zelda A Link Between
Worlds and
There's also something
About and I'm not finding here Miiverse
On 3DS but I know we have a
Kind of a follow up on that in a little bit here
So I'll wait for that but one other
Big thing I wanted to mention here is Super Mario 3D
World the rumors
From a couple weeks ago that Rosalina is going to be
A playable character turned out to be true
You will not only have your classic
Mario Brothers 2 characters meaning
Mario, Luigi, Toad and Princess Toadstool
But Rosalina will be unlocked
And she does like a little
Spin attack type thing
So she will be available in Super Mario
3D World I missed what the
Qualifications were to unlock her
I want to say that if you had like a
Save file from the old game you get it right away
No no that's um
If you have Super Luigi Brothers you get the
Classic Mario Brothers
Reskinned into Luigi Brothers you get
That but
Yeah that's really cool Rosalina is another character there
So hooray
Yeah I'm very excited about Mario
3D World
I'm glad
Yay excitement
Alright DarkSakura what do you have for us
Well speaking of
3DS stuff Miiverse
Has got a few restrictions on it that may
Not please people
It's the Wii U social network
That they're doing
It's going to be out on 3DS in December
But they are not going to allow
Private messages or
Friend requests they don't have those
Features basically I think
That's kind of going along with what
Happened with
Not PictoChat
Swapnote
To avoid
You know getting out anything
That may not be safe for little kitties
And you know
An easily offendable adult
So it's
They're still
Going to be able to use this for
Consolidating their eShop
Balances like you were saying
And
But they can leave
Comments about games
There's a sort of a bulletin board thing about that
But you're not going to be able to
Do the actual private
Message person to person
Cause there might be a penis
If you allow that
You know what
If they're allowing you to put comments on a bulletin
Board it is very
Easy to do an ASCII cock
Yeah but Miiverse is moderated
That stuff gets poor
It'll be on there for 5 seconds Rob
That's right somebody might see it in 5 seconds
Someone will see the penis
They will touch it they will love it
With their little stylus
Boop it
Boop the penis
Boop
Oh I thought you meant to say boppet
Like I'm thinking about those old like
Boppet twist it throw it
Turn it
I saw one of those at the thrift store the other day and some kid was playing with it
And was like this toy
Sucks
I was like that's what we thought
When it came out
Didn't they make like boppet for the Nintendo Wii
Am I crazy or wasn't there like actually
A boppet game
No there wasn't a boppet game
There was like Jenga
They had a few Jenga games
And I was like what the
That's dumb
People can barely play Jenga in real life
No I guess there was
There was a family game night
That came out
That boppet I guess
Why did I think there was a boppet game
Because that would be a retarded enough idea
Where they might do something like that
I mean they made Jenga
Wow really S2 under Matt says there's a boppet TV show
I didn't know that
Why?
I had no idea
If it was like chicks topless
And dudes pantsless playing
Bop it
That might be the reason to watch the TV show right
Fair enough
Maybe
Cinemax needs to get in on the boppet TV show
Bop it
Twist it
Turn it
Touch it
I'm sorry you were talking about
I don't like where this shows going
You were talking about pantsless guys
Hilarious mental imagery
Equal opportunity
If you gotta have topless chicks
But I imagine that male dangly bits look a lot more hilarious
Than boobs bouncing
Alright
Moving on
I don't like where this shows going
It's going to a dark place
Let's go to release dates
What your pants
Loki save the show
And please read the release dates
See how sis think of the children
Shut up
Well next week we have the launch of the
Xbox One
So that will be coming out on Friday
Along with that a bunch of other games
Including and not necessarily all
For the Xbox One
Zumba Kids
For the Wii and Xbox 360
NBA Live 14
For the Playstation 4 and Xbox One
Assassin's Creed 4 Black Flag
Coming out on PC and Xbox One
Walking Dead Game of the Year edition
The good one from Telltale
Another crappy Activision one
That's on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
Need for Speed Rivals on all the other systems
Other than Playstation 4
It's on PS3, Xbox 360, Xbox One
And PC
Young Justice Legacy on Playstation 3
Xbox 360 and 3DS
Let's see here
Zuma Fitness World Party on Xbox One
The Amazing Spiderman on Vita
Just Dance 2014 on Xbox One
Battlefield 4 on Xbox One
FIFA 14, Madden 25
Also Xbox One
Banfuse Rock Legends on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
That's sort of like Rocksmith
But not Rocksmith
Although hey that game did have a cameo
In what was it
The movie 43
Or whatever that was
Isn't that movie awful?
I heard horrible things
Oh it wasn't very good
I watched it, it was not funny
Adventure Time Explorer Dungeon
Because I don't know
That's coming out on Playstation 3, Xbox 360
Wii U and on the 3DS
Fighter Within on Xbox One
Aqua Pasa
Aqua Plus Dream Match
On Playstation 3
And what else we've got here
I know there's some Nintendo games coming out as well
Of course
We've got Mario Party
Island Tour on the 3DS
We also have
Angry Birds Star Wars on Xbox One
Lego Marvel Super Heroes on Xbox One
Gamestick!
They're still claiming they're coming out that week
So maybe that'll be out
Zoo Tycoon on 360
Forza Motorsport 5
Dead Rising 3
Girls Fashion Shoot
For the 3DS
Rise Son of Rome
The Legend of Zelda
The Link Between Worlds on 3DS
Tearaway on the Vita
Super Mario 3D World
On Wii U
As well as that wonderful Nintendo 3DS XL
Golden Black with
The Legend of Zelda The Link Between Worlds
That's it
And then it officially dies to nothing
I was gonna say last big week of the year
It goes into a coma for the next
Two months
Last big week of the year because then
After that you've got Black Friday
And that's when all the stuff is supposed to be out by
Well actually there's like
The first week in December you've got
Gran Turismo 6
And then it literally
There is nothing
Well the South Park game was supposed to be there
Yeah the South Park was supposed to be on the 10th
Now on the 10th there's
Sorcery Saga
Some game about Curry
That's coming out on the Vita
And then January there's literally
The disc version of Wii Fit U
The pedometer and you want to buy
The disc version of the game
And then the bundle with the
Balance board
And Dragon Ball Z Battle for Z on PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360
That's it
That's literally everything between now and January
And February
It's like nothing
This segment will go by quickly
What's coming out?
Nothing
Let's see go into our chatroom at
Live.vognetwork.com
I'm all over that shit
Cause I'm a classy bitch
You and me both Cody
By the way speaking of classy bitch
I want to thank Alan for bringing me the wine
To drink during the show
Can I smell it? Yes you may
You could have a little taste if you want
I don't know if it's against your
What you can and can't eat right now
You know what I have to try that stuff that Victoria told me about
The Fravolo?
Yeah
I need some of that in my life
Actually we're looking at going out to the winery in a couple weeks
To do that
Kidnap me. I don't know if Lady Victoria will be here
But she hasn't been on the show in forever
She was on like one show in the old studio
None of the listeners here probably know her
We need to kidnap her. We do
Victoria would be great on this show
Because she's a wow widow
In one of her relationships many years ago
The guy cared about World of Warcraft
More than her
And so she's got all these stories about how much she hates
The storming the castle game
I've wanted to get her on Horde House because of that
But anyway, I digress
Let's talk about Japanese release dates
On the Playstation 4 this week
You guys don't get the Playstation 4 until February
I'm so mean. Why did I say that?
Well actually
I will bring this around because
I kind of think that whole
Delay in Japan kind of plays
Into part of the reason why I'm not feeling
The Playstation 4 here right now
Because I think a lot of stuff isn't coming out
Until Japan has the Playstation 4
So I think that plays into it more
Than we might want to admit here in the US
I don't know, but anyway
That just kind of was a little reminder there
As I was looking at the release dates
Oh yeah, Japan didn't have all this craziness that we had here this week
With Playstation 4
However, on the Playstation 3
Still kicking this week in Japan
Hey, if you're mad at me about what I said about the Playstation 4
You can get your revenge this week
With Lightning Returns Final Fantasy 13
I really want that game
I can't play it until like February
It takes me revenge because after the last one
It might be just like
I thought Final Fantasy 13 2 was good
It was good
Whatever
Final Fantasy 13 Lightning Returns
It'll be interesting, we'll say that much one way or the other
That is out in Japan this week on the Playstation 3
Hanasaku Mani Mani also comes out
Monster Hunter Frontier G
In like a beginners package
Is out this week as well
In Japan
Need for Speed Rivals makes its way to Japan as well
And Shin Atelier Rorona Hajimari no Morgatari
The Alchemist of Arland
Comes out this week on Playstation 3
As well
There's also by the way like a special
Ultimate box for Lightning Returns
I guess that's some type of collector's edition I didn't really read up on
Because I don't plan on importing it
On the Xbox 360 this week in Japan
Looking there real quick
Just Lightning Returns on the 360 as well
And Need for Speed Rivals
Also comes out in Japan this week on the 360
Going over to the Playstation Vita
The Shin Atelier Rorona game I mentioned earlier
Is also on the Playstation Vita
And that's really it this week on the Vita
And the Wii U this week
Gets Super Mario 3D World
Taiko no Tatujin on the Wii U
Damn the Wii U for not being region-free
Damn it because I would so import that game
I love Taiko no Tatujin
It's so cute
It still had the inflatable drum
Although it probably doesn't
It probably uses the touchpad and the stylus
Oh no I guess they're selling a bundle set
That has a Taiko with it
And a bocce
They don't have a picture of what it looks like
Oh there it is
There's a tiny tiny little picture of it
I love the little Taiko on the thing
They're so cute
And they look like kitty faces
I want to take one of the little
I have a Taiko plushie
And I wanted to put kitty ears on it
Just because it looks like cat faces
So cute
On the Nintendo 3DS
This week in Japan
We have a Nintendo 3DS XL
In Chopper Pink
And Luffy Red
In conjunction with
One Piece Unlimited World R
From Bandai Namco
And gets those special 3DS's with that
There's also Tongari Bushi
To Maho Nomachi
And Atsufutari
No My Princess
Biohazard Revelations
Or Resident Evil of course
Gets a price reduction this week
And most importantly on the 3DS
If you screw up on all those other games
Don't worry
Mama will fix it
And Cooking Mama 5 out this week in Japan
I'm glad Mama's going back to her roots
After all that gardening shit
What the hell else did Mama fix?
What were all those spinoff games?
I know there was Gardening Mama
I thought there was one other one
There's Crafting Mama
Babysitting Mama
Remember with the creepy one
Yeah they put the Wii Remote inside
It's ass
I remember that
There was Crafting Mama
Gardening Mama
Babysitting Mama
And then 3 or 4 Cooking Mamas
Alright
There you go
By AkumaJP in our chatroom
I have no problem understanding that
Good job
Yay I pronounced at least one of those games correctly
12 years
Will do a lot
Never had a class believe it or not
Let's go around for the
UK releases Dark Sakura
There were a few things
Actually a few things coming out
It's a pretty long list
So I'm just going to start from the 19th
We have on the 19th NBA Live 14
Then on the 20th we have
Contrast and Soul Calibur 2 HD Online
And then on the 21st
There is Battlefield 4
FIFA 14
Madden XL
I got the 3DS thing on the head
Madden NFL 25
And Shiva Kosher Edition
Wait
I need to check this out
Then on the 22nd
Angry Birds Star Wars
Assassin's Creed 4
Basically all the new release stuff
The system release stuff
So there's Crimson Dragon, Dead Rising 3
Connect Sports Rivals
Preseason, Need for Speed Rivals
Blah blah blah
Tearaway
Legend of Zelda, Link Between Worlds, Watch Dogs
Young Justice Legacy
Power Star Golf and Zoo Tycoon
Alright, that's it
Yarp
Busy busy week, that segment is going to slow down
In the coming weeks
Have fun with all the games
There's a lot to choose from
It's a great time to be a gamer
No matter what system it is you're backing right now
Or if it's several, lots of great stuff to look forward to
And PC gamers
Not leaving you guys out because
There's that rumored Steam sale coming right after Thanksgiving
There's a fall sale and then there's an
Actual
Xmas or holiday sale
Prepare your wallets
Winter is coming
Winter Sale is coming
Alright
Let's do a few more news stories
And then the classic game of the week, Loki
So Nintendo has actually
Purchased some stake in
I guess this company
Dwango
Dwango owns Nico Nico
Which is a video
Delivery service
And I guess
Maybe they're planning on
Using that to
I don't know, either deliver
Games or
No idea
But it's interesting
To see that they
Purchase
612,000 shares
So
Interesting, web services
It's a web service company that provides
Content through mobile phones
I don't know if that means
Streaming videos or something
Interesting that they're getting involved
Hmmm
Tinfoil hat
Tinfoil hat time
Could this be a clue
Just buying stock in the company doesn't necessarily mean
It's not buying the company
Could this be a clue
About where Nintendo wants to go
With their next handheld system
Not going to say that they're going to make it a phone
Because I don't think that's correct
But maybe something about
What if it
Could get data
I think it's like an iPad
It does 4G and it does streaming video
That's the one thing we didn't really see
On the 3DS that I thought we would
Like I know it's got Netflix and that stuff
Well they had that at first
Remember they were going to do 3D movies on there
Yeah, whatever happened to that
They kind of fizzled out I guess
I remember when they were showing the demos
The very first E3 or whatever
I think they had the trailer for Tangled
Was the one thing we saw in 3D
On the 3DS
An animated movie that was in there
And Tron was like something I was like, fuck yeah
They need to put Tron and 3D out on the 3DS
But that never happened, it fizzled
Maybe not enough demand
Could there be a hint there
If this is some type of streaming service
Could there be some type of movie thing
Being built into the next DS
I'm totally tinfoil-hatting
But I don't, I mean
The 3D movie thing sounded cool
But now that they're getting away from 3D
I don't know
It's true because maybe 3D isn't going to be such a big deal
WhatupG even agrees with you there
I think Nintendo's next handheld will be 2D
That comment from our chatroom at live.vognetwork.com
Alright
We'll see if anything comes of my tinfoil-hatting
This will be happening for sure though
Heroes of the Storm
Was another game that Blizzard announced at BlizzCon
I'm excited about this
I'm not super into MOBAs
But even though I'm terrible at them
I've tried to play them and they are fun
League of Legends and Dota 2
This is Blizzard's answer to that whole craze
Because after all, one of the first MOBAs
Defense of the Ancients
An add-on for Warcraft 3
So it kind of, in a way, started with a Blizzard game
But obviously spun out in all these different directions
Heroes of the Storm
The beta sign-ups are available
So if there's something you're interested in beta testing
You don't have to be an active WoW player
Or anything like that
You just have to have a battle.net account
And you can update your beta preferences
For Heroes of the Storm
So that's something I know I did right away
But if you guys are interested in this
Don't forget to update your battle.net accounts for the same thing
Now, they announced
Some of the heroes that are going to be in the game
And I have to admit
Even though cinematic trailers kind of bother me
Because you literally see none of the game
In these Blizzard cinematic trailers
As far as fan wank goes
It was pretty awesome
To see all these characters just out and outright
And each other here
Did you see this cinematic trailer they were doing for Heroes of the Storm
That had some of these bad guys
And good guys in it all kind of coming together
It was pretty neat
To see everybody in that one video
But I noticed, the first thing I said
Is I said, where are the lost Vikings?
Exactly, they're still hanging out in that cave
I looked at this trailer
And I said, where are the lost Vikings?
It's like an old school Blizzard property
A lot of people remember, right?
Well apparently I'm not the only one
Who came out this week
During Blizzcon
While Dustin Browder, who's a Blizzard game designer
Was being interviewed with GameSpot
He said, quote, there's a good chance for lost Vikings
That's one of the characters we've been really interested in doing
It's a way we can do three characters
And you're controlling them and swapping back and forth
I think we've really got some ideas
That we might be able to make work
But we're going to have to test it first
To really see
That's interesting, they don't want to put in the Vikings separately
They want to have like ice climbers
That's some shit
One character that you control one of
And it's all three of them type of thing
That could be very interesting
So don't count the lost Vikings out
Another one not to count out
What's that Super Nintendo game, Blackthorn?
Whatever's the one they did on Super Nintendo
They released that for free on Battle.net
You just go download it, totally for free
And have a blast with that
I have a feeling they could be putting him
In Heroes of the Storm 2
Why not?
More than just World of Warcraft
For the record, I do absolutely
Love that the lost Vikings
Are in World of Warcraft
You can just go hang out with them if you're Alliance
And you can kill the shit out of them if you're Horde
That part's pretty cool
Very cool
Alright, let's
Travel to a time that was simpler
We're going to go back to a time when lost Vikings
Might have actually been out
It's the classic game of the week
No, Dark Sakura didn't pick lost Vikings
But she did pick something else that's very cool
I picked something that my autocorrect
Tried to change to Zantac
I picked Zanac
Zanac is the classic game of the week
Zanac, and if you ever
Have played this game or have seen it played
You can definitely tell it's a freaking compile game
I mean, seriously
It's fucking compile
Um, it is
Um, like I said, designed by
Compile and released in Japan by
Pony Canyon and by FCI
In the US
It was first an MSX game as was
Gardic
Um, which we got
We got Gardic Gaiden as the guardian legend
Um, and
It came out on the Famicom Disk System
And the NES
And later on came out for the Virtual Console
And it also came out
On MSX2 as
Zanac EX and PlayStation as Zanac
X Zanac
So basically you play one ship called the
X502 Zanac through twelve levels
And you have to destroy the system
Ooh, taking down the system
So you have
Um, it was
Actually developed by
Some of the main developers at Compile
Um, these are the
Same ones who went in to do the guardian legend
Blazing lasers and Puyo Puyo
Um, it was basically
And
This is where I say you can tell it's a freaking compile shooter
Because watching it looks like
Playing through those shooting levels of guardian legend
I mean down to graphical style and everything
The music
Is definitely compile stuff
And just watching it through
It's a very fast
And kind of difficult game
It's really not super easy
And uh, you know you've got your
Weapons boost, you have uh
You either, you know
Game over when you lose your lives or you beat
The game, you do get
Extra lives as you go
Excuse me
You do also
Have like
Your special weapons
That are based off of whatever number
Is labeled
And you lose all of your powerups
Of course if you get hit
Your enemies are
You have meteors
You have different aircraft
You have these discs
That are
You can't shoot them, they're impervious
You have ground turrets
Different planes, you have your different bosses
Can I just say real quick, those discs come right out
Or are in guardian legend, I swear
Like, I have to admit
Dark Sakura, I know of Xanac
And I know some of the stuff with the lunar
Lander and all that, which we'll probably get into in a minute
But I've never actually played it
And I'm watching this
Little video here and I'm like, wow
This really does look like a shooter stage out of the guardian legend
I mean the sprites are a little different
But just the way, like the sound
Is very similar
And that's the thing about compile
You notice they did have the little
Ground things that you shoot there
Those exact things were in
Guardian legend that had your powerup
Your little
And even the way those bullets look, those are bullets
Straight out of guardian legend too, so this is interesting
Sorry, sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt that
It's good that you did because compile
I mean basically until
For all of their NES shooters, compile really did
Or, I shouldn't just say NES
They're 8-bit shooters
Really did stick
With a certain style, even blazing lasers
To an extent, has that
Overwhelming compile look
To it, and I hate to say
If you play one compile shooter, you've played most of them
You know, except
Guardian legend actually happened to have
A really cool adventure sequences
And so much to do
Now, there was that
Compilation, like I mentioned for Playstation
That was Xanac, ex-Xanac
And
As far as
That's concerned
It also had an updated version of Xanac
Called Xanac Neo
And the different NES versions
So I'd definitely say if someone can find that
They should go ahead and do it because
All in all, even if you get over
It's striking similarities to the
Other games
Then
It's still, you know
It's still
It's still a very
Good shooter to play
And I'd definitely say
It's worth adding to any library
So, that's it, Xanac
There it is
If anyone's wondering if I've done this before, I think you might be getting
Confused with Zexes
Yes, you did do Zexes, I remember that
But you've never done Xanac
Wow, somebody has already updated
I was on the wiki, because somebody in chat was suggesting
That you do Shenmue
And I was like, yeah I know, Act F was like
And I'm like, really, when?
And sure enough, you did do that in episode
326, somebody that was long, 356
You did a long time ago
Yes, this list is getting very long
But as I'm on the list, already updated
To say Xanac there, episode 527
Well done, wiki editors
And honestly, and I have to say
For the people who update the wiki, I seriously do rely on you
Because, I mean
If you guys are having trouble remembering what I've picked
Imagine the trouble I'm having
When, no no no, I have to describe
This, I've got
A wall of shelves behind me
At my house that's loaded with video games
And I have to look at this shit
Going, what have I not done?
So I've just started picking games
By freaking year, and I picked 1986 this time
So it worked
Fun OLR trivia
The very first Classic Game of the Week
Episode 250
Was the very first Classic Game of the Week
And we all know what it was
Do we? Do you remember? What was it?
It was Vibribin, no it wasn't
It was Fantasy Zone
It was Fantasy Zone, was the very first Classic Game of the Week
Because Fantasy Zone is my favorite
No, my second favorite video game ever
My first favorite being
Guardian Legend, and my third favorite being
Space Harrier
You did end up doing Guardian Legend later, and I remember you came in here and you were like
Ah, fuck it, we're doing Guardian Legend tonight
I was saving it, but
You were very much like, you know what?
The hell with it, episode 256
I kind of go through this thing where I don't
Want to do things that are too expected
Or too much of the
Everybody loves this fucking game, ooh
You know, I want to do something
That maybe people haven't heard of
Or good games that people just
May have overlooked
Sometimes you have to do Final Fantasy 6 twice
No, sometimes
Yeah
Well, like I said
It's hard to remember
You know, I'm probably going to have to do Kickle Cubicle
Just because
Dan was playing it the other day
I still have a list like a mile long of Commodore 64 games
Whenever you're ready
You need to show me some of these games
I'm going to do Oregon Trail next week, guys
That would be awesome, why don't you do Oregon Trail?
I might
If you have some suggestions for Dark Soccer
Oregon Trail is stuck in my head because I just got finished reading
Problem Sleuth
And there's a whole tribute to Oregon Trail in there
Nice
You can hit Dark Soccer up on Tumblr
I usually would give out your Twitter
You know what, I make sure to check Twitter at least once a week
So my Twitter is
DarkSakura
My Tumblr is Kurotsubasa
K-U-R-O-U-T-S-U-B-A-S-A
Blackwing
Because I'm so dark
Or, uh, shoot
Harass me on the mailbag
I'll complain about it and then critique your grammar
And then I'll probably do it
Alright, mailbag at orangeonstrader.com
We're going to take a break, though
I think I've done Twinbee
We're going to take a break, then we're going to come back
And we're going to do the mailbag
And the FUs of the Week
And your live phone calls
Rapid Fire News
PS4 sales
Politics and games
And pornography in part B tonight
Yes, a legit porn story
Coming up in part B tonight
So you definitely don't want to go anywhere
We will be right back after this
Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio Live on this Sunday evening
November the 17th, 2013
With the 527th episode of our show already in progress
And some good classic songs from some old games there during our break
Which sadly we can't play during the podcast
But we do play live
We had the epilogue from Final Fantasy IV
Which I always love that ending
And then Mega Man 7's introduction
Which, you know, I think there's mixed opinions on Mega Man 7
But I thought it was pretty cool
During the break, a lot of folks in our chat room
I noticed over at live.vognetwork.com
Talking about weight loss and a lot of successes
Which is interesting
Because Thanksgiving is not usually the time of year
When you hear about weight loss
But a lot of people have been successful with their various things
Including Dark Soccer
You've been doing very well
Yeah, I'm actually
And I know it's going to sound fad-like and everything
But I've done similar stuff before
And I honestly feel better doing it
As I'm doing this whole ketogenic eating thing
Where it's like really low carb
But you also have a percentage of like how much fat you eat
And how much protein you eat
And that's a lot of protein
But I also go to the gym at least once a week
And I do body weight exercises in my house
If I don't go to the gym
So it's working out with weights three times a week
And walking on the opposite days
I really couldn't do low carb
Because I just love bread
Is there a diet where I can eat nothing but bread?
Well, I did find a recipe to make bread
Out of coconut flour
Oh, I like coconut
And Tiara sent me a recipe to do red velvet cupcakes
Which I'm going to be trying
I have actually found a lot of people
Speak very highly of almond flour bread
And coconut flour bread
Interesting
I haven't missed it, honestly
I need to get motivated
I need to get Wii Fit U
Well, to be honest
It was just sort of like
You remember when I moved out here
How much I put on
I'm going to say it on air, I was a size 20
I don't mind saying it
And I dropped down to a 12
And then I put back on some
So it's like
I could just continue
To eat all of the stuff that makes me feel like shit
Because I've got digestion problems
Eating too much sugar
Actually makes me
Have a harder time concentrating
And since cutting all of it out
I'm actually feeling infinitely better than I ever did
And plus, I have more energy for
Stuff I want to do
I'm planning on playing DDR again
Gene in our chat room at Live.vongnetwork.com says
Wow, we are all so healthy
Not me, no, not me
AgDef says Wii Fit U up
I need to figure out something to get into
We'll see
Alright, moving on
Let's get into some rapid fire news
Back to games
This is another reason why I'm not losing any weight
Because I'm too busy playing video games
Although, no, I shouldn't play into that stereotype
Because there's a lot of people
That play an awful lot of video games
It's about finding the balance, absolutely
And for those of you guys who don't listen to Hoard House
I know Extrovert has a great story there
He plays a lot of video games
But he lost a lot of weight
It's really quite something
Well, what I've started doing now
I have set times now
For me to play my games
I play Animal Crossing in the morning
So that I can go to the island and get a tan
Because fuck
But I play while walking around the house
And feeding the cat
And putting up dishes
And doing chores in the house
I'll do parts of it
And then the hour while my character is on the island
Is when I go do yoga
I'm actually using my games
To help me set my exercise times
Okay
So I know that when an hour is up
I do about maybe 30 minutes of yoga
And then I do
Just wandering around the house and some housework
Because housework counts as exercise, fuck it
And by the time I'm done with that
I know it's time to come back from the island
And hit Ed with a bug net
Because fuck him
Yeah, I guess maybe there's a way I could
Get on the treadmill and have a 3DS
With an iPad or something
I used to play Pokemon on the recumbent bike
Nice, maybe I could figure something like that out
Oh well, for now, let's get back into video games
Because that's what the show's about
So, Loki, some rapid fire news for us
Yes, Infamous Second Son
Which was supposed to be coming out
First quarter
They finally announced that it will be launching
March 21st in North America
And they had a wonderful trailer
That was during their whole launch special
That they did
Definitely one of the only games I'm looking forward to
Another interesting one
Towerfall Ascension
You may remember Towerfall from being one of the
More popular Ouya games
Now it's coming to PC
And it's going to be coming to Playstation 4 as well
That's gonna suck for Ouya a little bit
Also brand new levels
And they've got 50 new levels coming
And 50 new versus levels
4 more playable characters
And 12 player cooperative quest mode
6 additional power ups and more
And last but not least
Rayman Legends is supposed to be coming to
Next gen consoles in February
That's so funny
It's like when the Wii U
Was supposed to be coming out in the Wii U in February
And it never did
Are you throwing shade that that might not actually happen?
I don't know if it's going to be in February
Yeah, it's going to be coming out in next gen consoles
I don't know how they're going to make that
It's going to look as good
I would think on a next gen console
They're going to have to
Yeah, maybe they don't do anything with the graphics
They might just up rez some things
And do some new textures and things to make it
Look a little sharper
Frame rate would be really good
All I can think of in my head is that
Extrofer will have yet another reason to do a stream
Of Rayman Legends over on his little Twitch channel
That he does
I think he played the thing start to finish on Twitch
Interesting
Moving on, some stuff that I hear
I hear click click click click
Click click click from Loki
As soon as he's done with his story
Cookie cookie cookie cookie cookie cookie
I'm going to be done with this game today
Your addiction is affecting your life in the following ways
I may have cheated a little bit
Look at your life, look at your choices
That's a teensy bit
Well maybe the next thing that Loki can get addicted to
Is Hatsune Miku Project D.Va
Nope
Ah hey, now this game is really cute
And if you missed it on the Playstation 3
For whatever reason, A buy it on sale
Or something, but B it will be coming out
On the Vita in early 2014
Very cool, so yeah
Hatsune Miku coming out in the North America and Europe
In early 2014
On the Vita, so that was announced this week
Very exciting
When we were getting into it a couple weeks ago
On our last episode about the whole fact that
Swap Note was
Disabled on the 3DS, somebody had brought up
Well, we karaoke you
Has some, you know, F words
And things in it, so why is it that
You know, you can't send
Pictures of
Dongs on Swap Note, but yet you can
Have fucking shit and all these words
In songs on We Karaoke You
Well, apparently this week it was
Announced that warnings
Will be added to the game's eShop
Page when you get an access
Token for We Karaoke You
And in the app itself
That will warn people
We Karaoke You by JoySound
Is intended to provide users with
Access to a large catalog of songs
From a broad range of music labels across a variety
Of musical genres designed to appeal
To all musical tastes
As such, Nintendo does not restrict which songs
Are included in the catalog of songs
Featured within the We Karaoke You by JoySound
Application
Blah blah blah blah blah, the songs aren't rated by
Peggy, blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
So
Interesting little
Retcon they had to do
For lack of a better word on some of their
Other games that have adult themes
I find this
Fascinating and I've got to check this out this week
I heard about this before
And I'm sure you all did too
There was a Chinese hack a couple years ago
Of Final Fantasy 7
That they shoved it into an NES
Cartridge, I don't know which Final Fantasy game they had
Hacked or if they programmed a new game or something
But somebody took Final Fantasy 7 and put it
In an NES cart, well that was a
Couple years ago that that happened but
This week it was
Actually a translation
Patch that happened by
Modder Luigia
I'm tempted to say Luigia
But it's Luigia 2009
Actually it was a whole team it wasn't just one guy
But this modder led this team to
Actually translate the game but at the same
Time they actually fixed
Some things, they redrew some of the graphics
Improved the music
Did an actual ending, bug fixes
Improvements, this is kind of crazy
Now it's like a legit game
That you can play through and check out if you
Want to check it out in English because I guess it was super broken
In its original form but now it's
Able to play so really
Curious to see what that looks like
Yeah
Their next project that they're working on
A
Unlicensed NES port of
Pokemon Yellow that came out from
The same company on the NES
They're going to redo that one in English and fix some of those
Issues next
That's pretty awesome
Dark Sakura
Sounds fairly cool
Well in other news there is some information about
Metal Gear Solid 5
Ground Zeroes there's going to be
A
Snake skin
A solid snake skin
So that you can run around as actual
Snake
And there's going to be a Playstation exclusive
Mission called Deja Vu
There's a trailer for it that's been out
And this is supposed to come out in the spring of 2014
For the various systems
Of Microsoft and Sony persuasions
In
Other news
There is
Going to be
It looks like a third
A new third person game that's coming out by Monolith
Called Middle Earth Shadow of Mordor
That is going to be based
In the Lord of the Rings universe and
You play as a ranger
A ranger named Talion
So
He's resurrected
As a vengeful spirit
And he gets to be a wraith
Like person
And then last but not least
In the
Thing that refuses to load on my
iPad
There is a new character that has been confirmed
For the next Smash Brothers and that's Marth
Not really a new
Character but you know
Marth fans will be happy that he's back
As long as we get Roy too
I think some of the
Partner characters are the ones in danger
Like you know it's no
It's no surprise
That Star Fox will be a character
That's in the game but will
Captain Falcon come back or not Captain Falcon
God dammit
Captain Falcon from F-Zero will absolutely
Be there
This bird Falco
He may not be back
Good
But I would think that those are the characters in danger
Of the partner characters
He is kind of a bitch isn't he
Yeah he's totally a bitch not even a good kind of bitch
Only good Falco did music in the 1980's
Hey Rob
Show me your moves
I will show you the FUGO
Question of the week
Every week over at
Facebook and Google Plus
You take those words and slam it together you get FUGO
We ask a question of our listeners
And we read some of the answers here for y'all
Here on the show
This week's question as asked of our communities
Since the Playstation 4 came out
We've noticed an increase of social media
Posts coming from the device
This can include tweets or Facebook
Posts when someone starts playing the game
Have y'all noticed this cause I sure did
Lots more Facebook posts coming from the Playstation 4
I ignore Facebook
Kind of, well I haven't blocked it
But I haven't really paid attention
I noticed a big increase in the amount of posts
I see posts now when people start
Playing a game
So I was very surprised at the increased
Amount of
You know I don't want to say spam
But automated posts
Coming from the Playstation
Anyway so that led into our question this week
For the Playstation 4 owners
Do you use social media posting features on your new device
Why or why not
For the non Playstation 4 owners
Do you like seeing the social media posts
Made from the Playstation 4
So let's get to some of the answers
There's so many tonight I'm not going to be able to read them all
We'll start with a couple from Google Plus
Colin M replied and said
I only like to see posts when a person starts a game
For the first time
That way I know what games they're playing
And maybe join in or talk to them about it
I do not need to see every time an achievement
Or trophy unlocks
I would agree especially if you're meaning
Not to say like the first and
Not the subsequent times
They start the game but the very first time
Just to kind of know that they have it
And you can ask them questions about it
But I don't need to see like
So and so is playing Resogun for the 7000th time today
I don't need to see that
Redertainment says
As a non Playstation 4 owner
Posts of people having fun with their PS4
Serve as a taunt to me
A taunt of things that they have that I don't
I'm experiencing this more and more as I pursue
When but not if but when
I buy my house and I begin to fill
Social media with pictures of my house
Those pictures will taunt people with what I have
And they don't
That's true
What's the whole point of doing it though?
Is to say oh so and so has this
I want that
Is that why people post pictures of their kids too?
My kids the cutest
Happy face
Well I personally think that for some people
Having children is an unspoken competition
Don't get me started on that
For some people I've met
Buying a house is an unspoken competition
So I'm just saying
In the past
A good friend of mine just bought a house
I'm not shading that I'm talking about in the past
Many years ago
And Alan
Alan knows exactly what I'm talking about and he's over there
Saying it too. Alright anyway
Let's see
Act Def says I only try to use any
Social media sharing when it's something like
Truly special or great
Like getting a really hard achievement or trophy
Or telling people that I'll stream a game
Since now that's possible with the new consoles
Let's go over to Facebook and get some
Of the answers over on Facebook
And see what people said there
How about Burr who said
So far as a PS4 owner I've only posted one
Gameplay clip to Facebook
Mostly just to see if it worked
Nobody responded though so I'll probably save it for funny bugs
Or things that are actually interesting
People probably don't want to hear about every little thing I do
So I shut off the automatic posting
The real fun so far has been the Twitch streaming
It's actually an incentive to keep playing
Since you're entertaining others as much as yourself
Scott W said
I've just started trying it out with screenshots
I like it
Code Man says I don't have a PS4 yet
But I don't mind posts if they are from consoles
What frustrates me is when people invite me to
Facebook games and Candy Crush
But I enjoy seeing what my friends are playing
And it's a chance to get an unbiased opinion
Rather than the media companies
Telling me what to play
I like that answer
Tiger Claw says
While having those features on the PS4 is good
When you want to post something
The only downside is your Twitter or Facebook posts
Would be spammed with so and so playing this game
Or unlock a trophy
If they give the player the ability to control
What is posted on Twitter and Facebook
Then some people won't be bombarded with PS4 spam
I kind of agree
I don't like the whole idea of all or nothing
Let me
I know on the PS3 you don't get to pick
Either you turn it on or you turn it off
And you can turn on certain types of posts
But I can't tell it
Only post these trophies or what have you
That would be a little better I would think
Or they could have the trophy pop up
And say hey do you want to post this to your wall
Gene W replied
I currently do not have a PS4
However I'm against these messages
Because I dislike them already on Facebook
And don't really have a desire to have a friends list
Flaming Toilet
God I love that name
Responds and says I may be a grumpy old man
But I think we've gone way overboard with social media
Integration everywhere not just gaming
The world doesn't need to know my business
I certainly don't want to annoy people with it
Anymore than I have to
And I don't really care what trophies other people get or whatever
And yes there's every bit of irony
In using social media to bitch
About social media's ever growing presence
In our lives
So that's a good way to end it
I only read like half the answers
So please do check out Facebook and Google Plus for more answers
Facebook.com slash
Orange Lounge Radio
Or Google.com slash plus Orange Lounge Radio
That's right we finally have a short URL
Google.com slash plus Orange Lounge Radio
And then there's the whole like you know
Google Plus shoved down throat
YouTube comments thing
All tweaked and stuff and how people love that
Yeah I'm not sure how I feel about all that
Like I'm trying to embrace it
I'm trying to do the whole hug it for 15 minutes
And see if I like it
I will tell you this the fact that I
Hug it for 15 minutes and see if you get a skin disease
I'm trying to
Trying to embrace it
With the whole fact that I'm getting into YouTube
More which is unrelated but I'm like alright
Well maybe this is an incentive to use Google Plus
To do more like gaming style posts
That tie into the YouTube's ideas
I'm like I'm trying to like it that way
But obviously it's a very
Unpopular change
But I don't know
Google used to be the company that you know
Could do no wrong and
Lately between
You know what was that
Before they had Google Plus they had
What was that social net Buzz oh god
That network yeah that was
Just bad and then you know
They've done some weird things lately
No hmm
I still love them but I question some of their
Choices alright let's
Let's get back into some long gaming news
Loki Buzz
I forgot about that
Anyways
Let's talk about PlayStation 4 again
Why not
Sold 1 million units the first day
So that's got to be pretty good
And kind of
Along the lines of their
Prediction which is or I should say
Projection
3 million units sold by the end of the year
The estimate by Jack Tritten
So
Yeah so that's
Pretty good and you know definitely
I think availability is gonna
You know factor in quite
Heavily especially with the
Systems coming I don't think it's gonna be an issue
Where I'm not really sure
With the Wii U whether it was you know
Availability as a problem
Or demand not being
Actually I think it's demand not being that high because
I remember there was a bunch of systems
Sitting at retail
In piles and no one gave
A shit but
PlayStation 4 you know and if
There's any sort of indicator whatsoever
The grey market
Is pretty profitable right now so
There is demand for the system
It's just gonna be availability is gonna kind of
Slim until
I don't know a few months from now
And actually it may even be a few months more
Because you know with the launch and other territories
You know they're gonna
Have to ramp up production more
Or you know there's just gonna be less systems
That go around
What types of shortages though that we saw
Like with the Wii and the 360
I don't think it's gonna be as bad
As you know the Wii
You know what I've been hearing is like a few weeks
Out or probably a month from
Launch we're gonna see some more shipments
Coming in although
You know this is completely one other side
Of you know the spectrum
If you're you know consumer trying to
Pre-order one of those things
Keep in mind that these places taking pre-orders
May have already sold out their second
Third fourth shipments so
You know whereas I've been saying four weeks
When we're you know expecting to see some more
They yeah
Are gonna expect them you know more systems in
But those may be for customers that already have it
You may in fact I think a lot of
Like the game subs and stuff are saying
February now if you haven't pre-ordered yet so
You know keep an eye on that and Amazon
Yeah but you know what GameStop
Loves to use scare tactics to get people to
Pre-order so fuck that I don't believe anything
They say as far as the pre-order
I think Amazon had bundles available
You know game system bundles
It's probably people like me that cancel their pre-orders honestly
They probably had a few of those
To go so somebody bought my PlayStation 4
Which is fine
But yeah that's probably what that was
To be honest
Alright um
How do you think the Xbox One will sell?
I mean I don't want to get too fanboy wars-ish
But what do you think?
I think it'll sell alright
I'm worried that they're gonna have a bigger problem
Because as of right now
They're really
Shrinking down who's getting the system
And you're not gonna see it
You're not gonna see it at all
Independent retailers you're gonna see it at
The big stores and that's it
So if they're having an issue with production
On that stuff then
Yeah they could be a problem but
I think they've got a pretty decent lineup
At launch and I think they'll do about as well as the
PlayStation or the Xbox One
Or the PlayStation 4 and the
Xbox One will do about the same
Really it comes down to exclusives and
Let's be honest going
Forward you know in the least immediate future
A lot of the games that are coming out next gen
Are on both systems so it's
There's not a whole lot differentiating
One from the other
As far as games go I mean
So I don't know
Titanfall I guess I mean there's that
But that's on 360 even
And PC so I don't know
Alright well um going back to
A story we talked about on our last episode before
We had a break we talked about Pocketstation
Remember the Pocketstation was that
Cool little portable thing that they
Had on the PlayStation
With the kitty mascot
And that there were rumors
That it was making a comeback because of some
Trademarks that had been registered well guess what
Pocketstation came out as a
Free app for the PlayStation Vita
In Japan and
Yeah the app is free for
Japanese PlayStation Plus members
They say it includes Crash Bandicoot 3
Mega Man, Ape Escape and other
Original PlayStation titles I don't know if that's some type of
Perk for the PlayStation Plus
Some free PS1 titles that actually maybe used
The Pocketstation
But that's pretty cool
On December 3rd non PlayStation Plus
Japanese owners will be able to get it
There's also
A PlayStation title that's going to be added
To that Dokodemo Isho
Comes out no word about
When this is being released in the US but
You gotta think that hey if it happened over there
It will probably happen here too at some point
That's pretty cool
That'll be a fun little perk for PlayStation Plus
Users over here especially if those free games
Are still involved
The other thing I was going to mention and we kind of forgot to mention
Is the PS Vita
TV came out over in Japan
Oh yeah!
The other thing that I heard
That kind of sucked about it is it's region locked
Oh come on!
The Vita doesn't normally do that
It's a little strange that it's like that
They're trying to stop us from
I'm not sure
I don't know if it's region locked
I don't know, I had to read up
I didn't really look into it too much
I gotta be honest when that thing comes over here
I kind of want one
Especially with all these free games I'm getting
From the PlayStation Plus
I could play these PSP
And Vita and PlayStation games
And stuff on there
I don't know, I think that'd be pretty awesome
You know Jean has a good question in our chatroom
At live.vognetwork.com saying
I wonder if the Vita sales went up with the PlayStation 4 release
You know we're not hearing a lot about that
But I'm hearing about the second screen
People are really loving that, those that do have a Vita
I do have to tell you that Dan was telling me that
Vita actually went on sale at Radio Shack
For 120
That did happen the week we were gone, yeah
I remember reading about that
Loki, have you heard anything about the sales for Vita?
I mean I can't imagine there's a lot of people
That can afford to buy both at once
I haven't really been seeing, we haven't been seeing
A lot of Vita sales
I mean it'd be interesting to see
If it does go up at retail
I'm thinking if anything people just clearing out
Inventory because they probably are sitting on a bunch of them
I'm sure with Black Friday you're gonna see
Some special deals on that stuff
There was supposed to be one that was with Tearaway
But that got retailer exclusive
Well it will
Also still be interesting to see what happens with
The PlayStation Vita in Japan
Versus here because I realize that Christmas
Has been quite the same in Japan as it is here
But it's still, you know, a deal
And there's gonna be the PlayStation Vita
That new, the new colors
And the new redesign
Of it already happened
So that's kind of what Sony's pushing in Japan right now
So I'm really curious to see how that kind of affects things
Cause you could look at potentially
There being more Vitas
Per person in Japan
Than there are here
It'll be very interesting to see how that affects the development of the games
So
Go to our channel at live.vognetwork.com
Brad, our buddy from Pod Culture
Who has renamed himself
PS4 Culture tonight
Says his co-host Glenn bought a Vita
Just for the PlayStation 4 tie-in stuff
Wow
That's a heck of a purchase
But hey, if you can do it, why not?
Alright
More news, Dark Sakura
Taking a different turn here
Well, game politics has alerted us to something
Remember how we kept talking about
The 38 Studios and their
Sort of
Down turn with the
Local economy in Rhode Island
Yes, that was the one that was owned by
What was the name, Curt Schilling, the baseball player, right?
You are correct
The kingdom of Amalur
Exactly
Which was free on PlayStation Plus
Now there's State Senator Dawson
Hodgson
Who is a Republican, so whatever
Is putting out legislation to
Basically keep pushing to
Have an independent commission investigate
What happened with 38 Studios
Which, I mean
100 million on the state's
Debt
Is a pretty big deal, especially for such a tiny
State, I mean
I don't know too much more about Rhode Island
I've known people from there
The state loaned them money
Which is probably the reason for this
Which comes right out of
You know, tax funds
To pay for
State improvement
Help benefits, that type of thing
So I can see them wanting to
To
Investigate this
And one thing that he said
I know that I'm not alone
In the belief that the response of our government
Has been wholly insufficient to the task of delivering
Answers, accountability, and leadership
In the wake of this massive destruction
Of public resources
Swift enactment of the bill and diligent
Prosecution of its mandate would vindicate these needs
And I get where they're coming from
At the same time
I wonder
If it's just something that
Is time to let go
Let go, move forward, find other ways of raising
The funds, because you can't
Get water from a stone
Unless you happen to be squeezing cheese
Yeah, I mean I understand the reason why
They might want to do the investigation
But at the same time, it's like one of those
Well, it's not going to get the money back
You know, what
Ultimate good is it really going to do
I mean, I guess they can
Make sure this never happens again
But I kind of think a lesson
Has certainly already been learned somewhere
But maybe it's about holding certain people accountable
I don't know
I do think accountability is something
To look into
But at the same time, I'm wondering if perhaps
The state might have been a little short-sighted
With the company in the middle of a recession
Were they starry-eyed
At the fact it was a sports star?
Probably
Did you hear that they found a full
Finished game on their servers
That they're going to now auction off in December
Really? No
There was another game that was literally done
It was for Mac, actually
It was a PC game
Weird, some sort of tactics game
Well, they should do it
I thought that was kind of funny
Well, Rhode Island paid for it
Why didn't you sell it?
You could have made some money back
Yeah, a little bit
The sad thing is it probably won't sell for very much money
Because nobody knows about it
It's got not a lot behind it
Probably go at bargain-basement prices
And somebody will flip it and do pretty well with it
We'll see
Alright, let's move on
Loki
So let's talk about
Zune
And the fact that
I think we already knew it was kind of shutting down
But it's
It's going away
As soon as the Xbox One launch
And yeah
They're not going to support rental purchasing
Or browsing of content
And it's going to be
I guess now everything is being taken care of
Through Xbox Music
I guess if you're a previous Zune user
And you log into the
Xbox Music service
It will show your library
As a virtual collector
And I guess any previous purchase
Video content
Will transfer over
So that's good
It's too bad
They really tried to
They tried to make Zune happen
They really tried
They sort of tried to compete with the iPods
And it just didn't quite happen
We had a nice listing in the Zune Cast Store
For a while
Thanks to the new listeners we got through Zune Cast
Sorry to hear about what happened to your Zune
But you know, it is what it is
So
Alright, well in
Somewhat brighter news I guess on the Microsoft
Front, one of the games that people are
Very excited about on Xbox One
Killer Instinct
And almost more so because of Killer Instinct Classic
It's not just the fact that there's the new Killer Instinct
Heck yeah
But that you can play the classic Killer Instinct as well
The Ultra Edition
Is coming out of the classic Killer Instinct
It will have two versions
Of the arcade version
Of Killer Instinct, obviously it's not the
Super Nintendo version, I mean right
So Killer Instinct will get
The arcade versions
Killer Instinct Classic will have the original
Arcade version, version 1.4
And the upgraded
ROM revision 1.5D
Which has glitch fixes
Infinite combos that were discovered
After the game's initial releases
Were fixed
Also some emulating scamline
Options
A training mode is there now though
And sprite galleries will be available
So that's pretty cool
The Killer Instinct Classic
It is only available in Killer Instinct
Ultra Edition
And the boxed pin Ultimate Edition
You will not be able to buy it separately
So if you want this, you have to buy
The free to play Killer Instinct game
That's the only way to do it
But there's definitely a lot of
I know people that are going to be buying it
Just so they can have the classic version
Because you know what, Killer Instinct
Especially the classic version was awesome
And it will have more characters than the new one
That's the sad part
They announced
Full Gore
For what it's worth, Full Gore
The classic one is way better than the new one
Alright
You know what's way better each and every week
Is our mailbag
Guys at our email address
Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
Dark Soccer
Is going to dive into the mailbag head first
And find some emails that she
Deems worthy of reading on the show
And I imagine after a week off we have quite the backlog
No?
A few
There is a really
Long one that I'm just
Going to
Only read the first paragraph
Because this is really
Fucking long
And I'm not going to read the uber novel
Sorry
It's from
RawStillUT
Well in a few hours I'll be waiting
In a midnight line for the PS4 at my local GameStop
So I thought I would shoot you guys an email before that
Anyway when talking about the news
That define the generation
I am surprised that Brown vs Entertainment Merchants Association
Wasn't brought up
With all the talk of blaming video games for society's ills
It's hard to argue with a 7 to 2 decision
When the time comes
For another state to try and strip the gaming industry
Of its right to free expression
After all, even if a law could be narrowly
Tailored to
Alito and Roberts
I am not sure
Which I'm not sure
Even can happen in the current political climate
It still leaves 5 justices
Who were pretty much close to the idea
Outright
Whoever eventually replaces the older members of the court
Will almost certainly be more aware of gaming as a medium
And California's already beaten economy
Was done no favors
By the massive reimbursement they had to give the EMA
No doubt we'll continue to see
Scumbag politicians try to pass
Feel-good legislations restricting game content
We're probably not going to see
Yet another case go to the Supreme Court
Anytime soon
As they tend not to listen to the same issues
That often
This case has given us a huge buffer
And while we can't take anything for granted
It's hard to see where we'll see
Much more than summary dismissals
Of the sort of poorly written
Headline chasing tripe legislation
I love that term, tripe legislation
That had defined the previous
Decade
I'll go so far as to say this will define the next generation
As well
That is a good pick of something
That kind of fell off of our radars
I'm not going to deny that that is a very good selection
I think one reason
That maybe we don't think
Of it right away compared to some of the other things
We talked about last week is because we did kind of dodge a bullet
And I think in a lot of our minds
Yeah, this is the way it should be
Duh!
Oh, the whole fact that the Supreme Court
Decided to say that this is a bad idea
Duh! We all knew it was a bad idea
So no harm no foul, right?
I'm not belittling
The response because I think
Yeah, absolutely, this is a decision
By the Supreme Court that impacts
Gaming, period
But I think that's why
A lot of us kind of neglect to remember it
Because it's kind of like, well, they ended up
On our side like they should have been
So, la di da, didn't really change anything
At the end of the day, hooray
Anyway
And I always have to give it
To Rossdale, UT for
Definitely bringing up points
That are
Definitely apt
When it comes to comparing
What you see in
The current generation of gaming
Especially with bringing up how
We are on that line from changing
Sort of how we're thinking
Of our games
To how we used to think of our games
It really is a line that's been crossed
Too many of the people now
That are in charge of the industry
Were people like us
Who grew up with it and now see it
As a true medium of expression
As opposed to
You know, just bang bang
Yeah, I seem to remember that whole
Supreme Court decision thing
I think the justice knew what Mortal Kombat was
Because he or she
I don't remember which justice it was
Had interns or people
In the office that knew the game and played it a lot
So, I remember
I just remember that that was
I don't have the story in front of me so I don't remember the details
I remember that was something out of it that I found fascinating
It's like, hey, the Supreme Court knows Mortal Kombat
It's not just a niche thing
Dan's old boss named his daughter
Melina
Because his wife wouldn't let him name her Katana
This is corporate boss
I like the name Melina a lot
Not even just because of Mortal Kombat
I actually met the guy, he's pretty cool
But still, you know
Robin Williams named his daughter Zelda
True
So
Moving on, and sorry Russell
You'd see the rest of the email was just way too long
But I did glance over it
This comes from
Nark
Which was a great 90's arcade
90's arcade game by the way
But this is with a Q and not with a C
Oh, you're like Joystick
The AOL block
Well, I'm weighing in a little late on the matter
But I believe there is an overarching theme
That connects the defining game
With the defining news for the past generation
That is online everything
Someone mentioned crowdfunding
And an ME3 multiplayer
It hasn't been that long
Since well launched
Now there are so many MMOs
That once had spins
Although Ragnarok Online was the best of them
And now you have MMOs being funded
Produced by the community
Star Citizen doesn't even exist
And the players are already pumped for over
Already pumped over 25 million dollars
Into it
And that's not the news story of the generation
And if that's not, I can't read today
If that's not the news story of the generation
I don't know what would be more poignant
So online everything
But if I had to narrow it down
World of Warcraft is the defining game of our generation
Like the game or not
And even the Star Citizen crowdfunding
Story is this generation's defining news event
Great topic, game on
Nark
I'm thinking of Pinky
From Pinky and the Brain
Instead of Nark
Here's the one reason
I respectfully disagree with your choice
Of World of Warcraft is because the game
Came out in 2004
Was it 2003? 2004? I think it was 2004
During the last generation
Because this generation didn't really start till
2005-06 depending on
You know, if PS3 or 360 kicked it off
So that's my one
Slight
Dispute with that, but otherwise
Honestly, I'm not invalidating any of your points
Because the rest of it's all very good
And you know, with the Kickstarter
And all that, absolutely
And Gene says, he's naming his first child
Baraka
Which is better, Baraka or Blanca?
Food for thought
If you want your kid going around being named white
No with a K
Wasn't that uh
Yeah, but still
Hello peoples
I'd like to extend my gratitude for Loki
For the VoG Grand Theft Auto online community event
That was held tonight, Friday night
I'm sure it was a good time for those of you
Who could stay connected to the game
Unfortunately, I could not
The reason for this lies not with Rockstar Games
Anyone I was attempting to play with
The reason I couldn't stay connected is due to my
So-called broadband
Uh
DS fucking L
Okay, oh never mind
My failed attempts to play Grand Theft Auto online
With the VoG community has only given me more
Incentive to achieve my long-held goal
I will accomplish project buy a house
And when I do, I will get
Cable internet, string cat5
Throughout my house, and finally achieve the true
Broadband gaming dream
I have only dreamed of
I will do this, I will stay
Blackwatertainment trainer
You know what
Um, you also want to look into your router
If you're going to do the ultimate
Uh
The ultimate uh
Wi-Fi or
Internet experience
Don't use whatever your
Provider gives you
Goodbye your own
It's also partially, I think, Rockstar as well
I had trouble connecting it
Some of the times I was getting disconnected from stuff
I blame everything on
Rockstars because they make me too jittery
Anyway, um
This one, uh, here is
An update for OLR
It's been six months since my wife Tracy
Passed away from a stroke at 47
Uh, when I called in
I was being- Oh, I remember this one
Yes, when I called in I was being
Evicted from the house I was renting and had to
Move in with a friend, the sad part is
That re-
Is that really happened and I thought I was
Going to have to get a second job just to survive
I was getting depressed but was surviving
I still listen to the podcast regularly for
A smile, I got more
From the retirement system she was in than I figured
Being a responsible adult
Bites, I could have flown to Vegas and partied
I paid off my SUV five years early
And now I have no car payment, I paid off the bills
Left over from the last place, I bought
Myself a new 55
Inch 3D TV, I will be getting
An Xbox One and I
Find one and a new
No, when I find one and a new laptop
For gaming, thank you for all your prayers
It looks like I will be okay, I would call in
But I am East Coast and work Monday
I'm happy
To hear that follow up, those of you that were here
Six months ago I'm sure remember that was
I think in the 12 years that we've been doing OLR
It was the hardest phone call we've ever taken on the show
Yeah, I'm just gonna guess on a
Nickname that's a name in lights
I believe that's right
He's a really good guy
We chat on Facebook all the damn time
Yeah, he used to do wow with us too
So that whole thing though was really a testament to the power of community
Yeah, I get warm fuzzies hearing that it's gonna be okay for him
And I'm glad to hear it's gonna be okay
And I'm sure the listeners appreciate it
Even if it's six months later it's really nice to know
Thank you
Stay in touch
One more email
Howdy guys and gal, smile
Yes, thank you for acknowledging my womanhood
Nice tits
I was acknowledging your womanhood
Yes, they are quite nice
I have a gorgeous rack
I get complimented on it daily
Firstly, although we missed you last week
I hope you all had a fantastic week off
I did sleeping so that was great
I went to Disneyland and BlizzCon
It was amazing
Okay, now that we have the touchy feely bullshit out of the way
Oh hey
A couple weeks ago I was watching Under Sedation Live
Which you can view and participate live every Saturday night
At 10pm EST on vognetwork.com
Are you on Travis Donovan's payroll?
Are you on his payroll?
Who is this?
Are you on Travis' payroll?
Did he offer you vog points?
Travis and Jessica were talking about cult movies
Of the 90's, Boondock Saints, Cutthroat Island and Hackers
This conversation got me to thinking of cult video games
And what makes a cult game
Is a cult game a game that people enjoy
Despite the low review scores like Too Human?
Is a cult game a game that did not have a stellar launch
But managed to gain a huge following such as Demon's Souls?
Is a cult game a game that people like to play
Despite the low sales numbers such as Bulletstorm and Shadows of the Damned?
I'm interested in hearing your thoughts on this
And I'm eager to find out what you consider a cult game
I'm also interested in finding out what your favorite cult game is
Not so sincerely, Degenerate Johnny
AKA Rob's Parody Songwriter
Thanks
Thank you for not bringing that to this show
That's a really good question
And for the record, even though Travis gives me shit all the time on Under Sedation Live
You really all should check out that show
They have a lot of fun over there
It's a bummer though y'all missed episode 6-66
Because I live for DJ Satan who was on that show
Anyway, sorry
But I just wanted to go ahead and let that plug air a little bit
As far as the question on hand
What makes a cult video game?
Degenerate Johnny, I think it's kind of all those things that you named
I don't think, there's no definition
You don't go to the dictionary and see what makes a cult game
I think it's a little bit of all those things
And I think the definition is a little different for everybody
Well that and also when you have
I think you should also look at the factor of
Well this is more like hipster game I would think
When you have people outside of an age group the game is intended for
Playing the game
Like, I hate to say it
Pokemon
Pokemon's totally a cult game
But does that label really fit when Pokemon is like a hugely selling game
See that's why I relabeled it a hipster game
Definitely a cult of Pokemon
I was going to say one of the biggest cult games there is is World of Warcraft
Yeah, but now it's doing well
It's such a huge game
I feel weird calling that a cult game too
This is how I look at it too
Maybe when you have something's popularity
Emerge after it was supposed to have its heyday
For example, look at Rocky
Rocky Horror Picture Show
Yeah, the play was pretty good
And had pretty decent following when the movie came out
Didn't it tank?
Yes, the movie originally tanked
It was based on a play
But the movie originally tanked
Which I've seen the play finally
They noticed that in New York or somewhere
A lot of the same people were going to see it over and over again
And they started doing the midnight showing
And the minute that somebody yelled
Buy an umbrella you cheap bitch
At the screen, things changed forever
Well yeah, but I mean that's the thing that you have
Popularity is of a different sort
Than what was intended when the movie came out
Correct?
So I think that if you look at
For example
Portal, okay
I think Portal was just sort of a throw in kind of game
It was meant to be a fun little puzzler
But it's the whole
Quirkiness of it that really got it a huge following
And maybe got people
Got people moving outside of whatever was written in the game
Into the retarded vant-
I hate using that word, why am I saying it?
Into the crazy-
Leo-tarded
That's what they say on Drag Race, totally Leo-tarded
But I hate using that word because I do know people who
Anyway
Sorry
Oh yeah, and if you want to go for
Like Jean just said, Shock Treatment, Ultra Cult
Oh my god, Shock Treatment
Shock Treatment's fucking hilarious
You have to watch Shock Treatment like seven times before it even makes sense
But the music is really good
I need a bit of ooh
Shock Treatment
You remember when we ate the hacker cookies
When Evan lived with Jessica
And these were cookies that were made with so much chocolate and no doughs
That I was shaking after two of them
I remember when I got really sick
In 2008
I was actually supposed to be in a shadow cast
Of Shock Treatment playing Ricky from the Rest Home
I had to drop out because
That was the year I got really sick and I had to go to the hospital
So somebody replaced me
But anyway
Well, SSJ100Matt is saying that Darkstalkers is a cult franchise
But- Kinda
Yeah, kinda, it wasn't as
Overly successful as most of Capcom's other things
But see, it was always in the circles
I lived in arcades with fighting games
So they always had people on it
I think a cult game is that game
Is that game that everybody
Asks for a sequel for
That you're never gonna get
Like Shenmue is a great example of a cult game
Like Half Life
Half Life by that definition
Is definitely a cult game
Or I was gonna joke Mega Man is now a cult game
As of recent
You know what a good example though of the
I think
Blaster Master is a great example of a cult game
Yes, it got some sequels
But they were worse than Shock Treatment
Let's be real
It's hard to be worse unless you're Yaris
What if Yaris got a sequel?
The Wii remake wasn't awful
But that's not saying much
I'll give you another example of a great cult game
Because I don't think people know this one
Very well, Cultcept
Talked about this in the game before
It's that whole like Magic the Gathering meets Monopoly
I love that game
But there's like one on the 360
And on the Playstation 2 and that's really it
I think it's bigger in Japan
There's a lot of points in the chat
Rama brings up Rival Schools
Being more than Darkstalkers
Which I fully agree with
And I fucking love Rival Schools
And the people who love Rival Schools
Really fucking love Rival Schools
And Jean says PSO2 in the US
Which I was totally into PSO2 for a little while
And then there's Final Fantasy
And Queen Samia says
Any Bimani game
In America, yes
I would say
VR got super super popular
And now it's fallen into
Because of the cult status the imports had over here
Now it's more in the mainstream
But as far as I was aware
In Japan, popin' music is everywhere
And everyone fucking plays popin' music
I love this
Technus says those Burger King games
Yeah, those
Sneak King was a cult game of sorts
Or fuck, everyone I knew that played Ragnarok online
Because that game was like
Oh, we have 3D games
No, fuck you, we're playing our 2D little MMO
SSG100Matt says
So Chrono Trigger would be considered cult
No, because you got Chrono Cross
I'm just trollin'
Chrono Trigger was pretty popular
It is a cult game of sorts
Rageinator says Earthbound
Kinda, yeah
Kid Icarus for a long time
I would definitely call it a cult game
In fact, in some ways it still is
I would not consider that one a cult
Um
Pig bumpin'
We had that
Because the Parappa series
For what it was
It took off, I think, bigger
In a way than it was supposed to
And then Umjramalami
And Parappa 2, those are sequels
So I'm not gonna really count them as much
Now I will agree with Skullgirls
Because that game is
Pretty fun
It wasn't getting a whole lot of attention
But you have your dedicated
Fan base to it
And because of that, we've had the Kickstarter go in
A lot more of that too
So yeah, Skullgirls is a pretty recent one
Or maybe even La Mulana
You know
La Mulana is definitely a cult game
If your name is Dark Tetsuya
Cave Story
Ooh, that's a good one too
This is a great topic, but we are dragging it out
Yeah, it's time to move it on
But great question, love it
Yeah, and we definitely
Sort of discussed a little bit of what defines a cult game
And Travis will now be able to say
Yet again, they jacked another segment for my show
And you know what I say?
Nothing, because it's a gesture
And just remember, that saying
Love you, just a really strong love you
Love it
It's a very deep kind of love
It's a very thrusty, deep kind of love
Alright
Speaking of thrusty, deep kind of love
Thank you to all you guys that emailed us tonight
And those of you that will email next week
In advance, mailbag at orangelaungeradio.com
Is the place to send those emails
Well, right along with that gesture
We'll cue a new segment
Or not a new segment, a new segment?
We need a new segment
It's a brand new segment here on the show
We've been doing it since episode one
We're growing segments like bugs
You wanna get a new segment on the show?
We should get a new segment for OLR
What should the new OLR segment be?
Tweet us ideas
We'll crowdsource this
The OLR shit list
New OLR segment
Tweet us your ideas
And I'm not bringing you back website of the week
But, if we get a new segment
Then an old segment's gotta go
No
We'll just live here forever
I'm just gonna live under your table here
And eventually Sanrio will like me
Alright, let's get to the FUs of the week
Fuck you to me
Not having a job yet
And I'm still waiting back to hear
From Cool Job
As I've been referring to it
In writing Cool Job with a trademark
Um
It's really just very difficult
To find work
And, you know, Dan and I
Are actually gonna be going out looking at houses next week
Cause
We feel we're wasting money on rent
And trying to
You know, it's really hard
To improve your situation when you are not
Given the means to improve your situation
And all those people who are
Bootstrap theorists
Fuck you very much
Fuck you
Loki?
Fuck you to Cookie Clicker
I agree, fuck you to Cookie Clicker
Do you have a permanent dent in your finger now?
Uh, no, but I'm almost done
Seriously, I'm almost done
Cosdula has somehow arisen
I don't know how this has happened
But
It's part of the game, I guess
But he's in the devil
Grandmas turn evil
Have to do an ancient practice
To stop them from being evil
Um
And I'm cheating, a lot
Of course you're cheating, this is Loki we're talking about
It's to get done with the game, it's all about the end game
You know?
Alright, uh, my FU of the week
Um, I guess I don't have a lot I'm mad at
My FU of the week goes to these holiday candies
But
And, it's, Alan says they're grandma candy
And they totally are
It's like the mix, the holiday mix
Of those hard candies
That grandma always had in a glass jar
At her house
Kinda, but they're not like
Butterscotch or anything
Everybody knows, you've seen these, they all clunk
Together too, like the hard candies
These things are so addicting, I eat them and I've almost
Eaten like an entire bag
And I wonder why I can't lose weight
So FU to
Candy for being delicious
Bob, you suck
What? You can do anything
You put your mind to
Okay, I wanna be a princess
I'm thinking really hard
It's not working, Dark Sakura
I'm taking this home
Are you compensating it?
It looks nasty
It's really good though
It's just that candy pink in it
You know? Uh, Codeman in chat says
So I come to your house, you will offer me candy
Absolutely, if you're gonna make the trip out here
From Oklahoma or wherever you are
I will absolutely get you candy
He only uses it to get people in his car
Not his house, in the van
You don't have a van yet
That's what you think
Can I have a bite?
That's the perfect alibi right there too
I don't have a van, what are you talking about?
Alright, that does it for the FUs of the Week
Let's get to some more stories and then
We are not that far away from the Skype line
I'm excited to talk to some folks tonight
I hope we get calls tonight
1877 Game OLR
Or I use the name on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio
But first, a couple stories for you
Sadly we missed a wonderful transition that we would have had
Had we gone into the story straight from the mailbag
But, you know, whatever
So hey, in case you need some more information
About which system you should buy
For the next generation
Pornhub would let you know
That hey, they're fully supporting
The Playstation 4
And you'll be able to view Pornhub
And all of its video content
Through the Playstation 4's web browser
Nice
So that's why I was joking
Does Pornhub offer the freaky porn though?
I only like the really crazy stuff
I will never forget that New Years
It was like 2007 or something
With the pterodactyl porn on the Wii
That was the most hilarious thing I've ever seen in my life
That is a good question
One that we should just look up the answer to
Why not?
You have to do some research here
It's, you know, it's strange
But let's see
Dinosaur
Hey, that's weird that that came up as a recommended
Yes, it has dinosaur porn on there
So you are all set
Dinosaurs? Like the old ABC sitcom?
Dinosaurs as in like CG dinosaurs
And they even
And
And someone that's dressed in green
I don't know
But yes, they do have dinosaur
Pornography
You'll be happy to know
Alright, anyway
Very happy to hear that
Congratulations Playstation 4 for
Definitively winning the console wars with that
Although, we all know
If there's any way to do it
Pornhub will also show up on Xbox One
Of course, well it is Internet Explorer
It'll have to happen
But here's the thing
I always bring triple X rated
Video
To the actual web stores
Like I can go rent a copy of
You know, the Dark Knight
Returns or
The Dark Knight bones some chick
In the ass too
You know, that's
That's how you win the console wars right there
Alright, speaking of vulgarities
Did you know that South Park
Is still on the air? It's in its 17th
Season
South Park is kind of hit and miss these days
It's still worth watching once in a while
Especially this past week
And I actually watched this episode
A friend of mine alerted me to the fact that
The latest South Park episode was about the
Playstation 4 and Xbox One
Console wars
They kind of put a Game of Thrones parody into it too
It also looks very much like
It does
Look like their game which made it funny
Because there was a part where they totally
Shade the fact that their game got delayed
Like something about
Someone says, who wants to sit around and wait for a stupid
Game, a game that's not even that good
Oh, then they slam the pre-order
Thing, that's what it was, they say like
You know, pre-orders are just
The way of them dicking you over every time
Like they go
The five dollars you spend on a pre-order
Is just going to some guy who hasn't even
Finished the game yet and da da da, like that was the
Part, I'm totally not doing it justice
Sorry, I don't have it queued up right now
But it was worth watching
I lulled a couple times
I think it's going to be a two-parter
Because it didn't really, the ending wasn't really
An ending, so
It makes sense because they have both consoles coming out
Yeah, I'm curious to see if maybe they're going to end it after the
Consoles actually come out, I don't know
Yes, they actually
Split up and choose a side and it's
Going to be Playstation 4 fans
Versus Xbox One fans
And an epic throw down at the mall
And they're actually recruiting other clicks for their side
Like I think the Sony click had
Kyle in it
And they recruited the Goth kids
I thought they were trying to recruit them
But it didn't work, I don't know
I don't know, this is way
Too much seriousness for an episode of South Park
But it's always fun to see
This whole stuff get kind of made fun of
In the media, who better to make fun of it
Than South Park
By the way, if you do want to watch the whole episode
And actually get the quote that I butchered
South Park Studios
Has the full episode
And Dark Tetsuya in our chat room
Says they did confirm on Facebook
Part 2 is this coming week
So there will be a
Part 2, so check that out
Jean asks, was Wii U ignored?
Of course, of course it was ignored
Just like real life
This is next gen wars
Well
Maybe that'll be the twist in the second part
Is that they all come together and buy Wii Us
I doubt it
I highly doubt it
I don't think so
Alright
That's it for stories
So I think we can open up the Skype line now
1877 Game OLR
Or our username on Skype, Orange Launch Radio
If you'd like to give us a call on Skype
The Skype line is open
And in the meantime
We can go to some Twitter topics
I know we had a few good ones tonight
Also, last minute stories
Loki, I don't know if you had any last minute stories
No
I was gonna mention that there's this teaser site
Now it's the Survivor
That people are thinking might be for Fallout
Originally it was thought
Oh, maybe it's a fan site because it wasn't registered
To the usual Bethesda stuff
However, Bethesda
Just recently trademarked
Fallout 4
And also the timing kinda
Coincides with the Spike
VGX stuff
Oh lordy
Expect an announcement maybe in December
Most likely, let's go to the phones
They're lighting up now, we shouldn't have a problem with calls tonight
Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio, who's this?
This is Codeman
Hey Codeman, how you doing? What's up?
Not much, I got some candy here waiting for you
I learned that you like
Freaky porn on this episode
That was kinda weird
Freaky porn makes it sound like
I'm like this lecherous creepy
dude that lives in a basement
There's a tonki punch video where they actually dress up
Like a donkey, that's funny
I like funny porn, Codeman
My favorite are the parodies
Have you seen the Batman ones?
The Batman ones are great because
They do it sort of the old
Adam West style Batman
But it's with the actual
characters from now on
I think the last one I saw was a parody of Lord of the Rings
It literally had a bunch of midgets
I remember when you invited me over
To see Ali McFeel
Ron Jeremy was actually in that
And for the record
The last one I watched was the Mork and Mindy one
I wanted to see the one that was called
This Ain't Glee
Because now they don't even bother
They just say, this ain't whatever
Oh wait, I did see another one
More recent, I saw Nalen Palin
Which is hilarious
I know you must have seen
Not the Cosby's because we were so fascinated
We were so fascinated by the guy
The guy that played Bill Cosby
In there
He never got into any of the scenes
But his impression was fantastic
And that was the part
It was like, we don't give a shit about the porn
His impression was just dead on
It was hilarious
Codeman, I don't know if you actually called to talk about porn
But clearly we could do that all night
But what's on your mind, buddy?
It's all porn and orange lounge radio tonight
Orange lounge radio?
No, I haven't called in a while
I haven't called in a while actually
I've been pretty busy with life
I guess you could say
But no, I just figured I was up tonight
And figured I'd call in and just talk
PS4, because I
I cancelled my pre-order like you did, Rob
I'm glad I'm not alone
Would you give out your Twitter on the show
So that the people that are about to
Send me angry tweets after tonight's episode
Can send them to you too?
Yeah, it's Codeman Games
Look it up
But I will tell you
Xtifer
I've been keeping up with his
He posted, I think, a RezaGun
On Facebook
And I'm just like
I'm seeing all these videos and I'm like
God
I should have kept it
That's the exact same thing I've been doing
And you know what that means
All that social media shit that Sony
Infused into its console is working
This is exactly what they want people to do
Actually, for me, it's the opposite
Another video of the stupid robot
I've already seen that
I know what it looks like
Well, it's just
You see all this stuff and you
Cancel it because you know, okay
I kind of go with the same thing
A console is good at what
Games are on them
But then you see all these people playing it
And you just get this feeling of
God, I need this because it's new
It's different
In a sense, and so you get to this point where you're like
Oh my God, I just need this console
But you know you have other
Things to do and you can't spend that much money
On something, but you're just like, oh my God
I need it, but at the time, I had the money
And I was like, okay, well I have the
Pre-order, I'm going to get it and all this stuff
And I got to the point where I was just like
You know what, there's just no games that are selling
The system for me right now
About the only thing that was
Selling was the RezaGun
I wanted to check out
What was the
What was the little
With the little guys
And the
Playroom? No, not the Playroom
It starts with a K
Knack
I wanted to play Knack because I played
A demo of it at Target and I thought it was kind of fun
I've heard it's kind of repetitive, but at the same time
I don't really care
I felt fun when I played it
And the controller just felt so
Amazing when I played it
It's like, oh my God, I should have got one of these
But I do have to make a confession
I did
Sell my Xbox 360
And got like
Well, and some games and got like
300 something dollars for it, so
That will be going towards a PS4
So I probably will be getting one
How about the old and the new and the new?
I got some extra systems at my
Office that I'm not using, I might as well
Just take those in
You know, I'm not a big advocate
Of the evil G, but today they had
A 90% trade-in
Value on console, so I was just like
Oh wow, why not?
Oh dang, I wish I had known that
I might have done that
Alan and I actually have two
Because, you know, when we got together and moved in
Together, we both had 360s and PlayStation 3s
So we have two PlayStation 3s and two
Xbox 360s and there's really no reason for us
To do that, so we really should sell my
Systems because they're the older ones
And keep Alan's
Oh well, maybe they'll do something like that again
Although yes, I'm with you, I really don't like
The evil G, but if they're willing to give me a lot of money
I can cross picket lines
We've got extra
Systems lying around
Why not?
And also, lastly, before I go
I wanted to tell you guys about a game I've been
Playing that I think kind of fell under
The radar a little bit because I don't think
A lot of people play this game anymore, but maybe
They do, I don't know, but the Ratchet and Clank
The new Ratchet and Clank game that just came out
It's like super fun
It's the first full length type
I guess Ratchet and Clank that they released
Because they released the All For One
Which is like the multiplayer, which kind of
Wasn't that good, and then they released
A full frontal assault
Which was the
It was like a tower defense Ratchet and Clank
But this one that they just released
Into the Nexus was fantastic
And I'm playing it right now
And I actually, with the game
Got a
A code for a downloadable
Game for the Quest for Booty game
Which was like the first downloadable
Game that they released or whatever
And I'm willing to give it to
Somebody in chat if they want it because
I already own it
But I have a free
Code here, so if anybody in chat likes
The Ratchet and Clank games and they
Don't own this game
It's really fun, it was a full length downloadable
Ratchet and Clank game, it's all like pirate themed
And stuff, so
So if you, anybody
The first person to
Direct message me in chat
Maybe, I want it, I wish you told me
I want it, no it's fine, give it to a listener
Do you want it Rob?
Of course, no no, give it to a listener, I have so many games to play
I'll never get around to it, give it to a listener
Who will actually play it
Alright cool, and welcome back guys
After a week of being off
Thank you, appreciate it
One more thing I just want to leave you with is that
You're not the first to talk about porn here on Orange
Radio, you need to go back in the archives
On the OL archive or whatever
And find the episode where we did review
And we watched live on air
Because our show was a lot different back in the early days
We actually watched live on air
Final Fuck X, which I still have
Somewhere, and Dance Dance
Fuck
Where some Japanese
Where some Japanese porn we
Watched, and for the record
All Final Fuck X's is
Really good cosplay with fucking
I remember I was looking for Dance Dance Revolution
Like stuff, like games on eBay
And I'm like, hey what's this?
I gotta buy that
Dance Dance Fuck has nothing to do with the games
So it just, which was hilarious
So, anyway
I'm just gonna have to channel my inner Shane on this one
And go, I don't care
Alright, well said
Alright, take care buddy
Alright Rob, everybody
Thanks for the call
I will talk to y'all later
Alright, that was a good call
1877 Game OLR, or our username on Skype
Is OrangeLoungeRadio
I wanna do some quick Twitter topics while we wait for another call
Tigerclaw tweets us
And says, Mortal Kombat producer
Hector Sanchez leaves NetherRealm Studios
That's right, I did see this
Coming out today
That one of the guys over there at NetherRealm did leave the company
As of I think yesterday
Was his departure, no word yet where he
Went, but obviously he was a big
Part of not only the new Mortal Kombat
But Injustice, so
Very interesting to see him
Take another job somewhere
So let's go to the phones and go to another call
Hi, you're on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
Hi, this is Def
I see your picture has changed
It's a little, is that your new Wii U?
It's a Kirby
Yeah, it's the screen of my Wii U
It's actually a video
Of it
Oh, it's live video
Oh, no wonder I hear myself echoing a little bit
Oh yeah, I can see the pixels
Oh, there it goes
Alright, it is live video
Nice, love that
Even though I'm hearing myself echo
But that's okay, what's on your mind buddy?
Basically
Sorry
I was gonna talk about
Basically
Or ask you
Why do people still
Say that Nintendo is gonna
Be in ruins
I don't know
Lucky, why do people say
Nintendo is gonna be in ruins
It's doom and gloom, doom and gloom
It's just because the Wii U is not selling well
So they assume that because the Wii U is not selling well
That Nintendo doesn't have anything else
That they're selling that's not doing well
Except
They have this thing called the 3DS
That seems to sell like crazy
I don't know, I don't think they're in ruins
But as far as getting the platform
Of Wii U
Ehhhh, that's not
Doing so hot
That's about it
And actually right now they don't really have any
EA games
At all, and there's nothing on the slate for next year
So that's gonna hurt
Well to paraphrase something
That someone very aptly put on
The tumblers
The Virtual Boy
Didn't tank it
The Micro didn't tank it
The 64DD didn't tank it
So
They're just not going to
Recapture what
Happened with the Wii
I think the Wii set the bar so high
It was such a successful console
That expectations are very high
Is the Wii U going to win
This generation?
Not likely, but never say never
I mean, I think we also have to remember
In the last generation
PlayStation 3 didn't come out the gate too hot
And PlayStation 3 took a while
To turn around
PlayStation 3 took a good two years
And when did Little Big Planet
Come out? Because that's when things really started
Turning around for PlayStation 3
That was almost two years into it, right?
I think it was 2007, so it was a year after it came out
I think it's still just
A little too soon to write off
Nintendo completely
Are they having a bad day?
Absolutely. Are they done?
I don't think so. Are they going to be number one?
Probably not
I think it's going to be a little more even
Steven across all three of them this time
Because let's be real, last generation
Nintendo blew the other two out of the water
Whether you like it or not
This time I don't think it's going to be
I think Nintendo may actually be the one that lags behind a little bit
But we'll see
Xbox One's out next week
We've got to see where things are at six months out
We'll see
But it's not over for Nintendo
3DS will always keep them afloat
And whatever else they've got up their sleeve
It's going to be a Wii U next year
It's going to sell systems
Along with Super Smash Brothers
Just wait
But what about you Actif?
You just bought a Wii U
So what finally made you decide to take the plunge?
Basically
First of all, Super Mario 3D World
It's
Seeing the videos
Over and over again
It looks like it's going to be a pretty fun game to play
And I really
Wanted to play it
As soon as it comes out
So
I pretty much wanted that
And also
I topped this with Bobby
Rayman Legends
Even though it's a multi-platform
Game
I still want it on the Wii U
And it's even on sale right now
On Steam for 20 bucks
I want to purchase that
But now that I have the Wii U
I really
Want to get it for this console
So yeah
Basically those are my two main reasons right now
To get one
And even then
Something that you said on the beginning of the show
It's like pretty much
Right now Wii U
Has the games
Has at least
More games to play
Right now
Since it has
The
Year
Since it launched
So yeah
It already has
A big library so it
Doesn't have that many games
Maybe to play but
At least you have more of a selection
Right now than the
PS4 or even the
Xbox One
Even though there's not a lot of games on Wii U
There will be some really great
A-list titles on it
That help keep the system afloat
Which I'm not sure PS4 or Xbox One
Has as much of right now anyway
Alright
Well Akdef, thanks so much for the call
And enjoy your new Wii U, have fun
Thanks
Alright you're welcome, take care buddy, have a good night
See ya
1877 Game OLR
Or a username on Skype, OrangeLoungeRadio
If you want to give us a call
Guess what, nobody sent
CodeMan a direct message for that code
So he ended up giving it to me anyway
Haha, suckers
Alright
Let's go to the phones one more time hopefully
1877 Game OLR or a username on Skype
OrangeLoungeRadio
While we wait for a call to come in
There's a call coming in right now so let's go to it
Hi on OrangeLoungeRadio, who's this?
It's Legend, Zaku here
Hey Zaku buddy, how you doing?
Long time no see
What do you do?
Nothing much, just shuffling between
Battlefield 4 and GTA 5
I love that you're calling in when you're in your
camo shirt, I couldn't see you for a minute
That's my PJ's
What, what's that? Those are my PJ's
I was going to say it kind of looked like a PJ top
You call in when you're in your camo jammies
To talk about Battlefield, so please by all means
How is Battlefield?
Well I haven't, to be honest I haven't
gotten into the multiplayer yet
Because I'm still, you know, it's always
A thing of mine to always do single player first
Then just jump into multiplayer
Same thing I did for Battlefield 3
But so far
I mean, if you want single player
It is kind of like very
Cinematic
But that's all I can say about it other than
It looks like it's gonna
It looks pretty short than the
One for Battlefield 3
But I'm hearing a lot of great things about
Online, except of course when you
Have people
Crashing the servers maliciously
Like what happened this weekend
Yeah I heard about that, what's up with that?
Did the DDoS
Attacks go against
Battlefield 4 today or something?
Apparently from what I'm hearing
When I'm glancing through Kotaku
Right now
Yeah they were getting
They were basically getting hammered
By denial of service, yeah they were getting
DDoS'd
I guess
Now that the PS4 is out
This kind of opens the floodgates
Since most of the
PS4 games will have dedicated servers
Whether or not that will actually
Translate over to consoles
Assuming one can just
Slightly sniff
Outgoing packets
Outgoing network packets
To see if they can
Find an IP to exploit
I mean that's one way to do it
You just snip the traffic
Between the private dedicated
Servers and the console and you might
Be able to get some info
Assuming it's not encrypted
But if it is
Then they're still a bit lucky
I'm assuming you
Did not jump on the PlayStation 4 bandwagon
Did you, you've been doing that?
Not yet, I still have a PS3 to go over
As I said I still have GTA 5
That I played yesterday, last night
And I've been juggling
Battlefield 4 so those are the two things
Those two gaming things are going on right now
So you're sitting out
This new
Consoles for a little bit too
You're not planning on Xbox One either?
Not yet, as I said I'd rather give it
At least a couple of years
Or until the prices start dropping
I mean when I
Got my Xbox two years after it came out
That was the first
The first 360
And then after that
That one crapped out and then I bought another
But yeah, it was
I waited at least two years before buying
That current generation of
Console
And PS3 I got last year so
Yeah
Still juggling, but as I
You know, I'd rather, it's not
It's not really good to be an early adopter
In this stage
Especially for a new generation console
Because you're pretty much dealt with
What you have already and not
What improvements Sony
Or Microsoft will make on their hardware
Yeah, but
Other than having to deal with that aftermath initially
I'd rather just see how they find
How they flesh it out
But you can be the cool kid on the block with your cool new toy
You're the coolest kid in school
Sure
That is true, but
I know it's $400
That I could put to good use
You know, like
Buying myself a new video card
Or basically getting
Two terabyte hard drives
I could set up on RAID so I could put all my
Steam games and get a lot
More of them so I don't max out my current drive
Stuff like that, like putting stuff
On my PC
As opposed to the PS3 which I still
Invest, but it's not as
It's not as urgent as
Something that's almost like reaching
Two years old
And I still need to get a new video card for it
But other than that
I mean, it's not like my
My head is Seth Child called the 360
Which I barely put anything
Except for an Xbox Live membership earlier this year
And that's it
Alright
Well, Zaku, we're gonna let you go so we can wrap up the show
But have fun with your Battlefield
And get in that multiplayer and let us know how it is
You know, when the servers work
Maybe you guys do need to
Jump on it
I'm certain there are Battlefield PC players
The best argument
I heard for playing Battlefield 4
And Jamie, you'll appreciate this
The best argument I heard for Battlefield 4 and playing it
Is it's using the same engine the new Mass Effect
Game's gonna be using
Of course, it's Frostbite
And you can actually do
Countering knife attacks
I don't hate shooters
I'm so bad at them, Zaku
I am so, so bad
Do you want to play with a scrub?
Do you want to?
I will lower your team's
Collective performance
Other than that, I barely see VOG network on GTA Online
What's up with that?
I don't see many on the PS3
I'm on all the time
Except I'm on two different Sims
Good day, though
Can't you hit me up on a social club?
Don't they have messaging systems?
I have it through my phone now
Because I'm not
Doing my best to dodge, chop
I put messages on there
Are you friended on
PlayStation Network with me?
It's there
My profile should have my PSN ID
I'll even post it up right now
After this call
But yeah
Hopefully
OLR can get a VOG network
Group on Origin for Battlefield
3 and or 4
Yeah
That requires me to install Origin
It's not that bad
Oh my god
I basically bit the bullet and did that
Alright, Zaku
I gotta wrap up
We're running long
Have a good one, buddy
Thanks for the call
I love it when we get the webcam calls
It's always good to be able to see our people
I should probably put a webcam on the computer
Just for Skype
So that way when they call in
I can remember the one I've been using
For my drawing
It's more incentive for people to call
Microsoft would like to let you know
That you can get your free Skype camera
With the purchase of an Xbox One
In the form of a Kinect
I am so sorry, the phones are still lighting up
I've gotta wrap up because we're running long
We're 15 minutes past midnight on the East Coast
I still have some Twitter topics
So one of these is a really good question I want to get to
So please, please tweet, email
And we'll get to you guys in a later week, hopefully
I want to get this tweet from
ActDeaf who sent us a tweet
This is something I totally missed from the Nintendo Direct
I'm so sorry
I get Kirby, how very dare I
I'm mad at myself, y'all
Kirby Triple Deluxe
Will be coming out in Japan on
January 11th
And there's a teaser site for that
Kirby Triple Deluxe
Get it? Kirby 3D
Get it?
Oh my gosh
Alright
And one other question here
That I really like this
This is from AJ Twist
So, in O.L.R.'s opinion
Who won
The last gen
Console Wars?
Dreamcast
The dramas are still not over
So, I mean, it's still going
It's still going?
Alright
Define when, do you mean by sales
Do you mean by units
Specifically sold, do you mean
By what country, do you mean by
Gallup poll, I don't know
I think the question is vague on purpose
It's his opinion, in your opinion
Who won
My 3DS
The 3DS won the last console
I think that's a perfectly valid answer
See, that's a console, not a handheld
Ah, alright
You know what I think won?
My computer, the end
PC's
PC's won
You know what, there's a lot of people
There would be a lot of people in that camp
It would be a home run with the Ouya
I mean, the Ouya won the last gen console wars
There's just no doubt about it
No
Loki, who won?
Who won?
Probably Xbox, just because they had
A lot of units out there
They still have the strongest support, I think
From all third parties
I mean, it's still going strong
The Wii's gone
I mean, the support for Wii U
Is gone, and now it's Wii U
So, they're in their own
Gen, I guess
It's the way they want to classify themselves because they can't compete
With the Wii U now
So, I think Xbox, but
I mean, PlayStation 3 did turn it around
And now they're selling
Quite heavily, so that's
Pretty neck and neck, I mean, it's not like
One clear winner
I think, it depends on your criteria
I think, for me
If you're going by sales, specifically
Nintendo won, clearly
Like it or not, love or hate what they brought to the table
Just speaking by the numbers
And no, that's not me being a fanboy
I mean, Wii Sports is the
Biggest video game of all time, period
You can't dispute that
But, the answer
That was in my head
Was actually something Bobby said in chat here
Who said, who won? The gamers
Absolutely believe it, the gamers won
The last generation
There's a lot of choice available out there now
And more ways to
Connect with each other, and our voices
Are really having an impact
For better or for worse
And so, yeah, I think the gamers won
Absolutely, if I had to pick a
Company though, Netflix
Won, big time
Netflix won the last generation
Huge, because
That's what a lot of these gaming boxes are
They're Netflix devices and so forth
Gene in chat says
Apple won, you know, that's
Not a stretch
It just depends on what you look at
Alright, great tweet, great question
Maybe we'll get some emails on that
Mailbag at Orangeloungeradio.com
Again, sorry to the call
So I didn't get through, but we do want to wrap up
We are after
9.15 on the west coast
Which means it's 15 past midnight on the east coast
So it is about time that we wrap up
But before we say
Goodnight for good, we gotta go around and get everybody's
Final thought
And I do want to also say one more time
Thank you very much for downloading us
Thank you for supporting independent radio
You made it this far in the show
I just, I really appreciate you guys' support of the show
It's what keeps us motivated to do this
I know we've had some very strong opinions
And devil's advocate positions
And things like that throughout the night
So I really appreciate you guys that stick with the whole thing
To listen to it
If you do like what you hear, please tell a friend or two about the show
Help spread the word
We do do this show for free
We do perform this show for free
All we ask is help spread the word
Help grow our family
Get some more awesome people into our community
It is so appreciated
And support independent broadcasting
There's so many great people that do this
If you hated our show
Yet you made it all this way
There's probably some other indie shows out there
That are for you
So check them out
Let's go around and get everybody's final thought
Loki, we'll start with you, your final thought tonight
I'm done with Cookie Clicker
I'm done
My 24 hour foray into Cookie Clicker
Is now complete
You divorced it, so it's done
You're over it
Party's over, get out
My final thought tonight is
That
Game capture card I bought
Really ended up being a waste of money
Because I don't have a TV next to my PC
Which means I need to buy a TV
No, I need to buy a Playstation 4
Which means you need to lend it to me
No, I need to buy a 3DS XL
I need to buy all the things
But I'm broke
You need a roof over your head
Food in your stomach and water and shelter
I already said shelter
And fucking
And sex
And a kitty
Dark Soccer
Your final thought tonight
I got up to go grab my shoes
Because my feet were cold
And um
My legs hurt from doing squats
I was walking like the hunched
Back old woman
And also tonight's cookie is fun
Alright, that's it you guys
Thank you very much for listening to our show
And I was also going to say all you need to do is
Get a really long HDMI cable
And you're problem solved
Maybe I will do that, that's a good idea
Might as well instead of
I didn't even think to get
A 50 foot HD cable
Just what we need in this apartment
I don't know about 50 feet
I don't remember how long it is
You can make an HDMI cable before you have to have
Some sort of signal booster
You should be able to get at least 20 feet
I think without having to do that
And that should be enough
Yay, just what we need, another big cable in the house
Alan will be so happy
Alright, he's cheering you live here
Alright, that really is going to do it
Thank you guys again for listening
Well again, next week's not Thanksgiving right?
No, that's two weeks
But I'll have to bring over sweet potato latkes
That are left over
Oh my god
It is the latke feast, the OLR latke feast
We ate like a whole bag of those fucking latkes
Last year, they're so good
Well then maybe I'll bring jelly donuts
Alright, that's it, we're done, we're out
Good night
Tune in to vaughnetwork.com Sunday nights at 6pm Pacific, 9pm Eastern
The views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily reflect those of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio or Vaugh Network
But you know they were all still true
See you next week
Join the crew