[SPEAKER_03]: It's a videotape!
[SPEAKER_03]: Put it in!
[SPEAKER_13]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_13]: Our live talk program begins now.
Boring!
[SPEAKER_07]: This video sucks!
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge may contain nudity.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hide Orange Lounge radio for the fucking children.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess there's just two kinds of people, Miss Sandstone.
[SPEAKER_07]: My kind of people and assholes.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, Warner, he's good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Missed it by that much.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's Dr. Evil's cat.
[SPEAKER_06]: How can you tell?
[SPEAKER_08]: I never forget a pussy.
[SPEAKER_08]: 37.
[SPEAKER_08]: My girlfriend sucked 37 dicks.
[SPEAKER_08]: In a row?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: And monkeys might fly out of my butt.
[SPEAKER_08]: You are the weakest link to fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you get nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good day, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dear diary, my teen angst bullshit has a body count.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would like, if I may, to take you on a strange
[SPEAKER_09]: DarkSakura, Sky, Orange Lounge Radio We are live and this is episode number 14 for September the 29th of 2002.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're tuned in to the Bomani Scene's most incredible radio station of all things B-Money.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are the greatest Bomani Talk radio program ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are the only Bomani Talk radio program ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: My name is Rob Roberts.
[SPEAKER_17]: But you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_17]: Joining me as always is our resident Happy Bunny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everyone, please say hello to Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_09]: You smell like butt.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've got a few people around here tonight.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to introduce them one at a time.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've got Matt, also known as Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've got Dave.
[SPEAKER_17]: We had some other people, but they ran away.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's beef in the other room.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's why they ran away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beef is bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: They got enticed by some big beef.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's hiding in the other room.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beef is bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Beasts taste like murder and murder tastes good.
[SPEAKER_09]: To quote Dennis Leary.
[SPEAKER_17]: I will tell you right now, this is going to be one of those shows.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll get into it later.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you want to go ahead and send me your FUs of the week, just join our chat room at irc.eggheads.org, any other side IRC server, and you're just going to join Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we'll be talking to everybody else a little bit more later, but first we're going to take a quick break, and we're going to play some old school 2DX songs, because they're cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Any other opening thoughts from you, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_09]: I would like to open someone's head to see what they've got.
[SPEAKER_09]: Brains!
[SPEAKER_09]: Brains are yummy.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can use a straw to eat them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because remember, I can sniff your spicy brains.
[SPEAKER_17]: Red Dragon 2, starring Jamie Summers.
[SPEAKER_09]: Brains.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'd starve in here, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, we'll be right back.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: From the 23rd Megas, our source for useless Bomani stuff, comes our Bomani Science Lesson of the Day.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not even the Orange Lounge is immune to the effects of gravity.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: Big thanks to 23rd Magus for sending us that promo we just used to come back in on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unfortunately it came out a little quiet, but we'll work on getting that a little louder for future broadcasts of that promo.
[SPEAKER_17]: We need more promos on this show because I'm getting lazy.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm getting lazy, so the audience needs to take care of that for me if they want.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm just reading some things in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you do want to join our chat room, go to any other site, IRC server, and just join Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they're just talking about those songs that we played, Panorama and Shine On.
[SPEAKER_17]: And all sorts of different opinions on that.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do we want to do first?
[SPEAKER_17]: We want to talk about Max USA or we want to talk about FU?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, I was going to start us off on a positive note.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we're going to talk about Max USA, DDL Max.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, basically, I've gotten a little bit of information about the release of DDR Max.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sure for everyone who's been looking on DDR Freak, you've seen the release of the box art.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you have not, just go to DDRFreak.com, and it should be the second announcement there.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a direct link to the box art.
[SPEAKER_09]: I warn you, it is a very large image.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's very high quality, though.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also a few hints on what you might be hearing on the new version.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, you can also check it out over on SoCalKicks.com.
[SPEAKER_17]: One of our faithful listeners, SoCalKicks, has a site that's pretty much very up to the minute on all the Max USA news.
[SPEAKER_17]: And one thing that we found out through the cover, and I'm going to pull up the cover because some people in the room here haven't... Ah, shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I haven't pulled up the cover for some people in the room here.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to do that right now if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see... But the cover of DDR Max USA...
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm not particularly fond of that version, but... It's just all fucked up.
[SPEAKER_16]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_17]: They look like parachute pants
[SPEAKER_17]: is best known for a song of theirs called Sandstorm, which you may or may not have heard.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, speculation is that that will be the song that will turn up in DDR Max USA, although, who knows, you have a different opinion on this, Matt, do you?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, there's another song that's pretty much the same song.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's Feel the Beat.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's got a lot more stuff that they could do with instead of Sandstorm, which is the same thing repeating over and over and over and over and over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_16]: I actually have an MP3.
[SPEAKER_16]: We can play that later on in the show if you'd like.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is Sandstorm, for those of you who maybe haven't heard the song before.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, if you have an idea of what you can look forward to, possibly.
[SPEAKER_17]: We don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll hopefully get confirmation on that very soon in the near future.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, there's a little teaser of that for you.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then Reel2Reel did that song...
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't have an audio copy of it, unfortunately, but it goes like, I'd like to move it, move it, I'd like to move it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You might know that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I haven't heard that song at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'd probably know it if you heard it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You'd probably be surprised at what you've heard.
[SPEAKER_09]: We also, I asked if it was okay for me to say, so the tentative date is going to be November 5th.
[SPEAKER_09]: It could possibly be pushed back a week after that, but that's what I have so far as a release date.
[SPEAKER_09]: So get over to GameStop or EB or wherever that you like to go and reserve your copy, like now.
[SPEAKER_17]: November 5th.
[SPEAKER_09]: Buy your copy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Purchase your copy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Spend money on this copy.
[SPEAKER_17]: And so that's very cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: We got a, hopefully, it's tentative release date, but it sounds pretty certain it's going to be November 5th.
[SPEAKER_16]: And as mentioned last week in the October 8th issue of the official PlayStation Magazine will be a demo of DDR Max USA, so go check that out.
[SPEAKER_17]: And actually, that was the other bit of news that was released this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people have gotten their hands on that demo.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also, I believe DDR Freak has the news, as does SoCalKicks.com, as does most of your faithful Bomani news sites out there.
[SPEAKER_17]: There are some pictures out there of the DDR Max demo.
[SPEAKER_17]: And what it does reveal is that Secret Rendezvous is going to be one of the songs on Max USA, which is... Yes!
[SPEAKER_17]: You can get your hot lesbian action on with Secret Rendezvous, which is interesting because that means there's a Max 2 song in there, so who knows what other Max 2 songs might turn up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Perhaps I'd like to see, you know, like Burning Heat or Kakumei.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want Burning Heat?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't want Burning Heat personally, but I'd like to see it in DDR, yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: So...
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, just make sure that you release your copy.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just think it's funny, though, how they replaced the kanji with little three-letter acronyms for the... Not acronyms, that's not a good word, but abbreviations.
[SPEAKER_09]: And standard is apparently STD.
[SPEAKER_17]: STD, so if you're playing a song on Trick, it's now your STD.
[SPEAKER_09]: So make sure you wear those latex shoes.
[SPEAKER_17]: You need to talk about your new shoes that you got, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: You've got burning heat shoes on today.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Unfortunately, we don't have our cam on today because it's really dark in here.
[SPEAKER_09]: I will scan my shoes so that everyone can see and put them up on the Sack of Imani forums.
[SPEAKER_17]: But they've got little flames on them, so it looks like the Max 2 logo.
[SPEAKER_17]: So she's got burning feet, we all say.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep, replaced the laces with black laces, so now they're all sleek and cute.
[SPEAKER_17]: My shoes own, and I got them at the Vans outlet, so... The other thing the demo reveals, there's no .5 speed mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was something that was on the E3 demo that's not on this demo, so who knows if it's going to be on the final release or not.
[SPEAKER_17]: There are no dark mode.
[SPEAKER_17]: Rumor saying not, because of technical issues, but who knows what they're going to do.
[SPEAKER_17]: The demo also did not include foot rankings, which was something that's supposedly supposed to be in the final release.
[SPEAKER_17]: So that might be added later, we just don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just saying for the preview, there are no foot rankings currently.
[SPEAKER_17]: So that's about all we see for right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let the beat hit them, look to the sky, exotic ethnic and secret rendezvous, all playable with this month's official PlayStation magazine.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we'll definitely get our hands on that and share our thoughts on it with you once we get it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Still working on it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, let's see, any other chat room?
[SPEAKER_17]: They're saying they want to see, like, Long Train Runnin', The Whistle Song, and, uh... Uh... Foot Rankings will be in the final release.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, we have some information in there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some insider scoop.
[SPEAKER_09]: The last thing to be put in is going to be, uh, the Foot Rankings.
[SPEAKER_09]: So... They're still working on it.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're encouraging us not to share our thoughts, but to share an ISO of the demo.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ha ha!
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: Go out and buy your copy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Or just wait and buy Max USA.
[SPEAKER_09]: Save your money.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why Am I Being Shot?
[SPEAKER_17]: What else do we want to say on Max USA?
[SPEAKER_17]: Any other thoughts on Max USA?
[SPEAKER_17]: Things that they need to do quickly before the final release?
[SPEAKER_17]: Other songs we hope to see?
[SPEAKER_12]: Any opinions?
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, actually, if you look really, really, really, really, really closely in the background of Max USA, the cover, you'll notice in really, really, really small print hidden in there, it says, yes, there will most definitely be Let Them Move in this version.
[SPEAKER_16]: So just, you know, to warn you guys.
[SPEAKER_16]: Watch out for that.
No.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm pretty sure it's been confirmed by Jason himself that Let Them Move will not be a song.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I heard a rumor that it might be the Training Mode song.
[SPEAKER_17]: It better not be.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would rather have After the Game of Love for Training Mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's like in third mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: Why don't you just get rid of Training Mode and give us a couple more songs?
[SPEAKER_09]: I use Training Mode to listen to my edits with the clap assist on.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry, actually we're confusing lesson mode and training mode.
[SPEAKER_17]: Training mode is the one where you can slow down the song and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Lesson mode is where you learn how to play TDR.
[SPEAKER_09]: Lesson mode is to just keep, you know, like in 3rd Mix they had a pimp song, you know, after the Game of Love.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did they?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's when you're not quite ready for the STDs, you go to lesson mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: and remember, wear latex shoes so you don't catch those STDs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're like poor little Miss Muffet who saddled her trumpet.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, this is... Black Lab suggests that instead of Max 300, Let Them Move will be the extra stage.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everyone will be feeling that because they'll be like throwing up or something.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let them...
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, so we started on a positive note.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shall we go to the FUs of the week?
[SPEAKER_17]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: You got one, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, let's start off, as we always do, with Jamie's FU of the week, which turns in always to everybody's FU of the week, so here you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: My FU of the week goes to Taco Bell.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hadn't eaten a damn thing all day.
[SPEAKER_09]: I get to Taco Bell.
[SPEAKER_09]: and I wanted to have a nice, you know, chicken grilled stuff burrito.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I wanted a chicken mix and melt.
[SPEAKER_09]: My chicken mix and melt was yummy, but it had tomatoes on it, but I forgot, that's okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, we get over here to Rob's place, and I take a bite into my grilled stuff burrito, my chicken grilled stuff burrito, and it's beans, all beans.
[SPEAKER_09]: All beans and a little bit of rice, and then I found one piece of chicken in the whole damn thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I paid for chicken.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, that's my F.U.
[SPEAKER_09]: of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, that was beautiful.
[SPEAKER_14]: My F.U.
[SPEAKER_14]: of the week is to Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I need to change the song here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, my own song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, what was my song?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Petite Love.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_14]: What an effing cool song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: My F.U.
[SPEAKER_14]: of the week is to Roseville Golf Land for...
[SPEAKER_14]: Even though they did upgrade both their Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania machines to 8th and 7th mix respectively, they broke Guitar Freaks already after one hour.
[SPEAKER_14]: One hour.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a new record.
[SPEAKER_14]: They can't upgrade- IT'S A NEW RECORD!
[SPEAKER_14]: You've got a new record, save it on the memory card!
[SPEAKER_14]: No, but it's really shitty now, because I played Drone Mania a lot, and that's cool, but if I want to play session mode, too fucking bad, because Guitar Freaks, they already fucked it up, and they haven't even started playing yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was open, I think, for one hour.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, if you think about it, it wasn't as bad as when they got the seventh mix.
[SPEAKER_14]: The seventh mix, they couldn't even play it, it just broke.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because of some coding.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind, when we got this mix, do you know who installed that?
[SPEAKER_09]: Who actually got it working?
[SPEAKER_09]: My fiancé did!
[SPEAKER_09]: Dan got it working!
[SPEAKER_09]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: So maybe we should just send Dan over there and say, hey, fix this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Of course, that's also why this mix was set for two tokens when we first got it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Matt, you got any fuckies of the week?
Um...
[SPEAKER_16]: Actually, I don't think I do.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, fine, for once.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know, I haven't really been thinking about things to be angry at.
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, let me see here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, you lose.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yeah, I got it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got one.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_16]: Okay, this FU goes to the makers of EJ Software, the programs I use for making wonderful songs.
[SPEAKER_16]: Unfortunately, I have a sample kit, and I wanted to steal samples from it.
[SPEAKER_16]: And they have a little thing in there to bump the pitch up so that it's, you know, at 140, which is what EJ uses.
[SPEAKER_16]: And the damn thing kept crashing every single time.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I have to do that.
[SPEAKER_16]: And that's kind of weak, but that's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's all I got.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'll have more next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: You promise?
[SPEAKER_14]: I promise.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: One thing I do have to say is that drumming is something that's totally owned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kuchaka and Concierto in Blue and the Extra Stage in Japanese, I can't read it.
[SPEAKER_14]: They all play the coolest songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, I just need to get over there and play it so I can play Another World and have my gags fixed.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be bringing that song next week and we are going to play Another World on Orange Lounge because Gactones, he's pretty.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have some FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Very, very, very, very, very, very interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have some FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_17]: My first FU of the week, as wonderful as they are for hosting this wonderful program, Live365.com gets my first FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_17]: First of all, for playing that goddamn Prodigy ad and we missed the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm all for, you know, playing the ads occasionally to help pay the bills, but that Prodigy song sucks, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Quit playing that ad during my show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Second, F you for them, is that they keep stats.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we can see, you know, how many people are listening to the show, how many hours we get and all that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_17]: For every station on Live 365, they lost last week's stat.
[SPEAKER_17]: And by the way, I happen to know, because I see live stats that are coming in, that last Sunday happened to be one of our biggest nights for the show to date.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we don't get any credit for that now, so our ratings suck, thanks to Live365.com.
[SPEAKER_17]: So FU!
[SPEAKER_09]: So poo-poo on them.
[SPEAKER_09]: Everybody, plug in twice.
[SPEAKER_17]: Although, thanks for hosting the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_17]: But you fucked up on that one, so poo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Poo-pee.
[SPEAKER_17]: Poo-pee on you.
[SPEAKER_17]: My other FU of the week goes to my 2DX controller.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because button number 3 and button number 7 have been sticking like, like a lot.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I hate it.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's my last FU.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have another FU, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: My next FU goes toward Holic, R5, and Y31, yet again.
[SPEAKER_09]: I am so close to passing this one.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, I had a freaking full combo on R5 going into right before that one really hard part that I always had issues with.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I lost it the whole song because I can't figure that one part out.
[SPEAKER_09]: But, you know...
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you to all of the seven star songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to pass one of you.
[SPEAKER_09]: One day.
[SPEAKER_09]: One day I will.
[SPEAKER_09]: One day my prince will come.
[SPEAKER_17]: Is that a promise?
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's what I promised at the threat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I mean, not at the threat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Max, chatroom, any FUs?
[SPEAKER_17]: The chatroom has a ton of FUs right now, so I'm going to get some of those.
[SPEAKER_17]: But first off, I have to state that, actually, our resident comedian in the chatroom, Pyro Man, is back, and he suggested how you can get a sticky controller.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just the secret rendezvous video and four hours on Kazop.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, let's get to the FUs from the chatroom, shall we?
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, hold on, this isn't fair.
[SPEAKER_14]: They get a cool song, and I get the tea bug.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, life sucks.
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: SoCalKicks says, Fuck you everyone who is bitching because for me life has never been better.
[SPEAKER_17]: And fuck you everyone who is calling him Fox version 2.0 because his latest picture makes him look like Fox even though I'd rather laugh at the situation and go along with it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever that means.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think that was half inside joke.
[SPEAKER_17]: JB says, F you to SyFam for being so cheap they can't properly advertise their artists like Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's such a Jenny Rom whore.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, you saw it in his...
[SPEAKER_17]: DJ Konami wants to give an F you to the assholes that don't take it seriously when I'm teaching them how to play Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_09]: Maybe we will.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, this is a huge one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh... Oh, he sent it three times.
[SPEAKER_17]: One is enough, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_17]: 23rd Magus wants to give a big F you to Absolute Trick, because it caused him much embarrassment when he failed it on the Max 2 on Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fuck you, Absolute!
[SPEAKER_17]: I also want to say, fuck you to Earthlink for screwing with their FTP servers for my site.
[SPEAKER_17]: And he wants to know if that was, uh, fuck instead of fuck.
[SPEAKER_17]: It was a spelling thing, anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, more F... Oh, Bradley's here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hey, what's up, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_04]: My power went out, so I had to come over here.
[SPEAKER_17]: You couldn't hear the show at your own house, so you had to come over here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's nothing to do in my apartment without power, so... So you want to give a big F you to power?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you, power.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, Twen has not only... Oh my god, he's got a bunch.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's got six, here we go.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU number one, Japan played every other fucking song on Fifth Mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's FU number one, that's where you've been.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU number two, Feet of Fury beta being pushed back nearly half a month.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU number three, AIM for always crapping out.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU number four, no one appreciating his mixes, aww.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU number five, can't view anything while listening to Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: FU number six, people dissing me for not passing End of the Century Maniac with a B. Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Which mix?
[SPEAKER_17]: It depends.
[SPEAKER_17]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_17]: His FU is to himself for being a moron and closing Microsoft Word in the middle of an assignment.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dope!
[SPEAKER_09]: That's why you save.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's why we use autosave.
[SPEAKER_17]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep in mind, this is a rule for whenever... The rule for word processors and programs applies to RPGs.
[SPEAKER_09]: Save often.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Pyro Man wants to give an FU to me for starting the show so damn late in Illinois.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, fuck you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait, hold on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hold on, Pyro Man.
[SPEAKER_17]: I got something for you.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have exactly the message to give to you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me call you an ambulance.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, Twin wants to point out that that's Fifth Mix that he plays in the Sentry on.
[SPEAKER_17]: And...
[SPEAKER_17]: Black Lab, I missed your FUs, you're going to have to resend them, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you didn't send them over to... Oh, he has nothing, I guess, unless you wrote them in black.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Chaos says, FU to Beautiful Days, because he got one regular grade on it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oops, a little loud.
[SPEAKER_17]: And everything else is a flashing grade.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frowny face.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pyro Man says... Oh, same thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: DDR Mike says, FU to Big Black Cock.
[SPEAKER_16]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't want to see pictures right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Those are all the pictures.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was relating to SoCalKick's post.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to say, yes, sort of.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll look at that during break.
[SPEAKER_17]: He did want to point out also we have some follow-up on DDR Max USA stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: From the E3 beta version of DDR Max USA, it was announced a new half-speed would be in the list of modes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Right now, its absence from the first November-issue demo of Official PlayStation Magazine is rumored that it was removed from the final version because of technical difficulties.
[SPEAKER_17]: Foot rankings confirmed here on SoCalKicks.com.
[SPEAKER_17]: People began to worry about that, too, because it was also absent from the demo.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I can tell you right now, it is one of the last things that's going to be put into the game.
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: will make it into DDR Max USA, similar to an Oni mode, perhaps.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, take that all with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's still rumor, rumor, rumorville.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, that's it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay, and there you have it.
[SPEAKER_17]: There you have it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And now you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: And knowing is half the battle.
[SPEAKER_17]: The more you know.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's another FU, but it's a personal FU, and I don't like to name people by name for FUs, but Pyroman does want to give an FU to a certain individual because he smells.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, you know who you are.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know who you are.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everybody make sure you've been bathing, because you're pissing off Pyroman.
[SPEAKER_17]: And on that note, I think we're going to go to break.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that is a wonderful idea.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are going to take a quick break, and we will come right back.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to take a quick break and we'll come right back.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've been requested to play the DJ Konami thing, which I'm going to have to dig up and find.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll get to that pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to start off with one of my favorite songs from Max 2.
[SPEAKER_17]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_07]: Winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey everyone, this is DJ Konami.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know you all know Beatmania, but I want to go back and teach you the basics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Listen carefully and try to follow.
[SPEAKER_08]: The objects will come down from the top.
[SPEAKER_08]: When it hits the red line, push the button.
[SPEAKER_08]: When it hits the red line, turn the table.
[SPEAKER_05]: You get it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, let's practice.
[SPEAKER_07]: First,
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Now it's all the keys and the turntable.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's hard, but you can do it!
[SPEAKER_07]: New Feet Mania
[SPEAKER_08]: We often wonder how some of those Bomani songs are chosen.
[SPEAKER_13]: We think we figured it out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 14.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's an old promo.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm starting to play the old promos again.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because they've been a while.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's been a while, so they're fresh again.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's like a fine wine.
[SPEAKER_17]: You let them age a little bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: We want to also talk about another new Bomani game that just hit.
[SPEAKER_17]: I believe it is official as of Monday.
[SPEAKER_17]: 2DX8Style is out and about.
[SPEAKER_17]: And unfortunately... And somebody... I accidentally closed the window.
[SPEAKER_17]: They sent it in a little too late.
[SPEAKER_17]: But...
[SPEAKER_17]: It took them a while to do that with 7th Style too, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's pulling up right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've got a bunch of the songs that are released, and some of the non-stop courses, which I think is really interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have a Tran course, that's what I like, I think that's really cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's a Tran course, which consists of Beautiful Days, Alien World, Starmind, G2, and Stoic.
[SPEAKER_17]: Although I think G2 is a scary-ass Tran video, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: This song is scary.
[SPEAKER_17]: Some of the other non-stop course names that are interesting, Feel, DJ Taka, of course, Eurobeat, Super Eurobeat,
[SPEAKER_17]: Vocal, Performance, Trance, VJ Hess.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's an interesting one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Number five, Newcomer, UG2, Rapid2, Original, Cinderella.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that's all... Look what that is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Look what the songs are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stick Around, Jelly Kiss, Glorious Days.
[SPEAKER_09]: Are those the sauna tracks?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I don't think Glorious Days is a sauna song.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's just kind of happy sounding songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Piano, Tack...
[SPEAKER_17]: Hirata, Hell, of course, and Saturday Night.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a pretty cool course, Saturday Night.
[SPEAKER_17]: You got Dancing into the Night, Blown My Heart Away, Funky Bingo Paradise, Wow Wow 7 Days, and Please Don't Go.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's some very interesting genre names in 8th style, which has been getting a lot of laughs out of people.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's one called Cuddlecore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Murmur Twins is the name of the song, and that's in the genre.
[SPEAKER_17]: Metalhouse just sounds cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Cuddlecore.
[SPEAKER_17]: Where's Metalhouse?
[SPEAKER_09]: Metalhouse by Sunglasses of Night.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be the song.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sunglasses of Night would be Metalhouse, and that's good, cool, featuring Hidosewa.
[SPEAKER_17]: Psychedelic techno.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, this will be a good one.
[SPEAKER_17]: In the girl rock genre, Halfway of Promise by Yutakami.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just need to do the sauna course
[SPEAKER_17]: Sonic Wars would be cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: But unfortunately, we don't know much else about 8th Style.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're still waiting to see if any arcades in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_17]: are going to be getting it.
[SPEAKER_17]: We know of one that ordered it.
[SPEAKER_09]: It has seven buttons on a turntable and effectors.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, 8th Style will have seven buttons and a turntable.
[SPEAKER_09]: 14 and 2 turntables.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it's this little hole that you put your coin in and a big plasma screen if you're getting a brand new one like we are.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, Scandia anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: What are they saying in the chat room?
[SPEAKER_17]: Some people know more.
[SPEAKER_17]: A few arcades are ordering it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, which ones?
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't just tell me a few.
[SPEAKER_17]: Tell me which arcades.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not like that many arcades even have 2DX to begin with.
[SPEAKER_17]: We happen to know locally where we base Orange Lounge out of in Sacramento that there's an arcade...
[SPEAKER_17]: Black Lab quotes a famous Beck song, Two turntables and a microphone.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be Kraken DJ.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, with a little switch in the middle.
[SPEAKER_17]: Was there a microphone?
[SPEAKER_17]: There's not a microphone in Kraken DJ.
[SPEAKER_17]: Kraken DJ is a cool game.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know why they don't have more of it in places.
[SPEAKER_17]: Kraken DJ, for those that have never played it, it's two turntables and they kind of automatically spin like a real turntable would.
[SPEAKER_17]: As you're playing the game and it's all scratching, there's no buttons at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: You just scratch.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's a switch in the center.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, there's a switch in the center because you have to scratch one turntable and you scratch the other one.
[SPEAKER_17]: You have to move it back and forth or you have to...
[SPEAKER_17]: This is a pretty difficult game.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that 2DX is easier than Kraken DJ.
[SPEAKER_09]: By far.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wouldn't be more than 100.
[SPEAKER_17]: DJ Konami says that San Jose State is also supposed to be getting an 8th mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Or 8th style, sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think they're upgrading the 6th.
[SPEAKER_17]: I also heard a rumor that Beatmania 7th mix is finally coming out for PS1 on Christmas Eve is the tentative release date.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's about freaking time.
[SPEAKER_09]: Time to get ordering.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: So go place your pre-orders for that on your favorite import game site.
[SPEAKER_09]: But do not buy from BuyRipe.
[SPEAKER_09]: When you're buying it buy right, you're buying wrong.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they will cheat you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sure, go ahead, but I'm not going to cue the music because I'm lazy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, it's an old fuck you, but just my reasons for saying don't buy it, buy right.
[SPEAKER_09]: When I bought my Tekken 4 there, I was expecting to get a Japanese copy so I could have a chance at reading the manual.
[SPEAKER_09]: They sent me the Asian release and then wouldn't replace it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And they said, oh, you didn't say it was Japanese, we just said it was import.
[SPEAKER_09]: I could have bought that at YesAsia.com for about $30 cheaper.
[SPEAKER_09]: So buy right will cheat you.
[SPEAKER_09]: They will cheat you.
[SPEAKER_09]: So don't buy there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Pyromance said that he held an employee at Gunpoint and now Nickel City in Illinois will be getting 8th style.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lovely.
[SPEAKER_17]: Which we all know is probably a load of crap, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's change gears a little bit here.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is a story I want to... Oh, unless you guys have anything you want to say about 8thStyle?
[SPEAKER_16]: I can't play 7-key, let alone 5-key, and all that stuff, so... F you to 8thStyle for being so damn hard.
[SPEAKER_16]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_16]: Practice!
[SPEAKER_16]: Also, I'd like to point, that guy that you just flashed the picture up on the screen is very ugly.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll get to that in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're a 2DX player, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do you think of 8thStyle so far?
[SPEAKER_04]: Looks cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've listened to much of the music so far, but... Do you think it's going to be the biggest 2DX style ever, ever, ever?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know about that, but we shall see.
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought 5th style was awfully hard to top.
[SPEAKER_04]: 6th style?
[SPEAKER_09]: I thought 5th style was hard to top.
[SPEAKER_09]: 6 tries.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's matching, maybe, but I don't think it's better overall than 5th.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's get to this other story.
[SPEAKER_17]: Completely changing gears here a little bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: As if the show wasn't already on its way to a train wreck.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to talk about... This is interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: TwinGalaxies.com This is a link that was sent to me at the end of last week's show.
[SPEAKER_17]: I forget who sent it to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whoever sent it to me, just go ahead and give yourself an ego boost in the chat room and thanks.
[SPEAKER_17]: TwinGalaxies.com The worldwide authority on player rankings, game statistics, and championship tournaments.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, I'm supposed to mention the extra stage for 8th Style is a revenge song.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_17]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll all laugh.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is breaking news as of July 29th.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're a little late in reporting here.
[SPEAKER_16]: What can we do?
[SPEAKER_16]: This guy's ugly.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now be nice.
[SPEAKER_17]: He might be listening.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nobody listens to this.
[SPEAKER_16]: No, he's working on breaking his own world record.
[SPEAKER_17]: One of the hottest new series of modern arcade titles to play is the Dance Dance Revolution series by Konami, with the most current and popular release officially known as DDR Max 2, which in effect is the seventh mix in the series.
[SPEAKER_17]: For those unfamiliar with the game, players select different songs and become physically engaged in the game itself.
[SPEAKER_17]: It makes it sound like the last stage of Nick Arcade when they were swatting flies on the blue screen.
[SPEAKER_16]: Judging by the look of this ugly person, he hasn't been engaged in this game very long.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dancing literally in order to hit the specific arrow directions on the floor pad with their feet.
[SPEAKER_17]: This title, along with others such as MoCap Boxing and Police 911, are part of the latest trend in modern video gaming.
[SPEAKER_17]: physically interactive gameplay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bunga Bunga always gets a laugh on this show.
[SPEAKER_09]: Back to the article.
[SPEAKER_17]: We can talk about that until the cows come home.
[SPEAKER_17]: Making sure, okay, I just... So back to our article.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry, back to the article, yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Twin Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_17]: Twin Galaxies chief referee Robert T, I can't say your last name, proclaims gamer Damien Sarkoony as our first verified and recognized world champion at the DDR Max 2 title with a five score song total of...
[SPEAKER_17]: of 315,802,020 points.
[SPEAKER_17]: If I recall correctly, if you play a 9-foot song, the max score you'll get on a max 2 is 90 million, correct?
[SPEAKER_17]: Multiply that by 5, that's 450 million.
[SPEAKER_17]: So even if you fucked up your 5 9-footers completely, you should have a score of at least 400 million points, correct?
[SPEAKER_17]: This guy has the world record with a score of 315 million.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's like 4 7-footers and a 6.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: Hell, I could play friggin' Dynamite Ray Basic on stealth five times and still beat that damn score.
[SPEAKER_17]: The sirens are going outside.
[SPEAKER_17]: The world thinks this is madness.
[SPEAKER_17]: The world record is 315 million, held by... The official Twin Galaxies tournament settings have already been determined for this title and appear later in this breaking news story, which we'll read.
[SPEAKER_17]: But before we get into that, let's recap the experience.
[SPEAKER_17]: The game's record capabilities are unusual in that the scores are not permanently kept in the game's memory as far as points are concerned.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, if you have a memory card, it'll save it to the memory card.
[SPEAKER_16]: Also, I should mention that one of the rules for entering this world record is you have to be fucking ugly.
[SPEAKER_09]: The scores are too safe.
[SPEAKER_09]: Matt, go!
[SPEAKER_09]: Go do it!
[SPEAKER_09]: The scores are safe if you've got your initials in the machine that has your score beside it when it pops up on the screen.
[SPEAKER_16]: While his score was world record breaking, it wasn't good enough to place on the top ten.
[SPEAKER_17]: SoCalKicks is going right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: He says he's running out with the camera.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's going to take a picture of it.
[SPEAKER_17]: SoCalKicks, you can't do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're not ugly.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're Fox 2.0, remember?
[SPEAKER_17]: You can't do it.
[SPEAKER_09]: And besides that, you still owe me that screen capture so you can get my GameCube pen.
[SPEAKER_17]: So sit your ass down.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to be in trouble for that one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Further machines set to five song attempts use only the sum of the last three songs for the record.
[SPEAKER_17]: To be fair, I'm authorizing two different records to be tracked separately.
[SPEAKER_17]: One for three song and one for five song submissions.
[SPEAKER_17]: Most machines are set to a minute thirty to two minutes per song.
[SPEAKER_17]: I didn't think time ever had anything to do with it, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Further, there are several rest periods in between songs based on the actions you must do for the setting and song selection.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have included my ruling on this with the TGTS information below.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, Twin Galaxy, a little bit of Judge Judy action here.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're making a ruling.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because these guys have been around since the 80s, so they're old and sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, it's sad.
[SPEAKER_09]: They have no concept of how a DDR machine works.
[SPEAKER_17]: How can they be considered an authority on something?
[SPEAKER_17]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me restate.
[SPEAKER_17]: Since 1981, the worldwide authority on player rankings, gaming statistics, and championship tournaments.
[SPEAKER_09]: They're pretty good at that for me to poop on.
[SPEAKER_09]: I mean, you can't be an authority on something that you apparently know nothing about.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's keep going here.
[SPEAKER_17]: I've got to finish this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Speaking with Damien, as well as fellow DDR fan and Crazy Taxi World Champion, JC Padilla, because Crazy Taxi and DDR have so fucking much in common.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because you use your feet on a button.
[SPEAKER_17]: Because they both are utilized by ugly people in playing.
[SPEAKER_17]: and also some other local expert players.
[SPEAKER_16]: But you'll never be the world champion because you're not ugly like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would love to know who the other local expert players were.
[SPEAKER_17]: We picked up these random 8-year-olds from the kindergarten room.
[SPEAKER_17]: We reasoned out the rules and you will see below in their entirety and hope to start logging some more scores on it soon.
[SPEAKER_17]: One of the most important discoveries is the decision that gamers view using the same song up to five times in a row as cheesy.
[SPEAKER_17]: So to be fair, my official ruling takes this into consideration.
[SPEAKER_17]: So if you play five songs in a row, that's cheesy.
[SPEAKER_17]: The chat room is going off on this, by the way.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll get to them in a minute.
[SPEAKER_17]: The game itself is pretty intense.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wow, that was intense!
[SPEAKER_17]: And some players even brought their own combination water spray and fan handheld device to cool down in between performances.
[SPEAKER_09]: Did they buy it at Walmart for $2?
[SPEAKER_16]: Along with Goofy drinking hat filled with Sobe.
[SPEAKER_02]: and elaborate entourage of people with fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm picturing one of these fucking dorks wearing those hats with this straw that goes right in their mouth, a little thing they can squeeze when they're in between songs.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is sad.
[SPEAKER_17]: I wonder if this guy did it playing like Dynamite Rave, love to me.
[SPEAKER_17]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: I are Dynamite Raver world champion, yeah!
[SPEAKER_17]: Though quite the physical game, I am told that players of all ages, shapes, and sizes have been able to perform well.
[SPEAKER_17]: Even one player who I am told was in the 300 pound range.
[SPEAKER_16]: It should also be noted that facial deformities do not affect gameplay at all.
[SPEAKER_17]: So DDR doesn't discriminate against fat people.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's good to know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Definitely a game where both eye and foot coordination is required.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, duh.
[SPEAKER_17]: So now here are the rules, and I would officially like to thank Damien Sarkoony for not only taking the initiative and becoming our first recognized and verified world champion, but to assist me with creating the rules.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, basically, he made the rules, and he's the world champion.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay, alrighty.
[SPEAKER_09]: Is this like one of the editor's kids or something?
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, the rules.
[SPEAKER_09]: You want to read the rules, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Go for it.
[SPEAKER_09]: General rules.
[SPEAKER_09]: First, player must be performing in single mode.
[SPEAKER_02]: So no doubles.
[SPEAKER_09]: Players can compete on either three-song or five-song machine setting variations, which is determined by the arcade proprietor.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, if I'm not mistaking, there's also a four-song machine, so those people are just fucked, huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Referees must log the song difficulty and score per song for all three or five songs.
[SPEAKER_02]: The referee.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do they wear the black and white shirt, too, and make bad calls?
[SPEAKER_09]: They walk around playing, you know, Blow My Whistle, Bitch, with their little whistles there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Battle, dammit!
[SPEAKER_09]: Force.
[SPEAKER_09]: Players are allowed to utilize the entire duration of the game timers in between songs as rest.
[SPEAKER_09]: This includes song selection and setting selection.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, yay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Fifth.
[SPEAKER_09]: Players are allowed to utilize the same song no more than twice.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, so they can play the same song twice, they just can't play it more than twice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Regardless of whether playing three songs or five songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh my god, I'm gonna cry.
[SPEAKER_17]: These people make me cry.
[SPEAKER_17]: At this time... Twin Galaxies.
[SPEAKER_09]: Twin Galaxies will not be tracking records on the Oni, a.k.a.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, that's incorrect.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oni means ogre.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, Hell Mode, assuming I spelled that right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, they're stupid.
[SPEAKER_03]: How can you misspell Oni?
[SPEAKER_03]: O-N-I.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can't misspell it.
[SPEAKER_03]: God.
[SPEAKER_09]: First of all, they mistranslated the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oni does not mean hell.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, hell is what, Jigoku?
[SPEAKER_09]: Aren't I correct?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, how does Jigoku sound like Oni?
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell me.
[SPEAKER_09]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sorry, that's one of my pet peeves there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Keep going, girl.
[SPEAKER_17]: You go, girl.
[SPEAKER_17]: Go on with your bad self.
[SPEAKER_09]: All songs contained within the mix are eligible for selection.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would hope so.
[SPEAKER_09]: Which means Dynamite Rave!
[SPEAKER_09]: Love to be!
[SPEAKER_09]: Twice!
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_09]: The following rules are applicable for each of the three song or five song selections.
[SPEAKER_09]: Only one of the settings, difficulty, can be the player's choice.
[SPEAKER_09]: The rest are determined to be the official TG... Twin Galaxies scoreboard.
[SPEAKER_09]: Difficulty player can choose between light, standard, or heavy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speed has to be on 1.
[SPEAKER_09]: Easiest?
[SPEAKER_09]: My butt!
[SPEAKER_09]: 1.5 is easier than 1.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wait a minute!
[SPEAKER_17]: They said speed has to be set to the easiest, which is 1.
[SPEAKER_17]: I disagree with that.
[SPEAKER_17]: My god!
[SPEAKER_09]: Retards!
[SPEAKER_17]: Retards!
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: If they say easiest, then I can play it on 1.5.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because it's the easiest.
[SPEAKER_09]: Boost set to off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Appearance set to invisible.
[SPEAKER_09]: Turn set to off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Other set to off.
[SPEAKER_09]: Scroll set to standards.
[SPEAKER_09]: They don't say anything at all about three zeros.
[SPEAKER_17]: So you can't do Dark Reverse, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: No Dark Reverse!
[SPEAKER_16]: So why didn't they just say no modifiers?
[SPEAKER_16]: Since that's pretty much what they're saying here except for difficulty.
[SPEAKER_16]: No modifiers.
[SPEAKER_16]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_16]: Because there's no modifiers.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is going to get beautiful.
[SPEAKER_17]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_17]: Keep going, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: It only gets better from here, folks.
[SPEAKER_17]: Keep going.
[SPEAKER_09]: The following rules apply to the scoring of the title.
[SPEAKER_09]: The Twin Galaxies referee must log for tracking purposes the song selection difficulty chosen and final tally for each of three or five songs.
[SPEAKER_09]: At the very end, the Twin Galaxies referee must manually tally the five song total.
[SPEAKER_09]: The three song machines tally for you at the final score screen.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, that's still stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Note that the sum of the last three songs in the five-song selection are not simultaneously tracked as three-song record.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is understood that as the five-song machines do not display the sum tally of all five songs at the end, that the discretion and integrity of the TG referee is accepted for such submissions.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tenth, some song titles are listed in foreign wording.
[SPEAKER_09]: For example, a song called... Okay, what the hell is wrong with them?
[SPEAKER_02]: They put this... There's a song called Kamumei.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, the song is fucking Kakumei.
[SPEAKER_09]: It means revolution.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, first of all... But you're allowed to play Kamumi.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're allowed to play Kamumi.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, you want to know what I'm going to do tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Except that I have work tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, I got a job.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anyway, I'm going to be drafting a letter to these stupid fucks.
[SPEAKER_09]: I love this.
[SPEAKER_17]: In the chat room right now, they're all going, rebel, rebel, rebel, rebel, rebel, rebel, rebel.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, these people are idiots.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm going to be drafting a letter.
[SPEAKER_09]: Going item by item.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why they are wrong.
[SPEAKER_17]: Black Lab suggested the same thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's with you on that.
[SPEAKER_17]: You need to get a mob together.
[SPEAKER_09]: What if we draft up, you know, we get a few people.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm talking, give me a speak on my phone.
[SPEAKER_09]: We get the people together, we draft a letter, have all of us who were agreed with this sign it and send it in to them to let them know exactly how stupid they are.
[SPEAKER_16]: By the way, if you all take screenshots of us playing the game and all beating that score... Bring the digital camera!
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, we've got to keep going here because they have their specific rules submissions here.
[SPEAKER_17]: We might just post about this later, so we're going to keep going with this.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is the player's responsibility to inform the TG referee what the recognized name of such songs are because they're stupid.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, that being said, I look forward to refereeing future game attempts by Damien and anyone else wishing to compete in this highly popular modern arcade release.
[SPEAKER_09]: And this person puts their stupid name on the site.
[SPEAKER_09]: And their phone number.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_09]: And their email address.
[SPEAKER_17]: By the way, he's the Star Wars arcade champion.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should, do we have this link in the chatroom?
[SPEAKER_17]: Unfortunately, yeah, I believe we did post this in the chatroom, but if they don't, I did say it was on twingalaxies.com, but if they want to see this article for themselves, there it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just posted a link in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_17]: Uh, yeah, we gotta crank call this shit out.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_17]: Don't crank call.
[SPEAKER_17]: Be professional.
[SPEAKER_17]: Everybody, be professional.
[SPEAKER_17]: I believe I was reading now.
[SPEAKER_17]: It wasn't on this page.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought it was on this page.
[SPEAKER_17]: But I guess it's not.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can videotape it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can't take pictures because those could be altered.
[SPEAKER_17]: But you can videotape it.
[SPEAKER_17]: So all we've got to do is get a camera and we can videotape the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would be willing to go out there with a camera and tape one, both of you guys breaking the record.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_17]: And everybody in the chat room is already wanting to go do it too.
[SPEAKER_17]: So they might beat us to it.
[SPEAKER_17]: But if you guys want to be lazy, you don't want to bother with this, we're going to do it.
[SPEAKER_17]: This week...
[SPEAKER_17]: Watch as DarkSakura, Loki, and Sky all smash the world record and submit our videotape.
[SPEAKER_17]: You in on this too, Bradley?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I'm that good.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bradley, Bradley, a five-year-old is that good.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're that good, trust me.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let me just add, I couldn't PA to save my life, so this ought to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_16]: If I beat this, this guy really sucks.
[SPEAKER_17]: so not only will you be seeing us all smashing the world record but we'll be submitting an open letter and we'll post about that on our website this week sometime we'll post where you can also add your name to the letter or something we'll figure something else
[SPEAKER_04]: And if I could send them the link to Konami's 7th Mix ranking page, probably hundreds of people have already beaten that score.
[SPEAKER_04]: A zillion people have beaten that score.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should probably go ahead and get that pulled up.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're going to pull up what?
[SPEAKER_17]: What site are you pulling up?
[SPEAKER_09]: Internet Ranking.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, here, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let me do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Actually, I wanted to check some of these private messages real fast because there's some things going on here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, nothing new there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Playing it on one speed, you know, that's standard.
[SPEAKER_09]: How is that hard?
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, how is that hard?
[SPEAKER_17]: I believe...
[SPEAKER_17]: SoCal Kicks was already submitting a score at Bachelorette School.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, that's only $185 million from what I see.
[SPEAKER_17]: That wouldn't do it, but that's only... See, that's Max.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a problem.
[SPEAKER_17]: Max 2 and Max grade differently, so you're not going to be able to get a score on Max that beats it because they grade completely differently.
[SPEAKER_17]: But he just wants to show off that he's elite, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, and AaronJapan.com has some great stuff, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Black Lab wants to break the record too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Black Lab, come with us.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're local.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can come with us and break the record with us.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we're all going to break the world record and be the latest DDR players in history.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, Black Lab's like, when and where?
[SPEAKER_17]: If I had a video camera in this house, I would go out to Scandia tonight after the show because they don't close until 10 and we'd be able to make it out there.
[SPEAKER_17]: But unfortunately, we'll have to do this tomorrow or sometime during the week and figure that out.
[SPEAKER_17]: 23rd Magus wants to point out a hedgehog sleeping in a wet paper bag could beat that score.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we want to pull up 7th Mixed Internet Ranking?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_17]: The only problem with Internet Ranking, if I remember right, it tracks the percentages, right?
[SPEAKER_17]: Not the actual scores?
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, it is scores.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, I have to find Max2, there it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, here's the Max2 site, and now I'm looking for internet ranking.
[SPEAKER_17]: Help me read some Japanese here, there it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Here we go, Max internet ranking, ranky.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to find out the real world champion here.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see, what, do we hold up for one of these, one of those stuff, keep going, keep going, keep going?
[SPEAKER_17]: What, just any one of these, or what?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, they don't have scores!
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, they don't have the charts anymore, that's the problem.
[SPEAKER_17]: Aw, well, shit on Konami.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shit on Konami for not having the scores, oh well.
[SPEAKER_17]: But trust me, they were much better than that.
[SPEAKER_17]: We guarantee it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Maybe, oh, maybe I can get it from up here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, don't do, uh, the Onis, keep going.
[SPEAKER_17]: Where do I go?
[SPEAKER_17]: Go down to these?
[SPEAKER_16]: Down to those, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, there we go.
[SPEAKER_17]: On one of these, let's see, 139,576,495, no that's not high enough, but these songs aren't hard enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: I bet if I go down to like number 15...
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, here's a documented score right here.
401,845,325.
[SPEAKER_17]: That already puts that other score to shame, so... All these other scores, look at that, they're all higher.
[SPEAKER_17]: And this is a certain set of songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're probably not even all nine-footers.
[SPEAKER_04]: And actually... Those are probably just three songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually, that's including the extra stages.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, including the extra stages.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Kakumei.
[SPEAKER_17]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well...
[SPEAKER_17]: Poo on Twin Galaxies
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to take a real quick break, but this break is going to be special.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to play some original works during this break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki has a new one he's going to play for us, so we're going to get that in.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I wanted to get a new artist in who hasn't been featured on this show yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just have to pull up his song here.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is Takeout Kid, and he's got a song called, it looks like Donkey Kong Remix is the name of it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Perhaps he'll elaborate on that in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_17]: He's in there right now.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we're going to play that creation by him.
[SPEAKER_17]: and then we're going to... I wanted to plug his website.
[SPEAKER_17]: He wanted me to plug his site for playing this.
[SPEAKER_17]: His site, if you like what you hear, is at www.mp3.com slash liquidkid and he can post that in the chat room if he wants.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to hear that.
[SPEAKER_17]: and then we're going to hear another bit from Loki and you want to introduce the song that you're going to be doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, this was going to be an actual Paranoia remix but it didn't work out that way so it's something else entirely.
[SPEAKER_16]: I think I was calling it like Shadow Style or something like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, so we're going to do some originals this break and when we come back more talk and venting and the typical kind of anger you'd expect from Orange Lounge Radio.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching
[SPEAKER_00]: After listening to three hours of them, you'll want to ski into a tree headfirst.
[SPEAKER_00]: Undersedation Live with Travis, Rob, and Jessica.
[SPEAKER_00]: Saturdays, 6.30pm to 9.30pm Pacific Standard Time at UndersedationLive.org.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Bitch, get a new song.
[SPEAKER_13]: An open letter from Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 14.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we've been going off on TwinGalaxies.com and their completely made-of-ass ranking system for Max 2.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is one word, two syllables.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Inane.
[SPEAKER_17]: and we're all on a rampage to go beat that sometime this week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Black Lab and Dark Tetsuya over the break, by the way, have also joined in on our campaign.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are all going to go and smash the world record this week sometime.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we're not doing it to be mean.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're just, well, yeah, we're doing it to be mean.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're doing it to make a point.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, my God.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's like saying, you know, I'm the best kid on the planet because my mommy loves me best.
[SPEAKER_17]: Honestly, it's like, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Follow up to last week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Last week we were going off about Naoki's diary.
[SPEAKER_09]: Today I decided I wanted to be a woman.
[SPEAKER_17]: and all sorts of fun dear diaries were submitted by the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_17]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's take some more.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you guys in the chatroom have more diaries... It's been a week.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you have some more diary entries, if you think Naoki has some more diary things that he's written that he's maybe just not sharing with us, give us some diary entries.
[SPEAKER_17]: Submit them to us in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just send me a PM, your best Naoki diary entry, and we'll read some more tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, I don't think that they can see that you're waving your hand.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, come on...
[SPEAKER_09]: Wave of hand bringing towards me By the way In defense of Rob Because I can read the kana in it In Naoki's diary It did have Be-Mani Spelled out with the kana Be, the extending kana Ma, and Ni So it's Be-Mani According to Naoki, it's Be-Mani Be-Mani Radio Program So don't be a bee-itch about it
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, let's read what Naoki wrote this last week in his diary, shall we say?
[SPEAKER_16]: Your diary.
[SPEAKER_16]: I've decided to let Paul Oteri write the music and I'm gonna sing!
[SPEAKER_16]: You could probably do a better job.
[SPEAKER_17]: Naoki's diary.
[SPEAKER_17]: Time has... Oh wait, we need some music, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's find some music.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's find some good Naoki music.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's do Journey to Wonderland.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's make that be Naoki's diary.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's not a Naoki song, but it's funny.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's what's important.
[SPEAKER_17]: Time has gone.
[SPEAKER_17]: These days, music games are as common as dirt.
[SPEAKER_17]: But when DDR started in 1998, DDR seemed like the hardest thing in the world to work on.
[SPEAKER_17]: Even looking back on it today, I feel exhausted just to try to remember it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now it feels like a sleeping memory deep in my heart.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's going to be the next Naoki song, by the way, deep in my heart.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, there was still in my heart.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, you know, deep and dive and whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dive into the butt.
[SPEAKER_17]: When we began work on DDR, I started writing four pieces of music for the game.
[SPEAKER_17]: But as production advanced and the public waited for the release of DDR, only one of my songs, Paranoia, was included in the game, and a major collaboration was formed with Hoshiba EMI's Dance Mania compilation series in order to provide the rest of the music.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, if I remember correct, wasn't Brilliant to you in the first DDR?
[SPEAKER_17]: Did he just... Oh, it's just 1.5?
[SPEAKER_16]: Uh, hello, what about Trip Machine?
[SPEAKER_16]: That's still him anyways.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, wait!
[SPEAKER_16]: He's not Desire.
[SPEAKER_16]: Not Desire.
[SPEAKER_17]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Naoki's getting forgetful as he's getting old.
[SPEAKER_16]: He's got Alzheimer's.
[SPEAKER_16]: Technically it wasn't the Naoki personality, it was the Desire personality that wrote that song.
[SPEAKER_16]: So obviously he wouldn't have a recollection of that one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: The other songs were put on the shelf, and although I was the only person in the world to hear them, they didn't go to waste.
[SPEAKER_17]: The DDR Max 2 song, D2R, was based on some of the songs left out of the original DDR game.
[SPEAKER_17]: D2R!
[SPEAKER_16]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_16]: There's more that's going to sound like brilliant to you.
[SPEAKER_17]: You may think of Paranoia as a song that most people fondly remember, but in fact it was something I was forced to make under many restrictions.
[SPEAKER_17]: The end result is a song that felt very underground slash urban.
[SPEAKER_17]: These days, my music is very different.
[SPEAKER_17]: The Royal Route high-energy dance songs, such as Brilliant To You, Can't Stop Falling In Love, etc., are my new forte, and although I much prefer them, the underground style was a projection point in terms of my music.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rob, when was Brilliant To You a new style?
[SPEAKER_14]: Wasn't that like 1.5?
[SPEAKER_14]: He's talking about 1.5, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, but he's like, my new style was Brilliant To You.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: I know, Dave, I know.
[SPEAKER_17]: These days I still try to develop the underground style using the Revenge and Desire labels.
[SPEAKER_17]: Paranoia, Trip Machine, and Make It Better appeared in DDR Internet Ranking Kit.
[SPEAKER_17]: 1.5, and with every maiden voyage, trial, error, and conflict always appeared from time to time.
[SPEAKER_17]: Although my music has moved on and evolved, I still look back on these three songs and realize that if they hadn't existed, much of my current music wouldn't be possible.
[SPEAKER_17]: In the grand scale of things, these songs are very important to me in my career, especially when I remember the pressure I was under when I produced them.
[SPEAKER_17]: With the songs completed, and DDR only... Is that Taco Bell coming back up or something there, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_17]: With the songs completed and DDR only several months from release, I took a deep breathe and prepared to face the next challenge, DDR second mix.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's read some of the submitted things, shall we?
[SPEAKER_17]: That was it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, it also revealed that the Max 3 song, there's going to be a B4U song called Graduation.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_17]: Shock of shocks.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh my god, B4U and Max 3.
[SPEAKER_16]: I was expecting that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Naoki himself, which I believe is just the 23rd Magus Disguise, but we won't say anything.
[SPEAKER_17]: Naoki himself says, Dear Diary, my newest song is called Dynamite Afronova BD24UR Trip Machine Deeper and Deeper Eternal Rebirth Evolution KZ Dirty Mix.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_09]: I'll buy that for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_17]: DJ Konami says this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, I've made a kickin' tune for the next DJ Konami tune.
[SPEAKER_17]: He seemed kind of reluctant to use it, though.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, more B4U crap coming soon in Max 3.
[SPEAKER_17]: Enjoy!
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, I am done with the extra states for Max 3.
[SPEAKER_17]: It is called Max 3.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am the king of the originality.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dear Diary, I make music so people like me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks, you, bye.
[SPEAKER_17]: TwinSenses, Dear Diary, today I earned the world record in DDR Max 2 with a score of 315,802,020 points.
[SPEAKER_17]: I am the best because my mommy and Paula Terry love me.
[SPEAKER_17]: Praise me!
[SPEAKER_17]: Biter.
[SPEAKER_17]: SoCalKicks submits a follow-up to last week.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, my English, I would like to know what this blow is.
[SPEAKER_17]: And if you missed last week's show, you're just going to have to wait 11 weeks for it to turn up in the rebroadcast.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear Naoki, to find out what the blow is, take your vacuum cleaner and stick it on your groin.
[SPEAKER_09]: Press the on button.
[SPEAKER_09]: She's gone from suck to blow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, I hate my life and want to die
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, after he told me I still wanted it, I knew he would do a better job than Paula.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you, SirDuckX.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dartetsuya says, Dear Diary, I'm having B4U remixed Let Them Move for DDR Max 3.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_09]: Then it would be even more out of tune, just with more people singing it.
[SPEAKER_17]: How about a sim update, Loki?
[SPEAKER_17]: You want to talk about what's going on in the sim world?
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, actually quite a bit's going to be happening next week.
[SPEAKER_16]: We have the site opening again of Team Guilo, so they're going to be coming up on Tuesday.
[SPEAKER_16]: So everyone look for that on October 1st there.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know what the website's going to be, probably Team Guilo, but...
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know yet, because they haven't really gotten a host name.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, we'll have to wait for that.
[SPEAKER_16]: And then also, I've heard rumors that the Melting Pot's going to be coming back up in about a couple weeks, too.
[SPEAKER_16]: So, we'll have to watch for that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Other than that, still waiting for StepMania Beta 6.
[SPEAKER_16]: DWI, it's been quiet, so don't know anything coming out for that.
[SPEAKER_16]: Don't really care.
[SPEAKER_16]: Kind of abandoned them.
[SPEAKER_16]: Other than that, there is some major news.
[SPEAKER_16]: The Tourney Mix 2's done.
[SPEAKER_16]: and we have results somewhere.
[SPEAKER_16]: We can pull them up.
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, I suppose I can do that.
[SPEAKER_16]: We had some locals win.
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm excited for them.
[SPEAKER_16]: We need to get them on the show so they can brag.
[SPEAKER_16]: DJ DropForce
[SPEAKER_16]: SoDeep Wire Remix was third place, and that was done by the Sacramento's Agent Chang.
[SPEAKER_16]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, we're playing favorites.
[SPEAKER_16]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_16]: For standard, the official placing was Klung Klung 1655 from Keyboard Mania.
[SPEAKER_16]: That got first.
[SPEAKER_17]: That was some of the Seattle folks that did that, I believe.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't remember the exact names, but I just know they're on that board over there.
[SPEAKER_16]: Second place was Flying to Your Soul.
[SPEAKER_16]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_16]: and third place was The Great Giana Sisters, which was pretty good from what I played.
[SPEAKER_16]: Now Public, this is what was actually voted on by the users themselves and not the judges.
[SPEAKER_16]: First place went to So Deep Choir Remix, which was, you know, our Agent Chang.
[SPEAKER_16]: Second place was Heaven.
[SPEAKER_16]: Third place was QQQ, and that was done by...
[SPEAKER_16]: Mooglehunter, Standard, The Great Gianna Sisters, 1 for 1st, M, The Fake 8th Style Song, 1 for 2nd, and Klung Klung 1655, 1 for 3rd.
[SPEAKER_16]: Woohoo!
[SPEAKER_17]: Congratulations to all the winners!
[SPEAKER_16]: Um, Tourney Mix 3 is gonna be, has been announced for December, they're gonna be doing that, so rules and stuff will be coming out in November.
[SPEAKER_16]: So look at that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh... Congrats you!
[SPEAKER_17]: Hold on, SoCalKicks had a, uh, his diary entry got chopped up, that's why it didn't make much sense, so I'm going to, uh, pull up the rest of his diary entry.
[SPEAKER_17]: He sent it over... Ooh.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_17]: I opened up a picture of Jenny Rom, my bad.
[SPEAKER_09]: I was about to say, I'm scared.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, this is from SoCalKicks, Naoki Diary.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Diary, my hipster experimentation did not go as well as planned.
[SPEAKER_17]: Paula begged me not to go, saying she would give me this blow and that she could do a better job.
[SPEAKER_17]: But the way she said it, I don't even think that she knows what this blow is anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: So I continued to go seek this white American who was going to give me the true form of this blow.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, I quickly made it to Northern California where this orange site is based, so it says.
[SPEAKER_17]: And my research finally led me to an address.
[SPEAKER_17]: I knocked on the door and said...
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, I am American hipster, knows Naoki, before I finish the rest of my English.
[SPEAKER_17]: I would like to know what this blow is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, after he told me, I still wanted it.
[SPEAKER_17]: I knew he would do a better job than Paula.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks, G. Thanks.
[SPEAKER_09]: Shine get!
[SPEAKER_17]: I get random, I get these random PMs for people.
[SPEAKER_17]: I just got one that says shine get.
[SPEAKER_17]: These people are weird.
[SPEAKER_16]: So now your little thing under your name on the website could be, gives a better blow than Politary.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, maybe we should do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Better blowing than Pol... Can you arrange that for me, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, thank you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, Pyro Man sent another one before he left.
[SPEAKER_17]: Dear Santa, I want a new Politary for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_17]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think that Politary's a fembot.
[SPEAKER_17]: You think Politary's a fembot, huh?
[SPEAKER_17]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what we just did?
[SPEAKER_17]: We just opened the door for people to send us random shit over private message.
[SPEAKER_14]: Her along with the B4U girls and Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're all friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: Especially Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, we're going to take a quick... Yes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_16]: New DDRPC characters.
[SPEAKER_16]: What the hell were they thinking?
[SPEAKER_17]: It's the gay and lesbian team.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know if you noticed.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's like bondage goth people.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't even know what the hell it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: The chick's a total dyke.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know about the guy, but I'm just assuming it's the gay and lesbian team for DDRPC.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hold on, let me pull it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's very scary.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to konamihwi.com slash ddrpc because that's where I can download all the newest and greatest characters.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm going to link that in the chat room for you folks because I like you.
[SPEAKER_17]: And they are called Kobe and Nikki.
[SPEAKER_17]: And you can see Kobe is a cop.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Nicky's just a dyke.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know how else to explain Nicky.
[SPEAKER_16]: Yeah, but I didn't know cops wore spiked hats with little skulls.
[SPEAKER_17]: And he's already got the handcuffs on.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's already ready to bust you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to tie you up.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm going to tie you up.
[SPEAKER_14]: And he's wearing bubbles on his shirt.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the next four characters are all like, the construction worker is the next one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, we're waiting for the construction worker, then the Indian, then we're going to have the leather daddy.
[SPEAKER_17]: I bet you anything the Jason Enos one's going to be Leather Daddy.
[SPEAKER_17]: No.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_17]: But the rumor is that the Jason Enos one's going to be the last character.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's been spread like wildfire everywhere.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: Of course, the chat room's saying that Kobe and Nikki are probably supposed to be ravers or clubbers.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, big gay ravers and clubbers.
[SPEAKER_17]: And apparently Jenny Rom... Jenny Rom is a sliver slut.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sliver slut.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, we're going to take a real... Oh, do you want to... Well, okay, we're going to take a quick break and then we're going to come back and by popular demand in the chat room, they're begging us to do it tonight because we haven't done it in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to do a listless segment tonight for you guys.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to do...
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, we're going to do that.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then at the end of the show, Jamie's going to give us the update on the big, big, big tournament we're going to do here in Sacramento that Orange Lounge is one of the many co-sponsors of called Shaft.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sacramento hosts another fabulous tournament, and Jamie's got all the details for you guys.
[SPEAKER_09]: By the way, DJ Konami, no Kyle Snyder, please.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's going to be no Kyle Snyder character in DDRPC, sorry.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to be doing the DDR shaft update before the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're also going to do list list for best B-Mani artist.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we'll be making our list during this break.
[SPEAKER_17]: So stick around.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stay for our break before we break you.
[SPEAKER_17]: Stick around because we're going to be right back.
[SPEAKER_09]: Break down.
[SPEAKER_17]: Break down.
[SPEAKER_17]: In fact, I'm saying stick around so much I think I'm just going to play that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll be your dancing flower, dancing, I'll be your dancing señorita, oh oh
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Good to see you dancing in the life of the best that's keeping you so tight So tell me, senorita, what makes you feel the hardest?
[SPEAKER_07]: Give me, like you know, don't wait no more and touch me I just wanna feel the skin around me I just wanna be your señorita Don't go, getting too seated, I'm so hot for your love Boy, you gotta get a chance to try me I'll be just like you, I'm a bonita I'm going after your feelings, tell me I'm not afraid of what can be
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: From Step Squad to Orange Lounge, this PDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_07]: Holla!
[SPEAKER_07]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_17]: TTPO You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 14, and we're getting ready to do our list list.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're kind of having a little bit of debate.
[SPEAKER_17]: During the break, while people were trying to make our lists here in the studio, trying to think if a singer should be considered a Bamani artist.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, could you say Sana on your list?
[SPEAKER_17]: So, Brad was in here kind of... You've got to talk into the mic.
[SPEAKER_15]: Or something like Paula Terry, because she doesn't, as far as I know, doesn't write anything.
[SPEAKER_09]: I still count performers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_15]: I wouldn't consider them an artist.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_17]: of erotic dancing.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, you know, even though she doesn't really write her stuff.
[SPEAKER_17]: I have to make one quick amendment to the sim update, too.
[SPEAKER_17]: Feet of Fury was pushed back to October 15th.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's the Dreamcast one.
[SPEAKER_17]: And there is a video on the site over at CAgames.com.
[SPEAKER_17]: Looks interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Kind of looks like Disney's Dance Magic mode a little bit.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's going to be interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's an interesting idea, anyway.
[SPEAKER_17]: So here we go.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're doing a list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Who's participating in today's list?
[SPEAKER_17]: I know I am.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki is.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Bradley?
[SPEAKER_17]: Bradley is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, Brad, you're doing one, too?
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, well, then we've got five people on the list today.
[SPEAKER_17]: It'll be a fat, big list.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, we're doing three choices apiece.
[SPEAKER_17]: You got three?
[SPEAKER_17]: You better hurry up, Brad.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll do you last, okay?
[SPEAKER_09]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not like that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Not like that.
[SPEAKER_17]: Boy.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie, let's start with you.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's your number three pick for favorite Bomani performer ever, ever, ever?
[SPEAKER_09]: Osama Kubota.
[SPEAKER_17]: Osama Kubota.
[SPEAKER_09]: Osamu.
[SPEAKER_09]: Do not insult him.
[SPEAKER_17]: Any reasons why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Presto.
[SPEAKER_09]: Need I say anything more?
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Presto.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: And not to mention his Nanbe Mani stuff is absolutely gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I kind of forgot that it's performed.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not... Because, you know, Presto is like a famous song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Classical.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm still referring to his rendition of it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I know.
That's fine.
[SPEAKER_09]: Next.
[SPEAKER_17]: Chat room is... Okay, never mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're settling that debate in there internally.
[SPEAKER_17]: Somebody was saying Osamu Kobota is a girl, but it's a guy with long hair.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's a guy with long hair.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, Loki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, it's a guy's name.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki, your number three choice.
[SPEAKER_16]: Ryo Nagumi.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_16]: Naguma.
[SPEAKER_16]: Nagumo.
[SPEAKER_16]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: You got to spell that for me, buddy.
[SPEAKER_17]: Brad, spell that for me so I can type it.
[SPEAKER_15]: That is R-E-O space N-A-G-U-M-O.
[SPEAKER_16]: And what did they do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Everything.
[SPEAKER_16]: He did 20 November and all those kickass things.
[SPEAKER_16]: Instant love.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_16]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're saying that's DJ Naguro, same person.
[SPEAKER_17]: However, we did make the rule in here that people's multiple egos would not fall under their name.
[SPEAKER_17]: So Naoki will not count for everything.
[SPEAKER_17]: You either gotta put Revenge or Naoki Underground or whatever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Naoki doesn't count for everything.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, yes, Brad, you got a number three choice yet?
[SPEAKER_17]: No, we're going to Bradley.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bradley, number three.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will say Revenge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Revenge, because you like all their songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Good choice.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Revenge is the extra stage song, the special extra stage song, if you like AAA or 7, maybe it has to be a flashing 7, another.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's called Sakura.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a spritule, because they misspelled it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any comments from DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm never going to be able to play that damn song.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: My number three choice, and this should come as no surprise for me, but maybe that I put it so low on my list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Number three, Erotic, of course.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bestest Bomani band ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Well, third bestest Bomani band ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't care what you say.
[SPEAKER_17]: Chatroom is begging that one of us put down Jenny Rom.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't know if anybody will see.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, Brad.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, well, since Matt got my number three, Riro Nagumo, I'm going to have to go with Naoki Naoki, alright Any particular reason why?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, it was neck and neck with Taka, DJ Taka and Naoki But I think Naoki's been more responsible for a lot more of my favorite songs, so Alrighty, fair enough
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, that's our number three choices.
[SPEAKER_17]: On to the number twos.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Number two, well, I have a list here, and I'm thinking and thinking and thinking.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm actually going to say Bus Stop.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bus Stop.
[SPEAKER_09]: Because, okay, I like Long Train Runnin', and I liked, you know, Kick the Can.
[SPEAKER_09]: I really liked it when it was new.
[SPEAKER_09]: And I really dig their remixes.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, they take some of the things you don't really expect and make really good remixes.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, I'm going to defend for you, uh...
[SPEAKER_15]: Na-na-na-na
[SPEAKER_09]: Don't forget about how many people were trying to do the Pee Wee Herman Tequila dance.
[SPEAKER_17]: Very true, very true.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, Loki, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_16]: My number two pick has to go with Desire, because I love Chirp Machine.
[SPEAKER_16]: Desire.
[SPEAKER_16]: Sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we got Revenge and Desire both on this list.
[SPEAKER_17]: That'll be interesting.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bradley, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_17]: Good Cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's a good choice.
[SPEAKER_17]: Good Call on Good Cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, my number two choice.
[SPEAKER_17]: Any particular reason why?
[SPEAKER_17]: Good, cool?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they have a lot of good songs.
[SPEAKER_17]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: I do not want the nerd that fell on the floor.
[SPEAKER_17]: You can eat it.
[SPEAKER_17]: My number two choice, of course, duh, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge is my number two choice.
[SPEAKER_17]: And, come on, duh.
[SPEAKER_17]: I don't have to explain why.
[SPEAKER_17]: If I have to explain why, you're a retard.
[SPEAKER_17]: Brad, you're number two choice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Why is it your favorite?
[SPEAKER_17]: I really do dig their song.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, not only did it make a catchy title for the show, but obviously we picked it because they've got some good shit.
[SPEAKER_17]: Like, Mobomoga's a great song, retrospective song.
[SPEAKER_17]: And the videos.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think the videos have a lot to do with it.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're cute!
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, yes, Orange Lounge, rules.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anyway, Brad, you're number two choice.
[SPEAKER_15]: What are we doing here?
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, my number two is Akira Yamaoka.
[SPEAKER_17]: Ah, good one, Akira Yamaoka, except for 250 BPM, but... Akira.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yeah, spell the last name for me, I don't want to F it up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, Y-A-M-A, okay.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, any other, any particular reason why?
[SPEAKER_15]: Pretty much everything Akira Yamaoka has done, yeah, I feel, oh my god, that's a great song.
[SPEAKER_15]: But, yeah, pretty much everything, except, you're right, 250 BPM is kind of a shit song, but everything else has been wonderful.
[SPEAKER_15]: Okay, there you go.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Jamie, number one pick.
[SPEAKER_09]: This will come as a surprise to absolutely no one.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is my number one choice.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tack.
[SPEAKER_09]: Rob had it typed out before I said it.
[SPEAKER_09]: For people who know me, I have been quoted as saying that if I don't marry Dan, I'm going to marry Tack or Margaret Cho.
[SPEAKER_09]: So, that's basically... Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_09]: You know, everything he's done, except for stoic, has made me absolutely orgasmic.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, but Tech has Tran as it shows in the Stoic video.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's his girlfriend now.
[SPEAKER_09]: But Stoic is boring.
[SPEAKER_09]: Stoic is a boring song.
[SPEAKER_09]: And the video is kind of boring too.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, every other thing he's done, especially like his... I've been listening to a lot of that song, what is it, Bar Morgengrau?
[SPEAKER_09]: That song is really awesome.
[SPEAKER_17]: Chatroom is arguing with you on Stoic.
[SPEAKER_09]: This is my opinion.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't care for stoic.
[SPEAKER_09]: However, Gravity is awesome.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's Schlagwerk.
[SPEAKER_09]: Holic.
[SPEAKER_09]: The thing is, I had the site up on Sekbimani.com, however, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: I need to find what the new official tag site is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Last I checked, he had five of his original pieces for download.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you can't find the site, for people who actually know me, I'll make sure that they're made available since he had them up public on his site.
[SPEAKER_17]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: 23rd Magus would like you to know that Tomorrow Perfume makes a mess of pants.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's see here.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: You didn't write this down.
[SPEAKER_17]: You're just pulling this out of your ass here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Well, no, I see what Brad has, and I don't want to say it because that was going to be my number one pick.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right, what's yours?
[SPEAKER_16]: No, no, you can keep yours.
[SPEAKER_16]: So I'm going to have to go with...
[SPEAKER_16]: Oh, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going to pick one that's going to get eliminated anyways.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_16]: I'm going with NW260.
[SPEAKER_02]: NW260?
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: The number one of a money band?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, you lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_03]: Dropout.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: You lost.
[SPEAKER_03]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_16]: Can I get all the numbers and all the Roman numerals?
[SPEAKER_16]: All the Roman, like, you know.
[SPEAKER_16]: I want all the numbers.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, whatever.
[SPEAKER_16]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_16]: You changed your mind?
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright, he changed his mind.
[SPEAKER_17]: Goodbye, NW260.
[SPEAKER_16]: We're going to put in a real one here.
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's go with Captain Jack.
[SPEAKER_03]: Captain Jack!
[SPEAKER_03]: Good idea, Captain Jack.
[SPEAKER_09]: And why do you like Captain Jack?
[SPEAKER_16]: because, I don't know, because he sucks.
[SPEAKER_16]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_16]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: He does have that butt-ugly hoochie model with him.
[SPEAKER_17]: I thought you didn't like ugly people, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_16]: I didn't like Captain Jack, but his Captain Jack video had a lot of women in wet t-shirts.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, good point.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, chat room is getting very angry with us on our choices here.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's some interesting things that haven't turned up yet, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Change mine.
[SPEAKER_17]: No, come on, you just said it.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do you want to change it to?
[SPEAKER_17]: Taka.
[SPEAKER_17]: Taka?
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, okay, wait, let's see if somebody else does it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Let's see if somebody else does it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, next one is Bradley.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was originally going to say Taka, but of course she took it, so I'll say DJ Taka.
[SPEAKER_04]: DJ Taka, all right.
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to be very surprised if Taka didn't turn up somewhere, but there it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bradley put down Taka as his number one choice.
[SPEAKER_17]: My number one choice, Vincent Damore.
[SPEAKER_17]: No question.
[SPEAKER_17]: Vincent Damore is my absolute favorite Bomani artist, and if you don't like that, you can suck it.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's a good one.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Brad, your number one choice.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, since I knew, you know, before that Jamie was going to pick TAC, so, because that would have been my first, because everything TAC comes out with makes me cream.
[SPEAKER_02]: You all have this game rigged.
[SPEAKER_02]: You all are picking what the others are going to pick.
[SPEAKER_15]: So, instead of TAC, I picked LED, because also everything TAC ever does makes me cream.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, good pick, good pick, LED.
[SPEAKER_17]: I cream them in the...
[SPEAKER_17]: JB punches us all for not putting Jenny Rom on the list somewhere.
[SPEAKER_17]: Jenny Rom's the new SmileDK, haven't you heard?
[SPEAKER_02]: I would like to thank you all for not putting SmileDK on the list.
[SPEAKER_15]: Please, what does Jenny Rom do?
[SPEAKER_15]: Uh, Waka Laka.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_15]: Waka Laka...
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_17]: Yell about it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Now, this is going to be hard.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anything that gets taken off this list is going to cause some people to get nasty.
[SPEAKER_17]: So this is going to be a fun one.
[SPEAKER_17]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is the full list we've got so far.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have Usamo Kubota, Reo Nagumo, Revenge, Erotic, Naoki, Bus Stop, Desire, Good Cool, Orange Lounge, Akira Yamaoka,
[SPEAKER_17]: Yamaoka, Tak, Captain Jack, Taka, Vincent Damore, and L.E.D.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is going to be tricky.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Naoki just encompasses stuff that goes under Naoki, nothing else, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, you got it.
[SPEAKER_15]: Right, but we'll remember, well, that's... Naoki Underground is still Naoki, so we should go with that.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm not talking about, like, Desire as in Naoki or other Naoki monikers, but Naoki Underground is still Naoki.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll go ahead and start our vote off the list.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Jamie, take it off.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's going?
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate shirt machines, so take off Desire.
[SPEAKER_17]: Desire is off the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: There is only one version of Trip Machine that I've liked, and that's the jungle one.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is going to get dirty.
[SPEAKER_17]: I mean, this is going to be bad.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right.
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, Matt.
[SPEAKER_17]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_16]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_16]: Say goodbye, Naoki.
[SPEAKER_16]: You suck.
[SPEAKER_17]: Naoki is coming off the list.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm not surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear Diary, today some guy in America is going to be off the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: Dear Diary, I hate America.
[SPEAKER_09]: My feelings are hurt, so I took a bubble bath.
[SPEAKER_09]: Calcutta, take me away.
[SPEAKER_09]: Bradley.
[SPEAKER_17]: Bradley, what's coming up?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, since he's only done one song in all of Omani, Captain Jack's.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_02]: One song in all of Omani?
[SPEAKER_02]: He's one of the major people.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Race, Little Boy, Captain Jack, In the Navy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is it still going?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that still your point?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Captain Jack's gone.
[SPEAKER_09]: Goodbye, Captain Jack.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, God, this is hard.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is hard.
[SPEAKER_17]: I really don't know.
[SPEAKER_17]: This is hard, but I'm going to have to take Akira Yamakawa off the list.
[SPEAKER_09]: And Brad has a heart attack.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, Brad.
[SPEAKER_15]: What's left?
[SPEAKER_15]: Your last one.
[SPEAKER_15]: There's no revenge.
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yep, there it is.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_15]: Goodbye, erotic.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, you asshole.
[SPEAKER_09]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_09]: He's going to cut you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to cut you.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going to cut you deep.
[SPEAKER_09]: So let's go ahead and read off the list then for our... I have to post this in the chat room real fast before you read.
[SPEAKER_09]: Gorgeous and lovely chat.
[SPEAKER_09]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_17]: I actually have to close all my private message windows because people are about ready to vote here.
[SPEAKER_17]: So once...
[SPEAKER_17]: Here it goes.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's the list, and you can send me your votes over private message, and Jamie's going to read it off for you right now, for those of you that aren't in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Osamu Kubota, Rea Nagumo.
[SPEAKER_17]: How did that one survive?
[SPEAKER_17]: I was going to take that one off, but I figured someone else would.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have Revenge, Bus Stop, Good Cool, Orange Lounge, Tack, DJ Taka, Vincent Damore, and L.E.D.,
[SPEAKER_17]: So there it is.
[SPEAKER_17]: You've got to pick your absolute favorite and send it to me over private message.
[SPEAKER_17]: And we're going to take a really quick break.
[SPEAKER_17]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_09]: Absolute, since you said absolute.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to do absolute because I said absolute?
[SPEAKER_17]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: Send your votes in right now here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to take about four minutes.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll do two songs because this is a hard decision for you guys.
[SPEAKER_17]: And then we're going to come back, read the results, and end the show because we're already at 855.
[SPEAKER_17]: So here we go on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_17]: Vote now.
[SPEAKER_17]: Vote now, now, now, now.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter V, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, we are back, and I'm trying to prep to go off the air here, but I'm getting very last minute here, but we are going to read the results of the...
[SPEAKER_17]: Best Bomani Artist Ever!
[SPEAKER_17]: So we've got the results here and I'm trying to... Sorry, I need a minute here.
[SPEAKER_17]: You know what, I'm going to have to throw on another song real fast because I'm trying to prep for the end of the show here and I'm not ready yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: So we're going to play something very fast and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_17]: Sorry for the inconvenience.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, hello.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thank you, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm trying to do about a million things at once here, but that's okay.
[SPEAKER_17]: We got it.
[SPEAKER_17]: We are back.
[SPEAKER_17]: And right at the end of the show, we're going to announce the best Bomani artist ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Third place was Orange Lounge for best Bomani artist ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'm happy for that one, because that's our namesake there.
[SPEAKER_17]: Orange Lounge, third best ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Second best Bomani artist ever.
[SPEAKER_17]: Good, cool.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good, cool.
[SPEAKER_17]: And first place, this ain't going to surprise a damn person, it won by an absolute landslide.
[SPEAKER_17]: First place, DJ Taka.
[SPEAKER_17]: Best Bomani artist ever, so there it is.
[SPEAKER_09]: Poo-poo on everybody who didn't vote for Tak.
[SPEAKER_17]: Nobody voted for Tak?
[SPEAKER_17]: Nobody voted for Revenge?
[SPEAKER_17]: Nobody voted for Osamu Kubota?
[SPEAKER_17]: I was kind of surprised.
[SPEAKER_09]: See, I should have taken Taka off so that everyone would vote for Tak.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, you would have been the evil bitch of Bomani.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, well that's it.
[SPEAKER_17]: Taka's winner.
[SPEAKER_09]: Just really briefly because we were supposed to do this much earlier.
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh yeah, the shaft update, please.
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll run a little long, they won't mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: Basically we've got the perfect attack rules already posted for the upcoming tournament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sac Mimani hosts another fabulous tournament that will be held at Sacramento Scandia on Hillsdale.
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got directions, we have maps, we have the address, we have everything up on...
[SPEAKER_09]: and SACBEMANI.com.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you go to S-A-C-B-E-M-A-N-I.com, there is a link for Shaft and that is the whole section dedicated to that.
[SPEAKER_09]: The only rules we have up are perfect attack right now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, to be specific, it's accuracy attack.
[SPEAKER_09]: It is not a true perfect attack.
[SPEAKER_09]: If it's true perfect attack, we're only gauging by perfects.
[SPEAKER_09]: So this is accuracy attack.
[SPEAKER_09]: We should have freestyle rules posted by the middle of the week as soon as they're finalized.
[SPEAKER_09]: So make sure you go there.
[SPEAKER_09]: We have a discussion going on with psychedbymoney.com forums, so be sure to keep your eye on it.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's also a thread on DDR Freak Under Tournament discussion.
[SPEAKER_17]: And I'm not just saying this because I'm involved with the planning of this, but honestly, this is going to be one of the biggest tournaments in history.
[SPEAKER_17]: It really will be.
[SPEAKER_17]: Assuming we get the participation for it, which it sounds like we're going to be getting a lot of support for this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Honestly, if you live far away, you live a ways away, this is going to be worth the trip.
[SPEAKER_17]: There's going to be prizes up the wazoo.
[SPEAKER_17]: We've got door prizes.
[SPEAKER_17]: We have some really cool door prizes.
[SPEAKER_17]: We can't even announce them yet.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're that good.
[SPEAKER_17]: So...
[SPEAKER_17]: We'll have to... And we've got Loki donating hundreds of dollars worth of DVDs as prizes.
[SPEAKER_09]: As door prizes.
[SPEAKER_17]: As door prizes.
[SPEAKER_17]: Anybody can win this.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just show up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Just show the fuck up.
[SPEAKER_17]: That's all you gotta do.
[SPEAKER_17]: So, definitely come to tournament November 9th at Sacramento Scandia.
[SPEAKER_17]: It's gonna be huge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Huge.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: And also the A-Team Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_17]: If you're not gonna come for anything else, come for the A-Team Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you wanna see what Freestyle was two years ago...
[SPEAKER_09]: We are having a blast from the past.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're having a team freestyle mode.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's limited entry.
[SPEAKER_09]: We're basically leaving it to, we want past winners of tournaments to participate in at first.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if we get enough entrants, we'll open it up.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_17]: Final thoughts from everybody in the room.
[SPEAKER_17]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_16]: I don't have any thoughts right now.
[SPEAKER_16]: Too much big stuff's happening next week, so we'll probably have a lot more to report on next week, so I can't wait.
[SPEAKER_16]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dave.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kuchaka rules.
[SPEAKER_14]: Steel drums.
[SPEAKER_14]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_17]: And Bradley.
[SPEAKER_17]: I need power!
[SPEAKER_17]: Power!
[SPEAKER_17]: I love Bradley's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_17]: My final thought is nothing.
[SPEAKER_17]: Absolutely nothing.
[SPEAKER_17]: And Jamie.
[SPEAKER_09]: Wheel of Morality, turn, turn, turn.
[SPEAKER_09]: Tell us the lesson that we should learn.
[SPEAKER_09]: And today's moral is... I have no morals.
[SPEAKER_09]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_09]: Let's just end the show.
[SPEAKER_17]: Alright, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_17]: We're going to end this show now.
[SPEAKER_17]: See you guys later.
[SPEAKER_17]: Thanks for listening.
[SPEAKER_13]: Finish her!
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.