[SPEAKER_23]: Put it in!
[SPEAKER_02]: You're tuned in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our live talk program begins now.
Boring.
[SPEAKER_15]: This video sucks!
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge may contain nudity.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hide Orange Lounge radio from the fucking children.
[SPEAKER_01]: The last Metroid is in captivity.
[SPEAKER_01]: The galaxy is at peace.
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess there's just two kinds of people, Miss Sandstone.
[SPEAKER_00]: My kind of people and assholes.
[SPEAKER_00]: One.
[SPEAKER_23]: Dear diary, my teen angst bullshit has a body count I would like
[SPEAKER_18]: DarkSakura, Sky, Orange Lounge Radio,
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio Episode 12
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio, we are live here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, shut up, baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: The world's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: How would you like it if I shoved you back in?
[SPEAKER_07]: So, hello to everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got a pretty full room here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to get hot in here very fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is why we have the lights out.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're viewing our webcam, which is at a top secret location, which you can only get in our chat room, then it's going to be very dark in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: All the images are dark because we don't want to start sweating in here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to turn into a sauna.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then we'll all have to take our clothes off and that'll be the nudity.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be the nudity.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dork!
[SPEAKER_07]: I would like to apologize for anyone listening to this on the archives because I didn't start the archive recording until that break, so you missed the intro of the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: But all we were basically saying in the intro was that Mel B and Melody are here tonight, Shark Skrull, Mel B, and all our usual crowd is here tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you didn't get to say hi yet, Brad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: He's just slurping.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, hey, Molly.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you do want to join our chatroom, figure out where that secret webcam is, all you've got to do is go to any other side IRC server like irc.eggheads.org and join Channel Pound Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wee.
[SPEAKER_07]: So how was your week off, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: You were gone for a little while.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, last week, weekend thingy, I went to a big gathering of a bunch of people, mostly a step squad, a few RTF, a taco outpost, just a bunch of people.
[SPEAKER_22]: We went bowling.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bowling's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I sucked so bad.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then I got to see the crappiest machine in the universe.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Stepping Sage.
Woo!
[SPEAKER_22]: I've never heard of... The most ghetto fabulous machine ever.
[SPEAKER_29]: I have never even heard of 76... It ain't even ghetto fabulous, it's just ghetto.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like ghetto ass.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Imagine you have a machine consisting of one large monitor in the center and two smaller monitors on either side.
[SPEAKER_22]: You have a panel, like any normal dancing stage, except you have two circles in the front, two on the side, and two in the back, making a sort of circle.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then you have two dots on the screen.
[SPEAKER_22]: and then whatever color goes up, you have to step on the corresponding color.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, I think it's like red at the top, yellow in the middle, and blue in the back or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weird, okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then you have the crappiest videos playing in the middle one.
[SPEAKER_22]: All it is, is like, okay, you know at Great America, the karaoke, well, not the one that you actually sing with, the make your own video thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Right, okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where you, you know, dance around in front of a blue screen or a green screen and you have... With those like, just really lame, I know what you're talking about, yep.
[SPEAKER_22]: Imagine this with like real people, except the people think that they can dress cool and know how to dance.
[SPEAKER_22]: and they're the type of people who think that they're doing so well that you really don't have the heart to tell them that they suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: What kind of music is in this game?
[SPEAKER_07]: I never even played it.
[SPEAKER_22]: We have Saturday Night, we have The Hustle, we have Santa Maria, which I nearly threw up.
[SPEAKER_07]: By Samantha Fox?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, but it's not Samantha Fox.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, they have I Should Be So Lucky by Kylo Ren.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should be so lucky, lucky, lucky, lucky.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know that one.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they had Macho Man.
[SPEAKER_19]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which was the worst.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like limes?
[SPEAKER_22]: And they had, oh, shoot.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was another something I don't remember off the top of my head, but this machine just sucked.
[SPEAKER_22]: And it was sort of thrown away in the corner by the door, you know, like, we really don't have this here, they just make us.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then, you know, we played with balls all day, and then went back over for 2DX, and I got to see my friend Liz, who I hadn't seen in two years.
[SPEAKER_22]: I knew her before I... I actually met her at Anime Expo 2000, which was also where I played my first DDR machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll hear the... Well, you know, you interviewed Kim in these interviews, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: That you did?
[SPEAKER_22]: I interviewed Liz.
[SPEAKER_07]: I interviewed a bunch of people.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Liz is also... She's a Santoki on Step Squad 4.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to talk to Mel and Mel for a minute here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, because they went to the big Disney's Rave Tournament on Friday, which none of us were able to go to, because we all have to work, and then, you know, by the time, at least I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you went for that week?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, well, you guys... I'm like us unemployed people, why don't you?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if I worked in Milpitas, then I could get to the tournament in time, but I work here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, I'm unemployed.
[SPEAKER_22]: Don't... But...
[SPEAKER_24]: Watch out before the unemployed rise up and kill you!
[SPEAKER_07]: Smoke power!
[SPEAKER_29]: Okay, well, yeah, quick rundown.
[SPEAKER_29]: The tourney was on a dancing stage, Disney's Rave.
[SPEAKER_29]: It was at Milpitas, and it was hosted in one of the party rooms.
[SPEAKER_29]: And for the Perfect Attack tourney, it was all on doubles.
[SPEAKER_29]: And because Disney Rave is a rather easy machine to Perfect Attack anything on, like Triple S's are very commonplace, they had set the difficulty to eight.
[SPEAKER_29]: So it was like, you know, the good old third mix SSR days where four goods and you were out.
[SPEAKER_29]: and people did fail during the tourney.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, to fail a song on Disney's Rave, that's got to be the biggest heartbreaker.
[SPEAKER_29]: Not necessarily.
[SPEAKER_29]: Some of the songs are impossible.
[SPEAKER_29]: Some of them were ten-footers like Twilight Zone and Ducking Hardcore.
[SPEAKER_22]: I could just imagine Mr. Bassman.
[SPEAKER_29]: Bassman is actually relatively easy compared to some of the others.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, so now you came out of hiding, basically your freestyle retirement, and you did a freestyle at this tournament, correct?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_29]: I finally decided, hey, this is going to be a fun tourney, there's not that much pressure, what the heck.
[SPEAKER_29]: So yeah, I did the bump.
[SPEAKER_29]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_29]: The most ghetto song out there, and I pretty much milked it for its ghetto factor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, the last time Mel B was here on Orange Lounge, about six or seven weeks ago now, the last time he was here, we made an agreement that the next time he enters in a tournament, he needs to do a knee drop and a hand slap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did those two things get done?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, they were.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: And from what I understand, you got criticized by one of the judges for it, right?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yes, one of the judges was, I wasn't so sure about that hand slap knee drop somewhere in the game.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, I chained it pretty nicely.
[SPEAKER_29]: I kind of disguised it well.
[SPEAKER_29]: It wasn't the, like, love to ball hand slap.
[SPEAKER_29]: I thought I did it with class and style and all those good things freestylers should be doing it with, but no.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if anybody wants to blame the low points of Mel B's routine, that would be our fault here at Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you're welcome.
[SPEAKER_29]: It was all in fun.
[SPEAKER_29]: For the turnout I had on a Friday night, there was probably about maybe 20 routines or so thereabouts.
[SPEAKER_29]: Not too bad.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, 18, 19.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, it's cool.
[SPEAKER_29]: And everyone was just having a good time more than anything.
[SPEAKER_29]: There was maybe a few dancey routines, but for the most part, everyone was just goofed around.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's a Disney rave, you know.
[SPEAKER_29]: How seriously can you make it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, how many Macarena routines were there?
[SPEAKER_29]: One.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just one, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Did they actually do the Macarena?
[SPEAKER_29]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_29]: In fact, the audience did.
[SPEAKER_29]: Although, the funny thing was, it was Tigger, actually, of all people who did Macarena, and at the end, he pretty much turned it into Love 2 Macarena, complete with hand slaps and all that good schmazz.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, good tournament?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think they need to do another Disney's Rave tournament in the future?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or was it just kind of a one-time, ha-ha, that was funny, let's move on now?
[SPEAKER_29]: Maybe once in a blue moon, like once a year probably.
[SPEAKER_29]: I doubt you'd see anything twice because a lot of people were having trouble enough trying to memorize steps, trying to get it up really for the tourney.
[SPEAKER_29]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_07]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times, good times.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other tournaments coming up that you want to tell us all about?
[SPEAKER_07]: Any more appearances you'll be making that you want to plug?
[SPEAKER_29]: As far as I know, you'll probably catch me at a local 7-Eleven or something like that.
[SPEAKER_29]: Just catch me Thursday.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm getting a Vanilla Coke Slurpee.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'll be at the one on Branham in Monterey in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_29]: Bingo.
[SPEAKER_29]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_29]: But past that, as far as I know, I'm not too sure about any of the tourneys coming up.
[SPEAKER_29]: I know Scandia 2 is probably one of the bigger ones coming up in December.
[SPEAKER_29]: As soon as I know more details about that, hey, I'll pass it on.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's going to be a Sacramento tournament in November.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be determined.
[SPEAKER_07]: To be determined in the works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk to Melody for a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: How are you?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now you were just here a couple weeks ago, weren't you?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, because I needed donuts and Mongolian.
[SPEAKER_07]: And now I have pants and a jacket.
[SPEAKER_24]: Now I have clothes to go with the Mongolian.
[SPEAKER_07]: Explain why you had to come up to Sacramento this time.
[SPEAKER_24]: This time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Last time was for donuts, this time it was for... Last time was for donuts, this time...
[SPEAKER_24]: I was on a quest to get a pair of pants at Express that I absolutely adore.
[SPEAKER_24]: I called every single Express in Northern California.
[SPEAKER_24]: Only one had them in the right size, and it was here in Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_24]: And I thought, well, hey, now I have a really good excuse to come up here.
[SPEAKER_24]: So we were kicking around the idea anyway, because since the Miggle tourney just happened, we had to inform everyone that, yes, the can't-slot-knee-drop thing had been done.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was like, well, hey, now we have a really good excuse to come up here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I'm waiting to see the video.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I can't wait for.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: There is a three-minute video update.
[SPEAKER_24]: Did I just say three minutes?
[SPEAKER_24]: Yeah, here goes Rosie and Jamal.
[SPEAKER_24]: But it's a wrestling thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, okay, okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: But if you go on DDRFreak and the MiggleTurney thread, there is a link to a three-minute video on there that has some highlights from the MiggleTurney until the actual videos come up.
[SPEAKER_20]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: But I haven't been able to finish downloading it myself considering my computer crashed IE in the middle of it, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: They're giving a link in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to get that three-minute video, it's at evil.facuck.org.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Facuck is spelled, by the way, F-C-U-K.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that has anything to do with French Connection.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's an independent side of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think French Connection is F-C-U-K.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a Facuck shirt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Facuck Games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wear that to all the tournaments.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've seen that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't even... Man, anyone who downloaded the video, I make a brief one-half-second appearance in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are you doing?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you talking?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, no, I'm, like, watching Corey play Dumb Mania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right on, right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there's also, uh, you can download it from Oralsay.cx Oralsay.cx is another site you can get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And everybody's sharing when they appear in the video.
[SPEAKER_24]: See, I have to get my computer to actually cooperate and download it without crashing my browser in the middle of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Black Lab is in the chat room saying, I appear in it twice, I'm in it twice.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess it must just be a really fast clip kind of thing where you just got everybody in there at least once.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's kind of cool, actually.
[SPEAKER_24]: I only saw half of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you spot yourself?
[SPEAKER_24]: I have not seen myself yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, maybe you're in the second half.
[SPEAKER_07]: It could be, but... One day we'll bring a video camera in here and we'll do a quick promo or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Eep.
[SPEAKER_29]: But probably the greatest cameo we saw in the video that we did see from the tourney was a kneeling pad, of all things.
[SPEAKER_29]: It was a cow kneeling pad.
[SPEAKER_29]: True story.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, quick rundown for everyone out there.
[SPEAKER_29]: Me and Melody, we were over at Target one night.
[SPEAKER_29]: We was just checking out some stuff.
[SPEAKER_29]: I come by the gardening section.
[SPEAKER_29]: I see these things.
[SPEAKER_29]: They're butterfly knee pads.
[SPEAKER_29]: Literally.
[SPEAKER_29]: Knee pads with...
[SPEAKER_29]: And I thought, dude, that must be like the greatest gift we could give at a tourney.
[SPEAKER_29]: Like, we should give the worst freestyler, you know, a set of butterfly knee pads and just send them on their way.
[SPEAKER_29]: But right next to it, we saw a cow kneeling pad.
[SPEAKER_29]: And since one of our friends is big on cows, you know, we thought that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_29]: And see, that was a kneeling pad.
[SPEAKER_29]: We were already thinking the wrong things with that.
[SPEAKER_29]: So we gave the gift to our friend over at the tourney.
[SPEAKER_29]: And next thing you know, everyone was abusing it and all sorts of.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think the cows saw more action than anyone else that night.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie just pissed her pants at something here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It just happened.
[SPEAKER_07]: She just read that the local golf land here in Roseville got a crane game.
[SPEAKER_15]: They got a crane game!
[SPEAKER_07]: Explain your obsession with the crane game for a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry to change the subject on your melody.
[SPEAKER_24]: First off, Jamie, I'm hiding my keys from you right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, you are not... Jamie has to be rationed on how much money she can spend on the crane game.
[SPEAKER_22]: I rape the crane games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, it's not one of those... I need to talk to JB for a minute who's telling us about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not one of those shitty cranes for candy type thing, is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because that don't count.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that doesn't count.
[SPEAKER_07]: Give us a quarter so we can give you two cents worth of candy game.
[SPEAKER_18]: The claw.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're talking...
[SPEAKER_24]: I am all over shitty stuffed animals.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not a crane game unless the animals are shitty.
[SPEAKER_24]: It just doesn't happen that way.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's always choose the worst looking, ugliest piece of crap you see in there and you will get it first try.
[SPEAKER_24]: Don't make fun of my shitty animals!
[SPEAKER_22]: The best thing I ever won, and of all places this was at Spiegel, I got Tyrone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, Tyrone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tyrone was the best.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where is Tyrone?
[SPEAKER_22]: Tyrone is currently in lockup with his pussies and bitches.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tyrone, by the way, and maybe I'll find during the next break, I'll find a link to a picture of Tyrone and put it in the chat room because I know I have one up.
[SPEAKER_07]: If anybody knows of my secret picture page, it's in there with Sunnyvale Tournament pictures.
[SPEAKER_07]: Tyrone is a little stuffed bear that wears like a little... He's a real beanie bear.
[SPEAKER_22]: ...little Hugh Hefner pimp coat.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's a brown bear wearing a deep maroon smoking jacket.
[SPEAKER_22]: And his name literally is Tyrone.
[SPEAKER_22]: He is the coolest bear in the world.
[SPEAKER_22]: He has bitches, thanks to Melody.
[SPEAKER_24]: And he has pussies.
[SPEAKER_24]: You know how hard it is to find little tiny dogs?
[SPEAKER_24]: And just to be wandering around Target saying, wow, I need to get some bitches around here somewhere.
[SPEAKER_24]: Especially when you're in the toy section and all the kids are wandering around.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm just like, hmm, I need some bitches here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, yeah, can I get a price check on bitches on aisle three?
[SPEAKER_22]: Attention Kmart shoppers, we have a sale in the bitches department.
[SPEAKER_07]: Attention all Kmart shoppers, tampons and bitches half off.
[SPEAKER_24]: Excuse me, do we have any bitches here?
[SPEAKER_24]: Is there a bitch in the house?
[SPEAKER_24]: Remind me to never ever drink water at this show again.
[SPEAKER_24]: I nearly choked down my vanilla coke.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, we had some... Some bitches made a mess on aisle three.
[SPEAKER_07]: Can we get the little pink powder?
[SPEAKER_22]: We got a bitch in the line.
[SPEAKER_22]: We need a price check on bitches.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're so easily amused here today.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's for money?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't care about money anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just want to talk about... I just want to say bitch as many times as I can on the show tonight.
[SPEAKER_11]: Bitch mania 2DX.
[SPEAKER_11]: News Science Collection
[SPEAKER_22]: I had a chance to do it Wednesday night.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't tell you about that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just another stupid mom letting her child run rampant on the thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I was like, you need to control your little spawn there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You actually referred to the child as spawn.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, I said their child.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, there was also the incident with the giggling idiots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah, if you've ever seen the Clerks cartoon, yeah, and the two giggling girls, that's like what these chicks were like, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: They were sitting over at the little tables, and I was watching, I think, who was it that was playing Parapara?
[SPEAKER_22]: I think it was Sunil that was playing...
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know if anyone watches DigiCart, but I had a black Gamma Gamma Dawn hat with the little pointy horns on it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I went, I like your hat!
[SPEAKER_22]: Calling for another, and finally one of them came over and said, I like your hat.
[SPEAKER_22]: I go, thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: And so she walked off.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then they pointed to the African that was on my purse and I go, and one of them came over and I was like, she's like, would you eat your dog?
[SPEAKER_22]: Go away.
[SPEAKER_22]: You wanted to kill them all.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what this is kinda turning into here, I think?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we need to get into this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think we need to get into the FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's have at it, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have another one you want to start us off with, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I've been getting a lot in the chat room that I can talk about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really have one myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear it, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear your FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_22]: My first one, of course, goes toward those, you know, crappy, giggling, stupid, moron, stupid fucks at Rizvalgatan.
[SPEAKER_22]: My other fuck you of the week goes toward idiots in general, because I hate them.
[SPEAKER_22]: Especially idiots... What?
[SPEAKER_24]: That's rather vague in general, but I kinda like it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's the people who will fall for just about anything that you put in front of them.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, I will narrow down this level of idiocy to sheep.
[SPEAKER_22]: To the people who will blindly follow one voice and think that they are the end all.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, the little... You know, there's nothing wrong with, you know, fanboys and fangirls.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's a thing with people who are fanboys and fangirls to the exception of all else, who will take anything that they hear on TV, anything on the radio, by the way, do everything I say, anything that they...
[SPEAKER_22]: They read and act like it is, you know, the absolute scripture that they need to live their lives by.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, I must buy this thing for the sake of my American pride.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh my god, orange is the new red.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exactly!
[SPEAKER_07]: If you ever saw Josie and the Pussycats, one of those ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: But that is exactly the thing that I... And there's the people...
[SPEAKER_22]: who think, oh, well, you know, my life isn't very important, so I'm going to make up something really stupid so I can get on CNN.
[SPEAKER_22]: But no, I'm not talking about, you know, about... Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to tell a waitress at Shoney's that my van has a bomb in it, and I'm going to go blow something up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, my God!
[SPEAKER_07]: Boy, that killed the conversation, didn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Anybody else in here?
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, are you done with your... No, I just don't like stupid people.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other rants you have?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, then we've got Loki's got his round.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, my first FU of the week goes to the new version of DWI, which I'll go over that later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: But damn thing didn't work again.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not much of a surprise.
[SPEAKER_10]: They just can't program it right for some reason.
[SPEAKER_10]: I guess it's just incompatible with my computer.
[SPEAKER_10]: My second FU of the week would have to go to... By the way, Loki, happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your little party you had last night was quite nice.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for reminding me.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's my second FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's to 9-11.
[SPEAKER_10]: God damn it.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had that birthday 21 years before that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not fair.
[SPEAKER_10]: Everyone's like, oh, your birthday's on 9-11.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: That must suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, so pretty much every year from now on, everyone at my work and all that stuff, they actually forget my birthday because of 9-11.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that feeds to 9-11 and the new version of DWI.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I'm going to do just for you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because you have to go through that every year on your birthday, I'm going to change your song that you have to hear all the time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll have this be your FU song in the week for the future.
[SPEAKER_07]: How's that sound?
[SPEAKER_07]: This moment of political incorrectness.
[SPEAKER_22]: Speaking of political incorrectness, or correctness or whatever, my music, please.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, okay, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have requests for my song since, you know, that Drop the Bomb doesn't really work with 9-11.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe you can change it to Crash.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, yes, Jamie, you have FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_22]: My other one, it's also directed in a similar fashion toward the whole 9-11 thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: For people who saw my big rant in my live journal.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's actually directed toward consumerism in general.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am a consumer whore!
[SPEAKER_22]: And how!
[SPEAKER_22]: This goes toward all those people who are trying to make a quick buck off a tragedy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you!
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Go to hell and die there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_10]: and just to add to that, they named it a holiday.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's now Patriot's Day.
[SPEAKER_07]: No longer will it be called 9-11.
[SPEAKER_07]: Doesn't that sound like the greatest sale at JCPenney's?
[SPEAKER_07]: Patriot's Day sale, yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: But that's awesome because I get that day off every year, hopefully.
[SPEAKER_15]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other FUs on anything in general?
[SPEAKER_07]: Mel B's got one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have male music, but I'll find male music really fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Male music, male music.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would work for male music?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's try... I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: Word.
[SPEAKER_29]: Excellent choice, my man.
[SPEAKER_29]: Anyway, I got one big F for you, actually.
[SPEAKER_29]: And this is not just one person, not even one day, it's a whole damn city.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's the city of Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_29]: I don't know most of you who've been out there in a while, but apparently there was a problem about a month ago.
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, a month and a half, two months ago.
[SPEAKER_29]: Apparently a pipe that was a pump to...
[SPEAKER_24]: Here, since I know the story, there's a saltwater pond apparently on the edge of Milpitas in San Jose.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it's like 650 acres.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's huge.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it has lots of nice little organisms and crap in it.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the pump broke.
[SPEAKER_24]: And it's been very warm in the area, and lots of nice little organisms and stuff in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ha ha, smells like poopy.
[SPEAKER_24]: Um, try like bad sushi.
[SPEAKER_24]: Constantly.
[SPEAKER_29]: Really horrible, and it just smells all day long.
[SPEAKER_29]: I, that feels so bad for people like who work at- Like worse than the sushi place at the Metreon?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding, I've never had that before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, seriously, I mean... Trying to think of an easy place to knock.
[SPEAKER_29]: I feel so bad for people who work at, like, Dave & Buster's.
[SPEAKER_29]: They gotta sit out there all day long and, like, inhale this in.
[SPEAKER_07]: They just get headaches and, man, I just couldn't... You gotta wonder, though, because I've actually, I've been to Illuminations, the candle store, you know, and I've asked the chicks that work there, you know, doesn't it get annoying after a while smelling like candle?
[SPEAKER_07]: And they say they get used to it, so you gotta wonder if Dave & Buster's people get used to the raw sushi smell.
[SPEAKER_24]: I actually, since I'm like the nice person that I am, I actually talk to the doormen when I go in at Dave Buster's.
[SPEAKER_24]: I say, how the hell do you live with this smell?
[SPEAKER_24]: He says, you know, we get headaches all the time.
[SPEAKER_24]: We can't stand it.
[SPEAKER_24]: They actually still smell it.
[SPEAKER_24]: Believe me, I will run from my car to the door and get in as fast as I can.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mel and I were in Milpitas getting gas.
[SPEAKER_24]: He opened the window to my car.
[SPEAKER_24]: I started screaming at him, shut the damn window!
[SPEAKER_24]: It's gonna smell like fucking fish in here!
[SPEAKER_29]: But yeah, so in general, fuck you Milpitas.
[SPEAKER_29]: I can't even continue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, now we've got to get to the FUs of the week from the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is turning into an awfully long segment every week, but okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're negative.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's the people's FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's the people's choice, the people's FU.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to the FUs from the chatroom, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Twin says...
[SPEAKER_07]: FU to Windows XP because it's crashed on him again and it's making me format his drive again this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Tim says hi to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_21]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_07]: SoCalKick says his FU of the week is childproof safety caps.
[SPEAKER_07]: It took him seven tries to open the new bottle of pills that he got today in a new bottle.
[SPEAKER_24]: And yet, the childproof bottle will keep the adults out, but kids can get it at first try.
[SPEAKER_24]: Mommy, what's this blue candy?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the crack, put it back DCB has a fuck you of the week and he says it's to his parents Typical T-Gangs there For not letting him buy 2DX because it's too expensive
[SPEAKER_07]: So now he's stuck with a 2DX controller and nothing to play except for five key games, which get boring fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: I recommend Sixth and Core, because it's almost just like 2DX.
[SPEAKER_21]: When I was your age, we didn't have this beat mania stuff.
[SPEAKER_21]: We had to play on the Power Pad.
[SPEAKER_21]: It was Power Glove.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Power Glove.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so bad.
[SPEAKER_21]: All we had was Excitebike and Gyromite.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, Rob the Robot was the shit.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just like it because it's named Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk to Black Lab.
[SPEAKER_07]: His F.U.
[SPEAKER_07]: of the week is Denny's for their slow-ass service that caused him to be two hours late in getting home from the Disney rave tourney, thusly getting him in deep shit with the parents.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck Denny's.
[SPEAKER_07]: He didn't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki's got an F.U.
[SPEAKER_07]: of the week right behind him.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, speaking of Denny's, I don't know what it is about Denny's, but every time I go in there, they have to do one of two things.
[SPEAKER_10]: Either A, forget something I ordered, or B, make fun of my shirt.
[SPEAKER_10]: Normally I have a shirt on there, and it'll have like a phrase.
[SPEAKER_10]: One time I had one that said, I hear voices and they don't like it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you really hear voices?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why don't they like me?
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, go away.
[SPEAKER_10]: I hear one really annoying voice right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cram it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So F you to Denny's, because they suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, fair enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Carols is better anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you ever go to the Carols in Roseville, ask for Mary Lou.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's a sweetie.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, she is, and tip her well.
[SPEAKER_22]: Tip her well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three more.
[SPEAKER_07]: Three more FUs.
[SPEAKER_07]: 23rd Magus says... Oh, he wants two.
[SPEAKER_07]: He says a continued fuck you to Boom PlayStation... Oh, PlayStation 2 USB converters.
[SPEAKER_07]: Controller converters.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also a good-sized FU to the Player One keys on RVGL's Hip Hop Mania.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_22]: I would have to second that, except the way that I play, I really don't have an issue with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Joe Mama says, F you from school for being morons.
[SPEAKER_07]: They gave him three detentions for nothing.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yeah, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_07]: I somehow wonder if he really did nothing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I was only late a couple times.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not that bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know what he did.
[SPEAKER_07]: We gotta know, what did he really do?
[SPEAKER_07]: He did something bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I really didn't hit anybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, JB says F you to Karos for being slow.
[SPEAKER_07]: F you, JB.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's my F you.
[SPEAKER_24]: No, we have to add IHOP to that list because we had some slow ass service there after me the other day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Joe Mama got detention because he quote unquote missed a class.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh yeah, and furthermore from all IHOP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did he miss a class because he was out back smoking pot or what?
[SPEAKER_29]: I don't know, but to continue that IHOP thought, I'm just thinking, that's the four reasons why we gotta have a raw chicken and waffles up in NorCal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please.
[SPEAKER_07]: A chicken and waffle!
[SPEAKER_22]: Amen to that.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's it, just one day, come to my house, I will make you French toast.
[SPEAKER_22]: Cause I rule like that.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's not the same.
[SPEAKER_22]: My French toast owns.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've never had my French toast.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's just not the same.
[SPEAKER_24]: They add crack to their chicken and waffles.
[SPEAKER_24]: I'm talking about IHOPing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Kero's and Denny's and those crappy places.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've moved on to Roscoe's.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We gotta take this show down to SoCal sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're gonna tape a show in SoCal at some point.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somehow.
[SPEAKER_07]: AI chip anyone?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you guys want to take our recorder?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you guys live closer by, I'd let you take the recorder and tape fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_24]: We're going to AI for a while, but I don't know if we're gonna see anyone entertaining.
[SPEAKER_24]: We could take it on rides at Disneyland and start screaming randomly or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, cause...
[SPEAKER_07]: Now I'm thinking of how I could make this work.
[SPEAKER_07]: I might be able to let you guys borrow the remote unit for a while if you guys want to tape your adventures.
[SPEAKER_24]: Unfortunately, they won't let recorders or anything into the prices right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean the rest of your adventures if you go to AI or whatever.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh, we're going to AI.
[SPEAKER_07]: A live review of Martial Beat.
[SPEAKER_29]: A live review of Martial Beat, complete with punching and sweating and all that good schmack.
[SPEAKER_24]: And everybody was kung fu fighting.
[SPEAKER_24]: And the woman in my head was kick punch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, we should do a review for Punch Mania.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have it at Florin now.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I hear is that Florin Mall here in Sacramento got Punch Mania.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's the Fist of the North Star one.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Fist of the North Star one, yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, the ghetto-ass fucking mall got Punch Mania.
[SPEAKER_07]: So the gang members can train.
[SPEAKER_24]: I drove by there.
[SPEAKER_24]: That place was scary.
[SPEAKER_22]: It is very scary and desolate looking, but they have Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do have Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ooh, Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bounce with me, bounce with me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bounce with me, bounce.
[SPEAKER_27]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, speaking of... Oh, I see you're telling me to do a segue.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's do this segue.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is something we've actually talked about on the show before.
[SPEAKER_07]: But this is interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I find this interesting only because this is a story that is actually posted on Konami's site in the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Konami Amusement of Europe.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is their stance on the Konami versus Andamiro, which is the company that makes Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is their words on that whole lawsuit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And this is why it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think this is the first real comment I've seen from Konami on this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's read this, shall we?
[SPEAKER_07]: This is from Konami's site.
[SPEAKER_07]: It says, Konami's legal eagles have always had their hands full defending Dance Dance Revolution's genre, spawning style from being copied all over the world, but this latest attempt by company Andamaro, they call it Andamaro, has evened them slightly taken aback.
[SPEAKER_07]: This time it appears the Korean company's strategy was to claim they actually invented DDR in the first place, despite the fact it took them almost two years to make their complaint.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of interesting because they're kind of taking jabs at Andamiro, which you don't usually see in company press releases.
[SPEAKER_07]: But of course, in Europe, everything's tabloid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all about, you know, at least from what I've seen.
[SPEAKER_07]: The parties have been involved in legal disputes since then in front of the Korean and the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: courts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now that's interesting because I don't think we've ever heard before that this thing's been in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: courts, but this says it has.
[SPEAKER_07]: Namiro started manufacturing and distributing Pump It Up Dance Simulation Game, which was very similar to Konami's Dance Dance Revolution during September 1999.
[SPEAKER_07]: Konami filed a complaint with the Seoul District Court seeking an injunction against the production of Pump It Up.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: The reason was that Konami infringed the patent and Amiro had been assigned from a third party in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: The case was scheduled for jury trial this month.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Amiro filed a complaint against Konami seeking an injunction against the distribution of Dance's Revolution in the United States.
[SPEAKER_07]: No U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: mixes lately.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that opens the door.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep, so that's that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's an official word from Konami of the UK.
[SPEAKER_07]: And says some very interesting things in there we might not have known before.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anybody want to comment on this story?
[SPEAKER_07]: Have anything to say about it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does that mean we're going to see some U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: pump-it-up machines?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think pump-it-ups have already kind of been distributed in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: You seem to know about this, Mel?
[SPEAKER_07]: I know they've kind of been hawking the machines to U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: arcades.
[SPEAKER_29]: But of course, there's companies out there that hawk the mechs too, like US arcades too, so I don't know if Animero's necessarily launched in the US, but... Well, it has been targeted in the US for a while, I mean, like, if you went to... I forget what the major arcade game convention is in Vegas...
[SPEAKER_29]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_29]: about a year ago when I did a big interview for DDR Spotlight.
[SPEAKER_29]: Right, I remember reading that.
[SPEAKER_29]: And, you know, like, kind of off the record, we were talking about, well, how come you would never see, like, Konomics or anything in Arcade yet?
[SPEAKER_29]: Yeah, it told us, basically, it would have been a really bad move to put out, like, during this whole lawsuit, to put out a new US mix.
[SPEAKER_29]: You know, so Adamir would be saying, you know, what kind of, you know, strategy is that?
[SPEAKER_29]: You know, you're being sued for something, and you're already putting out a new Arcade mix?
[SPEAKER_29]: That's, you know, not right.
[SPEAKER_29]: It wouldn't look good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now this kind of opens the door here, it looks like, sounds like, so who knows what might happen.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm guessing probably someone else is going to distribute the Konami game since, yeah, I guess Konami shut down its coin off.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I think it's a given somebody's going to step in and fill in that void and we'll see something coming from Konami in the near future.
[SPEAKER_29]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe in the future we can get Jason on this show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to work on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to try and smooth him to get him on this program at some point.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, I've got pretty good, you know,
[SPEAKER_29]: I was about to ask, what's going on?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you want to update us on DDR Spot?
[SPEAKER_07]: I keep forgetting you're a major part of the DDR Spot group, so you want to say any plugs for DDR Spot, what's going on there?
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, right now, yeah, our site is down for more maiming because we're going for a new launch right now.
[SPEAKER_29]: We're basically tweaking a few things on the back end.
[SPEAKER_29]: We're targeting something to probably late this week.
[SPEAKER_29]: We're about to launch everything.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's going to have a new look, new feel.
[SPEAKER_26]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's going to have quite a few new goodies and a lot of things that haven't been there before and haven't been really on any other DDR sites.
[SPEAKER_07]: One thing I have to ask, you can say no comment if you want, forums.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: And try that again?
[SPEAKER_29]: We're looking at something alternate to forums, actually.
[SPEAKER_29]: I don't know if I'm necessarily at liberty to say it right now, but I will say there will be a way you can interact with all members without having forums.
[SPEAKER_29]: There's a way to interact one-on-one with either the members, the lurkers, or with the staff itself.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't want to get you in trouble, so we'll just say tune in to win.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so DDRspot.com coming back very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keep an eye on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sure they'll announce that everywhere.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll mention it on this show for sure once we see this back up.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, wonderful.
[SPEAKER_15]: And maybe we'll have the staff here sometime as well too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to get that to work sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, how about a quick break everybody?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's take a really quick break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll come back.
[SPEAKER_17]: What do I get to break?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: That dish, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to start, actually there's something I wanted to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to start this break off with something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, explain the background on this.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the good version of the song you were talking to me about earlier.
[SPEAKER_10]: Alright, this song that's going to be played is Instant Love.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was basically a training stage in Beatmania 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now...
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_10]: The guy did 20 November.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Nagarero.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyways, I'm going to try to find his CD.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think he actually put out a CD because I was visiting his website.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we're trying to find that, import it, and maybe there'll be a clean version of Instant Love we can listen to.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I have no guarantees on that.
[SPEAKER_10]: But just listen to the backgrounds.
[SPEAKER_07]: So this is the one time we're going to make an exception and actually play Let Them Move, because this is a good version.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, just try not to be annoyed by DJ Konami telling you how to play Beatmania, but just listen to the background and... Okay, so just, you know, preface, there's going to be instructions on how to play Beatmania, in case you didn't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: After that... I'm sorry?
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, for any of the old school hip-hop heads, I think DJ Konami looks straight up like a broke-ass Fab Five Freddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey everyone, this is DJ Konami!
[SPEAKER_13]: I know you all know Beatmania, but I want to go back and teach you the basics.
[SPEAKER_13]: Listen carefully and try to follow.
[SPEAKER_13]: The object will come down from the top.
[SPEAKER_13]: When it hits the red line, push the button.
[SPEAKER_13]: When it hits the red line, turn the table.
[SPEAKER_13]: You get it?
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's practice.
Easy, huh?
Alright, let's go on to the scratch game.
When the objects reach the red line, scratch!
With the fast note, the technique is to scratch fast.
[SPEAKER_13]: and the turntable.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's hard, but you can do it!
Okay!
Effector time!
Here's the spec of the new Beatmania!
[SPEAKER_13]: Ladies and Gents
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: The Guardian, Angel, Reflector, Light, Lyrically, I own the mic, you slept a deputy, but you established order, Inspector The Guardian, Angel, Reflector, Light, Lyrically, I own the mic, yeah
[SPEAKER_12]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm in the future, MCs who misdemean is left to be, history's a hoochah, think you spittin' at, I represent a different map, hip-hop diplomat, I've already seen a tip of that, see right through ya, I'm original flow jack, God glorify it, poor spiritual, I wish the crack remained anonymous, my lyrics out fit astronomers, ear tied to peril, third commandment for idolaters,
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_15]: The language, now excuse me, as I answer more archives than choosing Methods, my wish to carry out, whether by land or aerial Cause this gig cannot be stereo, type out my brothers at burial Right for harvest, bluejack, but not in office Call us a hip-hop band, blowin' away MCs like Thartis I promise, I ain't your average artist, my thought is Look into God's direction and not the God of sin Believe in what you're facing, use this reality Believe and God will set you free
[SPEAKER_15]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: You know how we do, it's B-A-R-B-A-L, represent the media right, no proof, you know what I'm sayin'?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yo, right around now, DJ Hori's in the mix, keepin' you in constant suspense Yo, 2012's sound is sakura, you know what I'm sayin'?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yo, and it goes a little somethin' like this, yo
[SPEAKER_28]: Hiho, Kermit the Frog here, informing you that today's broadcast of Orange Lounge Radio is brought to you by the letter B, the letter A, and the number 59.
[SPEAKER_15]: Can you tell me how to get, how to get to Sesame Street?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just go up the street and take a left.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, anyway, you are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Will you be my neighbor?
[SPEAKER_07]: Won't you be my neighbor?
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't that guy retire finally?
[SPEAKER_22]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: At least he didn't die.
[SPEAKER_07]: I say he didn't die.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's not an oh thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's an oh good thing.
[SPEAKER_24]: But eventually he is, and you just brought up that thought in my head.
[SPEAKER_29]: We're all going to... Melody, I'm sorry, but we're all going to die.
[SPEAKER_29]: Everyone's still traumatized Captain Kangaroo is gone, so...
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, we're Mr. Green Jeans.
[SPEAKER_29]: I mean, I know people still coming up to me asking where the heck he is.
[SPEAKER_29]: What am I supposed to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, Mr. Rogers did not die.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's not dead yet.
[SPEAKER_24]: Someone on Sesame Street really recently just died.
[SPEAKER_24]: I think the guy who played Gordon, I think he just died very recently.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope not Linda the Deaf Lady, I hope.
[SPEAKER_07]: She was my favorite.
[SPEAKER_24]: I don't think so, but like within the past couple weeks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gordon died?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is it always the brother that always got to get killed first?
[SPEAKER_24]: Man.
[SPEAKER_24]: Another instance of a man keeping you down.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can address those cards and letters to Mel B. Remember, if you want the proof, go to BurtIsEvil.com
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, it exists.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, they're reminding us about the HIV positive Muffet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Muffet.
[SPEAKER_21]: Little Miss Muffet.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_19]: That was very bad of you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Little Miss Muffet should be choosy on which tuffet she's sitting on now, shouldn't she?
[SPEAKER_10]: She can't just sit on any tuffet, just walks down the street and treats her to a nice dinner.
[SPEAKER_29]: And who knows how many seats have been on that tuffet.
[SPEAKER_11]: She should have had that tuffet tested.
[SPEAKER_11]: She's learned how to squat on that tuffet.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways...
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, shit, we all need to breathe.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think I'm actually tempted to play a song.
[SPEAKER_24]: Well, now that the show has grown to a complete and total halt.
[SPEAKER_07]: DJ Konami, which is actually DCB under a new name, wants to warn you all that Goat Say sat on that tuffet.
[SPEAKER_07]: For those who don't know Goat Say, all I have to say...
[SPEAKER_07]: That's, that's go say.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was me bending over and pretending, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't want to keep your ass on the chair.
[SPEAKER_22]: You just sit on your tuffet there.
[SPEAKER_15]: Keep your tuffets to yourself, bitch.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, yes, where were we?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tuffets.
[SPEAKER_07]: AIDS, something about, no, anyway.
[SPEAKER_21]: Nothing with HIV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, the Muppet with HIV.
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually have a Healing Vision AIDS mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: HIV mix.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: That sounds very politically incorrect.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yeah, it says this DWI will give you AIDS.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's just a really crappy remix of Healing Vision and Max 300.
[SPEAKER_10]: They purposely made it bad and made the set file impossible just because they were frustrated with all the remixes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, they don't like the Healing Vision remixes so they just went... They just don't like any of the remixes so they just got pissed off and made a HIV mix.
[SPEAKER_20]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, well, first of all, I recorded over old interviews, so I'm really not sure exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: I trimmed it up, so everything should be okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you have to explain why you sound really stoned in the thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think I was going on four hours of sleep, and I was really tired, and then I was traumatized by stepping state.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so stepping state.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you have any questions, okay, there, the cam should be better now.
[SPEAKER_22]: I sound really retarded.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oops, wait.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, you're going to see an old picture on the cam real fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll probably update soon, so just sit tight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cam's working.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, let's play these interviews, alright?
[SPEAKER_20]: This is the Orange Lounge interviews for Sunday, September 7th.
[SPEAKER_20]: 8th.
[SPEAKER_20]: The 8th.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just remember, stepping stage.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all about stepping stage.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was so tired.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the first of the interviews for Orange Lounge Radio, which, you know, we had the battery case off of the recorder, so it's kind of messed up.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, we're going to go ahead and try this again.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, go ahead and, you know, once again, we have someone who's no stranger to Orange Lounge interviews.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, go ahead and state your info.
[SPEAKER_04]: Con, Kiyoki, Su, Step Squad Family.
[SPEAKER_04]: Second interview for Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: Completely sober this time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_22]: That's not necessarily a good thing, is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually have Jenny here who gave me her... He's sober, but the question is, were you?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, just checking.
[SPEAKER_04]: ...on my arm when I was drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: She claimed she didn't draw on me, but my humor's a little hazy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I drew on him.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can you comment on that?
[SPEAKER_20]: All I wrote was my email.
[SPEAKER_20]: I was the one who drew the squid on the back of your forehead.
[SPEAKER_20]: I mean, head.
[SPEAKER_19]: I drew the eyes on the back of your neck.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I remember that.
[SPEAKER_04]: People are still wondering what the hell that was.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who was it that beat you over the head with my bat anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Ron Kitty.
[SPEAKER_04]: She did not make it today, but she's here in spirit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ah, yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, um, go ahead and, uh, you know, give your daily recap for our, uh, fun event today with the First Step Squad and etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hmm, well, let me see.
[SPEAKER_04]: Considering I was probably the first one up at six in the morning, lack of sleep, next thing to being high...
[SPEAKER_04]: Me and Jay actually had to clean up the house a little bit, but then after that 12 o'clock rolls around, Step Squad, RTF, and Otaku Outpost rolled out to the Holiday Bowl.
[SPEAKER_04]: From there, good times.
[SPEAKER_04]: We actually rigged the machine, so the last round, everyone got a strike.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was cool, but it's sad that they shut everything off.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, they ran out of pins, so everyone who bowled rolled a strike.
[SPEAKER_24]: On the last one, is that like the most ghetto bowling alley around that they actually ran out of pins?
[SPEAKER_24]: It's super ghetto.
[SPEAKER_29]: Scott's stepping stage.
[SPEAKER_29]: I think there's nothing that can go lower than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They want a clarification as to what exactly this event is that you were at.
[SPEAKER_22]: Basically, we had Cece down visiting from SoCal, and we had Liz visit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, she lives in California, but she was going to school in Washington State.
[SPEAKER_22]: So they were both in town, and we had a big gathering.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think it started off as just Step Squad, but it grew.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_19]: Guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wasn't bowling, so I really wouldn't care about that, but that sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would have loved to see the picture of everyone, last frame, triple strike each.
[SPEAKER_22]: They should have done that for ours, because mine were just like, oh, we're bowling, and I sucked, my score sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe, well, the thing was, they ran out of 10, so, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, well, I can't score anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sniff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, we have another couple people with us, so, yes, you.
[SPEAKER_22]: So go ahead and state your, you know, name, everything for our lovely, brilliant listeners.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hi, I'm Hattori Hanzo, and I'm doing... Yes, Mel, very fast.
[SPEAKER_24]: There's just nothing like butter enough for your listeners to brighten your day.
[SPEAKER_24]: Those lovely, wonderful people out there that we adore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we do love our listeners.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one thing to love your listeners, another thing to love your listeners.
[SPEAKER_17]: They're brilliant to you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mel Bellby just sends sloppy wet kisses to you all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Soda right now, and I'm feeling alright.
[SPEAKER_19]: And I see that is a Valencia orange soda.
[SPEAKER_19]: It is, and it's very good.
[SPEAKER_19]: You should try one.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is it your tasty beverage?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, since, you know, there aren't no other beverages to choose from, I think I'll just stick with the orange soda.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was the sound of a laugh on the head.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, so, um, go ahead and then if you'll state your name and everything for the list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie, quick, there's a wap on your head.
[SPEAKER_22]: By the way, I need to explain.
[SPEAKER_22]: We were sitting outside in the backyard in lawn chairs, just lounging, going, I'm tired.
[SPEAKER_15]: With a 40?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'd have 40.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, Hanzo had orange soda.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had milk tea.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, it was more like a 16 ounce.
[SPEAKER_22]: If you want to.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_22]: My name is Jin.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, I'm not male.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm a female.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: The tape did a funny thing there.
[SPEAKER_22]: The guy with the... Yes, don't you know Cyberbots is Capcom's number one game?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What happened there?
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, excuse me.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is coming from the person who had the screen...
[SPEAKER_22]: I made a reference that said, don't you know, Cyberbots is Capcom's number one game.
[SPEAKER_22]: And people got the reference.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who plays Puzzle Fighter?
[SPEAKER_22]: Me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who plays Devilot?
[SPEAKER_22]: Devilot Super 8.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, that was one of my old AOL names.
[SPEAKER_03]: I smell the D9, like, third mix Korean gates, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got the failed scream like what Melfi has on his signature.
[SPEAKER_19]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Care to comment?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, run that by you again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's listen to it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Run back a little.
[SPEAKER_03]: I smell the denied, like, third mix Korean gates, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: You got the failed screen like what Mel B has on his signature.
[SPEAKER_07]: He doesn't have that anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any comment?
[SPEAKER_29]: Hey man, what can I say?
[SPEAKER_29]: The world revolves around me.
[SPEAKER_29]: You can take anything in the world, you can take six steps, and it comes back to me.
[SPEAKER_29]: Oh, like Kevin Bacon?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but kosher.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mel B, the B don't stand for bacon.
[SPEAKER_29]: I think after Disney tourney everyone thinks the B stands for bling.
[SPEAKER_03]: The gate was the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm not kidding.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a clank and you know your... And you know your thread is locked.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, anyone have any comments for listeners?
[SPEAKER_22]: Anything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hanzo, keep talking your shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to jack you like I jacked that ice cream truck earlier with Jay Kinetic.
[SPEAKER_22]: I missed that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't want to know how you're going to jack Hanzo.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's pictures.
[SPEAKER_04]: Gary from RTF has them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes?
[SPEAKER_22]: I just have to say that half of everybody who was in that house did go and hump the ice cream van.
What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Explain now.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't even go out there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was like, oh, I have milk tea and 2DX, I'm happy.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I didn't even go out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't hump the ice cream man?
[SPEAKER_22]: No!
[SPEAKER_22]: I had 2DX to hump.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mean, I'm... I fear.
[SPEAKER_19]: I fear.
[SPEAKER_19]: Greatly.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_19]: I don't know what the hell this idiot's talking about.
[SPEAKER_04]: You were doing the solo run when we did it.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, you weren't here.
[SPEAKER_19]: Everybody ran outside and decided to rape the ice cream man.
[SPEAKER_19]: Then what does that have to do with me?
[SPEAKER_19]: You missed it.
[SPEAKER_19]: You didn't get to join in on the fun.
[SPEAKER_19]: I was... You got here.
[SPEAKER_24]: The black sheep.
[SPEAKER_24]: He was the one that was left out.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're just saying that because I'm black.
[SPEAKER_19]: Don't make me cornroll your hair, dammit.
[SPEAKER_22]: And this is the love of Step Squad here.
[SPEAKER_20]: And he left.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a comment from the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mmm, raping and ice cream.
[SPEAKER_15]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_19]: We have this on tape.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is the real world, Step Squad edition.
[SPEAKER_04]: On a closing note, Jamie, I'm waiting for Jay's birthday so we can roll up to Sacramento.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're having rum jello.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's this innocent look you're giving?
[SPEAKER_20]: I have to make some jello shots.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Speaking of which, where's Brad?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's his 21st birthday today, by the way.
[SPEAKER_19]: Brad's out playing 2DX, I guess, but... Happy birthday, Brad!
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to make jello shots for him, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, oh yes, back to the interviews.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, no, I'll go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_24]: If everybody pitches him a dollar, I will cornroll Khan's leg.
[SPEAKER_24]: Here.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's a nice little rose.
[SPEAKER_24]: It's pretty.
[SPEAKER_24]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_19]: How?
[SPEAKER_15]: He doesn't have... What was that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Run away!
[SPEAKER_22]: We have another absentee.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, you heard it here first on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our thoughts exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's what you get when you get sleep deprived people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I should delete it out of the silence, but I didn't want to.
[SPEAKER_20]: This is the second interview for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_20]: And go ahead and, you know, state your name, no nickname.
[SPEAKER_22]: I feel like I'm about to fall asleep.
[SPEAKER_07]: I had actually taken a nap outside.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is Jamie doing NPR Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what this is.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is the NPR edition of Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had already taken, like, a ten minute nap outside in one of the lounge chairs.
[SPEAKER_07]: A ten whole minutes?
[SPEAKER_07]: No!
[SPEAKER_07]: Idea for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, Liz, I usually go by Santoki on message boards and such.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you're visiting from where?
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh, actually, I live in California, but I'm on summer vacation from school in Seattle.
[SPEAKER_25]: And you've been with Step Squad for how long?
[SPEAKER_25]: Since March of 2001.
[SPEAKER_25]: Before there was DDR.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, before it was all over the place anyway, I guess.
[SPEAKER_25]: That's been like four years at least.
[SPEAKER_22]: It has to be more than that because I was living in Alabama when I first knew you online.
[SPEAKER_25]: Oh my god, memories.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you have any words to say for listeners?
[SPEAKER_22]: What's your DDR experience?
[SPEAKER_25]: My DDR experience isn't really that much.
[SPEAKER_25]: I used to just play for fun, but I haven't actually been on a machine in a year or so.
[SPEAKER_25]: But I usually play for fun when friends are around, but I haven't competed in tournaments or anything.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you have any other favorite games?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_25]: Usually puzzle games, actually.
[SPEAKER_22]: So do you have any final words for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_25]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_25]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_22]: Go to college.
[SPEAKER_22]: All of you.
[SPEAKER_22]: You're illiterate.
[SPEAKER_25]: Get an education because it's very important.
[SPEAKER_25]: You can't spend your whole life playing games.
[SPEAKER_20]: I can.
[SPEAKER_15]: Wow!
Whoa.
[SPEAKER_15]: The end.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the last interview.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's all this then?
[SPEAKER_15]: Just leftovers.
[SPEAKER_15]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is there anything in here?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, this is everyone trying to say goodbye.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, this is the goodbye.
[SPEAKER_27]: Hi, Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_27]: Yeah, Sapporo was good, and Orange Lounge kicks ass, and you should listen to it.
[SPEAKER_27]: SSF, RTF, Mountain Mike's, ASS, and fucking Nazi.
[SPEAKER_03]: All I have to say is,
[SPEAKER_03]: If Orange Lounge starts playing Fozzy, I'd have to hurt someone.
[SPEAKER_03]: That will not happen.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank the gods.
[SPEAKER_25]: Hello, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_25]: Play more Orange Lounge songs, like every day, all the time.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, we do.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and that brings an end to Jamie's interviews.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very random, but very cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for getting that for us, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I took a nice long nap when I got home.
[SPEAKER_07]: She's okay now.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're worried about Jamie, she's eating a couple donuts and she's got the sugar back in her.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's too bad I didn't record Jessica and I singing Absolute on the way home.
[SPEAKER_22]: We were in full Katimu style.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was singing a little bit of Summer Vacation there when somebody on one of the tapes there mentioned Summer Vacation.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, yeah, my horrible impression of Summer Vacation.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to have to get those vocals, that guy doing the vocal version of Dropout and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to have to get that sometime, play it on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got them?
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, get them for us.
[SPEAKER_07]: I remember they were on some website, but they're probably archived by now.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's talk about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: This would be an interesting interview I thought you all would be interested in hearing about.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is from Metropolis Magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Metropolis, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I've got a great career in radio ahead of me, don't I?
[SPEAKER_11]: Rob is very edumacated.
[SPEAKER_11]: I dropped out of college.
[SPEAKER_29]: Look at me now.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm a star.
[SPEAKER_29]: So smart, SMRT.
[SPEAKER_07]: Team Smart, SMRT for live, yo!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hooked on phonics, worked for Rob.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, SMRT, let me think.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sacramento, Metro Office, Radio Talent.
[SPEAKER_07]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Smart.
[SPEAKER_11]: SMRT.
[SPEAKER_11]: He's a real fart spiller.
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, fart filler.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, boy.
[SPEAKER_15]: We've got an... Brad!
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy birthday, Brad.
[SPEAKER_07]: Brad, come here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Come here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hold on, we're going to get to that in a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who wants to give Brad his birthday spankings?
[SPEAKER_07]: Irene, let's administer those birthday spankings.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're on air.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bend over, baby.
[SPEAKER_07]: And close your eyes.
[SPEAKER_07]: It might hurt a little bit.
[SPEAKER_28]: Back up to the camera.
[SPEAKER_28]: Beep, beep, beep.
[SPEAKER_28]: Can everybody see?
[SPEAKER_05]: Do we have... Okay, spanking, spanking.
[SPEAKER_21]: Because it's great radio, alright.
[SPEAKER_15]: Ready?
[SPEAKER_21]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_21]: Yes, he's 21.
[SPEAKER_21]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ooh, ah, ooh, hey, hey, ow, ow, why?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why me?
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, God, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You like it at home.
[SPEAKER_07]: I thought we were at 21 by now.
[SPEAKER_07]: and 1 million to grow on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Brad's starting to like this.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was so close, I was.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can stop.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can stop grabbing me yet.
[SPEAKER_11]: She'll spank the monkey later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Whoa!
[SPEAKER_07]: What was that comment?
[SPEAKER_07]: She'll spank the monkey later.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you guys leaving?
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, have fun at food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, you guys are coming back?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you guys going to Dairy Queen?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want the chicken strip thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, I'll share yours.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, yeah, great radio, huh?
[SPEAKER_22]: Totally derailed.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yes, interview.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: From Metrolopis Magazine.
[SPEAKER_21]: Metrolopis.
[SPEAKER_07]: Papadopolis Magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Weren't those the neighbors on Three's Company?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it was Webster.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Webster.
[SPEAKER_21]: The Papadopoli.
[SPEAKER_07]: This show's never going to get on track, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to find an actual Paula Terry song to play in the background.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I found one, yay.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have an interview with Paula Terry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, and this is about life in Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, for those who don't know Paula Terry, she's the singer that likes to torture us all in her DDR music.
[SPEAKER_22]: She can't hold a key.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's hear, uh, where are you from, Paula Terry?
[SPEAKER_07]: Sydney, Australia Sydney, Australia
[SPEAKER_07]: And what brought you to Japan?
[SPEAKER_06]: When I was in Sydney, I had friends who lived here.
[SPEAKER_06]: At the time, I had the travel age.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I was a child, I lived in France for four years.
[SPEAKER_06]: So at that stage of my life, back in Sydney, I felt I wanted to travel again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, I wanted to know anything about Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: I met these girls who had worked holidays in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: They worked in...
[SPEAKER_06]: Clubs and you come up to them and say, well, you're a singer.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have foreign singers in these clubs.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can give me a visa and make money.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not work in Japan?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I went out and took the risk and I've been here ever since.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow, that's really nice, Paula.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now doing Paula's voice.
[SPEAKER_07]: The next question will be Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody can do Paula's voice on one question.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll do this.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, Paula.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long have you been singing?
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, my brother's an opera singer, and my brother's, like, a classical guitarist.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I'm from the musical family!
[SPEAKER_22]: I love singing from being a little girl, but I really only started out to learn it when I was 16.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I skipped a line.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you got it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And my mother sent me an opera singing teacher.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love opera, but it wasn't for me.
[SPEAKER_22]: When I was 20, I decided to study jazz singing.
[SPEAKER_22]: I really love funky jazz music.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, play that funky jazz music, white girl.
[SPEAKER_22]: I love other funky things, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, now doing the voice of Paula will be Mel B. So, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: How long have you been boinking Naoki?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where do you sing, Paula?
[SPEAKER_26]: permanent booking at the Intercontinental Hotel on Tokyo Bay on Thursdays and Fridays from 7.30 p.m.
[SPEAKER_26]: to 11 p.m.
[SPEAKER_26]: I sing accompanied by a penis.
[SPEAKER_26]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_26]: We play everything.
[SPEAKER_26]: Then on Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday, I play in a Ginza at a piano ball, which is a totally different style, a slightly older audience.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's doing Paula's voice next?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, Melody, you pooper.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we're back to Matt.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: What sort of things do you sing, Paula?
[SPEAKER_07]: My repertoire goes from 30s to the 90s.
[SPEAKER_09]: I see you've been smoking, Paula.
[SPEAKER_09]: I have to keep up with the times.
[SPEAKER_09]: Recently, everywhere I worked, people were requesting some songs from Titanic.
[SPEAKER_09]: So I had to buy the CD and learn it.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also sing to carpenters.
[SPEAKER_09]: But I don't try to imitate the originals.
[SPEAKER_09]: I try to sing them in a different style.
[SPEAKER_09]: That would be key.
[SPEAKER_09]: To keep myself interested.
[SPEAKER_09]: I also really sing the standard jazz tunes like Summertime.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can do that in any number of styles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Next, Jamie doing Paula's voice again.
[SPEAKER_07]: Paula, are you planning to stay in Japan?
[SPEAKER_07]: Right here, yes.
[SPEAKER_20]: Uh, yeah, uh, I guess.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_21]: I just finished recording of my first CD, which comes out September 2-3.
[SPEAKER_21]: It's called, uh... Just Break Away.
[SPEAKER_21]: Uh, what's that mean?
[SPEAKER_21]: So, I'm going to wait around and see how well that does.
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm very pleased with it.
[SPEAKER_21]: If it goes well, I'll stay longer in the United States.
[SPEAKER_29]: Anything is possible in Japan.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's an incredible place.
[SPEAKER_05]: Waking up with a bit of a hangover, having a bad hair day, and not being able to blend into the background.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just can't seem to be inconspicuous.
[SPEAKER_05]: It may be half paranoia, but I often feel that people are staring at me.
[SPEAKER_21]: Oh my god, you sounded like Vera.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like from In Living Color.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm so embarrassed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Paula, do you organize your CDs alphabetically?
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely not.
[SPEAKER_08]: I favor total disorder.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're all in piles on the floor.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a drawback full of CDs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't play them often, but the ones that I like best are the ones in the piles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are we actually going to do this whole interview here?
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see if we can find some interesting questions here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's do this one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, it's like a game show.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to spend the rest of your life trapped on the Yamanote line.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're allowed to take one book, one CD, and one luxury item.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would they be?
[SPEAKER_05]: First, I need tampons.
[SPEAKER_05]: I need Naoki's hat.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'd like to record a CD of my favorite songs.
[SPEAKER_22]: from Ella Fitzgerald, Carmen McRae, right up to the 90s, the brand new heavies.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, that's a good group.
[SPEAKER_22]: She has taste.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, uh... Let's do this one here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Last question, last question.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the weirdest thing you've ever seen or experienced in Japan, Politary?
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of weird things have happened to me here, but one thing in particular comes to mind.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was told this story by a friend who worked in a hostess club where I was singing.
[SPEAKER_06]: The hostesses were all blonde, gaging, and they said...
[SPEAKER_06]: That there was one man... Whatever!
[SPEAKER_06]: Go fuck yourself!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyways, so they were saying that there was this one man who used to come in and beg them to sell a piece of their pubic hair for 10,000 yen per piece.
[SPEAKER_06]: So these girls would go in and use the toilets and pluck hair out of the heads and rub it until they were curly and looked authentic.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then they would come back and sell it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Paula, you're so clever!
[SPEAKER_06]: By the way, I don't want to really go into this thing with me and, uh, Naoki, but, uh, let's just say I'm sitting on his tuffet there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or, actually, he, well, yeah, my tuffet and, uh, yeah, there's some definite tuff, uh, touchy in there and stuff, and... Okay, I'm gonna go now.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you!
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, look over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on that note, I think we need to take a break and let this show try to find its life again.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, we'll be back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yeah, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: The chat room is just kind of, I can feel that blink from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just blink, blink, blink, blink.
[SPEAKER_07]: What the fuck are these people doing?
[SPEAKER_07]: My speakers are crying right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to go Kmart and get me some bitches.
[SPEAKER_06]: You are my destiny!
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to take a quick break, do a request that I saw in the chat room last break, and another little fun song, and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_15]: So you can be my my my my
[SPEAKER_15]: Honey, what we call love I still don't think of you at first My family still comes above If you wanna capture me It's as simple as can be Mr. Lennon said it, all you need is Mr. Lennon said it, all you need is Mr. Lennon said it, all you need is Love, my love, my love, my love, my love My love, my love, my love, my love
[SPEAKER_14]: and all that is.
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_15]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_15]: From Step Squad to Orange Labs, this DDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_15]: Holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla, holla!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, we were looking at the, somebody wanted to see the statistics for the station during the break.
[SPEAKER_07]: We were taking a look.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot more listeners in Japan recently, so a big hello to our friends overseas in Japan who started the addiction and it looks like we're just finishing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: If there's any truth to those rumors that DDR is dying in Japan, but somebody must still love it over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess 2DX is a very big game over there still, as well as Guitar Freaks and Drum Mania, very big.
[SPEAKER_07]: Still, from what we hear.
[SPEAKER_07]: Of course, I guess we don't really know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if anybody over there wants to email us, if you can write in English, because I don't know much Japanese, but if you do send Japanese... Many people in Japan know English very well.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's required learning for school.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obviously, if they're going to understand me giving the email address, orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com, give us a holler about what DDR and the Belmonte scene is like over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'd love to hear about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm being brought food.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't that lovely?
[SPEAKER_22]: It is great.
[SPEAKER_24]: So anyways, since you're eating and you're eating, I guess I could do the sim scene update.
[SPEAKER_20]: Some update.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually, we actually have some new versions of stuff out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: As you probably remember from my FU message of the week, DWI 203.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's brand new.
[SPEAKER_10]: There is one feature, though, I absolutely love in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the fact that every time you rebuild your song list, it exports a HTML file with your entire song list.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now I can actually update my song list and post it so people can see how many damn songs I actually have, which is...
[SPEAKER_10]: 1,218 right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Chatroom is saying, Slinky in the chatroom says, Stepmania Max 3 is coming out tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know if that's BS or what, but... Why would Slinky lie to us?
[SPEAKER_07]: He loves us.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know, but I play... Actually, though, I have to give props to Stepmania because it saved my party last night.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because since... For some reason, I don't know what it is, but some versions of DWI, they don't work my pads, and they don't work with...
[SPEAKER_10]: with my visualizations in the background.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I had to find something to work with my pads, and luckily I had a beta 6 of Step Mania 5, I believe, or 3 or whatever, and it worked, and it worked well.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was very pleased.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we played on Step Mania all last night, and it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other than that, DDRPC, two new characters have been released.
[SPEAKER_10]: Our fourth set of new characters.
[SPEAKER_10]: No pantsless rage?
[SPEAKER_10]: No pantsless rage.
[SPEAKER_21]: No three-titted at me.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was Rico and... Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ah, some chick, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rico and some chick.
[SPEAKER_10]: Rico and his hoe, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: So...
[SPEAKER_10]: So, that was that, and they have like white hair and look stupid, whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, that's some new stuff there.
[SPEAKER_08]: We go not so sloppy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other than that, um... We go ugly.
[SPEAKER_10]: Other than that, let's see, uh... Sylvia.
[SPEAKER_10]: Whatever, Sylvia is ho.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, Sylvia, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, um... See, last night, party.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was very fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got...
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell us about your little party while I shove chicken strips in my mouth.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I had a party last night for my birthday.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I had a little Beemani party there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Got to play on the Sim.
[SPEAKER_10]: Some of the popular songs there were Break Your Neck from Busta Rhymes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Peanut Butter Jelly, the baseball band.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, Peanut Butter Jelly.
[SPEAKER_10]: They loved that remix from Tourney Mix 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was pretty good.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, wait.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, that's not Tourney Mix 2.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's something else.
[SPEAKER_10]: But anyways, it's out there.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was also...
[SPEAKER_10]: I voted a poop.
[SPEAKER_22]: Whoopie on that!
[SPEAKER_22]: Big pile of the PCs.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I assume that since Tourney Mix 2 has been judging for about, well, close to a couple weeks now, that pretty soon we'll have results of who won that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't... No, I guess look for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jamie won.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyways... I have the update from the other room.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: I owned everybody in Tekken 4, thank you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I just owned Dave.
[SPEAKER_10]: Big Cans Part 2
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Big hands part two.
[SPEAKER_10]: See, other than that, some news, well, just some reminders.
[SPEAKER_10]: It looks like Team Guilo, their site's coming up October 1st, so look for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think, I'm not sure what their actual address is going to be, because Team Guilo got bought up by some guy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's nothing there, but they bought the domain name, so who knows for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: DWI, Insane... Okay, that's my FU of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you to Cyber Squatters.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unless they've got a valid use for the name Team Guilo, they shouldn't be allowed to buy that domain name.
[SPEAKER_07]: Julia Roberts needs to take them to court because she got her domain name and she knows how to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, DWI Insanity is going to be coming back up probably later this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: They said one or two weeks about a week ago, so I guess we can look for that.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's pretty much it for now.
[SPEAKER_20]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have gold.
[SPEAKER_20]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Freestyle Fridays
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't freestyle very well at all, so I haven't been paying too much attention to this, but I said I'd go watch sometime.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I guess a bunch of the good freestylers in town trying to get together and just have some fun little challenges and things like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are some fun ways to get people together?
[SPEAKER_07]: Does it have to be scheduled things?
[SPEAKER_07]: Could it just be everybody just kind of convening at one place?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like the bar cheers?
[SPEAKER_22]: We used to have our big gathering when we were trying to unlock stuff on Max 2 before they put in the code.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-huh, true.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, which pissed me and a bunch of people off.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, that was something that got the community together, was that common goal.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, there's other Max 2 machines where people don't know how the machines work well enough to put in the code, I guess, if you're, you know, retarded.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, there's all kinds of, you know, there's mini tourneys, there's our, you know, every so often bit money party that people randomly throw at random houses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you guys going to any fun parties in the Bay Area?
[SPEAKER_07]: What do they do in the Bay Area?
[SPEAKER_07]: What kind of get-togethers do you guys do over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we know we do it here in SAC, but...
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, you know, at Scandia over by Susan Valley or wherever it is.
[SPEAKER_29]: They have their Friday Night Fever and, I mean...
[SPEAKER_29]: Even people like RTF from the Bay Area, a lot of them, Friday nights, they make the roadie up there because the freestyle pod over there is so intense out there.
[SPEAKER_29]: It's such, things are really picking up over there.
[SPEAKER_29]: As far as get-togethers, I guess, for people like RTF Steps, well, we've gotten to a point where we like doing stuff, not just in B-Mind, we like doing sports stuff, like we either have to take a game of basketball or we'll have a big football game, which we are actually coming up, which is coming up soon, I think in early October.
[SPEAKER_29]: No, it's a fun thing to just throw people around instead of stepping on arrows, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I liked the whole bowling thing from last Sunday.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other fun get-togethers you guys have been to that have been Bomani-related?
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: and just make sure there's no drama.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anybody that's going to cause drama in your group, get them out.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, why don't they just do like, that'd be pretty cool, is, you know, they have like hacker conventions and conventions for everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: What about BimaniCon?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, this is a good topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why hasn't there been a big national Bomani convention yet, do you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think it's because the tournaments kind of take care of that on a smaller scale, so there's no need or desire for something national?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think it's just because the Bomani audience is mostly, now I know just about all of us, in fact, yes, all of us in this room are an exception, but the Bomani community is largely a high school base, which can't really afford to take the time to travel out of town for a weekend.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think the reasons are behind that?
[SPEAKER_22]: First and foremost, I've been going to conventions for seven years now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: You couldn't do, I think, a convention on just Beimani alone without, you know, without having it Beimani Plus.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, as far as a convention setting goes, I mean, it's not like you can sit there and watch, you know, go to a room and watch, you know, movies of people playing DDR or, you know, like you have movie rooms at anime sci-fi conventions or... You'd have a room that's like, oh my gods, meet Jason Enos and Mel B. Yeah.
[SPEAKER_29]: I think my importance level has just shot down 60 notches.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think for Baymani alone, as far as a convention setting, that it would be enough.
[SPEAKER_22]: You could maybe have your little small get-together.
[SPEAKER_22]: If it was something associated with, say, the release of a new game, something press-related, that might draw a crowd, I think.
[SPEAKER_22]: But you couldn't have BaymaniCon every year.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think that it would be big enough.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, well then maybe they can, instead of just Bomani, have like an amusing music gaming convention or something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because then you have Bomani stuff, you've got, you know, the Pump It Up, Parappa, all the music games, you know, Parappa and all that.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, a music gaming... I can see where a music gaming... Well, there is Classic Gaming Con that happens in Las Vegas.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess if Classic Gaming Con can pull it off.
[SPEAKER_22]: But they also have the betas, the prototypes, you know, old games that were supposed to come out that never did come out.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I think that basically anything that was coming out for Beimani has come out except for, you know, Smomics.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Smop one that was supposed... There was supposed to... There's a group called Smop in Japan.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's basically like the Japanese version of...
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: That has to be the worst Beaumontium I've ever played.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I like some of the music, don't get me wrong, but just the interface and everything, I didn't care for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just want to share.
[SPEAKER_10]: Seeing, since I do have all the Dreams Come True stuff and the True Kiss Destination, I have to say, all of those suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: They both suck.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're just awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: All their music just is very awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, aside from Sexy Planet and, like, Celebrate Night, they just, they all suck.
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked Africa.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the one song I liked on True Kiss Destination.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a cool song.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, but they've got one song called The Monster.
[SPEAKER_10]: The monster is coming.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's just, like, so awful.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, like, yeah, OHA is pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, but other than that, it's just crap.
[SPEAKER_22]: However, the beat meaning of Future Dreams Come True is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess maybe you could, but I'm thinking in terms of the broad spectrum of different conventions I've been to.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, I don't think you'd have enough to make anything larger than, you know, a one-day convention.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think it would be anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: So tournaments are pretty much as big as it's going to get.
[SPEAKER_17]: I think so.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then we could go back to that national tournament talk, but I think we even talked about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I think that was a talk last time Mel B was here.
[SPEAKER_07]: We talked about that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, uh, probably wouldn't be big enough, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd have to have huge prizes to entice people who want to fly all the way out to, you know, Las Vegas, uh, Bay Area, wherever you would choose to hold the tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, I don't know if it's possible.
[SPEAKER_29]: Well, it's not so much about incentive and prizes, but it's also, I mean, the thing a lot of people...
[SPEAKER_29]: and many more.
[SPEAKER_29]: We're quite at the level of networking where we can have a bunch of arcades all in sync, all on the same page, getting it all together.
[SPEAKER_29]: I'm not saying it can't happen, but there's just a lot more things people overlooked that have to be taken into account for such a thing to happen.
[SPEAKER_22]: It would definitely take a lot of work, and I don't know that many people would be willing to do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twins got a good idea for incentive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have it a strip DDR competition.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll judge.
[SPEAKER_17]: I'll judge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, another suggestion to make the convention more popular was to be a Bomani slash Hentai convention.
[SPEAKER_22]: That would definitely...
[SPEAKER_22]: S.S.R.
[SPEAKER_22]: Strip Strip Revolution
[SPEAKER_22]: I bought at least two of my, I have at least three Bin Money related products that I've purchased at Anime Expo, one of them being my second mixed step book, and a dance pad, and one of my versions of DDR, I think.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think it was, one of them or the other, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have like a ton now, so.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, I think we're going to take a really quick break, and then we're going to come back, and we're going to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: So... Wrap it up and what?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to wrap it up, and we'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_07]: What are we going to play in the break?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, let's play one of your mixes.
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to tell me a mix you want to play?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or not one of your mixes, but one of the mixes you brought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: You want to tell me which one you want to have the listeners hear?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, what I was going to do is introduce this one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Back in Fifth Mix, they had a competition, I guess.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't really heard much about it, for a Paranoia remix.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this guy who goes by the name STM won that competition.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I happened to find his website, and he has a Piano Ambient version of Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, you have to listen to the background there to fully get all of it, but you will catch some of what it is.
[SPEAKER_10]: But just listen to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It doesn't sound anything like you've heard before for Maximum Limited.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here we go.
Music
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: Listen to Orange Lounge Radio Because Bongo Demends It
[SPEAKER_07]: Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 12.
[SPEAKER_07]: When are we going to have Bongo back on this show?
[SPEAKER_22]: Whenever Bongo's not working on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_22]: I better talk to my man.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let Bongo have the day off.
[SPEAKER_07]: That kind of got a lot of reaction in the showroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of some mixed reaction.
[SPEAKER_07]: Majorly positive for the Max Unlimited.
[SPEAKER_07]: Again, a career in radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Far ahead for me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Sacramento Metropolis Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm the co-host.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't shut up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Smirked.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot of mixed reactions in the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of mostly positive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Kind of depressing though, don't you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: That song was kind of, I don't know, the way it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just feel like throwing myself off.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, Max Unlimited is depressing enough as it is because I can't pass it.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, you know, well, I can't on basic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Even in the chatroom, they said, Orange Lounge made me sad today.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just remember, little Miss Muffet sat on the tuffet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now she has HIV.
[SPEAKER_19]: Where's my red?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was just commenting in the middle of that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was funny because Mel B was sitting here reading scripture during that little passage.
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you like to share a little bit of that with us here, Mel?
[SPEAKER_07]: Would you like to share some of your voiceover talent with the Max song?
[SPEAKER_29]: Follow the light at the end of the tunnel.
[SPEAKER_29]: Do not resist.
[SPEAKER_29]: You shall be saved.
[SPEAKER_29]: Not.
[SPEAKER_29]: They'll be... 9 o'clock, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very pretty, thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of like the 5-9 piano version.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we have an amen!
[SPEAKER_05]: Woot!
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't you play it this way, please?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of like the 5ix9ine piano version we have in rotation on the Bomani Music and More program, which is always playing on the station when we're not here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty sad remix of that, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So is Bomani getting all depressed?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it the angsty phase?
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it the suicidal goth phase of Bomani?
[SPEAKER_22]: It will stay angsty as long as Politary keeps singing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Everybody will want it to slit their wrists after listening to her.
[SPEAKER_22]: At least we have Silhouette of My Mind, and that makes me happy in a sad and a gothy way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, Silhouette of My Mind, another little slit your wrist song there from Imani.
[SPEAKER_22]: That is a happy song if you listen to the lyrics.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, it's a happy song, but it sounds really... But I'm happy being all by myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm happy being sad.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am quite enthusiastically upset.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I guess that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we're going to wrap up the show now.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, any final thoughts from everybody here in the room?
[SPEAKER_22]: I have donuts.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have donuts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Matt, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't like Politary.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neither do I. It's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: She scares me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bradley, you have anything to say?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: Special guest Mel B, anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_29]: I had no idea DJ Konami sounded like Dick Vitale.
[SPEAKER_29]: Either way, I think he's dope.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Sharks Girl, Mel D, anything you want to say to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yawn.
[SPEAKER_24]: I've driven like 280, 300 miles today so far.
[SPEAKER_24]: I still have to drive home.
[SPEAKER_07]: You got two more hours to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I got to drive tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_07]: I get to drive to Frisco tomorrow, so that'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_20]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, um, what else?
[SPEAKER_07]: There was one other quick thing I wanted to say before the show was over, and now it's slipped my mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's slit your mind?
[SPEAKER_29]: I actually had a quick comment on someone who wrote something about glow sticks and ghosts being in a freestyle routine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_29]: Funny enough, I don't know if I mentioned this before, but when I was at an Omaha freestyle tourney back in April 20th of earlier this year, someone did do a glow stick routine with ghosts, and funny enough, he failed within 15 seconds.
[SPEAKER_29]: Somewhere, I believe, justice was served.
[SPEAKER_29]: That's kind of sad in a way.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm still not sure that anything involving lights and DDR is going to top Fuzzy Hat with candles on Healing Vision.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the number 420, either.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oops, I gotta switch CDs here real fast.
[SPEAKER_07]: Somebody fill.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fill, fill, filler, fiddler, fiddler, fiddler.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's Phil?
[SPEAKER_22]: Bimani is cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: Keep playing.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right?
[SPEAKER_24]: This DDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_07]: That really bugs me.
[SPEAKER_07]: We are in joy.
[SPEAKER_29]: Why aren't you?
[SPEAKER_22]: We expect you a nice play again.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now, new from Konami, the Politary sings the classics.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: Such wonderful... Such wonderful songs.
[SPEAKER_15]: Move!
[SPEAKER_07]: Move!
[SPEAKER_07]: Let them move!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh yes, that's... Shine Get!
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's an appropriate note to end the show on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shine Get!
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for listening, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see you next time.
[SPEAKER_30]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_30]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura, and Rob Roberts, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_30]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.