[SPEAKER_15]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Our live talk program begins now.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio may contain sexual and adult content and many instances of the F-word, which is not safe for children.
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn you, stop calling here!
[SPEAKER_12]: Isn't it 4215, pussywaves?
[SPEAKER_12]: You bitch!
[SPEAKER_12]: Now let me check this, it goes 212, fuck you!
[SPEAKER_12]: You have no morals, darling.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'd also like to add that I have my father's gun and the scorching kiss of purpose.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kiss my great nooch.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mecca lecca hi, mecca hi-dee-ho.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, I hate throwing up in public.
[SPEAKER_12]: Me too!
[SPEAKER_12]: Fucker, yeah?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm working on it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loser.
[SPEAKER_12]: Lame!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm the kind of my face...
[SPEAKER_10]: Breathing breath, heaving breath, heaving whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now you all just sit there and keep your mouths shut while I go listen to my Britney Spears records.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am your singing telegram.
[SPEAKER_04]: Live, but not really, from Roseville Golf Land here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a special edition of Orange Lounge Radio, I should say.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's so special it rides the short bus.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's episode number 10.5.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're calling it 10 and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: Episode 10 and a half of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because this isn't Sunday, but we're fooling you.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is our special Labor Day edition of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because we refuse to labor the day before Labor Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Jamie and I are going to be taking the weekend off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So as you're listening to this right now, Jamie and I are off somewhere vacationing.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't want to know what you're off doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Somewhere sunny.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since I know who you'll be with.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, actually, at the point that you're listening to this probably Sunday night at 7 o'clock, I'm probably going to be in Sunnyvale, actually.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I might be getting interviews and things like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish I could, but I'm spending all weekend and, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll just make Dan take me.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a private getaway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you should make Dan take you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Dan's going to be here tonight, correct?
[SPEAKER_22]: Somewhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to have to get an interview with him at some point.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_22]: For those who are uninformed, Dan is my significant other, also known as the great and terrible DanmanX, also known as GunstarHero for people who have seen me mention that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Also known as Big Hater of Bimani.
[SPEAKER_22]: He is not a Big Hater of Bimani.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's the one who got all, you know, who, like, you know, creamed his pants when he played Guitar Freaks.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Guitar Freaks is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_22]: Visual.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, nobody's allowed to vision dance with me.
I won't.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just...
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yeah, it's going to be a very experimental show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might not even be two hours long.
[SPEAKER_04]: It might be a weird kind of segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're kind of trying to divvy this up into little segments.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Brad is our timekeeper right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: He'll let me know when we hit 40 minutes for the first segment, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, we are now at a minute and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, I'm going to introduce everybody that's sitting out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I guess we should explain the layout.
[SPEAKER_04]: I wish this was TV sometimes, but we're going to explain the layout of Roseville Golf Club a little bit.
[SPEAKER_06]: Webcam, webcam.
[SPEAKER_04]: No webcam tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact, there hasn't been a webcam any week except the first week.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got to get that fixed.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we will.
[SPEAKER_04]: We promise.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, episode 11 next week is going to be a very different show because we're going to have a new intro.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've already got one planned out.
[SPEAKER_04]: And hopefully a new site and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you don't like the idea of a new intro?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I love the intro.
[SPEAKER_02]: It has right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we might dig it out of the archives occasionally.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll use it for tonight's show.
[SPEAKER_22]: We get the look from Irene.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, I'm going to introduce the people that are up here upstairs right now because we get some people here that we don't normally get on the show because when we tape at the quote-unquote studio, also known as my office, on Sundays we don't always get the same people.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we do have some of your old favorites joining us tonight besides the lovely DarkSakura and I. We haven't even introduced ourselves like we do at the beginning of every show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, they know who we are.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what it is?
[SPEAKER_22]: If they don't by now, then they must have been living under a rock.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't get to cheat tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have the computer screen in front of me with the script, the opening script, and what we're going to talk about.
[SPEAKER_22]: So we still have to plug the chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, because there will be people in the chat room right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they can talk about us while we're not paying attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, talk shit about us behind our back right now.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dude, Rick's playing with my wood.
You've got wood.
[SPEAKER_04]: I like wood.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was Rick.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's playing with my wood.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you learn lots about Rick on this show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to introduce everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to go around and introduce everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have Irene, lovely Irene, who's been on many, many shows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rice Princess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, I'm an old favorite.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think you need to change your Depends, dear.
[SPEAKER_04]: We have everybody's favorite DDRaholic say hi to Anita.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, you don't even know what we're doing, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you heard Orange Lounge before?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you even know...
[SPEAKER_02]: I've heard of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've sat through about two or three episodes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Biggest torture of your life, huh?
[SPEAKER_22]: It was so terrible, I just couldn't tear myself from the computer.
[SPEAKER_22]: A train wreck so bad you feel like you're in the middle of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then of course we have the always awesome Rick.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, this is Rick, also known on the boards as Rick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi, I'm Rick.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hi, Rick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that so?
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you have any words for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd just like to say that I'm Rick.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's Rick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm back again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Read the dang thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Before I ask questions, read the dank back.
[SPEAKER_04]: True words were never said.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or else, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm a funny man tonight.
[SPEAKER_19]: Motherfucker!
[SPEAKER_04]: Say hello to our timekeeper tonight, Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: We are now at four minutes and a half.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Four and a half minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: We only have two more hours to go, basically
[SPEAKER_22]: When we get tired of talking about Mimani, we do List List, and it's usually Mimani.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I was going to say, wait, Mimani, what's that?
[SPEAKER_22]: We have more people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, more people.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come over to the microphones and introduce yourselves.
[SPEAKER_18]: Introduce yourself.
[SPEAKER_18]: Look in the microphone.
[SPEAKER_18]: Say your name.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And who are you, miss?
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm Soonja.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Soonja.
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you are?
[SPEAKER_18]: Hi, I'm Rai Rai.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Rai Rai.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you an alcoholic, too?
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was the question?
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you an alcoholic?
[SPEAKER_22]: I like Holic.
[SPEAKER_04]: What games do you girls like to play here at Golfland?
[SPEAKER_18]: I like to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: She likes to play DDR.
[SPEAKER_18]: And what about you?
[SPEAKER_10]: I like playing Para.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ooh, she's a para goddess.
[SPEAKER_10]: Paralist.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to teach me some more because I don't know any.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know a few, but I look dumb when I do them.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to know more.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's barely.
[SPEAKER_04]: I clap and wave my hands.
[SPEAKER_22]: And shake your butt.
[SPEAKER_04]: And shake my butt to Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was like the first one I learned.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, actually the first one I learned.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was like the fifth one I learned.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the first one I learned was Boom Boom Fire because that's everybody's first para.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then Like a Virgin.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not mine.
[SPEAKER_22]: My first was Night of Fire.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, mine too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mine was 1-0-0.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-0-0?
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-0-0-0.
[SPEAKER_22]: One more whore.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-0-1 is the upgraded version.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1-0-1 is the upgraded version to 1-0-0.
[SPEAKER_22]: I still always thought it sounded like they were saying one more whore.
[SPEAKER_22]: One more whore.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you weren't at the show, the live show on Sunday.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was in Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like an awesome trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us all about it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Imagine 16 DDR Freak moderators sharing a room.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_22]: But no, there would just be random comments.
[SPEAKER_22]: Someone would go, oh, motherfucker.
[SPEAKER_22]: And someone would go, oh, you got three points.
[SPEAKER_22]: You flamed.
[SPEAKER_22]: Or, you're post-whoring.
[SPEAKER_22]: You're talking too much.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, does somebody walk around and filter people?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, if you're like, oh, shit, I messed up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Someone would go, poopy.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, but basically the first night when we got there, the first thing that happened is Evian, Colin, he came in, looked at Doreen, Miss Toy, and goes, oh, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, so once again, we get the, oh, I thought you were Asian for me, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those out there that don't know, DarkSakura is a honker.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we're going to introduce Ted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ted doesn't even know what's going on here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, I'm Ted.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have any idea what we're doing right now, Ted?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have no idea what you guys are doing right now.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's about as much as I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You've got to talk into the mics more or else we don't hear you.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_03]: I've got to...
[SPEAKER_22]: What are you talking about?
[SPEAKER_22]: He's a mushroom.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's a fuck guy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, more for my Vegas story.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because I am the mic whore now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to warn the listeners out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight's show, very different, very random.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could be the best show we ever do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Could be the fucking worst.
[SPEAKER_22]: You can hear a burp.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's more about burp later.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, I won a dog in one of the crane games because, once again, I raped the crane game and I won a dog and named him Burp.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, did the crane game call the police?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did it say... Oh, bye, Ry-Ry.
[SPEAKER_19]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: She left.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know who I feel... One of our regular listeners, Slinky, also known as Will, was here and, like, ready to be on the show and...
[SPEAKER_04]: We were supposed to start taping at 7.30 tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We got here and we thought, oh, we'll play one Bomani game and then we'll tape.
[SPEAKER_04]: Then one kind of turned into five.
[SPEAKER_04]: By the time we were ready to tape, Slinky's parents showed up and took him home.
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't last I saw him.
[SPEAKER_22]: He was napping in the sumo game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Slinky.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll get you on another show.
[SPEAKER_22]: We love you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Parents.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Take them away from the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you guys have to get going?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, wait, before... Okay, we'll take a break from the Vegas story.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to plug your new role-playing game that's coming out?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because this is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to plug it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, I guess so.
[SPEAKER_03]: My new game that I made after three years of work with me as the sole programmer, my friend Steve as the sole artist, is an epic-size role-playing game in 2D.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's an epic computer game.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's actually a...
[SPEAKER_03]: Dragon Warrior, Bitchy
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, it's a lot like Earthbound as well, which wouldn't surprise me because Earthbound, as some may or may not know, is Rick's most godly RPG ever.
[SPEAKER_03]: My favorite game of all time.
[SPEAKER_04]: The battles really remind me of Earthbound battles.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do you get a bat as a weapon?
[SPEAKER_03]: you actually get several bats as a weapon you can have a rock as a weapon or you can have a stick with a little nail poked through it that's what it's called a stick with a nail poked through it as a weapon no orange bat of justice?
[SPEAKER_03]: no but there's a hammer of justice that you get in the courthouse
[SPEAKER_03]: The Deer Carcass The Double Chin
[SPEAKER_03]: It's extremely powerful.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a very, very powerful item, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's a gaga, because if you hit people with your gaga, that's embarrassing as well as... It makes you go gaga.
[SPEAKER_03]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_03]: I wet myself.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: Daily.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are there any Bamani references in the game?
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you try at all to incorporate the DDR taking over my fucking life thing in there, or...
[SPEAKER_03]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_03]: There are so many jokes in there.
[SPEAKER_03]: So many megabytes of just text jokes that I can't even imagine that I didn't stick a few Bomani jokes in there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: So any expected time of release?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like in time for Christmas to put under the tree?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm hoping actually to be done with it by the end of September.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm thinking as far as that goes.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're getting really close to done.
[SPEAKER_03]: The bug counts.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're not getting anything back at all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I haven't played the new one yet, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the stickler on beta testing, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_03]: As soon as we're done with that, we're moving on to Cedric the Littlest Demon, where you fight the devil, then you fight Nietzsche in Limbo, and then you have to fight God in Heaven, and then you win the game when you can kill God.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so we're hoping that killing the God game will be cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's only on this Black Matrix-y, though.
[SPEAKER_22]: Have you ever heard of Black Matrix?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, uh-uh.
[SPEAKER_22]: Black Matrix is an RPG where, in their universe, God and Satan fought, and Satan won.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ooh, cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: So you play as the slave of a dominatrix.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm down with that, yo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it going to be something you have to pay for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Is it going to be completely free?
[SPEAKER_04]: Or what's the deal?
[SPEAKER_03]: QDRPG is going to be totally free.
[SPEAKER_03]: Depending on how many people we get playing it, we may or may not do Cedric free as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: But QDRPG 2, which is going to be completely different, has absolutely nothing to do with QDRPG 1 whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_04]: As most old Nintendo sequels did.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like Castlevania 2.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nothing like the first at all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and they're going to be completely different.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's going to be a completely different idea.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're definitely in charge for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: And actually the game after that is going to be 3D.
[SPEAKER_03]: But we still get free copies, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Always going to get free copies from all my friends.
[SPEAKER_04]: Always.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you guys listening have to pay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for interviewing.
[SPEAKER_04]: And we'll let all our listeners know when QDRPG is released and where you can get a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you like them RPG type games, you guys want to comment?
[SPEAKER_04]: And before we change the subject, I don't think Rick brought it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to give some credit to Timmy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Timmy did an awesome job on the soundtrack on this game.
[SPEAKER_05]: If you like techno-ish type of music and stuff like that, it's great.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's got good music.
[SPEAKER_04]: And probably the best thing that I like about this game, it's just full of great jokes and cheesy shit like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: You gotta play it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's not going to be like Diablo-style graphics or anything, if that's what you're expecting.
[SPEAKER_04]: But it's 8-bit goodness.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a cross between Super Nintendo and Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a little more than 8-bit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, maybe like 10-bit.
Three and a half!
[SPEAKER_04]: You wanted to say something, Irene?
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, did he say something about fighting Nietzsche on there?
[SPEAKER_02]: The philosopher guy?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going to be in the next game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that's what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the next game.
[SPEAKER_02]: The philosopher guy or whatever?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Knowing Rick, yeah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: It would be rather wrong to fight him with the Bruce's Philosopher song in the background.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ehh, Manuel Kett was real pissed that he was very ready, stable.
[SPEAKER_08]: The armies, yeah, run by Jesus and Santa, the holodeus and such, stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's great, just different references throughout the entire game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's good stuff.
[SPEAKER_20]: So, back to my Vegas thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, yes, let's get back to the Vegas trip.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we wanted to make sure we got Rick's plug on the air before he had to go, so.
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, anyway, I was in Vegas and y'all weren't, so.
So.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, basically, when we first got there, it was basically all the moderators hanging out together.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I mean, we were all of us moderators anyway.
[SPEAKER_22]: We went to the food court to hang out.
[SPEAKER_22]: I, like, played $10 worth of nickels and then won, like, five of it back on video poker, which I apparently own at.
[SPEAKER_22]: and then um yeah like my total winnings for the whole weekend was like two dollars and ninety five cents which is part of my cab fare um notable how much a foot long those those hot dogs i did not buy an elephant penis they were selling these hot dogs that were like two feet long and really fat so they were being referred to as elephant peni as the cock of the elephant anyway
[SPEAKER_22]: So as it went on that night, we went to the Rio for the gigantic, humongous seafood buffet.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like 30 bucks, but you could get sashimi, Maine lobster, calamari, all kinds of cool, awesome seafood.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, and then, you know, that night at the Rio, there was this awesome Perfect Attack showdown between, um, uh, Potguy and, um, uh, Enoan, or Nor, as he's also known.
[SPEAKER_22]: There's also, uh, uh, Blue was also showing off some pretty, pretty awesome, um, uh, double skills, you know, going up into the sixes and sevens on some of those.
[SPEAKER_22]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Um.
[SPEAKER_22]: I, of course, raped the crane machine there and ended up giving up a lot of my stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Walking back, we were going back inside of the hotel and all of a sudden I hear, DDR Freak!
[SPEAKER_22]: And that's when our Stalker fanboys, DJ Bubbles and his friend, found us.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess apparently they came from out of town to find us.
[SPEAKER_22]: and buy coffee for us or something.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: But the next day, well, I didn't fall asleep until after 7 a.m.
[SPEAKER_22]: for some reason because I was really tired.
[SPEAKER_04]: Too much excitement.
[SPEAKER_22]: We went to the Game Land Arcade, which was freaking amazing.
[SPEAKER_22]: That arcade, I played Mambo a Go-Go there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Mambo!
[SPEAKER_22]: No, forget this.
[SPEAKER_22]: For two tokens a play.
[SPEAKER_22]: DDR Max 2 for 2 tokens of play, Beat Mania 3 6-core for 2 tokens of play, Radiant Silver Gun.
[SPEAKER_04]: We apologize to your speakers.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was literally my reaction.
[SPEAKER_22]: I got to play the photo game in Biohazard Gun Survivor 2, which was really amazing.
[SPEAKER_22]: The arcade owned, and of course we were showing up the, well, I didn't, but the locals were sort of sitting there, you know, mouth open, watching as some of the more notable freestylers, namely Mel B, DJ 8-Ball.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is the story making you excited over there?
[SPEAKER_08]: Past memories of Boomtown in Reno.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_22]: But, you know, they were showing their stuff, and...
[SPEAKER_04]: And then everybody went back because some people wanted to go see O. No, I heard about, well, I heard about that I guess there was some kind of pump it up challenge going on.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was Friday night.
[SPEAKER_22]: Apparently one of the locals got really pissed off.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's like, you're stealing my spotlight, those are my arrows.
[SPEAKER_22]: And he was basically getting owned.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, I found a Prop Cycle, so I was happy.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because Prop Cycle is the best game ever by Namco.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, back to Saturday night.
[SPEAKER_22]: Iguana Girl, Islander, and I all went to the Star Trek experience and met up with my friend Tiara and her man Rick.
[SPEAKER_04]: Which you have to do if you ever go to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whether you're a fan of the show or not, it's just the coolest thing in Vegas, I think.
[SPEAKER_04]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, we went sober once.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then we had a warp core breach.
[SPEAKER_22]: We basically, between the three of us, between me, Iguana Girl, and Islander, we had a large, they shared a large one and a small one, and then I had a small one all to myself.
[SPEAKER_22]: And, ooh, okay, I just got given a tape.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tal just showed up.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to say hello to everybody?
[SPEAKER_22]: Your CD's in the car.
[SPEAKER_04]: And what up, my niggers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway... You can address those cards and letters to Tal, courtesy of Tal's house.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was telling a story!
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, yes, finish your story.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_22]: So after my friends left, we had this drunken walk over to Circus Circus so Iguana Girl could play the old machine up in the Midway, which was ass on the right player side because half the buttons didn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the same machine that I played DDR on for the very first time with Circus Circus.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lost your DDR virginity.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, lost my DDR virginity.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a USA machine now.
[SPEAKER_22]: The 1.5 is downstairs and actually has a good pad.
[SPEAKER_22]: Last time I played.
[SPEAKER_22]: But anyway...
[SPEAKER_22]: There was more, no we don't have 4th Plus yet, there was more staying up until all hours of the morning and playing Taboo, Drunken Taboo, which was like the absolute winner.
[SPEAKER_22]: And that actually had the quote of the evening, which was, it's like a penguin, but it's in this place where the British used to send their criminals and that was trying to get them to say kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, this is... Because, you know, Taboo, you have a list of five words that, you know, you cannot use to describe your main word that's on the thing, and you have a timer.
[SPEAKER_22]: Like, I used penguin twice.
[SPEAKER_22]: I was using penguin for tuxedo, and I used penguin... It's like, it's colored like a penguin, but it's equine for a zebra.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, mine made sense.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know where you get, you know, kangaroo from.
[SPEAKER_22]: Kangaroo?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm lost.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the other best one, it's like...
[SPEAKER_22]: I was trying to get someone to say the word blow.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I read that one online.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the quote was, it's like, if I wanted you to suck my cock, you would be giving me a blank job.
[SPEAKER_22]: So... Did they get it?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, actually, they got it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And our team actually did get the kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_22]: So that was... We just started listing off Australian animals like koala, kangaroo.
[SPEAKER_22]: So... Anyway, um...
[SPEAKER_22]: The next day was, you know, we all checked out and a bunch of people went to this other buffet and I went to All You Can Eat Sushi with my friend and hung out at Circus Circus and got to play Tsurugi, which is the best game ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's basically, it's like mo-cap boxing and...
[SPEAKER_22]: Police 911, only you have a sword with a light sensor and you get to, you know, cut people in half and cut off their head.
[SPEAKER_22]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: The U.S.
[SPEAKER_22]: name is Blade of Honor.
[SPEAKER_22]: Apparently DJ Abba found a Tegno motion machine at Excalibur in the basement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_22]: But I didn't get to play it, unfortunately.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I played Pump It Up Perfect, but it was a crappy, broken one.
[SPEAKER_22]: And they had a great firefighters machine, Ferrari F9355, the full three monitor one.
[SPEAKER_22]: New York had an awesome arcade for the casinos.
[SPEAKER_04]: But the best arcade you went to would be that game.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, Game Land.
[SPEAKER_22]: GameWorks is ass, except they have Sonic Fighters there.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Tekken 4 on a projection TV with a couch with controllers attached to it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is good for people to know, because Vegas is a big tourist spot.
[SPEAKER_22]: Do not play Guitar Freaks there.
[SPEAKER_22]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_22]: And the DVR is a USA machine, and they overprice everything.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's like $1.50 for a play on a USA machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, it's like the Metreon.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, but it's like ass.
[SPEAKER_22]: At least it's, you know, the decor is better, and they play Good Trance in the background.
[SPEAKER_04]: So...
[SPEAKER_22]: How many places did you guys go?
[SPEAKER_22]: All over the damn city.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get to see any showgirls?
[SPEAKER_22]: This one drag queen showgirl gave me a flyer.
[SPEAKER_22]: And people were collecting pictures of the boobs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you get any free prom?
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't want any free prawn because there was like... The free prawn in Vegas is stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was like they were all ugly and they were fake boobs and one of them was a man.
[SPEAKER_22]: Because you could see the Adam's apple.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ew!
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, so this is actually starting to lead into my fuck you of the week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now we don't have the music backdrops tonight, so we'll just have to hum it.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you can edit it in.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is fucked up!
[SPEAKER_22]: Okay, anyway, we can edit that in.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, so, my fuck you of the week starts off with us getting out, with Iguana Girl Jessica and I getting on the plane, and this like really rude asshole was on his cell phone, and...
[SPEAKER_22]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_22]: We, um, we, uh, I turned around and said, you know, excuse me, you need to watch what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, I fussed at him.
[SPEAKER_22]: He's like, oh, um, I'm having five conversations at once.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then he just started walking off.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, um, we were over there laughing at him when they told him to turn off his cell phone before takeoff because apparently he didn't hear that either.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then there was this guy behind me whose kid kept kicking me in the back of the chair and I kept looking at the kid.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I was just talking to Jessica, you know, my business was like, yeah, my fight was okay except I kept getting kicked in the butt.
[SPEAKER_22]: And he's like, stop whining.
[SPEAKER_22]: And apparently he kept bitching when I drafted him out listening to my, you know, Luna C compilation.
[SPEAKER_22]: He was, you know, he was a fucktard.
[SPEAKER_22]: So fuck him and fuck the guy on the cell phone.
[SPEAKER_22]: And my other fuck you of the week goes to the unemployment development department.
[SPEAKER_22]: Ha ha ha.
[SPEAKER_22]: Which, okay, I didn't get any sleep last night, so forgive me for slurring a little bit and being tired and bitchy.
[SPEAKER_04]: She just sounds a little drunk.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's a little hungover.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I'm PMS-y, so don't give me any bullshit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, I tried to get out of it.
[SPEAKER_22]: I couldn't get out of it.
[SPEAKER_22]: So I hop on the bus at 10 a.m.
[SPEAKER_22]: Go all over freaking Sacramento to try to get to... Basically, it's where Stockton Boulevard and Broadway meet, but it's like another block past that.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's at 50th and Broadway.
[SPEAKER_22]: I got down there, kept napping on the bus.
[SPEAKER_22]: I got there at a quarter after 1.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is from getting on the bus at 10.
[SPEAKER_19]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_22]: And I was there for 30 minutes.
[SPEAKER_22]: The guy was so condescending and was talking down, and I probably had more brain in my butt than he did in all of his head.
[SPEAKER_22]: So...
[SPEAKER_22]: So, you know, basically I got out of there as fast as possible and got home at like a quarter after five o'clock and decided and just wolfed down all these espresso beans so I'm a combination of tired and hyper.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, fuck EDD.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck them right in their stupid ass.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck the guy on the cell phone.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck anybody who acts like that on their cell phone.
[SPEAKER_22]: And fuck the stupid guy from Burbank who sat behind me.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck him.
[SPEAKER_22]: Fuck them all.
[SPEAKER_22]: May they die.
[SPEAKER_04]: So fuck Absolute.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Matt, also known as Loki, who just showed up, has a fuck you of the week as well.
[SPEAKER_05]: It goes to my fucking laptop because it won't read my card writer.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's the whole reason I bought the damn laptop is to use my card writer on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: And if it doesn't work, then what the hell did I get a crappy laptop for?
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll buy it from you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: That changes everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_04]: Scratch that from the list.
[SPEAKER_04]: My fuck you of the week, I don't have one.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't think of anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: If I think of one later in the show, I'll mention it.
[SPEAKER_04]: My fuck you of the week is you don't have a fuck you of the week?
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob isn't being nice to this week.
[SPEAKER_20]: The Penguin has a fuck of the week.
[SPEAKER_20]: And I've played Max Unlimited so many fucking times.
[SPEAKER_20]: I'm guessing over 30, I'm so pissed off, and so is my legs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he fails on the same note every fucking time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fails the same note every fucking time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's... Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of anger here.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll kill you.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh shit, he killed me.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we sympathize.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, I've been there so many times.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember the first time I tried to beat Max 300.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_05]: And one more, fuck Brazil Golf Land for not having 4th Plus yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though we're here right now, just pretty much loitering is what we're doing.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're just sitting upstairs.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're in the party area right now.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's a lot of partying going up on Yahoo.
[SPEAKER_04]: This employee came by and looked at us funny earlier, like, uh, are they supposed to be here?
[SPEAKER_22]: Apparently so, because we have the microphones.
[SPEAKER_05]: And is that any different than usual?
[SPEAKER_05]: They always look at us funny.
[SPEAKER_05]: True.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's when we're playing.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's when Rob's playing Deluxe.
[SPEAKER_05]: Let's go interview employees.
[SPEAKER_05]: That sounds like fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we could do that in a later segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: That would be great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think actually what I want to do maybe next segment is maybe just be mobile.
[SPEAKER_04]: Since we have a mobile unit here, maybe we'll walk around and tour Golfland and give our opinions on the games.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk about every single thing that is broken.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like everything?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, like everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it'll be a nice long segment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, we've got two hours to fill.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wee!
[SPEAKER_08]: Since we just kind of got off the whole Vegas thing, I was recently in Vegas, and I happened to come across a Dance Dance Revolution tournament.
[SPEAKER_08]: They had a Perfect Attack and a Freestyle tournament, and they had 40 slots for each.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got the 11th slot for Freestyle, so I was good there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I definitely got to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I got 41 on the Perfect Attack, and that pissed me off.
[SPEAKER_08]: And somebody dropped out, so I got 40.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm like, yes, but I played last.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, I was waiting for like, what, four hours to play, something like that?
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, I get through and I play my freestyle, and I did great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had fun.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did all three of the songs perfectly.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then the guy that goes after me does a fucking backflip over the freaking rail and goes through and hits his... I don't know how he did it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I got second there, so I got a CD player.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then in Perfect Attack I played last, and I triple-hit a couple of songs.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that was, um...
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I got first place, 500 bucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And there's, um, you know, that's my story.
[SPEAKER_22]: Sweet!
[SPEAKER_22]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't know we had a local that owned the Vegas tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's news.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've noticed that there's a different breed of freestyle in Vegas, you know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Exosauce?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey there.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: The views and opinions of our guests.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, the Vegas freestylers suck.
[SPEAKER_22]: I've noticed lots of A-Team action going on, so when I broke out, my new freestyle loved me.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had a crowd.
[SPEAKER_05]: I found a place for my freestyle.
[SPEAKER_05]: Vegas, here I come.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dynamite Rage.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, I'm making this announcement now when we have our tournament at, hopefully, you know, we're trying to get it at Folsom Game Room.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_22]: because we may have a particular machine by then.
[SPEAKER_04]: There may be a new machine coming in that we want to have another tournament on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Can't say anything about it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't say until it comes in.
[SPEAKER_22]: But we're either going to have it here or there, here at Roseville Golf Land or there, if ever I hear back from management.
[SPEAKER_22]: Anyway, I'm going to try to contact them again.
[SPEAKER_22]: But back to what I was saying, one of the freestyle segments is going to be a team style freestyle.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_22]: So you will be encouraged to pull out your best knee drops, hand plants, back flips, but no matrix walk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Aw, no matrix walks.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's pretty much going to be the replacement for improv freestyle.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, because improv was where it was a novel idea, the novelty.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a novel idea, just a lot of shitty entrants.
[SPEAKER_04]: And sorry to those of you that entered Improv Freestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: There were some good ones, but a lot of you got up there and PA'd.
[SPEAKER_22]: It wasn't necessarily that the skill was bad, it's that they got some ass steps.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know if it was ass steps or me, but mine really sucked.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, part of the problem was that, you know, our bad, we picked, I should just say my bad, blame me, I was in freestyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought, oh, four to six feet songs, people can improv those, those aren't too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoops, I probably should have done like two and three foot songs and one foot songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, if I ever do another improv freestyle tournament, it's all going to be beginner songs on USA as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can only improv on Heavy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I love improv.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's how I make all my freestyles.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's improv over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Were you playing last October?
[SPEAKER_08]: Were you playing in October?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I haven't gotten to play in any of the Sacbimani tournaments.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, there's going to be another one coming up by the end of the year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, if it's at Folsom Game Room, I have no way to get there.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll find you a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Somebody here at the table will get you.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're on the board, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'll get you there somehow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I posted on the whole series.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, but I do want to say one improv freestyle that I liked a lot at the tournament was Bradley.
[SPEAKER_20]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: For those who didn't see, he did Little Bitch.
[SPEAKER_04]: And he just kind of got into it.
[SPEAKER_04]: At the end, he was just like, rawr.
[SPEAKER_22]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And he didn't say hi, so I said hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_22]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_04]: The Little Bitch himself, Bradley.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whee!
[SPEAKER_04]: How was your move?
[SPEAKER_04]: You just moved recently to get a little closer to Golfland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, it went good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still unpacking stuff, moving things around.
[SPEAKER_04]: You had to move out of the town of sorority life and get into a little closer to Rosa Golfland.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, yeah, because he was in Davis where they film sorority life.
[SPEAKER_04]: Whoa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk to Anita, because we haven't talked to her much during this show yet.
[SPEAKER_22]: Spotlight's on you!
[SPEAKER_04]: Spotlight's on you, girl.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tell us about where you're from.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're from a little hick town up north.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I'm from Yuba City.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you want to give a little plug, because I know Yuba City has a little team of regulars up there that play, and I love the name of this team, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: So tell us about the team up there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, our team is called the Token Stealing Toddler Stompers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Best name ever.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate Golf Land for the sole reason that you have to babysit your freaking tokens.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we got sick and tired of doing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: We actually inspired this new setup of plastic tokens.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we don't use those anymore because there's not enough people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, you know when you got like a thousand tokens up on the machine.
[SPEAKER_02]: If everybody has their own color-coded token...
[SPEAKER_02]: Then you can tell who's, you know, in line.
[SPEAKER_22]: They were using licenses at GameWorks so that people wouldn't run off with their cards.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh!
[SPEAKER_22]: You know, ID cards student IDs licenses.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: And explain why, what do you mean by cards?
[SPEAKER_05]: Because some people may not have been to GameWorks ever.
[SPEAKER_22]: They use token, instead of tokens, they use those little credit cards like the Metreon uses.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, you were saying about your team.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Token Stealing Tyler Stompers was inspired by a little incident that happened at one of our arcades.
[SPEAKER_02]: A little kid got into a little trouble, and we sort of, well, one of our girls, her name is May, and she ended up pushing the little kid a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a little bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a tiny bit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_04]: So how is the scene in a little, because for those who don't know, Yuba City is kind of one of those towns that's like, it's just kind of there on the side of the road in the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, now it's getting bigger because it has the Sacramento Amphitheater in the town, so it's getting a little bit more notoriety that way.
[SPEAKER_04]: But how is it playing DDR like in the middle of nowhere, where you've got to really drive a long way to get something outside of DDR?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I work in Sacramento, so driving's not too bad for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But we do have a Max 2 now, so that is a lot of fun.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody has a freaking Max 2 now.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Illegal kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, happy kids.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, my boots.
[SPEAKER_04]: My legs hurt.
[SPEAKER_04]: My boots and my leg.
[SPEAKER_04]: Boot leg.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, yeah, same.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's the... Hey, we like to think that we're legal kids.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're the great pretender.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's really not that bad in Yuba City altogether.
[SPEAKER_02]: The folks, I mean, as DDR communities go, we've got a lot of really great people there.
[SPEAKER_02]: We used to have two places to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now we only have one, but the people who work there are really good to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: They listen to us.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we want the machine turned up, they're happy to do it, and we've never had problems there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's really great, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That sounds like a dream come true.
[SPEAKER_04]: In fact...
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, what was that again?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's unlike here at Golfland, where when we ask them to turn it up, they turn it down to half volume.
[SPEAKER_08]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's because they're backward ass here, but we're not complaining, are we?
[SPEAKER_22]: Because we're getting 4th Plus.
[SPEAKER_22]: I am complaining.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am very much complaining.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we going to complain when they get 4th Plus, though, to replace USA?
[SPEAKER_04]: USA will be gone, replaced with 4th Plus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that wonderful?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, somewhat, yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: You can play Konga, feel into your heart's content.
[SPEAKER_08]: As far as I know, everything on USA is going to be on there.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is my outlook on this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because USA is where the newbies go to play, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: So they take USA, we got Max 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we got 4th Plus, we're going to want to play Max 2 and 4th Plus.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where are the newbies going to go?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, they're going to fail 4th Plus immediately and you get to play up next.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to go to hell, that's where they're going to go.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, they're going to go play Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll just send them to play Spider Stomp.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, but see, here's the other thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: The people at Sunsplash are also very stupid in making it so you can't fail on your first song if it's on, you know, little, or not little, rather, you know, standard, the first note.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, standard, basic.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's stupid, and so that's still one song where you have to wait and stuff, and watching them hurts, I swear.
[SPEAKER_08]: It hurts to see them suck so bad, because...
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, some of them have the basic idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we all started off somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but we all... I'm going to say, I'm hoping that we all started off higher than some of the people that play here.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, just jumping around on the freaking pad.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know none of us would be where we are today if we started there, because we would have given up long ago.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no mercy with Ted, I guess.
[SPEAKER_22]: I started off at home.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that's something the announcer should start saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, oh, my eyes are bleeding.
[SPEAKER_22]: Your dance is like burning.
[SPEAKER_04]: Your dance makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_22]: We have more intros to do, more people to show up.
[SPEAKER_22]: Give us your name and your nickname and a little bit of your history.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any history you want to give.
[SPEAKER_04]: It doesn't have to be DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to give the black book history or your job history.
[SPEAKER_04]: Surgical, medical history, whatever.
[SPEAKER_09]: My name is Eric.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm Punk Knight.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't have a history.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just kind of appeared here, you know.
[SPEAKER_09]: Here, I'll do his history.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the leader of a... A cult?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not a cult.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, not really a terrorist group, but let's just say they get jobs done.
[SPEAKER_05]: Called the Triple F ETA, Former Fast Food Employees Turned Assassins.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_05]: See, other than that, he does his own music, he's totally into punk rock and that kind of stuff, and metal, and that kind of cool shit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dude, you know me better than I do.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay, here, somebody else.
[SPEAKER_22]: I need to make an announcement, Rob gave me a quarter, so I'm getting candy.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speak, speak, I demand you.
[SPEAKER_02]: If I give you two quarters, will you get me some candy too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we have a shy one?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll speak for them.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, I'm Melanie.
[SPEAKER_19]: I used to go on the boards by Carefree Mel.
[SPEAKER_19]: I'm very quiet, so I'm not going to say much.
[SPEAKER_19]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: That voice sounds so familiar.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, Mel, you sound really hot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is radio, you know.
I know.
Isn't it cool?
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, Mel, you're dating Punk Night, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: He's so dreamy.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it that you like about Bunk Nye?
[SPEAKER_04]: What is it that attracts you to him?
[SPEAKER_19]: It's his one eye!
[SPEAKER_04]: And your response to that?
[SPEAKER_05]: It hurts.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh yeah, I forgot to mention, he's also into Invader Zim, because Invader Zim rocks.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, that's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jonan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jonan altogether.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not just Invader Zim.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jonan Vasquez is a god.
[SPEAKER_09]: Jonan Vasquez is the godliest god of all gods.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, we're going to take a quick break here and we'll be right back with more of Orange Lounge Radio episode 10 and a half semi-live from Roseville Golf Land here on Wednesday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're taping a little early so we can have the weekend off.
[SPEAKER_22]: Add candy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yummy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back after some songs.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you want to join our chat room, the people who might be listening right now, join our chat room.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just go to any other side IRC server, like irc.eggheads.org, and you're going to join Channel Pound's Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: I almost said Sakmamani, but you might find some of us in there, but actually the channel is Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: You hear the priest that's trying to keep his goddess fleece Love's shining eternally, love will make you feel so free Come on girl, it's okay for satisfaction You must pray, same as passion, aim for love It's shining in the temple of love
[SPEAKER_17]: You threw the midnight out, it's a secret Love and peace, soul and heart, it will release So, bow your head and pray, it's gonna take your fear away Flying like the snow, I dove out of the temple of love
Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, Loki, VOG Network, DJ Ranma S, Actdeft,
[SPEAKER_13]: For the steps by the Orange Labs, this DDR sucks!
[SPEAKER_13]: Holla Holla Holla Holla Holla Holla
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, we're back and we're coming back from break and Jamie is going to attempt 3-2-1 stars.
[SPEAKER_04]: So this is 3-2-1 stars, the Jamie mix.
[SPEAKER_04]: She had a 9 combo.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, 11.
[SPEAKER_04]: She got double digits.
[SPEAKER_04]: She just lost about 70% of her bar in like 3 seconds.
[SPEAKER_04]: There she goes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, not too bad.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're not doing as bad as she said you were going to do, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh, she got danger.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Go, Jamie, go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, failed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, we are back, and we're on the lower level now, where all the games are.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can you start the clock for me, by the way?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you, that's alright.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hey, that's not bad for suck.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're walking around the bottom level.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we want to walk around and look at the various stuff that Golfland has here?
[SPEAKER_04]: We can do that once I'm done putting my initials in.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie's going to put her initials back in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is a special edition because we decided to take Labor Day weekend off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we thought we'd tape the show a little early.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's actually Wednesday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're at Golfland.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we are taping live.
[SPEAKER_04]: No do-overs.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's just like it was a live show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except we have lots of toys here.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Brad likes toys, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Mmm, toys.
[SPEAKER_04]: So what do we want to do?
[SPEAKER_04]: We want to walk around and give a little tour of Delphi?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't want to do anybody publicly.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm holding a bench of stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who wants to hold my wood?
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for volunteering for that, Ted.
[SPEAKER_04]: We just got a funny... Hi.
[SPEAKER_22]: What are you guys exactly recording for?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we're doing a school project.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: For Oakmont High.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we're doing an online radio program.
[SPEAKER_22]: We have an internet radio show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Would you like to say some words for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_18]: Actually, I need to tell you that you need to talk to the manager before you guys can go walking around recording stuff.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're just recording ourselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, we actually do a show online that promotes the line of the music games.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we advertise this place for free.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so... And then the shit hits the fan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we could go outside, I guess, if you'd rather not us taping here.
[SPEAKER_18]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_18]: You've got to talk to the manager.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_18]: We're going to talk to the manager.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: We hate Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might possibly get kicked out of the show, have to end the show early because of this.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll have to see what's going to happen here.
[SPEAKER_22]: We can fill up with music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we can fill up something.
[SPEAKER_22]: I will play more Beatmania for your listening pleasure.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can figure something out.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll listen to the Brad mix.
[SPEAKER_22]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might have to go to Folsom Game Room or someplace that would let us do a show there.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_22]: And he's going through the list and stopping on something tack.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what would really suck?
[SPEAKER_04]: What if they took the tape?
[SPEAKER_22]: Then that would make them buy us a new one.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're eagerly awaiting what's going to happen here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, this is somewhat funny.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could run away.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, what were you saying?
[SPEAKER_04]: I said, where's the fun in that, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know, where's the fun in that?
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because if they did throw us out for trying to do our show, I doubt we'd come here very much in the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see what's going to happen when Mr. Manager comes back.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't know if there's anything interesting new or going on in the Mamani world right now, news-wise.
[SPEAKER_22]: We haven't had Matt's sim update.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah, I bet Matt has a Matt's sim update.
[SPEAKER_04]: We should get him over here.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we're being stared at by an employee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, are we?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, is he waving?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, he waved and he walked off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, so we got the go ahead.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's go interview him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_04]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_04]: That manager looks like he's 16 years old.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't think that's the manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: If the manager's some like 500 pound like sumo wrestler, I'm getting out of here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, I gotta go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh well, she's coming back.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if she's going to give us an update or what's going on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Who was the manager?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we're going to see what's happening.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's step away from the machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see what's going on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we thought that guy was the manager.
[SPEAKER_18]: That would be the day.
[SPEAKER_18]: Can we get that on tape?
[SPEAKER_04]: So you enjoy working at Golf Land?
[SPEAKER_04]: She can't comment on tape or else she'd get into trouble.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I'm sure she'd say nothing but good things.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes, Gothland is winner.
[SPEAKER_04]: Except maybe the little kids who destroy things around here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows about that?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is that a go for the taping or not?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we don't know because the manager's got to come downstairs.
[SPEAKER_18]: I don't think he's going to decline you guys from taping.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Even though a lot of people film home videos and stuff here?
[SPEAKER_22]: Same difference, only audio.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's not going to talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is interesting.
[SPEAKER_04]: We weren't expecting this development.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, maybe we should take another quick break then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do we want to take a quick break?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, no, because I kind of want to get this on air, whatever happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_22]: What, are we leaving?
[SPEAKER_04]: No, we're going to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: The manager's coming down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: True.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, we can finish up the show somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're back here by freaking 10.
[SPEAKER_04]: 10 o'clock.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think they're closing at 10 now, so... We have more of the Brad mix going on on Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to go listen to Brad play on Beatmania?
[SPEAKER_22]: Um, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: What is he playing?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because it's hurting my ears.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't even know that song.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Crimson.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are they allowed to tape us and use us for their commercials, but we're not allowed to tape them?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good answer.
[SPEAKER_04]: They probably think we're profiting off of this.
[SPEAKER_22]: No, we pay to do our show.
[SPEAKER_02]: We pay out of pocket.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is the guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: We think.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're recording an internet radio show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Just our group.
[SPEAKER_22]: We run an internet radio show every Sunday night and we're basically taking the Sunday off so we decided to do a live show at our favorite Wednesday hangout because we come every Wednesday.
[SPEAKER_22]: And we didn't think that there would be an issue with it.
[SPEAKER_22]: If there is, we're sorry.
[SPEAKER_21]: Right now, I'll go ahead and do it.
[SPEAKER_21]: I thought you had a filming crew here.
[SPEAKER_21]: No.
[SPEAKER_21]: But usually we don't have a problem with it.
[SPEAKER_21]: We just like to book in advance.
[SPEAKER_21]: And so we can know what the interview's about and that kind of a thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, we're just a bunch of dumb kids and we're not doing anything special.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is spontaneous, really.
[SPEAKER_21]: And also, I recognize your kids, you know, in the group.
[SPEAKER_21]: So that's always a big plus.
[SPEAKER_21]: So we want to promote, you know, a good hangout environment.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to give a plug to Golfland?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any specials going on right now?
[SPEAKER_21]: Any specials going on right now?
[SPEAKER_21]: We always have specials you can call in advance to find out what they are.
[SPEAKER_21]: Family night special or laser tag specials.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't forget Arcade Mania.
[SPEAKER_21]: Arcade Mania, yeah, Saturday mornings.
[SPEAKER_08]: On this Saturday, by the way?
[SPEAKER_21]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_21]: They canceled it last Saturday, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_22]: This past Saturday, wasn't it something having to do with a private party?
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for letting us do our crappy show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, a near crisis.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're just doing your job.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's a promotion for you in the future, honey.
[SPEAKER_04]: A near crisis averted.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we ought to get out of people's way now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are we going to take this back upstairs?
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's get back upstairs and get out of the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, let's get out of people's way.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we're going back upstairs, so if any of the guests want to come back upstairs as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to fail GM's quiz?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that was a great radio moment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you my daddy?
[SPEAKER_02]: Apparently I'm one of your kids, Rob, as the manager pointed out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is kind of interesting because we didn't think anything like that would happen, but I guess a true Orange Lounge spontaneous moment there.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, as I said, we were not going to stop tape tonight, no matter what happens, unless that guy came down the stairs yelling and screaming, Stop the tape!
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop the tape!
[SPEAKER_02]: Even if he kicked me in my ass, would you keep rolling?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, yeah, scream harder, Irene, come on, get some realism.
[SPEAKER_04]: Possibly, quite possibly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it sounds like they like to know about these kind of things in advance because, well, they want to do their own little promotions with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should call five minutes ahead and say, hey, we're going to come, you know, record and stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's going on the best of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope we picked up his audio.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kind of afraid that we didn't get the Golfland employees' audio.
[SPEAKER_04]: That might have come out kind of crappy for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an experimental show tonight, as I promised.
[SPEAKER_04]: It would be... You know what we could do?
[SPEAKER_02]: We can just dub over voices if we didn't pick it up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe what we could do is come back and do that segment in a later show, like in a best of.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll do with voice dubbings by Irene.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you should put in stuff from Rejected.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm feeling fat and sassy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I'm kind of worried about, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: What if this guy actually tunes in and listens, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: Because what do we do?
[SPEAKER_04]: We sit around and we say, Gothland never updates their machines, and they're all dirty, and things like that, and now, uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we come here and give our money anyway, so what the hell does he care?
[SPEAKER_04]: We're a bunch of fat hypocrites because we bash Gothland, but we're here anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have the right to complain even if we do pay our money, goddammit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, they're all coming back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Jamie's doing some PR work here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: Talking to the manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, she's trying to sell the tournament right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, boy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, Jamie, is Jamie going?
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie's going bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Irene will fill in as co-host while you're gone.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, hey, Jamie's going to go work things out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some promising news, maybe.
[SPEAKER_08]: This guy is really awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's done so much stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: He turned up the Peripera machine.
[SPEAKER_04]: Actually, I do recognize this guy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll say it here.
[SPEAKER_04]: This employee here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Should I just say his name over the air?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're saying good things about him.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dwayne.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good employee here.
[SPEAKER_04]: He's the one employee we've run into that will fix games when we ask them to be fixed.
[SPEAKER_08]: As soon as they are broken, he fixes them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, Pera Pera was turned down.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a game called Sumo next to it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was about five times as loud as the Pera Pera machine, so my thing was to go and turn off the Sumo machine, but now Pera Pera, you can hear it from upstairs.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's insanely loud, and I love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And this guy has made all kinds of stuff happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's letting us do this thing here, and it sucks, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's leaving pretty soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh no!
[SPEAKER_08]: Where's he going?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's not going to be working here for too much longer, so what he's trying to do is get Jamie's name and number, possibly even the URL for the boards, into the right hand so that these tournaments will continue to happen on a regular basis.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you made a spotting!
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_04]: How could I not recognize the mullet?
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a feeling.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was going to ask him, but I was like, I don't know, he might think I'm weird.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear that whole little crisis that was going on downstairs?
[SPEAKER_04]: We were trying to do...
[SPEAKER_04]: A group of people out there.
[SPEAKER_04]: What was going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: We were trying to do our little online schtick program that we do here, and we almost got stopped, but thanks to the nice employee, the Bomani appreciating employee, we lucked out tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good thing we didn't have one of the bad managers here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was great.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, and Tal's doing all the introductions here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're meeting somebody new from the board for the first time, so this is exciting.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, hello.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dark Tetsuya is his name on the board.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, you know Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Linky style.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, they were just introducing people.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is odd.
[SPEAKER_04]: I lost the co-host.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is kind of weird, though.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, this might be a good thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: They went to the office and locked the door.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I don't know if they locked the door.
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie went off with Mr. Golfland Guy, and I haven't seen her yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe they're getting a 4-plus for us.
[SPEAKER_02]: We better not tell Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope she didn't have to put out to keep the show going.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's going to kill you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's going to kill me.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Brad making the noises.
[SPEAKER_04]: Address those cards and letters to Lanky style.
[SPEAKER_04]: We almost got kicked out of Golf Land for filming here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, not filming, taping.
[SPEAKER_04]: I call it filming.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had an idea, Loki.
[SPEAKER_02]: If we weren't going to pick up the audio from the employees here, we were going to dub it over with rejected lines.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's all up to Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's too much work to do that kind of dubbing with the time I have to put this show on by Sunday.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll voiceover it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'll just voiceover it then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, well, I'm leaving pretty soon tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm probably going to get all this done tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm Bran.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the biggest idiot ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ow.
[SPEAKER_04]: My tooth.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you have any sim news for us?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, have you seen Loki's most ridiculously retarded edit for Max 300?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: After the freeze, the thing comes up with 50 fucking billion arrows.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no way to do that ever!
[SPEAKER_05]: First off, I didn't make the edit.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy Gatton made the edit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Gatton actually was one of the ones that was in the databank on 5th Mix.
[SPEAKER_05]: About 90% of the Naoki edits that Naoki picked are all done by him.
[SPEAKER_05]: He's the same guy that made that edit, Swingman, that I love, that's so awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, but dude, this Max edit is fucking off the hook.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's insane.
[SPEAKER_05]: This guy should write steps for DDR.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, if he made steps for iFeel and all that shit, it'd actually be fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Anyway, sim news.
[SPEAKER_05]: I got some good news, actually.
[SPEAKER_05]: Team Guilo and the Melting Potter are coming back up October 1st.
[SPEAKER_05]: They're redesigning the site.
[SPEAKER_05]: What happened was they were switching servers or something, and when they did that, someone bought the domain name.
[SPEAKER_06]: For who?
[SPEAKER_05]: So someone bought TeamGuilo.com's name and so now they had to change it or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: But they're actually still up.
[SPEAKER_05]: You just have to type in their IP address in order to find it.
[SPEAKER_05]: So they're still up and they said they're going to be done with the site and everything October 1st.
[SPEAKER_05]: As far as...
[SPEAKER_05]: Other sim news, really no new versions of anything.
[SPEAKER_05]: Tourney Mix, I guess it's still going because their media section is down on DDR East Coast Invasion.
[SPEAKER_05]: And yeah, I won't be entering this time because I'm busy with everything else.
[SPEAKER_05]: I swear to God, I never have enough free time to actually sit down and make a decent step file.
[SPEAKER_05]: Or I don't have the patience or just don't care.
[SPEAKER_05]: One of those.
[SPEAKER_05]: And also DDR PC, still no new characters.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was interesting because we thought they were going to be doing them every Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: They released What's His Name and What's Her Face on the first week.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then what, Valencia and Guy were the second?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then there were no third ones.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, nothing.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm still kind of in shock over this interesting turn the show's taken where Jamie's gone into the office to talk about God knows what with the manager.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm kind of getting worried.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think we need to send a rescue mission?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, you know, actually this might be good because they're talking for a long time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, maybe they're talking about a tournament.
[SPEAKER_02]: That could be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I know.
[SPEAKER_05]: Actually, they are talking about the tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Really?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_05]: From when I was walking by him coming up here, I heard him talking about the tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: I heard the word tournament.
[SPEAKER_05]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: So we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear the words... Stop it!
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie, you can hit Brad once you hear this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it's all Brad that's doing all of these funny noises.
[SPEAKER_04]: My girlfriend's ratting me out.
[SPEAKER_04]: How's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_13]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're going to get it later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, Joe.
[SPEAKER_04]: And if...
[SPEAKER_04]: Man, if the what's-his-name bans us, I'm going to be pissed.
[SPEAKER_04]: Imagine if we all get banned from Golfland for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Then they won't get any money.
[SPEAKER_02]: Darn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Shucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll just have to take my business elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll be able to afford an apartment, move out, and actually get on with my life.
[SPEAKER_05]: Maybe, you know, tune up my car and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_05]: That'd be cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like the addiction recovery thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all ban us from Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, there's plenty of other places to play DDR, okay?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right?
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, Ron?
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_05]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_05]: Is anybody there?
[SPEAKER_05]: But see, that's the thing.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't really know if there would be a tournament here, seeing how anal they are.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, every single encounter with Golfland employees has been anal, anal, anal.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except for the nice manager who helps us out tonight.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, he's very nice.
[SPEAKER_05]: Except for him, okay?
[SPEAKER_05]: He's pretty cool, but everyone else has been kind of anal and stupid.
[SPEAKER_05]: Did you notice he looks kind of like an overweight Owen Wilson?
[SPEAKER_02]: But he's very nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, but he's got that face like Owen Wilson.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you think that Jamie might be telling him the date and time to listen to this very show?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope not.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I hope you're going to edit this out of the show.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, if that's the case, then all these comments have been made by Punk Night.
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't say anything wrong.
[SPEAKER_19]: This is Punk Night talking.
[SPEAKER_19]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi, Mel!
[SPEAKER_19]: Hi!
[SPEAKER_09]: And this is now Loki talking.
[SPEAKER_09]: Little kids are going to kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_09]: Little kids love to kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I get my ass kicked by little kids all the time.
[SPEAKER_05]: They don't kick my ass, they just threaten to kick my ass.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know why, I sound like I look like a little kid or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know where we are?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're in the upstairs part of Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're surrounded, we're in the happy birthday section or the party section or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there's all these drawings of dragons with really huge nostrils.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, what's up with that dragon right there?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, he looks like there's a bulge coming out of his stomach.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all look crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: They all look... He's having a very happy birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a nostril-saurus or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, it's like crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Are you an impersonator?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's one behind you with the shorts and burning cupcake.
[SPEAKER_08]: Burning cupcake?
[SPEAKER_04]: Look out, he's coming right for us!
[SPEAKER_04]: That's burning heat, my friend.
[SPEAKER_05]: See, now all those things that you would assume are like confetti, those are actually just spots he's seen because he's on acid.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, look at his eyes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I kind of look like a telephone operator.
[SPEAKER_04]: There's two conversations going on right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: This show is in stereo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, so I like Telephone Operator as I was continuing my conversation with Ted.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So let's get interesting talk on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that English or what?
[SPEAKER_04]: I like ass.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let's get our Bimani talk on.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be Brad again.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ass is good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad?
[SPEAKER_02]: Bimani.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bimani's neat and fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I think Bimani's super, but not laser knife.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should have done this show drunk.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should have gotten more people playing DDR, actually, and playing, you know, hip-hop mania and drum mania.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's an audio thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Visual aids don't help.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, but we could give reports.
[SPEAKER_02]: Very good, Einstein.
[SPEAKER_08]: We could undermine your intelligence and such.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Ted.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Your powers of observation are great.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, you have to read 8-bit theater.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, or maybe not.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, so anyway... It's probably too advanced for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, let's start talking about... Yeah, you know, keyboard media is fixed and working, I noticed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I went down there and played it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the right side is... Yeah, the left side has this tendency to make new chords.
[SPEAKER_08]: We need to tell...
[SPEAKER_08]: Dwayne or whatever the hell his name is about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dwayne the nice guy.
[SPEAKER_05]: His name's Bob, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Dwayne.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's Bob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dwayne.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bob.
[SPEAKER_05]: Dwayne?
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn it, it's Bob, okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bob, is it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Bob.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I hope we don't get sued for saying all these people on the radio, but we have no money and can't get blood out of turnips, so you'll never take me alive.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a cheesy saying.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I come in and I saw that and I'm like, wow, it's on, it's working, and the keys are all intact.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keyboard mania is, I guess, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait one minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, just wait one... Let me start over.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just wait a second.
[SPEAKER_04]: There'll be little kids pulling the keys off any minute now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been working.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now... Oh, yeah?
[SPEAKER_08]: For about a month, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: If...
[SPEAKER_05]: I was just thinking, say if we ever got banned, how would they support themselves during the winter?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, no one comes in here other than us.
[SPEAKER_05]: Who would run this place?
[SPEAKER_08]: How would they get the money to run this place?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think something like that would happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're their only source of income in the winter, except for maybe $3 off Pac-Man or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's like a week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so what's going to happen is we get banned.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to be going without us for about a couple of months and realize that they're in debt or something.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, let's just put it this way.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I spend unusual time coming here about $15 to $20 in tokens every time, which is why I don't like coming down here all the time
[SPEAKER_05]: It's really hard on my account, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_05]: But anyways, yeah, so if, you know, they just cut me off.
[SPEAKER_05]: Shit, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: Look at Qzar, man.
[SPEAKER_05]: If I stop coming there, I'd like spend 15 grand there over four years.
[SPEAKER_05]: Isn't that sad?
[SPEAKER_08]: I have to say, though, I'm very dishonest when it comes to the ways I get my tokens.
[SPEAKER_08]: I came here tonight, played a few games of DDR, maybe four, five, six of them, two of those being doubles.
[SPEAKER_08]: I came with no money.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm a scrounger, as it were.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so they don't make any money off me, so banning me... How do you scrounge tokens, exactly?
[SPEAKER_08]: You go around begging people, or you found them on the ground, or you hacked the machine, or what?
[SPEAKER_08]: He asked me, you know, oh, some machine's broken tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't tell him.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tell him the ones that I want to play that are broken, not the ones that are broken that I get money out of.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shame, shame.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't steal.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, a donation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, you're going to feed this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Give the money to people who actually spend it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I spend money.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wow, I see.
[SPEAKER_13]: He stole his token.
[SPEAKER_20]: Oh, gee.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wow, that's like giving to the Salvation Army.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was incredible.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ring, ring, ring.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here's my bell.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thanks for being on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any shout-outs you want to give here on our little program?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it was good to meet everybody.
[SPEAKER_04]: I do exist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I am Vandalus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I'm out.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nice seeing you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Goodbye, Vandalus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Later.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, the one person Anita's back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you see anything that happened to us downstairs?
[SPEAKER_04]: We got accosted by them.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, the employee came up to us and said, I don't think you're supposed to be doing this show here.
[SPEAKER_05]: I still don't believe that he exists.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think it was just an elaborate hologram.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anyway, as I was telling Anita, and finally the manager came out, but we got the cool manager tonight who likes the Bomani crowd and does things for us.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, but Jamie's in his office right now, and we don't know what's going on.
[SPEAKER_08]: She's been in there for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's been a recent plague of child reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie's not a child.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's been in this community and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: As we discovered on last week's Understation Live, she has the voice of a child.
[SPEAKER_04]: But she's not a child.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sorry, Jo.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's scary.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we don't know what's going on, but we're just going to keep this show going.
[SPEAKER_04]: We said it would be an experimental show, 10.5, and shit, boy.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is train wreck radio live.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show was brought to you by ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: God, I don't want to touch that microphone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you trying to... That's gross.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're nasty on your ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: And they're getting that rubbing noise on the air, by the way.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what it sounds like to be against my ass.
[SPEAKER_04]: I hope you all enjoyed.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't ever want to go back there.
[SPEAKER_05]: Don't blow into the microphone.
[SPEAKER_05]: You know what's wrong with this show?
[SPEAKER_05]: There's no donuts.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's why!
[SPEAKER_02]: None of us are hyper.
[SPEAKER_04]: We could go downstairs and get overpriced cardboard pizza.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm pretty hungry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not enough for cardboard pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sometimes though, if you go right before closing, you can get free cardboard pizza.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like saying you get free shit.
[SPEAKER_02]: God, I love free shit.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's like when you're driving down the street and they have the big signs that say, you know, free dirt.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Free pie.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the pie is also evil.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's worse than cardboard pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's foam pizza.
[SPEAKER_04]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fertilizer for sale.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, who gives a damn?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, did we have a Jamie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought we had a Jamie sighting.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, not yet.
[SPEAKER_02]: A Jamie sighting?
[SPEAKER_02]: What is she, like an alien or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm starting to wonder what happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we go into our next break, we won't come back from that break until Jamie's back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, somebody else is going into the office now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my gosh.
[SPEAKER_04]: A group thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, oh, oh, oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gosh, my gosh.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: What is going on?
[SPEAKER_04]: Take advantage of nobody being downstairs.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I did earlier.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was happy.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, take care.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now we've got to keep this show going.
[SPEAKER_04]: What to talk about now?
[SPEAKER_04]: I could give one of our frequent listeners a call, because I said I would at some point tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Can you get it on the radio?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, we're going to do it on the radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I don't know how well this is going to turn out, so we'll see.
[SPEAKER_02]: And after that, we can play a game if you want.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've got to find my phone, my super-duper phone unit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, this is experimental radio, as I said.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know how this is going to go.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I did say at some point in the evening I would give one of our early listeners to the show, early supporter of the show Damn it, Brad, don't call me Hey, go on What?
[SPEAKER_04]: Brad's calling me on my phone So, Rob, how you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm good So how's the show going?
[SPEAKER_04]: I heard you're doing a radio show Yes, and there's a delay on cell phones, did you know that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Isn't that cool?
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe we can get some real funky echo thing out of this Yeah, let's do it
[SPEAKER_04]: Talk into your cell phone, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello?
[SPEAKER_04]: That is so cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're breaking people's speakers as we speak.
[SPEAKER_04]: I said we'd call.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, back to the track.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's see, we're going to give somebody a call here.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to try calling...
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, what?
[SPEAKER_02]: She's got a backup topic if this doesn't work right away.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, well, we're going to try making the phone call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll go to the backup topic if we have to.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, I'm going to do my best to try to understand what the guy's saying, but I don't know how this is going to go.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's dialing right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to get him on the phone first, so fill in for me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know, it's a cute bag, though.
[SPEAKER_05]: I am here.
[SPEAKER_05]: And my name is Chaos.
[SPEAKER_05]: Rap is to me like music is to Amadeus.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wolfgang, the famous composer.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's telling me the number's not available.
[SPEAKER_04]: Uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, well, that's experimental radio right there for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: The number didn't work.
[SPEAKER_04]: Damn it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, now what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, we'll go.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's on your mind, Anita?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I have a fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, yes, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Such language.
[SPEAKER_04]: Fuck me or fuck... No, I'm just...
[SPEAKER_03]: Well... I'd buy that for a dollar.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Fifty cents!
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I got... Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: My fuck you of the week is... DVD region codes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what you guys think about this, but I can't stand them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I usually don't have a fucky.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm usually really mellow.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really, usually things don't bother me.
[SPEAKER_02]: She usually has a darn you.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just kidding.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for the past seven weeks.
[SPEAKER_13]: Tell me, have you never been mellow?
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever been lonely?
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you ever tried?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, okay, all right.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, anyway, I'm sorry to cut you off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, well, see, I don't understand region codes because I suppose they were invented to avoid piracy, correct?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, they didn't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also, what they succeeded in doing is screwing over people like me who want to buy nice DVDs from other countries that don't have any English translations.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, I have a Japanese PlayStation 2, so I can play DVDs with the Japanese region, and I bet if I hook things up right, I could do a dub.
[SPEAKER_04]: You should give me a call.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll talk.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, copying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not like I'm going to actually talk and do the dub.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to put it in the VCR and hit record and dub that one.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think you'd be a good dubber.
[SPEAKER_04]: Life is a mystery.
[SPEAKER_04]: Stop it!
[SPEAKER_02]: If you don't get that joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should start a dubbing company.
[SPEAKER_04]: A dubbing company?
[SPEAKER_04]: What would we call it?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Dubbers?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sacra Dubbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dubber Mentals.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dubbers Incorporated.
[SPEAKER_04]: Star Dubbers.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Dubby Dub.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rub-a-Dub.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lame.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that'd be good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rub-a-Dub.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dub-a-Rub.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: We should seriously all, you know, do dubbing for anime.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would love to be an anime voice person thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who would you want to do the voice for?
[SPEAKER_02]: Akane, Tendo from Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us a sample of what your dub would sound like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know any of her lines.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm feeling fat and saucy.
[SPEAKER_04]: You are?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say, would you like to go to a movie?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yo!
[SPEAKER_04]: I hate you.
[SPEAKER_04]: I know what voice you'd like to do.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who's the name of the main character from La Blue Girl?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's their name?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's La?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought it was LA?
[SPEAKER_02]: Or I would do Ranma-chan, the girl side of Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: I could do one from her.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going back to China, so suck on that, old man.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're clapping in the background.
[SPEAKER_02]: They love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really love you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cowduken
[SPEAKER_02]: Wait, that's... I'm gonna fry some Twinkies with this fireball here or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: From Texas, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm over here in California.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hire me.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, so any other, like, fuck yous of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's mine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm done for now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I can't... Where'd my fucking co-host go?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my question.
[SPEAKER_04]: I guess we'll find out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We will find out after the next break because we'll stop tape until we find out what happened to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I wanna know.
[SPEAKER_04]: So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, what are we paying her for anyway?
[SPEAKER_04]: You're paying her?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you didn't know?
[SPEAKER_04]: We give favors.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought we had this discussion.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're not getting paid.
[SPEAKER_04]: You may not be, but she is.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's like taking all of our money, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has these sponsors and she's getting all the money and not giving it to us.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Jamie's a black hole and she takes all of our money.
[SPEAKER_04]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Brad.
[SPEAKER_04]: Address those cards and letters to LankyStyle.
[SPEAKER_04]: Care of... Anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: Care of what, Rob?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's where I trail off and don't finish my thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about Bomani, since this is a Bomani show.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a good idea, yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: So what about Bomani do you want to talk about?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know, let's talk about, um, stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you guys turn off the microphone on accident?
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I thought maybe the battery ran off for a minute or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, that would be... We're okay, we're okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh shit, this thing's been on pause the whole time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Darn.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm not that stupid.
[SPEAKER_02]: So about, like, if we do have a second tournament, let's talk about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it would be SCAT 2?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would be STAB, Sacramento's Tournament and Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the idea.
[SPEAKER_04]: If we did it at CCL, we'd do STAB, Sacramento's Tournament and Bowling.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what's going to happen.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's not give out all of our secrets.
[SPEAKER_04]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, some stupid laser tag game thing.
[SPEAKER_04]: L-A-N-K-Y.
[SPEAKER_04]: K-Y.
[SPEAKER_04]: Emphasis on the K-Y.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I saw this license plate that said K-Y Lady.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, who wants to advertise that you're the K-Y Lady?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, here's somebody who hasn't been on this show yet tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Everybody say hello to Somnia Magus X, also known as Ryan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hello, Ryan.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, live broadcast?
[SPEAKER_04]: And Dan the Man's coming up, too.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now this is going to be interesting because we're going to have to explain to Dan what happened to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't know what happened to Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what happened to Jamie either.
[SPEAKER_04]: We lost your fiance, Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: We lost Jamie.
[SPEAKER_04]: Darren, come tell us the gossip on Jamie while she's not here.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's in the office right now with the manager.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's completely insane.
[SPEAKER_04]: How so?
[SPEAKER_04]: You know her.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was Dan the Man, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is true.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is quite true.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because that's the only school I know about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Rob's in gay charm school.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm the only one here that actually looks like I'm in high school because I am.
[SPEAKER_08]: And what are we?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're just your cousins?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, you're all of my cousins.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what you are, Rob.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're all my parents.
[SPEAKER_08]: All of you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's right, son.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now wash my damn car.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, long story short, manager came down, but it was the good manager, the nice manager that supports Mamani here at Golf Line.
[SPEAKER_04]: The one employee that likes the Mamani players.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now they're in the office right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We think they're talking about a tournament, possibly.
[SPEAKER_04]: But we don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not to spread rumors prematurely, but yeah, it looks like we're going to have a tournament at Golf Line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not like we're on the radio and we're spreading rumors or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one listens to this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, pa.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: This show is on every Sunday night from 7 o'clock till 9 o'clock Pacific time.
[SPEAKER_04]: You don't even know, you big putt.
[SPEAKER_04]: Like, how do I listen to it?
[SPEAKER_04]: How do you listen to it?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, this is kind of redundant for our listeners who are already listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: But you're just going to go to our website.
[SPEAKER_04]: They may not know the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you look at my signature on Sack Bomani or DDR Freak, I'm Sky High.
[SPEAKER_04]: Sky High?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sky High.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, kill me, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: Not DJ Mako, please.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's in my signature, but the website is orangelounge.sky.cx And that's the website.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like the old Sac of Imani.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just like the old one, except it's orangelounge, not DDR.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right, and no one commented on it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: Something maybe the listeners of this live show don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: When we're not on the air doing a live talk show, we've got Imani Music and More playing 24 hours a day.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dance Mania tracks, 2DX, DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: You gotta give me a second of like an hour or two each day where I can just run to the next stop.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to say anything to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_04]: You got an opportunity here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, it's, yeah, as Irene jumps to unplug my mic.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um, no, uh, I don't got to say that much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, the community doesn't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, this is a nationwide show.
[SPEAKER_04]: International.
[SPEAKER_04]: We've got listeners in Japan.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'd like to say hello to our listeners in Japan because I see there's people from Japan listening every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's really awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen a couple from Chile, apparently.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, Chile.
[SPEAKER_06]: And just to remind everyone in Chile, your big gay representative is here today.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sky's up in the game.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, I don't know any Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie does.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know a little bit, but it's like tourist Japanese and they'd probably get all pissed off and stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, Anita does.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say something nice to our Japanese listeners.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for saying good evening.
[SPEAKER_04]: She just told us to fuck off.
[SPEAKER_04]: What's her problem?
[SPEAKER_06]: Mexico is where it's at.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mexicans kick ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because they'll sell you liquor?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm Mexican.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was because of all the gas you got after you ate their food.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Only if you eat it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Only if you consider Taco Bell to be Mexican food.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to get rid of the gas, drink the water.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tried that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tried that, Ted.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it worked for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a joke.
[SPEAKER_04]: Play along, Ted.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's talk about Anita's tattoo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anita has a tattoo on her arm.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never knew that.
[SPEAKER_02]: She's a bad mama.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's a dragon, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a three-toed dragon from Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's awesome, dude.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I got it in San Antonio, Texas.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's balls or orange.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I've had it for, well, see...
[SPEAKER_02]: 11 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: 12 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's beep.
[SPEAKER_04]: You never ask a lady her age.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so don't ask Rob his age.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can bleep it out if you want.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm trying to find a clever way to say how old I am.
[SPEAKER_04]: Old enough.
[SPEAKER_04]: Old enough to know better than to tell you.
[SPEAKER_04]: The reflex is a... She's married, that's all you need to know.
[SPEAKER_16]: It's more than you needed to know.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was like a reflex.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear to God I did not want to ask you that.
[SPEAKER_08]: The reflex is a...
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, oh, she's coming out of the office now.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's coming out.
[SPEAKER_04]: She's drenched in sweat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Where's the time at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Where are we at?
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time for a break, Rob.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time for a break.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to go to break, and when we come back from break... You're keeping us in suspense.
[SPEAKER_04]: We're going to find out what happened with Jamie in the office.
[SPEAKER_04]: You're listening to Orange Lounge Radio, semi-live here tonight at Roseville Golf Land, who is going to let us do the show here after all, as opposed to throwing our asses out on the street.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll be back.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got metal to the metal
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm gonna getcha!
[SPEAKER_12]: It's great, man!
[SPEAKER_01]: This recording is Volume 2 in a series of unintended decisions made before microphone and camera.
DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio, because real radio makes Captain Jack cry.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right, and we're back from that little break we took of music.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hope you enjoyed it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Jamie is back.
[SPEAKER_04]: Jamie has a headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now, oh my gosh, what went on in there?
[SPEAKER_22]: It was just being so enthusiastic.
[SPEAKER_22]: Basically, we're a go.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to have a tourney here.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you're speculating out here, probably setting up some kind of tournament for Roseville Golf Line.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's what we're working on.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can't go into too much detail right now, but it's official.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're going to get this going.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now you didn't have to do anything naughty to make that happen, right?
[SPEAKER_04]: No.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know I had to ask.
[SPEAKER_04]: Dude, my fiance's downstairs.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_04]: He called you insane during the last break.
[SPEAKER_04]: Don't you know it?
[SPEAKER_22]: He lives with me.
[SPEAKER_22]: He knows.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you have any retorts?
[SPEAKER_22]: If I'm insane, Dan's like freaking retarded.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: I think Brad and Irene are leaving now, so I'll use my little...
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so as soon as they close, we're going to end the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Golf Line's closing in a few minutes, so as soon as they close, we're going to end the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys have anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_04]: Goodbyes or anything like that?
[SPEAKER_04]: Sayonara.
[SPEAKER_08]: This has been quite the interesting show tonight, fellas, ladies, gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sure we can, you're just going to go home and put this on?
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be on Sunday like every other show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't have time to edit some funny little things in there, like a little dubbing over?
[SPEAKER_04]: Not really because I'm leaving, I'm skipping town tomorrow, so.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Lucky you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, lucky me.
[SPEAKER_04]: All right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have fun at work while I'm off, you know, in a bit.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hey, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's my fuck you.
[SPEAKER_04]: You go and have your fun five-day vacation.
[SPEAKER_04]: Four.
[SPEAKER_04]: Four days.
[SPEAKER_04]: Monday's off.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, if you count Thursday night.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm only off Friday.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, I didn't know you were not going to work.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, the listeners really want to know this crap.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, no, the listeners, this is a little break from the Monotony Mountain.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an experimental show tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: After what Jamie is going to tell us, they're not going to be able to contain themselves.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm moist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I was moist.
[SPEAKER_04]: I have to go clean up.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, Jamie, here you go.
[SPEAKER_22]: Irene's looking for me.
[SPEAKER_04]: Are you getting ready to go, Irene?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you want to say any goodbyes?
[SPEAKER_22]: Bye!
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to miss everyone.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, okay, bye.
[SPEAKER_22]: You're going to miss everyone with everything you throw?
[SPEAKER_22]: Is your aim improving?
[SPEAKER_22]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Irene's aim is improving.
[SPEAKER_02]: You heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_04]: Anita, are you taking off too?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last shoutouts you want to give or anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, bye everybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been really fun doing the show.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, um, but Monty all the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: Loot.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rock on.
[SPEAKER_04]: Didn't you want to give a shout out to your friends?
[SPEAKER_04]: This new shirt you're wearing here.
[SPEAKER_22]: In honor of my Step Squad family, I need to go ahead and let you guys know I am wearing my shirt tonight.
[SPEAKER_22]: Too bad it's not TV.
[SPEAKER_22]: Iguana Girl and I both had a Heineken in your honor on the plane.
[SPEAKER_22]: Of course, we were too broke on the way back to have one other one.
[SPEAKER_22]: But we had one for our Step Squad homies.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, yo.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Holla.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess in reference to the promo that Step Squad did at Mt.
[SPEAKER_22]: Mike's Journey.
[SPEAKER_04]: So how are you liking this Wednesday night taping?
[SPEAKER_04]: Ted loves it.
[SPEAKER_04]: He wants us to do this more regularly, more often.
[SPEAKER_22]: As long as we let him know in advance, I guess.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who do we have to let know now?
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, now that you have an in.
[SPEAKER_04]: You have an in.
[SPEAKER_22]: I guess we'll just let him know.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a burning question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki says his name is Bob.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dwayne.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki's wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki was just being an ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moral of the story, you're right.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, exactly, as always.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm hungry.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, I suppose this is an idea we can continue to do in the future if, you know, we want to take another week off or whatever, because that happens sometimes.
[SPEAKER_22]: Weeks off are nice.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep, weeks off rule.
[SPEAKER_22]: I get to, like, sleep, go to bed early one night, I guess, or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_22]: Maybe I can convince Dan to have a barbecue and I guess I can have, you know, barbecue tofu or something since I'm having, you know, barbecue up some shrimp for me or something.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bye, everybody.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thanks for coming.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Of course, when we're doing this here at Golfland and pre-taping, we can't really interact with our chatroom right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: We can't experience, like I'm sure SoCalKicks is in the chatroom right now and he's promoting USA and yelling at us when we're dissing Konami in any way.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Twen probably has some new Hell remix that he's distributing amongst the folks.
[SPEAKER_22]: And Slinky's probably just very bitter that he's not here.
[SPEAKER_22]: We miss you, Slinky!
[SPEAKER_04]: Ten more minutes.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know what else is there to say right now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any other Bimani news going on?
[SPEAKER_22]: I haven't eaten anything today except a cupcake and some chocolate-covered espresso beans and this, like, orange creamsicle Dutch ice drink thingy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yum.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm nutritious today.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's probably why I have a headache.
[SPEAKER_22]: My God.
[SPEAKER_22]: I have Evangelion Redeath, though.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to watch the hell out of that tonight.
[SPEAKER_04]: Good stuff.
[SPEAKER_22]: and Steve.
[SPEAKER_22]: Apparently, though, I think that the lovely people at Gravity, who basically made Ragnarok Online, has blocked the servers.
[SPEAKER_22]: I could not get on.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm going to try again.
[SPEAKER_22]: I can only read the kana where it says, server, word, not works.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, I need to, you know, figure out the rest of it out.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, I'll have an update on my addiction online RPG.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, yay.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm sure everyone's so interested.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, you know, if people are online and they're not listening to our show and they're not listening to my music anymore, I don't know why they wouldn't be.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, you know, those are fun things to do.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: See, this is one reason we are on a modem-friendly stream, even though we know a lot of people are on DSL these days.
[SPEAKER_04]: We reach out to the folks still on modem, and those on DSL can still do other stuff.
[SPEAKER_04]: Their bandwidth's not being sucked down.
[SPEAKER_22]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_22]: As we get odd looks.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were trying to, during the last segment when you were in the office, we were trying to say things to our Japanese listeners because we noticed that there are people in Japan listening every week.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we wanted to say something, like a hello or something, but none of us knew Japanese.
[SPEAKER_04]: So you have anything you want to say?
[SPEAKER_22]: Nihonjin no minasan, domo arigatou gozaimashita.
[SPEAKER_04]: She just told me to go to hell.
[SPEAKER_22]: I think if I said it as properly as I could, I said everyone of our Japanese listeners, we thank you very much for listening and please keep listening.
[SPEAKER_04]: And not just Japan, but worldwide.
[SPEAKER_04]: Canada, we got a lot of listeners.
[SPEAKER_22]: Unfortunately, I forgot my French.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, give a shout out to our Canadian moderators, yo, for DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Europe, all sorts.
[SPEAKER_04]: Chile, of course.
[SPEAKER_04]: Can't forget Chile.
[SPEAKER_22]: And to all of our moderators in Alabama and the Mideast.
[SPEAKER_22]: And for all the people who didn't, you know, the moderators who didn't get to go, we missed you there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I just have to say right now, mad love to my fellow DDR Freak moderators.
[SPEAKER_22]: I had a wonderful time with you guys.
[SPEAKER_04]: And Matt loved Melody for coming from out of town and entertaining me and being the guest on last week's show.
[SPEAKER_22]: That was good that Melody came and I got to talk to her on the phone.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh yes, that's right.
[SPEAKER_04]: We were in the mall and talked to Melody.
[SPEAKER_22]: We were at a strip mall, in the cab on the way to the strip mall.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was kind of a support group because her boyfriend was out of town and one of my best friends was out of town in Vegas so we had to have a support group of we're pouting because we're not in Vegas time but I'm going to get to Vegas at some point in the next few months so just a warning to you Vegas folk, I will take the tape recorder.
[SPEAKER_04]: Unfortunately...
[SPEAKER_04]: We didn't coordinate it, we just weren't thinking I guess and didn't get Jamie the tape recorder to take with her to Vegas so she could do some interviews down there like she did an awesome job on the Dollar Mini interviews a couple episodes back.
[SPEAKER_22]: I did make a mention to a couple of my fellow moderators that I'd love to have them on the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Rad, good.
[SPEAKER_22]: And, you know, of course, I always want to have Mel back on.
[SPEAKER_04]: And there is a possibility in the future we'll have a few of the members from RTF on the show in the future.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's going to be very cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm hoping so, too.
[SPEAKER_22]: I would love to get Rain on.
[SPEAKER_22]: I would love to get, you know, I would love to just have an RTF show, have the guys there, have, like, you know, my Step Squad people here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: And even if we can't get you guys here, you know what?
[SPEAKER_04]: We travel too.
[SPEAKER_04]: As is shown from Jamie going out of town last week, going to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_04]: We might go out to SoCal.
[SPEAKER_04]: I might be going to SoCal in a few weeks.
[SPEAKER_04]: So we'll be doing some taping down there.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'll be sneaking off in Rob's trunk a la, you know, Spritle from, you know...
[SPEAKER_04]: Speed Racer Anybody want to be Jim Jim?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm the number one guest there Excuse me, I have hiccups Semi-live radio, ladies and gentlemen Vanilla Ice
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm dying, I'm dying.
[SPEAKER_04]: Myself, Melody, and Mel B, and my boyfriend Glenn, we're all going to try and go down to the Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, we'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_04]: Because I've been there before and I had a blast.
[SPEAKER_22]: The Price is Right factored into the trip to Vegas.
[SPEAKER_22]: It has to do with Monday morning with all of us piled up in J-Dog's room watching The Price is Right.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hollering at this one woman.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're like, lose, lose, you stupid bitch, lose, lose.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let me guess, she won the showcase.
[SPEAKER_22]: Two cars.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, one car in her normal round.
[SPEAKER_22]: She got a dollar on the wheel.
[SPEAKER_22]: And then came in again.
[SPEAKER_22]: She won the showcase, which was another car, a motorcycle, and kitchen appliances.
[SPEAKER_22]: And this woman was just stupid.
[SPEAKER_22]: That's what you get for yelling at her.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what you get.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's karma.
[SPEAKER_22]: We're laughing.
[SPEAKER_04]: Karma.
[SPEAKER_22]: Taxes, taxes, taxes, taxes.
[SPEAKER_22]: So, that was just the funniest thing hearing, you know, shouts from the bed.
[SPEAKER_22]: Lose you stupid bitch, I hope you die.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what's funny is that I can hear somebody playing Kakumei from here.
[SPEAKER_04]: I've heard that song so damn many times I can hear it from here.
[SPEAKER_04]: Did you hear how loud Power Power is here now?
[SPEAKER_19]: Yeah, I love it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can hear it like way up here.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like 10 times as much as it used to be.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm just happy as long as I don't hear D2R.
[SPEAKER_08]: I heard Night of Fire earlier.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, I hear Made of Fire.
[SPEAKER_22]: Made of Fire, I'm made of fire.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want to tell you a story about Pear Pear.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was sitting down across from it, and normally the way they had it, they had it solo, you could barely hear it when you're playing.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm sitting there, and I'm singing along to Eurobeat, and I don't even notice this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And at the end of the song, I go up there and I play it, and I'm like, I come back, and I sit down, and I'm like, you guys, it's really loud.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft
[SPEAKER_22]: I didn't play Guitar Freak, so.
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing, that video right there, the Evangelion, it is an anime.
[SPEAKER_08]: It reminds me of something I just got about two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, you might want to check your local grocery outlet, as I do every now and then.
[SPEAKER_08]: Grocery outlet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I found the entire series of Bubblegum Crisis there for $2.
[SPEAKER_22]: Dub or sub?
[SPEAKER_08]: Both.
[SPEAKER_22]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_22]: DVDs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: I will check.
[SPEAKER_22]: Although I already have, you know, two of the LaserDiscs.
[SPEAKER_22]: and Bubblegum Crash and LaserDisc.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm just saying though, recently the one down in Rockland here on SunEyes has been getting all kinds of DVDs and books, good books, computer games even.
[SPEAKER_08]: All kinds of stuff, just $2.
[SPEAKER_22]: I will check it out.
[SPEAKER_22]: Thank you for the info.
[SPEAKER_22]: Any of you who live anywhere near here... You heard it on Orange Sounds Radio first, y'all.
[SPEAKER_22]: So do we have any more things to say to our listeners?
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm going to hand it back to Rob now.
[SPEAKER_04]: Y'all.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_04]: So did you hear the news about why Jamie was in the office for so long?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was eavesdropping, yes, so I did hear a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: What did you hear?
[SPEAKER_09]: I heard something about a tourney.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_22]: It is official, once again, aiming for the November-ish range, you know, not committing to a day E yet.
[SPEAKER_04]: We don't probably want to avoid Turkey weekend, or maybe not, because a lot of people will be off school Turkey weekend, so maybe that's something to look at.
[SPEAKER_04]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_00]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_09]: Speaking from experience last year, went on vacation, a lot of vacation.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we'll see.
[SPEAKER_09]: The tickets to Turkey are really expensive.
[SPEAKER_09]: You're a dork.
[SPEAKER_22]: I'm thinking, you know, either weekend before or weekend after Turkey.
[SPEAKER_22]: As in, like, not the ones immediately next to it, but, like, way after or right preceding, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Right on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hopefully.
[SPEAKER_22]: But it is official.
[SPEAKER_22]: We will be having tournament here at Roseville Golf Land.
[SPEAKER_04]: So badass.
[SPEAKER_04]: What else can we talk about to close the show out here with?
[SPEAKER_22]: I have a really bad headache.
[SPEAKER_04]: Really?
[SPEAKER_04]: Why's that?
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_04]: Just everything.
[SPEAKER_22]: Probably because I haven't hardly eaten anything and haven't touched anything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we need to go eat before we go home.
[SPEAKER_04]: I need to eat.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, we're going to go eat then.
[SPEAKER_22]: Let's go like, you know, on a rampage and, you know, be cannibals or something.
[SPEAKER_04]: When you guys post something on Sack of Money Not just Sack of Money Because it's not just going to be a Sacramento thing It's going to be everywhere We'll post on Sack of Money We'll post on DDR Freak Hell, you email us at OrangeLoungeRadioYahoo.com We'll come spam your local board Even if you're in like Taiwan We're going to plug our tournament on your board Because it's going to be the biggest damn thing ever We'll have to use one of those online translator services To be able to post My horrible, horrible Babelfish
[SPEAKER_22]: No, I found a really nice Japanese one, but I'll be posting that on our forums.
[SPEAKER_08]: Make it big and shiny, you know, so I can find it.
[SPEAKER_22]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, now we got a... Because I'm retarded and I can't browse.
[SPEAKER_04]: You'll know, trust us.
[SPEAKER_04]: About that translator, yeah, I really like it.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Oh, the new one?
[SPEAKER_04]: The new one you found?
[SPEAKER_22]: Tell them about this.
[SPEAKER_22]: I don't remember the site off the top of my head, but it's actually a Japanese translation program.
[SPEAKER_22]: Well, translation website, I mean, as in a Japanese native site that will translate...
[SPEAKER_22]: Japanese text to English nearly flawlessly if you run a page through it.
[SPEAKER_22]: It will leave the kanji, katakana, hiragana up and put English text underneath it.
[SPEAKER_22]: And you can even read fan fiction with that thing.
[SPEAKER_22]: It's so good.
[SPEAKER_22]: Wow, cool.
[SPEAKER_22]: On top of that, it also translates English to Japanese in a fairly reasonable pattern so you can actually put something on there and look relatively literate.
[SPEAKER_04]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_04]: Have you guys heard the news about why Jamie was in the office for so long?
[SPEAKER_04]: From what I understand, she was talking with the tech, right?
[SPEAKER_22]: We are going to be having a tournament here.
[SPEAKER_07]: Winner, because I just spent a good 10 minutes talking with Mr. Tech Guy to fix every Bimani machine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I'm like, I was talking to him and it's like, hey, you know the Soul Calibur is broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: And since I have you, would you mind coming with me?
[SPEAKER_07]: We have a nice tour of the arcade I'd like to take you on.
[SPEAKER_22]: Oh, that's sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he's like, hang on, let me get my clipboard.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was lots and lots of happy fun.
[SPEAKER_22]: Yeah, I have to say, I want to give him a major kudo.
[SPEAKER_22]: Power to Dwayne.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dwayne, the greatest tech ever.
[SPEAKER_04]: We give Roseville Golf Land a lot of crap on this show.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, maybe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_22]: Really, this is the best arcade in town.
[SPEAKER_22]: This is the best arcade in town.
[SPEAKER_04]: One of the great places to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: But someone should let Shiggle Boss know that the people at RVGL don't actually know what he's talking about in regards to 4th Plus.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I talked to Dwayne down there, and he's like, you know, I just found out about that today, which leads me to believe that Jamie told him.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_22]: I mentioned it because I thought he might already know.
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't know what you guys are talking about, but I just thought I'd grab the mic here.
[SPEAKER_05]: Talk about why Jamie was in the office for so long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh?
[SPEAKER_04]: I did my DWI.
[SPEAKER_07]: In other words, I have no DWI.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, so we're going to have a happy, fun tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you like SCAT 2?
[SPEAKER_22]: First and foremost, it will not be called SCAT 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: It will be RVGO 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that's so generic.
[SPEAKER_07]: Where's Tad?
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to plan a clever name.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have to think of a better name than RBGL1 so we don't be like Swiggle1, Miggle1, and Kamiggle1 or whatever the hell.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know, I love how we try so hard to make this a national show yet we keep talking Bay Area topics.
[SPEAKER_22]: We will not have a tournament named after crap, okay?
[SPEAKER_22]: But it's what made us unique!
[SPEAKER_22]: We will not have a tournament named after crap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we could call it, like, SCAB.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sacramental Tournament in Bowling.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, SCAB.
[SPEAKER_22]: We are not having a tournament named after bodily functions.
[SPEAKER_22]: As in scab forming or feces.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll just call it SCT2.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's the final word because Jamie said so.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about, like, Sacramental's...
[SPEAKER_04]: and Upstanding Citizens... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_22]: Rob, how about we call it SackMyMoney.com Prevents... Prevents... Prevents Crap.
[SPEAKER_22]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_07]: SackMyMoney Prevents Tournament.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, you're not going to play the machine, damn it.
[SPEAKER_04]: How about the Orange Lounge Owns You Tourney?
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, this is going to be a long, fat discussion on the board.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know that.
[SPEAKER_22]: How about sakbemoney.com presents The Tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all I need to know is The Tournament.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, you know we've got to do something cool, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because we made ourselves unique last year at the Folsom Game Room, FTR, by doing freaking SCAT.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sacramento's Cosplay and Turning.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, everybody made fun of us for that, but it's still, everybody remembers SCAT.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who the hell remembers Miggle 2.5?
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_22]: We'll see what happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, incidentally, for those of you out there, Miggle is Milpina Golf Lands, Figgle is Sunnyvale Golf Lands, Shiggle is Southern Hills Golf Lands, CVGL is Central Valley Golf Lands, etc., etc.
[SPEAKER_04]: Well, it looks like they're shutting down Golfland right now, so it's just a matter of seconds before we get kicked out.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll work on the tournament details, and we'll have that for you.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll post on all the local boards about that.
[SPEAKER_04]: But, of course, this is a national tournament, and if you have any tournaments in your area you want to talk about on this show, drop us an email, orangeloungeradio at yahoo.com.
[SPEAKER_04]: If you've got a tape player, a microphone-type kit that you can take to your local arcade and...
[SPEAKER_04]: Film the tournament, or, you know, I say film, but I mean, you know, tape the tournament and get interviews.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'd love to hear it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Give us a five to ten minute package on your local tournament, and we'll air it here on the show.
[SPEAKER_22]: Our listeners just missed the anguish screams as the mania was shut down.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes, the anguish screams, the song's getting turned off.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, anyway, it's time for us to end the show, so you got any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: Any final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_04]: Later, Ted.
[SPEAKER_22]: My final thought is feed me, Simo.
[SPEAKER_22]: Feed me all night long.
[SPEAKER_04]: My final thought is thanks to everybody for listening to this very experimental issue.
[SPEAKER_22]: Shine get!
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks to everyone for listening to this very experimental show.
[SPEAKER_05]: I saw a really ugly chick.
[SPEAKER_05]: She looked like a horse.
[SPEAKER_05]: She scared me.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was the scariest thing in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: I lost my combo there, dude.
[SPEAKER_04]: Any last words from Punk Night?
[SPEAKER_04]: It hurts.
[SPEAKER_04]: You want to plug your CD real fast?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, I don't have any copies made of my CD.
[SPEAKER_09]: Never mind.
[SPEAKER_09]: You lose.
[SPEAKER_09]: I kind of lost all the files that were for the cover and everything, but I will be making a revision.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, fine, and I'll plug mine.
[SPEAKER_05]: You can listen to my music, Loki, which is also known as Nightmare Hunter on mp3.com.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's www.mp3.com slash nightmare underscore hunter, and that's it.
[SPEAKER_18]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright, we gotta hurry up and end this show.
[SPEAKER_18]: The final word needs to be made from Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wait, wait, wait.
[SPEAKER_04]: The final word from Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hold on, we're gonna go over and get the final word from Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: This is my sweetie fiance.
[SPEAKER_04]: And then we're ending this show.
[SPEAKER_22]: He called me insane.
[SPEAKER_04]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_04]: Final word from Dan.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's time to go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I suck my balls.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm sorry, one more time.
[SPEAKER_04]: No one can handle my crotch, baby.
[SPEAKER_22]: He waved at the camera.
[SPEAKER_04]: He said suck his balls.
[SPEAKER_22]: And apparently no one can handle Ryan's crotch.
[SPEAKER_04]: Alright, the end.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thanks for listening to the show.
[SPEAKER_04]: We'll see you next week.
[SPEAKER_22]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_15]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_15]: Orange Lounge Radio is hosted by Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura, and Rob Roberts, also known as Sky.
[SPEAKER_15]: And now, here's your fortune cookie message of the day.
[SPEAKER_15]: Thank you very much for listening, and we'll see you next week.