Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
This week, March 2020 just got a little bit easier on your wallet as more delays have been announced
The game I'm looking forward to is pushed into March, so I'm not worried about it
These are just a few headlines we'll hear again later
Join us for all the night's timely news, starting right now on the show where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello, my friends out there on the internet
Welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio live tonight
Episode number 807 for this January the 26th of 2020
My name is Rob Roberts and joining me as always, even if off cam because that's where she wants to be
Is DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
See my starry foot?
There you go
That our folks can see live at Twitch because we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
Right after the Bobby Black Wolf show at Twitch TV
I have to show my shirt off
VOG Network, sure go ahead
I will just mention we had to do like a second start on Twitch tonight because we had a weird network error
So this is actually the second time we've been doing the intro
But the first time DarkSakura showed that shirt, so there you go, thank you
I freaking love this shirt, it's a little too small but I love it
We're returning back from after a week off
We were all busy last week just coincidentally
DarkSakura you were in the city as they say, you went out to San Francisco
I did
Did you have a good weekend?
I had a very busy weekend but I left unwell
I did the women's march in face so I went with the sisters
And then we actually stopped about a block away from the Embarcadero
They're having us walk all the way down to the Embarcadero from like, what is it Fulton?
But anyway we walked down and then we're like, you know what, we're not gonna go down there
So we went and had lunch at the Cove in the Castro and guess who was there?
Patton Oswalt
I kid you not
They were there for a film festival over at the Castro Theater
And he just came over and chatted with us, he's the nicest guy
I did sneak a little photo
But I didn't want to interrupt his meal or anything
But he was just a really nice guy and we actually joked back and forth about sister makeup
I was like, what do you mean I woke up like this?
Oh just a little dusting then right?
I'm like, yeah a little dust wink wink
He was just a really, really, he's as charming and nice in person as he seems in his interviews
That's always nice to hear when celebrities are like actual real people as opposed to divas
Yeah and he was just, he chatted with us
He's like, I love the sisters, I love what you do, I'm like yay
Speaking of divas, also say hello to Techmaster Holoke
Hello
I'm just kidding, how are you?
I'm good
So you last week went on your trip to the Broccoli Farm
Yes
Which is code for Disneyland, if you're newer to Orange Lounge Radio
It was about a year ago, you lied to the kids and said you were going on vacation to the Broccoli Farm
Yes
And in reality it was a trip to Disneyland they were trying to surprise the kids with
Which became this huge in-joke on OLR
So you went back to the Broccoli Farm and you got to do Star Wars Land and all that stuff now, right?
Yes
How's that new ride?
It's great, so yeah, it just had opened that weekend actually
So that Friday the 17th
And so they have this thing, it's a virtual queue
So basically you get in the park with everybody that's going with you
And then you have to bring up the Disney app on your phone
And then right at 9 o'clock you have to hit the button and hit join and hope that you get in
Wow
And so the first day I had no idea what the hell I was supposed to be doing
So we didn't go there at all
Second day I figured out what I was supposed to do
So it was one of the days I figured out what I was supposed to be doing there
And so I actually did join
And yeah, so we joined, I made a group
But it just so happened that it timed it with nap
And so we didn't get back to the park in time
Oh no
So we missed it the first day even though we got in
Second day after that we got in and went on the ride
Okay good
And then the last
So how's the ride? No one cares about the line
Sorry
The ride's awesome
It is the most immersive ride in the whole park
Ooh
Like the line, the queue itself
So you start off in this like rebel based thing
And you get this briefing from Ray from the new trilogy
And they're telling you that oh hey the empire is, they found our base
We need to evacuate
Don't spoil everything but
Right right right
Well basically you know we have to evacuate you
So they put you on this ship and then there's like the ship sequence that you're doing it
But that's still the queue
And then I mean then you get captured and then you're on a star destroyer
And it is goddamn awesome like and you're still in the queue there
But they're treating you like you're prisoners like that you're rebel scum and stuff like that
And it's hilarious
It's fun at Disneyland to be treated like a prisoner
Yeah so then they eventually they put you into a prison block and then the ride starts
But it's just the queue itself is really amazing
That's kind of cool that Disney you know when you recognize that like lining up is like half the experience
It is it's really cool and so you know the way they did it yeah
And so like the one of the last days we were there like I was like yeah what the hell you know like
I heard everyone cheering because I was picking out my son's gift he wanted to pick out a gift
So we were at the the star trader and we were picking out stuff there
And I heard everyone cheering like oh I was like oh crap I forgot you know to jump in again and see if we can get on the right again
Like ah what the hell I'll just join okay and you know 88 probably not going to get in because usually they they stop
But each day they got more efficient at getting people through the ride
Oh this is like practice so that last day I think they were up through like over 100 in the groups or whatever
But we got to go on the ride twice that day because the first time we went on it it broke down
So we also got to see the backstage too which is great so we did all that but my son he wanted to dress up like Kylo Ren
Because he watched episode 7 all the way down and just like fell in love with Kylo Ren as a character
And so he wanted to dress up like Kylo Ren he wanted to get you know the Kylo Ren lightsaber
So he had like the little lightsaber thing that we built like earlier that week and he was walking around full costume
Just dressed up like Kylo Ren it's great though because because it's Star Wars land stuff everyone treats him like the supreme leader
Kylo Ren and so I love that they do that for kids and so like the stormtroopers were talking to him and stuff
And they took pictures with him the um you know some of the people waiting in the line of the rebels are like
That's just a disguise right you know and then like or like in it on I have some Twitter video as well like follow me on Twitter
Where one of the guards or whatever one of the people and officers you know talk to them is that is everything to your liking
Supreme leader you know we'll make sure that everybody is interrogated and stuff like that
And if we'll get the torture device is going immediately it's great you know so like love it he loved it it was great
The only thing he didn't like is you know there there's a drop in the right and he's very afraid of everything
So like most of the rides like when we were there I didn't get to go on a lot of roller coasters because I had to stay with him
Which is fine I don't really like a lot of roller coasters anyways but I still want to go on some of it
So he didn't care for the drop too much but we got him to go on twice which is fine
So going to our chat because we do tape live every Sunday night like I mentioned earlier over at twitch.tv slash vog network
Questbuster in chat says that's great Loki's kid was the leader of the first order for the day yep
And act-def says that's awesome it must have been a wonderful experience for him so
Yeah he had they they had a lot of fun it was like we're trying to let him know like like this is a big deal
Because like this ride most when you come home none of your friends will have gone on this ride
You know this is that you got to do it first so
That was exactly how I treated Alan when we were first together and we went to club 33 together because we got like that rare opportunity to go into club 33 right
And I told Alan you don't understand this is a big deal I know you're not a Disney gay and this is a new thing for you
But you need to understand what a big deal this is and he said it didn't really hit him until we were actually there
And then he was like oh this is like kind of a big deal what we're doing right now so yeah it's it's just funny
We did we did lunch at the Blue Bayou and stuff I would not do that again it was
Oh I like Blue Bayou it's fun
Blue Bayou is a mainstay every time I go
I love now that Buck and the Meat's gone
What the the
Karthay
No no well yes I love Karthay but what's the gumbo I love the gumbo they have
Really my wife
Well there's a little gumbo place that's like on the side that place is pretty good if you want gumbo and don't want to pay a bajillion for it
But last time I went to Blue Bayou it was when because I don't think I didn't go on the last trip because I was there by myself
But when JJ was with me from Australia we had like a rack of lamb and just amazing stuff
Damn y'all now you're making me want to go back to the parks and it's been a few years last time I went was when Al and I got married
The one that he liked though the one ride in Star Wars landing he liked was the Millennium Falcon ride
Okay
And so that one's kind of funny because you have to work together as a team my wife did not want to do any of that
Like she is just like
Your wife's not a team player
She's like I don't want to play a ride I want to just ride the ride I want I want it done to me I don't want to like have to like participate
Your wife really hates video games
So she found out that she likes Gunner because Gunner all you have to do is just sit there and just like push the button once in a while
And like you don't have to look at anything so that that's fine so like my son and I were
My favorite rides at Disney my absolute favorite rides at Disney and yes it is a video game show I know we'll get to it we've been gone for a little bit
But this does tie to video games because my favorite stuff at Disney is like the Buzz Lightyear that's like a game and the Toy Story Midway Mania
Midway Mania is so hard to get on but like Buzz Lightyear we went on that a bunch of times and Midway Mania we went on once
We wanted to go on the Cars ride but didn't get to do that and once again because my son doesn't like you know faster you know rides a drop or anything like that
So it's like I don't know we did get lucky we did get to go on Haunted Mansion while still the Christmas stuff because they had just closed that down like the day after we got there
Which is cool so I've never seen it before so we went on that and that was neat
What else like yeah we went on the Millennium Falcon ride a few times I like how he calls it the the mammalian falcon because he can't pronounce stuff a lot
So that was fun so we did that a bunch of times and I don't know just like my wife and my oldest son they like roller coasters so they were on you know
Incredicoaster a bunch they went on Goofy Sky School Thunder Mountain I like Thunder Mountain sometimes I don't know I'm very kind of like
Problem is like I have to really desensitize myself to like these rides and because I don't get to ride them that much with
Staying with my youngest son that like I'm afraid to go on a lot of like anything just like kind of I don't like heights I don't like you know
They're like you should go on Incredicoaster I'm like no I am not doing that thing I don't need to be accelerated the 55 miles an hour like it's fun
It's fun if like that's the thing it's like I look at him like that looks like a lot of fun but I'm scared to death of that
Alright look we're turning into a theme park podcast I gotta steer us back towards video games but lots of lots of fun stuff it sounds like you were doing at the parks
And you had going on San Francisco and I'll quickly say that Alan and I went to a musical we saw Dear Evan Hansen the touring show because it just happened to be here in Sacramento
It was our anniversary on Sunday well timed I suppose and it was good we had a good time I was not super familiar with the show so it was good to see and it was a good night out
So yeah now I think it's gone I think it closed well it's off to another city it's probably like Salt Lake City or something now but it was here through like last Friday so yeah
So that's the second time I've missed Orange Lounge Radio due to a musical because you remember back in November we went to New York and saw Broadway shows and I was at Moulin Rouge while OLR would have been on usually
So we'll see I'll try to go for a record this year 2020 the year of me skipping the show to go to musicals
Alright let's get into gaming talk because we weren't here last week we had the pre-planned night off just because we all had kind of personal vacation going on and of course like clockwork that's when all this big video game news seemed to hit right
So one of the big stories that came out last week was kind of a follow up to something we've been talking about the week before so on our last episode on the last Orange Lounge Radio we were talking about this at the time rumor that was going around that Sony was preparing to skip E3 this year
And we talked about like how wow that would be kind of nuts if they did that you know we were talking about the feasibility of that happening well like clockwork the next day Monday sure enough it came out Sony is skipping E3 and it was confirmed for the second year in a row
Sony is going to not be going to E3 this year and this is for a variety of reasons nothing that Sony is really confirmed so people are left to speculate what are the reasons but things being cited are things that E3 isn't as relevant as it used to be anymore
Attendance was down last year it was down to 66,000 from 69,000 the year prior in contrast to that Gamescom 370,000 people went to Gamescom I had no idea Gamescom was that big I knew it was big
It's huge I just thought oh it's the E3 of Europe so I just assumed it was about the same size that is very low like Comic Con isn't even that big right that is right and like I kind of wonder like I don't know what game the environment of Gamescom is like if it's as hectic as like you know the E3 heyday or if they have that organized you know down to a T
where it's not like ridiculous I would imagine with those numbers they'd have to have some sort it must be really spread out I really don't know too much about it aside from watching the press conferences but yeah I don't know I I just kind of kind of think it's I don't know if it's a mistake that they're not there but I know like definitely the focus is going to be on Microsoft this year especially Microsoft and Nintendo and I don't know if it's a mistake that they're not there but I know like definitely the focus is going to be on Microsoft this year especially Microsoft and Nintendo and I don't know if it's a mistake that they're not there but I know like definitely the focus is going to be on Microsoft this year especially Microsoft and Nintendo and I don't know if it's a mistake that they're not there but I know like definitely the focus is going to be on Microsoft this year especially Microsoft and Nintendo and I don't know if it's a mistake that they're not there but I know like definitely the focus is going to be on Microsoft this year especially Microsoft
I mean you kind of want your console there to like show off some stuff in contrast I guess but I don't know I'm sure they'll do their own thing hopefully sooner rather than later
I can still read some of the comments the joys of doing a live presentation anyhow so we talked about E3's relevance decreasing that's also part of it the cost of exhibiting E3 is pretty high you know it costs a lot of money to get booth at E3 and maybe it's something that Sony determined was not very much cost effective and now there's this whole discussion that you can kind of just do things and not actually pay to be at E3 like how EA does their own thing across the street we had groups that did stuff in the past
parking lot for the longest time I actually don't think that parking lot's there anymore but for the longest time you remember like there was indie stuff in the parking lot and stuff I think that the Ouya are one of those things was in the parking lot one year and that was a big deal so yeah these are all reasons potentially even though Sony has not really said their own type of reason for why they're pulling out I think everything you've seen has been very you know like it's just veiled like niceties professionalism but not really
telling us the tea for example a spokesperson talked to gamesindustry.biz saying quote we have great respect for the ESA as an organization but we do not feel the vision of E3 2020 is the right venue for what we are focused on this year so what is it that you're focused on this year but it's still a little early in the year it's hard to say there's rumors that Sony will unveil this console in a couple of weeks which would match the template of what they did with the PlayStation
before it would make a lot of sense and you brought up as we were doing the phone call with Bobby there a few minutes ago as well in between shows you mentioned about the retail thing right there's a big retail show that happens there was it used to be around February ish was when like you would have like GameStop and all the major retailers going to Sony it was destination PlayStation I think is what it was called I I think that that was something that they they used to do in February I don't remember
if it was the same time every year but I remember that's the year of the PlayStation 4 and everything that there was that because I got in trouble from that because I was kind of leaked a little bit information about Call of Duty at the time so yeah I remember that but yeah destination PlayStation I believe is what it was called.
you guys in chat as well like is this is Sony making a mistake or do you guys are you guys like not surprised at all by this news and just the fact that you know what E3 isn't really a necessary step along the way what do you think of this news Loki I mean I don't know it's not that different from last year but as far as there's a new console this time well right here was a lame duck but it was still like you know yeah they really have much to show last year I'd imagine but I mean there's
still other things they could be doing yeah I would think with a new console launch that they probably want to do something unique with it to get the attention directly on the console and not like share the limelight with other people but I don't know I kind of miss that competition that they have the back and forth like that we had with the Xbox one and PlayStation 4 yeah yeah I know that little the kind of the rivalry that goes on at E3 there's there's now you know there's that's
one thing that's gonna be eliminated this year finally that question of who won E3 is not really there it's irrelevant at this point right now I'll still be there it'll be which press conference was the best you know who had the best press conference and sadly most of the time it ends up being Ubisoft just saying I'm not a huge fan I'm not always the biggest fan of like their properties but it typically they have the best E3 press conference although hopefully
Microsoft maybe this year's Nintendo let me get to some comments from our chat room and then dark soccer I want to check with you as well hype mayhem says on one hand I can understand why Sony or other companies pulling out over the years but still I personally enjoy E3 coverage and I like seeing companies doing pressers and having boost there so I guess maybe that's kind of part of the bummer is that you know it was it was that one week we had to look forward to like everything happened and now maybe this year's just gonna be kind of spread out I don't know if that's really like a good thing or a bad thing I guess we'll find
out as we go through the years Zether in chat says I think E3 is just becoming less corporate I guess I don't know the best way to say it in some ways I think E3 is becoming less well I don't know how to say it it's almost more corporate it's not like it is less corporate because they've invited the fans I think that's one place where it's definitely not as corporate as it used to be but I think almost some of the rules that ESA has make it to corporate to be a pax or something
it's confused about its identity is it a corporate event meant to you get business done meant to you know inform your retail partners on what's coming out and make planning for you know releases down the road or is it a fan event that we're trying to get people hyped about the games coming out and that kind of thing what is it like we don't they don't seem to have any sort of agreement on what it is it's like almost like you're trying to make it both at the same time and it's just not working
for them it's not gonna it's not good either of the things and so that's why I think it's failing um let's see some other comments from our chat Bobby Blackwell says in television will be there so there's at least one other big car well that'll be sure yeah I hit stun says e3 isn't needed anymore videos online are good enough I don't care much about a game being showed off at a booth unless they bring it to my hometown let's see DJ Orwell in chat says I can't care about video games until Half-Life Alex comes out and
either obsoletes everything or makes me cope so hard I check into an asylum so it would be like just really focused on one thing and to be fair that game probably isn't gonna show up it would be out for you well it would be really cool if like say for example Microsoft got their cloud streaming platform like down and like hey guess what you want to check out the new Xbox games we'll stream them right to your device right to your Xbox one you can you can play the next generation
of games through the streaming service because since all that you know gonna be processed remotely or whatever then they could push the better graphics and that type of stuff so you can check out the next-gen games I remember in 2006 they did like that was one of the cool things that I liked about the Xbox 360 at the time is they had demos for a lot of the games a few of the games that they had at e3 so there was lost planet there was MotoGP and
one other one but I don't remember what it was off the top my head but they have those like you could play basically the same demo that's available for you know attendees you can go play that it's kind of like having bringing e3 at home type of thing and so I thought that was really cool and kind of wish they'd still do that but you know they're not alright okay Dar Sagra you've been to many in e3 in your time what do you think about this news that Sony is gonna
sit the air out do you think it's bad on Sony bad on the ESA what do you wear use your head out with this shrug emoji shrug emoji I really kind of don't care you know e3 hasn't been relevant in years it's just been a big waste of money in space where companies have basically just like you know go out to sort of you know stroke their dicks in public and look how great we are look how great we are and really no one kind of cares
they go to e3 to say oh I went to e3 and I saw this thing there's better ways to do it I'm happy Sony is sitting it out I want to see it either turn into something more relevant for the industry or just grow old gracefully die already grow old gracefully and die dark dark soccer to e3 okay boomer seriously
that is it that is the e3 is the boomer model trade shows in and of themselves are okay but trade shows are a remnant from a pre internet age you know maybe when we were first going to e3 and the internet was still relatively adolescent it was relevant it was fine we didn't have there were people still on dial-up regularly in those days
but now we live in a different age where all of this stuff can be presented online on demand to be seen whenever we want why should you pay money to rent a space when you could just have a limited thing on your own dime in your own chosen location or tour touring thing would be great but the internet is real
to quote word out we all have cell phones so come on let's get real all right hi well on that note we'll move on and talk about our gaming weeks by the way I'm just since we're doing this live I'm having to fly blind a little bit right now because I don't know why but my internet connection over here has just completely went I don't know if my wireless USB is doing I don't know if attacks I don't know what's going on it could be because it's still running Windows XP maybe it's like no no you can't go on the internet you're too old Windows 7
is no longer supported I know I know your computer is literally you know okay now I know the reality is there are children newer than your computer fair enough this is the this is the baby where it all started all our started with this like and babies grow throw it the ocean and technology dies right well they oh great give me money I want to give me money for new give me my note what how about that monitor that I donated anyway alright let's move on let's
talk about our gaming weeks and the types of video games that we have been playing this week so or the last two weeks if you have another video experience remember I was on a podcast last night oh yeah oh you want to talk about that now I can talk about it after okay well you brought it up go and talk about it now okay so I was on a podcast called the spinner is lit and they've had some questionable feedback because it was you know it was a budget setup we're not very budgeting
comparison but it was a great show they did in a different location it was nice and quiet and people actually took their turn and talk so it was good and it was really fun to be a part of it and talk about pinball and compare things are happening in the video game industry with what's happening in pinball industry so I will be on their next episode it's on like all the things but it's called the spinner is lit hosted by dance buddy Spencer Dan was on it we were on it together and dance buddy Brian and I forgot the guy's name but the one who
hosted it at the house and it was it was a good time and I said I would give definitely give them a plug but they're good guys and know a lot about pinball and are really focusing on the Northern California pinball scene so there you go a comment from DJ Orwell who I think is newer in our chat room who says there's things happening in the pinball industry new tables come out and stuff the answers hell yeah right well they talked a lot about stranger things because they went to go play it that's the hot new thing right right he does pizza yeah yeah
so but they the big discussion was on stranger things and there was a stream of it up so we were looking at a few things so in fact since since it was brought up pinballs kind of a Renaissance II thing right now right like I think like maybe there was a few years where there's only like one or two companies still really doing it but we're kind of and I don't know if that's because of the success of pinball in video games through like Zen pinball or it's just that like pinball has become a thing that's come back to bars and smaller things but like I feel like there's more people in that game of pinball right now
then there have been really since the time we're doing we've been doing the show is that a fair assessment it's not a pinball is coming back pinball has been back I yes I know pinball has always been here but it's no no I'm not saying always been here I'm saying it has been back already for years now that the resurgence started years ago I mean we had that pinball 2000 thing and it was kind of hokey and then there was another little bit of a lull after it and then pinball started getting a massive resurgence
and Stern really started putting their mark back out on the market by releasing quality tables and getting IPs that people were interested in and then we started getting like the rise of Jersey Jack for example what was thanks smoosh smoosh is lending his comment to the show I'm trying to remember because there's another one that I'm trying to remember that isn't Jersey Jack or Stern but but at the very least there's you know there's also now new innovations being made in pinball
that give you that feel my thought about the stranger things table is that it's doing what pinball 2000 was supposed to do but it's got a lot more yes spooky pinball is one of the other ones I was thinking but the but the thing is is that I think that that interactivity with having projections on the post and having that big you know kind of background monitor ish thing you know the projection and everything has added
a lot more to pinball however I understand that right now that stranger things table has I'd probably say needs quite a bit of tweaking in their rules and the programming and also big issues with the with the locking mechanism so like the post don't work and post have existed in technology in pinball tech for like ages so I don't know why they're like so many tables are having problem with their posts but we go we go into that on the spinner is lit alright cool so
if you want to hear more about pinball culture there's there's a place to check it out so cool also quick programming note my internet is back you know how I fixed it you know how I fixed it shut it off I turned it off and then I turned it back on the cat and then I took care of the cat anyway alright I'm sorry what how is your so how is your gaming week outside of the podcast and pinball chat I did play some pinball I was actually super sick with a sinus infection so my attention span has been like what
I played some of the tables at home I got the new Sims expansion the university life and I got the tiny living expansion but every time I try to like sit down to play like I'm tired don't play so really not a lot Dan and I went though on a Shenmue rampage so we are have now been through all three games so far and like wow this story is Convo Lou Ted and I think that they voice acted Shenmue 3 like that on purpose
so and of course you know I'm back to yeah we found sailors we in a forklift and one D anyway so we oh and the other one yes Shenmue anyway we haven't done that Dan has got our freebie black rose working well kind of working it will turn on and start a game but it still needs a lot of love to it and it needs some
some love done to the play field and there's a few other repairs that need to be done but crap there was another thing oh yeah I'm playing patterned again on Apple Arcade which I fucking love that game and of course Pokemon and the dumb Harry Potter game and Animal Crossing and the stupid Ria Kuma farm it's kind of stupid by kind of I mean really but it's a waste of time
that's it all right Loki how was your gaming week what'd you play it's all been Orna it's all oh you get your well as that is in chat the Orna pimp I don't know what else but the one that brought that curse to this program but you're still having a good time with it yeah I'm a bit of a 217 now are you I'm 131 but a big part of it is like I'm trying to claim new land so like I was I went on the trip to San Francisco just this weekend actually I just came back this morning I'll get into that in a minute but while I
was riding Bart I just was like just had Orna up and I kept attacking new or not attacking but you know how like you know how like you can take an area for exploration and you can like take an area from another player yeah well I'm too weak to take them from other players really but like I was able to fight like all these bosses just while I'm like on Bart and so you know it all turns into like daily and weekly incomes that was cool yeah so I've been doing that and I've been doing some of the arena stuff and some of the dungeon things like I like
I've been finding that I just fight a lot of the bosses with like especially after collecting some of the XP boost stuff that it really boosts your level like I went through 116 117 very quickly just doing that so yeah it's mainly been just Orna this week I also like so we were gonna bring we were supposed to see our two sets of cousins or my kids were supposed to see the two sets of cousins and one of them they were sick so
we ended up keeping they have the little arcade cabinets like you have but the stranger things one like these little baby one so we have we have the stranger things one so we have two of those games and that aren't very good though that's exactly what I was gonna say is they are terrible like I get it like it's supposed to be Stranger Things thing but like could you really like come up with something better than just like everything having to do with waffles I mean like seriously like all of them had to do with Eggo waffles and I get it 11 likes Eggo
waffles that's not the only plot point in the whole show you know it's funny that plot point never comes back in season two or three no it doesn't it's just like it's like ridiculous boiler I guess you're like it's just like come on you guys like stretch it out a little bit but they're just knockoffs of like other games like there's a game that's just like Space Invaders and it sucks and there's a game that's like like Arkanoid it's
sucks and like all of them suck except for like you know the pack it was Pac-Man Dig-Dug Galaxian and Galaga I think are the only four official games in there and then everything else is like there's like 20 other like knockoff shit games that are in there and none of them are good from what I've seen but hey what cares is you know my kids got it for free because her wife meant to give it to her cousins and they're like yeah played it for a second and they're like okay I'm gonna turn this off
back to my other tablet that has like an infinite amount of games all right that it for your gaming week um yeah that's pretty much it cuz like actual games I did a little bit of programming I'm trying to get you know my level creation stuff done for my game because I'm already starting to like you know think about other games I could be making and I don't want to get into that so I've been working on getting that stuff I really like I was thinking about cuz like we even though this was a very
vacation like it doesn't really feel like a vacation to me it's like more stressful than anything it's like I didn't really have a ton of fun going to Disneyland which is kind of weird so like man I really wish I could just like take a week off and just sit here and just program stuff or but I've done that I've taken a couple days off before to do that and I don't get a lot of stuff done so I just need to find a way to focus and then you have to leave your house to do it probably like I feel like yeah
that might be better but like it's hard to do that okay my gaming week so I have been playing a few video games I've also been playing a few board games there's quite a few let's see a couple that I can like remember off top my head some of the details I was playing a game called terrorists which is it's like it's from Star Trek it's like in the background in Star Trek the next generation but they made like an actual board game of it so it's kind of like chess but it's not like you but the way you the way you
learn how the pieces move and stuff is a lot easier than having to remember how does the night move what is that what is the bishop what is that yeah it's a little easier to pick up and learn that was cool and then I mentioned I went to the city real quick this weekend because it was the last it was like some of you know I've been involved in the rocky horror community for like years and years and I was at the very first show in San Francisco at the clay theater which the clay theaters been around for a hundred ten years you guys and today's the last day of its operation it's really
sad so the last rocky horror was this Saturday and it was like I had to be there so luckily our our pal JD who I know listens to the show helped helped me with a place to stay and so forth so I could go check out the last rocky at the clay which is very sad for me but I'm glad I could at least be there and support the show anyway the reason why I bring that up is that this weekend happened to be like his board game day so I played a board game with them too even though I went out and played a lot of ingress and stuff as well but I was able to play it was like a Star Trek dice game I don't remember
the name of it but it was basically like cooperative Yahtzee like you would have these red alert cards and you had to roll like certain dice in order to like put them on the cards and and be able to remove them it was it was interesting I liked it yeah I I like those like cooperative games especially things like like Sentinels in the multiverse and you know things where you're kind of working together to like build a deck to like take out a boss and things like that so I think they were playing one after I left or something that was like Marvel themed that they were doing that sort of thing
so that was pretty cool so yeah so that I did I did board games and more traditional sorts of games this week but it played video games as well still playing way too much Final Fantasy 14 I got all of my healers to max level for the new expansion so I'm a healer supreme and I finally got to play dancer for the first time which is fun I think dancers really fun to play even if it's a little they're not quite as strong because they're more of a support character I talk about that game enough on the show so let me also talk about randomly decided to play No Man's
Sky again completely random sort of like huh what game haven't I touched in a while that I want to go back to and I'm like so I'm probably more into it now than I have like ever been just because there's just new things with all the new little quality of life patches they've done and again if you haven't checked out No Man's Sky since I have it in a long time and I have it on PC and recognize it I mean you'll recognize it visually but the game itself you'll be like oh this game actually tells you like go do this quest go do
this question like walks you through the story and it makes sense and it's kind of neat and yeah so I'm just there's something just very Zen about that game and just like exploring new planets and landing in places and knowing that like technically it's multiplayer because now it is although it's also kind of not because the universe is so big you're never gonna run into anybody ever so yeah I don't know that game is just like fascinating me I really like it one other game I'll shout out I got to play I got to play the the game and Bobby's talked about this game a lot on his show
so you music game fans will appreciate that I played Otica I played Otica in VR first well actually actually Otica is only VR so I'm sorry I played it on a PC based VR which I think was the Oculus what's the independent headset that the rift I think the ones not wired you're talking about the Oculus Quest yes I think it's that sorry I'm probably getting it wrong let's go yeah so I played it on one of those and
I really liked it and I was like oh I should pick this up on PlayStation 4 because I forgot that this actually came out for PlayStation 4 it doesn't run quite as well in my setup because I don't have a great VR setup but I still enjoy the game it is everybody's kind of described it as its elite beat agents in VR and that would be kind of accurate yeah I like there's a lot of expansion songs like completely like there's like Nicki Minaj starships and Ariana Grande into you and like all these very
poppy type songs but mixed in with like the symbiotic project stuff that is always with harmonics games I bought Beat Saber I should actually play Beat Saber now that I think of it so yeah so anyway yeah I had fun playing that so that was my that was my gaming week pretty much so yeah and then obviously I was gone all weekend so I didn't really get to game a lot this weekend but that's that's a variety of stuff so
alright let's move into more gaming news I'm trying to get any other housekeeping I need to mention you plug the show oh I do there is one big thing I gotta get this out there this is a huge deal you guys have been asking for this and I'm proud to say finally we're delivering on it so when we were getting emails on it everything you guys are asking when in the hell are you gonna get on Spotify like I've started listening to podcasts on Spotify where the hell is orange lounge radio why aren't you on Spotify well you can ask that question no more because now we are on Spotify so if you are a Spotify
user and that is your preferred method to listen to podcasts I'm happy to report just search for orange lounge radio we're really easy to find go to Spotify search for orange lounge radio there we are so your follows your listens on that platform mean an awful lot but no matter how you're listening to the show if you're using the Apple podcast or Google Play you know what it helps no matter where you're listening to the show so thank you for your support of the show so there's that so we're on Spotify and then the other housekeeping thing would be that there's we're gonna be
actually two weeks without a live show and that's my fault and that's gonna be March 1st and March 8th so I will talk to my lovely co-host about recording something in advance kind of like we did before the last time I missed pre-planned two weeks in a row so here's the deal for those of you that have listened to the starboard power coupling here at VOG Network the Star Trek based podcast with Captain Matt and Dr. Ken and all that they have convinced me after however many years
it's been I think it's been four years to go on the Star Trek cruise so I'm going on the official Star Trek cruise but because it's a week-long cruise and it's Sunday to Sunday so I fly out like Saturday the 29th and I come back like that Sunday so actually I might be back that Sunday night but I feel like I'm really pushing it and I'll probably be really tired so it's not in my best interest to plan to do a show that night so I just want to let you live folks know and we'll
we'll figure something out if nothing else maybe Dark Sakura will do a because you remember when when when my mom passed and I missed all those shows you kind of took the reins for a little bit and did your own little thing and I would totally support that if you want to do that while I'm gone so alright do you remember that yeah so yeah right okay okay I'm just a little bit mad at people right now all these people do you find someone who raped a teenager
oh alright well let me move on so let's move on into some gaming news so let's talk about all the things you're not gonna get to play in March yeah what's up with that so we had a joke intro like last week or no two weeks ago that was like March 2020 is coming and I really should have had the joke intro tonight be never mind March 2020 is no longer coming false alarm because not only like while we were gone but this week like everything
is getting pushed back right Loki yep so all the games even waiting for well some of the games you win waiting for having pushed back so let's start off with Final Fantasy 7 remake that's been pushed to April and the Square Enix Avengers game that has been pushed to September and it will join my it really anticipated game which was Cyberpunk 2077 which has also been delayed by
to September 17th that's unfortunate and last but not least so along with Avengers we also have the Iron Man VR game has been pushed to May 2020 that was originally coming out in February and I guess this is good news in the sense that hey you know it's better to wait for a functional a better game than to just have them rush it out in
have it be broken a bad game is bad forever a good game yeah we all know the not always nowadays but like some games are bad so long that they decided they don't want to fix them to the point where they are functional and game delays aren't like bad news I think we're all at the point where it's like you know what these delays are gonna happen and the game is usually a better product for it and in retrospect there are some games I wish would have been delayed Andromeda that weren't that probably needed it so you know what you can't really look at
a lot of this and go this is horrible but certainly when it's all happening at once it does kind of go like wow that's a little weird what's interesting Bobby's pointing out in chat and I think this is important too is anyone remember how Animal Crossing was delayed to March so you know March would be empty without that delay right Animal Crossing was originally supposed to be a holiday
we're only like we're how far we out from that would be like are we at the six-week mark a few weeks yeah so I'm pretty sure that is a thing at this point so as you 100 Matt says push it all back more time to save up for them and to play the games I already have so yeah so a lot of stuff getting delayed but now it's just spread out throughout the year and I guess more time to play other stuff like was mentioned their doom or Animal Crossing in fact it's interesting
because doom eternal and Animal Crossing are actually due to come out on the same day and there's been interesting like fan art online of like doom guy and Isabelle have you seen some of the stuff it's really crazy like her in full armor and him wearing you know being all buff and wearing the dress yeah no it's like really funny some of like the crossover and stuff that's happened it's really cute but well and I'm curious is are there people out there that are interested in both games day one release like I'm I'm like on the line I thought the doom
reboot was really good and I'm interested in doom eternal but I don't think I'm $60 interested in doom eternal like I kind of wanted to see how that pans out a little bit but like Animal Crossing oh I'll definitely pick that up day one just because I'm a dork for that stuff and I like it but what's interesting is that Game Informer did an interview with Hugo Martin the game director for doom eternal talking about this release and the fact that these two games are out the same day and Hugo Martin said I
think it's awesome and speaks to the amazing diversity that we see in games today I honestly root for other games and other studios which quick aside in my own thing not a part of the quote I think when you do work in such a small industry where there's a lot of turnover at different organizations and stuff you don't want to burn your bridges by being like well fuck Microsoft there are a bunch of assholes like you know you never know when your studio might close down and that is the place to get a job right so you know people don't burn their bridges very often
in the industry is not a smart thing to do and I think too because in a way they're all in it together a lot of people in that industry have worked the crunch time have done those types of things you know so it's like almost like it's a fraternity slash sorority of all these people who have kind of like been through it and so they support each other I think anyway back to the quote from Hugo Martin I'm so proud to work in the game industry and the fact that two games that are so completely different getting a ton of press come out on the same day
it's an incredible time to be in development and I'm excited to play Animal Crossing so yeah and you know what in the movie world don't we always get like you know the big like action blockbuster type thing coming out versus the sweet rom-com right and they come out the same day because it's like there's not a lot of audience that's going to be interested in both there might be some but you know there's not a lot of audience is going to be interested in both
day I'm not a huge fan of doom it looks like a good game though but I you know I'm more interested in Animal Crossing so we'll see I'm orange right in chat says the recent update with the first two doom games is definitely making me more interested in the doom 64 rerelease you know I didn't talk about it during my gaming week but I'm kind of same Z's on that with you because I downloaded the original doom on PlayStation 4 just to check out like the wad support and all that and it's it's fun to go back and visit it's it runs
man I wish my computer had been that good back in the 90s running that so it's fun to play it it does kind of make me interested in doom let's see zither says that game rules I feel like it's the real doom 3 fair enough let's see s2100 mat says cyberpunk being pushed inclines me to wait until the new consoles come out to play them there that's a really good thought hmm do we wait for PlayStation 5 at this point to check out cyberpunk
because we're kind of banking on the fact we know Xbox will do it and we're banking on the fact that PlayStation 5 is gonna play all the PlayStation 4 games because one of the big things they've been showing off on PlayStation 5 is the spider-man I think by the time we get to that point we'll know sure what the situation is and I think on the case in the case of like Xbox stuff that a lot of these like especially like the Series X stuff will still be playable on Xbox one so it could come out as an Xbox Series X game
and just that functionality won't be in place until the new system comes out or maybe they'll release a version of it that still works with the Xbox one it'll just replace the other one I don't know Bobby Blackwell says real cyberpunk players will play it on PC anyway now now I do love PC gaming but there's certain things I just prefer to do on console we'll see we'll see I haven't really thought that far ahead to cyberpunk yet I kind of want to see how it reviews like I expect it's going to do pretty well
but I just kind of want to hear some of the feedback on the game again 60 bucks is a lot of money doing this little podcast for y'all like as long as we've been around and everything that doesn't mean we're like showered in free games okay and even if we were then that creates all sorts of like you know ethics types of things and what have you so we we buy our own games so at 60 bucks a game like you know things start to get expensive right y'all feel the same struggle so you really have to think about like what games do I want to drop 60 bucks on but Animal Crossing is
one of those games and I know dark soccer is the same case for you you're not even gonna flinch dropping my orders already in yeah so I don't care I mean I already said I was gonna get Dan and I were talking about getting a switch light oh yeah so that I don't have to take our house switch with me to play I'm surprised they haven't announced like an Animal Crossing themes we're holding out for yeah and if they don't do it they don't do it so I but I'm super excited about it I'm in like
three different groups are like oh my god I just don't want to get a switch light because I have a lot of my games digital and like well and what I was saying is that the one of the groups that I'm in got some pictures from the trade show where they had like a brochure that was out in their scans the brochure they even has a little comic in there and the new Animal Crossing manga is following New Horizons
so do we know like how online is gonna work in the new game they haven't really talked about that right we don't like is it still like you got to open your gates type of thing with the old Nintendo talking about online like what I don't think it's gonna be like that but we'll see cuz I mean that you have like the the local play and then there's gonna be I don't know it look like it's gonna be a lot more of an interactive kind of thing so it might not be a gate thing now me I don't go online so y'all bitches can stay out of my village unless you come over
yeah I probably will let a few people come online right yes yeah that's why I thought DJ Orwell and Chad says someone give me a quick rundown on what's new on this new Animal Crossing so I mean some might say it's just the same format again somehow this one does feel different though because they've kind of changed the landscape right you're not like doing your own town it's like you're going on vacation and you have your own island and so it lends itself to these different types of mechanics so it's trying to kind of differentiate itself from the old formula right
if I'm understanding a little bit yeah their soccer is nodding there a little bit so I I would expect some point between now or well says no reset II know by that reset he's got to be in it come on come on well I mean reset II they're actually I think is nothing sing that reset II was gonna be in the game I don't think you should have been any of the material although they did confirm blathers which means Celeste is gonna be there there's the new airport which I have a feeling that the airport is gonna be more of the way to visit the
other islands but they had like as a sort of an Easter eggy kind of thing in you leave where you would if you placed a manhole then every so often you would find the manhole open and you would go into reset his house okay so so even if like autosave is now I think on the switch janitorial office there's no need to reset II they'll put him in the game yeah I know that they have in this one versus the other games is that you can decorate the
outside of your house oh yeah that's a huge news and like I think even like a garden in like pathways and stuff like that like you can actually change more the landscape in that sense it's almost like the creators of Animal Crossing are aware of Stardew Valley incredible that game yeah they are aware of that game wants to know are you doing any streaming of Animal Crossing dark soccer I can get it set up sure it's basically gonna be me you know walking around hitting people with a bug net
and you're not gonna build you a switch light just saying you can get a bug net and you can hit animals with the bug net I think any stream it's gonna be harder to stream but you you'll have both right you just move your game cartridge yeah cuz I always keep everything on my game cartridge so whatever all right well anyhow let's move on and talk about some other gaming news and a little bit more of gaming in the real world right dark soccer yeah so I don't know how much
many people remember this it was I think we kind of brought it up it happened in March but there was a guy who was trying to sue I'm trying to get his his full name out of here it doesn't actually this Oh amro Ellen sorry of Exton was suing that his civil rights were violated when he was muted out of an online video game
he did a hand written lawsuit that Jagex incorporated in the UK and several Chinese firms violated his free speech and due process of law when he was muted out of some streaming game in March of 2019 doesn't say the game is he said he had over 2,000 hours invested in the game when he was booted out Jagex denied the appeal of muting him without telling him why that's what he said
and he was looking for damages in quote whatever the jury sees fit plus D muting at any rate the US Eastern District Judge Mark A Kearney allowed Ansari to pursue the case as a pauper's case and then promptly dismissed it on grounds that there hadn't been any real constitutional claims and so he applied to circuit court and the circuit George was like
that it wasn't unequal treatment as compared to the other players who weren't muted and so basically they said that Jagex was perfectly fine to allow him to be muted that that was their policy it was fine and there have the guy has done this is the second in two months that they've killed a lawsuit by this guy and they also in November refused to reinstate a case he lodged claiming that he was
scanned by the tinder dating app so I think this guy's got problems I think he's just a frivolous lawsuit kind of person in 2016 the Superior Court denied appeal that he filed after he was arrested by the Bloomberg Bloomberg University Police for lighting up on campus in front of campus cops and he was also convicted on a marijuana felony and he has ten lawsuits in the US Eastern District Court
in the last year and a half he lodged four of them in 2019 in July 2019 alone so yeah he's he's one of those frivolous sewer sewers right and let's see they're confirming in chat that RuneScape is the game that was a question here SG100Matt says I just scrolled off the screen whoops you guys are very chatty SG100Matt says this dingleberry wasted everyone's time in tax dollars with this garbage lawsuit
yeah I mean and as that says perpetual victim and yeah I mean you know when it comes to the First Amendment I think we all know we all know but some people clearly don't the First Amendment does not protect you when it comes to private property you know when it comes to the RuneScape servers and stuff if you say something stupid they have a right to ban you and handwritten yeah you can't just say freedom of speech that isn't that freedom of speech means the government can't arrest me if I get up here and I say Donald Donald Trump is a fucking asshole I can't get arrested in the government because
you know in some countries I would get arrested for saying that good check the news sometimes you can't talk bad about the leaders of certain countries in those countries right but I can say that but what it doesn't protect me from is that if I say that somebody might go well that guy's an asshole for saying that about the president I don't want to follow him anymore block I can't sue that person for blocking me I said what I said but I think it's not freedom from consequence go that being said I think that this guy just seems like one of those perpetually
entitled little shits hey guess what dude I think you're a little shit and I can say that on air here in America because I can say what I think you're a little shit you can get mad and that's the consequence but it won't affect my life any Phoenix 7726 brings up you can't compare a certain leader of a major nation to Winnie the Pooh and we did see some well we saw a lot of that remember the Blizzcon protests with the Hong Kong issues and all that so I mean you know as there was a student
arrested when he returned to China because he had posted pictures of Winnie the Pooh on his Twitter yeah so that is an example of what happens without the First Amendment right so anyway y'all y'all know and I think pretty much most of us watching and listening kind of understand the same page like hey this guy is not you know able to just get himself on band with a lawsuit I suppose the furthest I could go to meet this guy is that most companies should have a system in place where if you
get banned you should have a way to appeal that ban that is fair but there's nothing that legally says a company has to do that it's just one of those you know if I'm gonna give a company money there should be a way to do that I kind of think about some of the GPS games I've played like Niantic Games and Ingress and like if somebody gets banned from Ingress for like spoofing or breaking the rules or something like that they should have a mechanism to say no I didn't do that and I want to state my case and so forth especially if they've spent a lot of money on the game you know cuz
even though false bans aren't the norm it can happen you know and even 1% of players getting falsely banned well that fucking sucks if you're the 1% so that's just my example for like there should be a mechanism there between the company and the individual but at the same time there's nothing legally that says they have to have one so it's something you have to think about before you spend your money on something like this what the fuck the dude was doing to get muted anyway he had to have been doing something wrong so
just I hate entitled people yeah so anyway all right moving on let's talk about the next story which has to do with another game subscription service yeah so this is interesting so paradox a company that normally makes a lot of these big paradox interactive they make some bigger PC strategy games that they are working on putting out like a that's a lot of
stuff a like they're testing the waters with like a streaming service basically you know and looking at like some of the DLC that they have for some of these games it's ridiculous the amount of money that would cost it by all of DLC so you basically they haven't really announced the details of the service yet but apparently some fans of what was it it was Europa
universe universes for have found out about the service because the game the code for the trial is in the game's latest update so maybe this is something that they're going to be announcing soon but right now it's not necessarily they don't know what the details of it are yet now Phoenix 7726 in chat wants to say to be fair to paradox their DLC
goes on sale for cheap often and EU for is on humble right now so it may not necessarily be the sign of this but I think it does beg the question because we have seen a lot of companies going down this path right we see Xbox game pass we see EA's what are they what the hell do they call that thing the EA access that's it Ubisoft has one now to write and they launch one my point being we all know these different things are out there right
but in the television movie world we're having a big conversation about the streaming services right because we got Netflix we got Hulu we got CBS all access and now what they just announced this week they announce we knew it was coming but now we've got a date for peacock another one that's coming out right so and a lot of people are starting to say yo fuck this like there's too many streaming services I'm gonna go back to piracy so one of the big television stories this past week
was Picard came out right now I haven't watched it yet I plan to in the coming days but I wonder how many of you all pirated the first episode of the card because you don't want to subscribe to CBS all access I have not I bet I bet there's I mean you don't have to out yourselves I understand you don't want to confess that but I bet there's a lot because they are not interested in anything else on CBS all access outside of that so they they likely have done that and so my point is now we're getting into this gaming I'm kind of watching
what's going on in the movie film world and kind of going like gaming needs to keep an eye on this too because what happens if gaming ends up in the same boat we might be rid of the $60 video game in the next few years if if gaming goes down the same route which I don't think is outside the realm of possibility again Xbox game pass point we may be done with the $60 video game in a few years but are we going to be splintered into way too many different subscription services
where it's too hard to like you're ending up paying more because you're having to subscribe to all these services I don't know how do you guys feel about the subscription service what would you do if the $60 video game went away but now you have all these different services like what's what's the answer here I would just have to look at what I'm playing the most of because I mean honestly at the end of the day like I have a lot of stuff I play on PC and so I think that words you may have a lot of subscription services on the console side of things I don't think PCs ever gonna go that way
so I mean at the end of the day it's gonna be which of these services would I get the most use out of and even still like I have a back catalog of games that are in my libraries that you know it may be more prudent for me to get like an Xbox you know games pass you know subscription because I don't I haven't gotten the free games from games of gold in a long time because I haven't subscribed to gold because I don't use my Xbox but
you know that might be more beneficial for me it would just have to depend on what's what each platform is offering really y'all are quite the model citizens I'm reading chat and you guys are for the most part like saying you did not resort to piracy for this Bobby Blackwell says if I don't want to pay for something I don't consume the content I'm not entitled content that probably the closest answer we got here Phoenix 77 26 says why pirate when you have free trials and disposable email addresses okay so not piracy but maybe
using the system perhaps hype mayhem says not me I want to see it and can't afford CBS all access but piracy is a road I won't go down yeah so sg100 Matt says that Harley Quinn show on that DC streaming service is great I hope it gets a second season but it sadly pirated a lot I didn't even know DC had a streaming service until I read that yeah they do see now there's so many of them I don't even know what's out there anymore so what happens if gaming ends up going down this route I hope we see some interesting alliances for
them and you know to be fair Xbox game pass seems to be doing a pretty good job of that where they not only have their own stuff but they're collecting a lot of different indie stuff some big third party stuff on there and I think that's one thing that Xbox has over yeah yeah and you play in that that type of stuff well and also with those I mean I like how they have all their new games on there it's a really good value for what you're paying but like at least with the streaming service since it's month to month for most that stuff unless you're prepaying for a bunch of it I mean if for whatever reason if it ends up going
the way of like Netflix where you know content leaves content comes in you know if it doesn't have what you're interested in at that time just stop subscribing to it or you know $10 a month honestly when you're looking at games and like how many games you buy like that's not a huge or even like $15 a month is not a huge that's like a game every four months that really when you look at it you probably spending more on games anyway
and so you're getting a lot more content here but at the same time like I don't want to get caught in the you know where as I happen like I'm paying for Hulu Netflix and Disney Plus right now but am I consuming a lot of that content nah you know it's just nice to have
what about when you weigh your family into it like do your kids consume Disney Plus even if you don't?
No we watch the Star Wars movies on it sometimes I'm trying to get them to go through the whole Marvel series the Marvel Cinematic Universe but like that's gonna be like pulling teeth it's hard enough to get them to go through Star Wars but they're finally getting caught up on Star Wars so that I can take them to see the new one in the theaters but like you know like with Hulu we watch a lot of Food Network stuff on there like it's just chopped all the time that's what we watch in there and Netflix is like kind of a smorgasbord of like also a lot of their original series
stuff a lot of just some of the unique content on there.
I hate to admit it but the circle was so fucking good. It's such trash but it was so good. As far as like trashy reality TV shows go it really was one of the better ones like the people they cast were not like like that's the problem I have with Big Brother these days they're casting horrific people like it's just there's there's never anyone to root for anymore on that show or anything
but like the circle was like okay some of you all are like very clearly like these little like niche things but like I really like the people like they weren't assholes
I'm just gonna I don't know what the circle I mean I've seen the stupid trailer I watched them like is this something we're gonna watch and my wife's like no let's watch Chopped
it's Big Brother meets that one episode of Black Mirror where you rate everybody that's what it is so but like they can just live out who they are and stuff like that because they they never see each other so what happens they're all playing in their own apartment rooms so they're all living in this big apartment complex and they all live in their own apartments and they only interact through this television thing that's the circle there's no camera there it's just like chatting and stuff so like for example and I won't spoil anything because this is in the very first episode
one of the guys going in is playing as his girlfriend because he thinks that he'll have an easier time meeting and connecting with people as a woman so he does this and playing and playing as a girlfriend and does a really good job of the catfish through the whole thing whereas there's another guy that is playing it's like a younger hotter version of himself who kind of screws it up like is not very good at being a catfish so it's just kind of interesting to see how that all works out and then the twist is
when one of them they have to rank everybody how they like everybody and then you know like I think it's like the top two get to kick somebody else out they get to block somebody so when somebody gets kicked out of the show on their way out they get to go to somebody's apartment meet one person face to face and so like in the case of like one there was like a romantic connection thing going on and like they met and they found out oh my god you really are you and they like they ended up making out and stuff because they're like you're hot you're hot oh my god I'm so happy
and so they did that whole thing but then there were other circumstances where like I want to go meet this person and when they went they were not who they said they were and it was like oh my like what the hell were you doing type of thing and like that person had to explain their reasons on why they didn't so it's interesting yeah anyway sorry but I will I will agree with Bobby Black Wolf who says the only good reality show was the mole with Anderson Cooper honestly I wouldn't say it was the only good one but it was by far the best one
there will never be a better reality-based competition show than the mole specifically when Anderson Cooper was the host absolutely correct so I would have I would have loved it like that was the show I would want to be on more than anything anyway all right it was like James Bond is a TV show but anyway let's move on okay I get excited when trashy reality shows come up there's a you know there's a real big season of Survivor coming up right that show has been on so fucking
long you ready for this the next season of Survivor is a bunch of people who
have already won the show competing to win again and now the prize is two
million dollars and that's the whole catch so it's but was the previous prize
one million dollars yeah one million dollars but now they already you've all
already won a million dollars but you've never won two million dollars this is
the biggest prize in reality histories I don't know so yeah but a lot of the fit
longtime fans of the show are like these are the best of the best people get in
to play so it's like the true all-stars anyway enough that back to games back
to you all right Nintendo switch an interesting patent that was filed for
the Nintendo switch a patent application that went to the United States patent
and trademark office you can't always read too much into these because
sometimes companies are piloting things that they end up never actually
releasing for example what was the thing for the weed the monitor of the pulse
thing on the vitality that's a little bit different cuz they actually show
that off I think they did but you know it didn't it didn't actually happen at
the end of the day right yeah and the zapper looked different too yeah I
remember that so some of these things get so far along some of them don't but
what's interesting about this is that you know it's it's kind of a stylus but
not really it's a touch pen attachment that slides into the side of a joy con
and works with the controller so you don't put this on your switch and use it
like on the switch what you do once you've taken the controller out you put
the pen in the controller and so you have the controller but then you just
flip it upside down you have a pen so it turns your controller in both kind of
interesting the way I guess yeah I have the stylus plan with that so that is
what the patent basically says apparently the joy con will vibrate when
the pen comes into contact with an on-screen object so you could have oh
my god what was that game and it was so the incredible maze or so what was the
maze game irritating me here was that it yeah dark soccer I feel like you
brought this up on the show before it was a arcade game really a big stick and
you had to move through a maze irritating stick is that irritating
stick yeah that is it irritating stick that's I feel like this attachment could
get us an appropriate port of irritating stick everybody in chat is yelling out
the name yes thank you thank you that's what I want that's what I'm thinking
this could do is it could give us a proper port of irritating stick anyway
but it's also pointed out this could be great for things like Super Mario maker
2's course creator and things like that so I I think this would be neat who
somebody put somebody spoke it into the universe that this would be perfect to
bring back elite beat agents if they wanted to do that yes yes yes yes are
you paint or you know there's a variety although that doesn't look I don't know
if there's enough detail style of support I mean that's all you need yeah
I feel like it kind of already supports stylus I mean it doesn't specifically
support stylus but like we know there's a brain age game that just released in
Japan there's been that that was it Vox or something like that was like it you
had to play it on the touchpad like a music game that came out kind of early
on yeah you know this seems like a very logical step but a very Nintendo way to
do it is like it's not just a pen it's a pen that goes with your joy con so you
can have a vibrating pen just what you need thank you it's a voice vo easy or
like putting those like those additional things on the joy cons because I find
that they're so hard to take off so like yeah hopefully it's a very easy way to
release it all right anyway let's move on dark Sakura another another real
world kind of story this is fascinating kinda um and I even wonder if part of
this happened just out of coincidence but there's a little bit more to it
than what's listed in the article so after the advent of the corona virus
which is basically that big virus that's pretty much infecting a lot of a lot of
China right now we've had two reported cases in the u.s. and shut down like
Shanghai Disney or something for something yeah and there's I think nine
people in Alameda that are being tested do people die from this yeah there's
been deaths but not always it's like a really bad it's a real it's like West
Nile level like swine flu when it first hit okay you did and I did too but we
didn't get it at first yeah but you know I didn't know I had swine flu when I had
swine flu I'm sorry I didn't mean to give it to you know it's fine but you
know what early on cuz you know I knew somebody that passed away from it and it
was horrible she was only 24 but my point is I'm not trying to bring up bad
memories but I'm just I remember that like certain people but as the strain
got weaker it wasn't so bad like I'm just like how serious is this it's
pretty serious right now I on it like I've heard this is a thing but I didn't
know like is it you get it you're dead I don't think if you get it you're dead
but you're gonna be out of commission for a while I feel really a little bit
worried for my friend who I hung out with today is going to Thailand in a
week or so so at any rate there has been an uptick in people playing plague
Inc which is a real-time strategy game that has you releasing a pathogen and
making it spread to pretty much destroyed humanity it's a very kind of
black humor type of game well that's kind of morbid but that's how some
people cope it came out in 2012 and you pick your pathogen and you decide how to
transmit it and blah blah blah you know you start off with patient zero and to
quote the description the title now you must bring about the end of human
history by evolving a deadly global plague whilst adapting against anything
humanity can do to defend itself or everything sorry at any rate they have
actually repeated on their Twitter from endemic creations that their servers for
multiplayer and custom scenarios are trying to keep up with a high number of
players and the funny thing is someone you know happy to post it maybe a few
days ago that steam was having a sale for plague Inc and it could have just
been a coincidence the sales probably a coincidence those things have to be
planned out in advance a little bit but the popularity probably isn't as of
right now well as of this the the details I'm looking at the coronavirus
was detected in Wuhan it infected more than 1,300 people and killed over 40
with cases confirmed in all over Asia US Europe and Australia Bobby Black Wolf is
also pointing out that with lunar new year steam is doing a lunar sale right
now everything's on sale so that's yeah the very good point that lunar new year
probably comes into play there but one thing that endemic pretty much said is
that they said that the game shouldn't replace a scientific understanding of
the illness that it's just a game not a scientific model so please don't use
this to track how you think the virus would spread fascinating but it is it
does kind of bring up the interesting fascination that like you know some of
these things that video games have brought have actually been studied and
like you know my brain goes to the the early version of World of Warcraft or
more they had that event or pretty crazy yeah so if you this is news to you
like there was like an in-game plague type of thing basically when you when
you went and fought one of the bosses you would get like a plague and like it
would eventually like sap your health and could eventually kill you and some
people were actually trolling and running to big cities to spread this
plague and like this whole event was studied by real-life epidemiologist yeah
see like what would happen potentially if this like a big outbreak happens so
this was published on September 27th 2005 about the about yeah the the virus
like effects of the of the the thing I'm trying to see what the name of the
quest buster says the corrupted blood corrupted blood that was Warcraft thank
you and it was called by the demon Hakkar so yeah I kind of that was like
after I quit one of the first times but yeah it was a Zul'Gurub one interesting
yeah but but I mean at any rate I agree plague Inc is a game don't don't use it
to track like real epidemiology especially since they have like a
nanovirus that can affect your brain in it those don't exist you know nano
machines in your brain not right now not yet but at any rate it is rather
interesting just how kind of like those things kind of go hand in hand and maybe
some people are dealing with it oh no yeah wow all right well let's move on
and talk about I guess somewhat some less serious news but people are taking
this very seriously still what's happening here yeah definitely big news
so Activision is moving to YouTube to air their major competition so for
example they're going to start airing the Overwatch League on YouTube so
basically now they said that YouTube will host the official live broadcasts
of Activision Blizzard popular sports eat our eSports leagues and events
including the newly created Call of Duty League Overwatch League and hearthstone
eSports so yeah it's interesting that they are moving over to that platform
I'm wondering what kind of money they threw at them for that but yeah I
wonder what this means necessarily for twitch I mean I don't know like I don't
really watch these normally so it means nothing to me once in a while
especially the first year when I was playing more overwatch I really played
overwatch in a while but when I was playing it more often especially because
it would be in the Blizzard launcher you know I'd be like oh I'll check it out
and they would actually tie for a short time they tied like if you watch the
stream you might get in-game rewards oh yeah that was kind of and I imagine that
might still be a thing they're just gonna tie it to your Google account they
have that for YouTube though like that works I don't know either but we'll see
but yeah I mean I'm not really often on YouTube seeking out live game stream
content no I go to YouTube because somebody linked a funny one on on
Twitter or something like I don't really watch a lot of YouTube which by the way
speaking of funny stuff I don't know if you guys heard the that vine is
essentially back but it's got a new name called bite just throwing it out there
because I made a bite account I know I saw that you did that I was like what
social media platform is this six second video thing again it's interesting so
anyway um but sorry they couldn't they couldn't they couldn't stand seeing
tick-tock take off and kinda I think that's part of it actually damn it
close it down but honestly like sometimes when I was on Twitch I would
see Oh Overwatch League is streaming I'll go you know maybe watch a little
bit of that because you know there's not it's kind of interesting to watch video
games of sport sometimes but the point is I probably am NOT going to go to
YouTube to seek this out so like for me it's gonna be a loss I'm not gonna end
up watching as much of it as I would have on Twitch I understand money talks
and all that but I just I don't know Twitch was always to me a better
environment for that but I understand they had a contract contract was up they
didn't pony up the money to renew it so they went somewhere else that's business
but it'll be interesting to see if it maintains the type of numbers over on
YouTube so yeah but you know to be YouTube's are also incredibly easy to
link into and things like that even when live so they might just put it like
right in the launch or just embed the YouTube and you can kind of watch the
live events right there I don't know it'll be interesting to see that so all
right moving on talking a little bit about something else to look forward to
in 2020 and that is more game streaming different types of streaming one of them
is streaming your console to a device and this is something that you can
preview now if you have an Xbox and you are in the Xbox insider program you can
actually play with streaming Xbox game to an Android phone and tablet so you do
have to have an Android device that runs marshmallow or higher and you have to
have a Bluetooth Xbox one controller and of course a fast home network to be able
to stream things through but if you have all that you can test that now streaming
from your device to your phone and using your Bluetooth controller to play so
that could be very interesting yeah cool I don't well I don't maybe Alan has an
Android device maybe his tablet runs more I should see if his tablet will do
it but I also kind of feel like if it's within my house I'm just gonna play it
on my Xbox or my PC I don't really have a need for this myself but when they
start opening it up to Oh through the magic of you know 4G and LTE and someday
5g will be fast enough for it it'll be interesting to see what this is like
when it's on the go anywhere so it'll be cool yeah yeah now there's that industry
means there's that and then there's also X cloud which is kind of like the stadia
model where you're playing on someone else's in the cloud and then that's
coming to you down to your TV Microsoft is going to be expanding project X cloud
into Canada the testing will start in Canada on January 29th and you can
actually a register to try that if you want and if you're in the program you'll
have access to over 50 games through an Android phone or tablet so again you
have to be using the Android device because that's what Microsoft is testing
with I imagine everything else will roll out slowly later on so that's kind of
neat that that is expanding and I'm very much looking forward to seeing what more
streaming brings in the year 2020 so alright well let's let's go back to a
simpler time we're gonna take a trip down memory lane when you couldn't
stream video games you know you you had to have the cartridge you kind of could
I was gonna say there's Sega it was a Sega net or whatever and actually I
think tonight dark soccer has stepped into the gaming vault and found a game
and she does this sometimes so the qualifications is a game has to be 10
years or older to qualify and I looked on the list and this wasn't done this
well it was you know why it wasn't done because it's like it's it's like 11
years no it's not I think in the u.s. I think it's 10 years old this month yeah
and so I definitely had a note of like this is one of those selections tonight
where you're gonna go shit it's that I'm so old I remember talking about this
game on her time waits for no one that's right so there's our mortal dark soccer
what is the classic game of the week Bayonetta cuz it's fucking Bayonetta and
so at any rate the game came out in in Japan it was in October 2009 on Xbox
360 and PlayStation 3 it was developed by Platinum games and published by Sega
it later got a Wii U release along with Bayonetta 2 in September 2014 in Japan
and worldwide the next month there's an enhanced port for Windows that came on
April 2017 with 4k and a switch release along with Bayonetta 2 and a third game
is in development set to release on the switch as well and apparently there's
gonna be a another release of Bayonetta along with Vanquish on PlayStation 4 and
Xbox one next month so Bayonetta takes place in a fictional European city
called V grid and she is a witch well technically it's not a spoiler by now
she is the child of a Lumen sage and an Umbra witch so and she is in possession
of one of the the eyes of God or something I always forget the name like
for the stuff but anyway it's got a really kind of convoluted storyline but
she she does magic and shoots things and uses her hair for a lot of her magic it
functions a lot like Devil May Cry I think it was actually built on the same
engine and it was had the same creator Kamiya Hideki so you basically run
around hacking and slash and shooting things with with gun and kicking people
with giant high-heeled boots made out of a demon from another dimension that
you open with your hair and just kicking a bunch of ass there was even an anime
which I watched the anime it was really really fun you also have some special
commands including torture attacks where you can do like pretty hardcore damage
and you get chainsaws iron maidens it's pretty pretty crazy and she also has
witch time that lets you dodge attacks it slows down time as well for extra
attack she has double jumps and backflips and getting rid of background
objects and doing door things you know very interactive and then you have
different chapters with different verses in them as you're going through fighting
all of these angels and you also have a mini game called angel attack where you
can use arcade bullets that you find through the level to shoot angels and
earn points you can trade them in for items or trade them in for halos and
that one dude I don't know his name but in the game but he sounds a lot like Joe
Pesci that's the one takeaway they had from I don't think I've actually played
it in English dude right there oh yeah like Joe Pesci yeah I don't think I've
played this in English anyway your difficulties are very easy easy normal
hard and non-stop infinite climax I just think that that's a fun name and as far
as you know the various characters you have you have Bayonetta herself you have
a child that she meets you which I'm not gonna say any more about the child
because again if you played it you played it if not you haven't there's
another character named Luca there is Bayonetta's rival Jean there's Rodin who
is like her armorer there's Enzo the informant and yeah he's the one that
sounds like Joe Pesci and the little girl's name's Teresa but again we go
back into that later at any rate it kind of borrows a little bit from the divine
comedy if you've noticed where it's named the the various settings are named
after the books for the divine comedy a Paradiso Purgatorio and Inferno I can't
think of having ever maybe I'm thinking of the anime because that's the last
Bayonetta thing that I looked at so I didn't remember the English voices
anyway but at any rate the the way that you beat the game though is so
over-the-top and extra that I still can't get over it you literally punch
the soul out of God and into the Sun spoilers at any rate the the game was
meant to be fashionable and meant to be a little sexy and it really kind of
focused on that very high style and then of course when it came to creating
the characters their whole point come here said that the characters were the
Jean the one that he came up with was supposed to be his ideal woman I'm like
okay but okay I candy and that he actually took from a little bit of
Scandinavian mythology and and that he named Bayonetta's guns after the
Scarborough Fair ballad with her guns being named parsley sage rosemary and
thyme but at any rate the whole game was just meant to be sexy very very very
sexy and fun and it is a very fun game with a really weird freaking really
weird freaking storyline especially when you get to Bayonetta 2 and it's kind of
a weird post prequel on the level of the homestuck Dancestors type concept
but I mean there were so many things that came out afterward there was like a
bayonet a theme for chrome there's a song called reaping beauty by MC Lars
but I love MC Lars that was inspired by Bayonetta I'll kind of there's like a
hundred and fifty song five CD soundtrack for the game and then there's
another one that for they came with pre-orders the game called Rodin
selection and then there's like all this stuff I mean it's all crazy and then of
course there's the anime that came out at Bayonetta bloody fate which for me I
would I just I have that on my iTunes account I'll just pull that up and watch
it whenever because it's really fun but it was really really well received
Famitsu gave it for the 360 a 40 out of 40 the ps3 version got a 38 out of 40
but still like that's Famitsu giving it a 40 out of 40 which is an Xbox game at
that that's unheard of in Japan yeah and I I guess the the PlayStation 1 had a
few other issues with it like for control I have to dig deeper because I
mean it's it was yeah it was criticized for having a lesser visual quality frame
rate and control problems compared to the Xbox 360 version I remember that
the control had been part of it but yeah this is it was like an instant classic
and there you have it Bayonetta which also watching the Bayonetta 2 speed run
AGD Q pretty freaking rad I'm excited for part three yeah the story got extra
convoluted with Bayonetta to just saying all right and I loved this comment
actually made me laugh from a nifty 805 in our chat who usually says funny shit
in our chat nifty 805 says Bayonetta could totally host tonight at hamburger
Mary's mmm I mean Bayonetta is kind of like a drag icon like I Bayonetta is
like a bio queen basically I mean that and and to be fair Jean Valjean is Jean
Valjean is totally bad as well huh Jean Valjean was from Les Mis I was reading I
have my eyes on it Jean yes not not the Les Mis character J-E-A-N-N-E Jean Jean
sorry I'm saying things aloud but anyway monsieur the man I would be madame the
mayor but anyway they are totally bio queens and you know Lady Gaga has
tweeted about Bayonetta and how much she loves it and you know it's kind of funny
oh it's a good game all right there there's classic game of the week a real
classic there oh one other thing too is that there's just all kinds of references
to other Sega games in there too like you have the part where you're riding on
the plane that was oh sorry that we just had the car sequence that has I think
outrun music yeah so you did the game actually spawned the one like I think
three different climax mixes one of them was for afterburner when it was for
outrun and there was another one that I can't think of off the top of my head
but yeah there were the and they were called the climax mixes so there you go
all right good choice Bayonetta oh and thank you Seattle Barry the the prisoner
number was two four six oh one yes yes now I yes of course I remember they miss
anyway the film was the same guy that did cats
dar Sakura was Les Mis and cats were the same director so I think as was
brilliant and that well that's part of the reason why I wanted to see cats
because I loved Les Mis and cats was brilliant moving on to rapid-fire news
and talking about some things quickly that are happening in the gaming world
lots of other headlines Loki says we're talking about Animal Crossing earlier
it's only fair to mention Stardew Valley which has reached the 10 million
milestone for copies sold and it's still going pretty strong it's out on all
major platforms nowadays and might even I don't know who knows where it's gonna
go as far as sales goes but I know I was talking to one of my co-workers the
other day they mentioned that they're playing Stardew Valley quite a bit and I
never pegged him to be a Stardew Valley type of guy but yeah it's interesting
and then we've got the news that Pokemon Mewtwo strikes back evolution is gonna
be headed to Netflix on February 27th apparently the movie this is the season
remake of the first movie this is a CGI remake of the first movie yeah okay I'll
take things I really didn't need for 500 it was really good though no I mean the
first movie was cute but I just I'm alright whatever oh I'll check out the
new one on Netflix why not I already subscribed to Netflix anyways I'll check
it out so alright moving on let's talk about the Mortal
Kombat collection online this was something that was in development but
then they canceled the project but now apparently a ps4 version has been rated
so maybe it came back maybe got uncancelled who knows what happened with
all that but there's yeah the definite spotting of this out in the wild this is
going to be the upgraded trilogy so it's the original trilogy but they've
upgraded all the graphics to HD so it's a little different than the Mortal
Kombat collection already exists out there because there is like a like
arcade port one but this was no they were gonna go back and redo everything
widescreen HD and all that and redo the sprites and so that's kind of
interesting yeah so we don't know anything else at this time we don't even
know if it's actually legit happening or something really weird that came through
or what but there it is Mortal Kombat collection online stay tuned we may have
more on that something else to stay tuned for I know I'm excited about this
release Xenoblade Chronicles Definitive Edition for the switch remember this
this was the game that you really couldn't get on the Wii unless you went
to GameStop years after it had already been out in Europe but yeah so a lot of
people kind of missed this one but it's definitely one I want to check out when
it releases on the switch and apparently a retailer has listed the game for the
29th of May it was a Swedish website that did that we're just waiting for
Nintendo to confirm it maybe they'll announce a direct in the coming months I
can't like there has to be a direct before Animal Crossing that's gonna do a
deep dive on Animal Crossing and I imagine might go over some of these
releases for the next few months but you know I don't think that direct is gonna
happen as soon as next week but maybe in February at some point so that's what
I got dark Sakura well for one thing looks like that Soulcalibur 6 is getting
another DLC character which is how Maru who is also from the summary showdown
series so he's gonna be joining in there along with a few other characters and
another one that for me I really think deserves a lot more gravitas than being
a rapid-fire thing is the riot games lawsuit with re-evaluation of the case
and how much the women have lost with gender harassment and income disparity
instead of being paid out 10 million as part of the settlement they're pushing
for it to be 400 million which is in line with how much time money and stress
that they've been put under based on their employers they reach a preliminary
lawsuit settlement in December they were waiting for it to be approved but then
two more state agencies weighed in and on a document for January 8th the
California Department of Fair Employment and Housing said the women of riot games
could be entitled to over 400 million in potential back pay based on wage
differential between men and women at the company excluding any additional
penalties based on those calculations and this is you know considering from
October 2018 they're adding adding that the non-monetary terms of the settlement
were inadequate in writing it says no enforceable changes to employment
policies at a company alleged to be rife with sexism were part of the settlement
and should be included in the settlement so I always thought it here because it's
not finalized and it's a follow-up so but we'll see we'll keep our eyes on it
and see what happens in coming weeks so something that could potentially have
big ramifications the gaming industry as a whole but definitely you know it's
and riots trying to do is definitely trying to defame the the whole the DFEH
by saying that they're filling they're filing with inaccuracies and false
allegations but and they say oh we've tried to make things diverse and
inclusive um no not if what other people are saying is true no you haven't no not
at all so uh and of course with all those exposites out you know I'm really
glad that their ass is being handed to them so all right it'll be interesting
to see if there's any others that come out I mean I would hope not but there's
that realist in me that says it's coming you know I mean like you don't
want it to be true but you know in the back your mind it probably is right so
we'll see what happens all right moving on let's travel around the world and
check out some release dates coming out to a store near you in various regions
starting with the u.s. Loki we've got journey to the savage planet on PC
PlayStation 4 and Xbox one Kentucky route 0 TV edition on Nintendo switch
PlayStation 4 and Xbox one pillars of eternity to dead fire on PlayStation 4
and Xbox one Warcraft 3 reforged on PC and Mac and yeah that's finally
happening yeah yeah it is and last but not least hyper charge unboxed on PC
and Nintendo switch all right traveling over to Japan and checking out some of
the releases on Nintendo switch Rivera dune menagerie I hope it's in it's like
got a French accent thing going on I have no idea what is that game I'm now
I'm curious but that is on the release of the Nintendo switch and I'm still
waiting for that to load tell me more about this game oh it looks oh it's one
of those like manga wedding oh it's the French word for dreaming of a carousel
and it's about a traveling so dreams of carousels seriously that's boring maybe
when I have a scary dream anyway that that huge two-story one at Great America
truly frightening anyway other Japanese releases coming in Nintendo switch the
Kemco RPG selection volume one that's pretty cool that sounds like a bunch of
like retro releases of old Kemco games ooh it is it's as divine hearts revenant
saga antico lost and dragon sinker that's pretty cool some old-school JRPGs
also on the switch we have coffee talk no it is not with Linda Richmond it's
just a game called coffee talk I don't what is this another anime based game
oh the main character she's got green hair she looks and she has some coffee
tales of people from an alternative Seattle a city where elves orcs
mermaids and many other fantasy races live together with humans in a modern
world we all find familiar hmm sorry but I can't I can't if Mike Myers isn't in
it with that big hair I can't the Nintendo switch it's neither Nintendo
switch discuss that was supposed to be his mother-in-law at the time oh was it
yeah Linda Richmond was based off of his mother god his mother-in-law a o tennis
too is also coming out on the Nintendo switch on the PlayStation 4 the Kemco
RPG selection volume 3 is out on the PlayStation 4 I'm assuming previous
volumes have already been released there as well as coffee talk is also being
released there and boku tojo I know shinsatsu
is coming out in regular and a limited edition type of game and that is a game
where the character is just finished medical school and is now an intern at
the hospital but this doesn't look like trauma center this looks like Grey's
Anatomy to me just saying so there you go those are the Japanese releases how
about the UK dark soccer oh just a handful on the 27th which is already now
in Europe I think is pillars of eternity to dead fire on the 29th we have a o10
s2 on the 30th we have hero land noble edition we have Blair Witch also journey
to the savage planet and ash of God's redemption all right so that does it for
the release dates around the world usually at this part of the show we
would go into our mailbag because you can email us every week at participate
at orange lounge radio.com but I believe the mailbag came up empty tonight right
yeah all right well we're kids if you remember the punishment for no emails is
Drag Race talk but here's the interesting thing I'm what you you can
and you can say briefly about this because they just announced the new cast
of season 12 I only paid attention to two of them I'm yeah I'm I'm kind of
burned out on Drag Race this might surprise you guys but I'm a little
burned out I'm not gonna be doing reading his fundamental podcast this
year I've already talked to the guys about that it's nothing they're all
wonderful I love those guys to bits but this time I'm just I don't want to talk
about that show for another year good names on here yeah no and it's it's not
about the talent that's on the show it's the best thing about the show is
introduces you to new people but dark soccer quickly who are the two that
you're rooting for the two that I'm rooting for is rockin Sakura just cuz
that's funny and it's a San Francisco Queen and I am also really really happy
about sherry pie sherry pie I've followed on the Instagram's and things
for a little while now just seems like a quality person very talented Queen
and rockin Sakura is a you know like I said San Francisco girl we have to
support our locals who is the one if you remember because I did JD really likes
this one and made me watch the video and I liked her too the one that's um she's
Iranian Canadian I think but lives in the US now and she had like her look was
very like Iranian inspired that she showed she was really so I'll read I
liked her the names we definitely have an artsy one Aiden Zane hmm and then
Zane is from Ackworth Georgia and I thought yeah I'd be black wolf and I saw
that and then we have just the names this season are great Brita filter from
New York of course we've got New York Queens we have who's this next one
crystal method me th YD from Springfield Missouri we have Dahlia sin from LA who
I actually think I ran into a drag on we have Gigi good from LA we have Heidi
in closet mm-hmm it's the best thing from North Carolina mm-hmm also we have
Jackie Cox from NYC another fucking New York Queen maybe that I think that is
who I'm thinking of let me go back and look I think it's Jackie Cox doesn't say
in the bio oh well it's fine um but anyway I'll just go ahead and read
through the names quickly there's Jada essence Hall from Minneapolis we have
Jan sport that makes me think my backpacks in high school we have Nicky
doll another new fuck New York Queens we have Rockham Sakura who already I'm
super happy about definitely pie though it's definitely a gamer girl just say
absolutely a gamer girl oh absolutely I've been I've been on her insta for a
little while too cool I'm excited about sherry pie as well who is just like
classic drag we also have kind of like the Miss Kasha Davis Pandora box type
yeah we have widow von do from Kansas City yeah and that's them very very
clever group I mean I I have to when we've got a San Francisco Queen after so
long I feel I have to watch all right all right there it is
uh send us emails to avoid drag race talk next week
participate at orange lounge radio just like see me torture well I might have to
think of a new stunt because I don't really plan to watch it so I mean I
probably not be able to are you caught up on the good place because there's
only two episodes I have to episode well I think the second the last episode and
the last up say things this week all right well let's move on we have some
more video game stories for you guys and then we'll open up discord to see if
anybody wants to call in tonight over at vog network comm slash discord Loki I
think it's been a while since we talked about this but you may remember there
was a company I life technologies who was you know claiming that the Wii
remote infringed upon several of its patents this was back in 2017 they found
apparently in Texas or they found that the company they awarded them I guess
ten point one million dollars for that however apparently they have Nintendo
has successfully overturned that lawsuit so they're not gonna be responsible for
the $10 million overall says claim one encompasses a sensor that senses data a
processor that processes data and the communications device that communicates
data no further and inventive concept is recited to transform the extract idea
into a patent eligible invention so basically saying that you know what they
patented was not really worthwhile so interesting I mean basically Nintendo
of course saying that Nintendo has a long history of developing new unique
products and we were pleased that after many years of litigation the court
agreed with Nintendo we can continue we will continue to vigorously defend our
products against companies seeking the profit off the technology they did not
invent fair enough hmm just like in it just so you know companies if you're
gonna sue Nintendo they will keep suing until they would know is a litigate
litigates company you can never say that word litigious litigious litigious
company they will definitely defend themselves in court absolutely and we
all know they love their cease-and-desist to protect their
intellectual property which you know as much as you can say Nintendo is the
bad guy for that they kind of you know it they have to do it I think in this
case I don't obviously I don't think this is sounds like more like a patent
troll company you know that they're trying to get a piece of that Nintendo
money but didn't work out for them yeah and also the fact that we're just now
talking about a Wii remote settlement I think also shows like how long these
things fucking take in the court well yeah 2017 is when they have that
judgment which means the court's case probably started in 2016 I mean it's
been a long time all right well moving on to talking about Niantic and some of
their real-world events because you know they do the big Pokemon go thing which
was a huge flop the first year but it got a lot better in subsequent years
I've talked about ingress events on this show before I've attended several of
them in person myself and Niantic has announced some of their plans for the
next year turns out Pokemon go events not just gonna be happening in Chicago
they had spread out to these Safari zone events and other places as well but you
know as far as like the u.s. to we weren't really seeing a lot of stuff
outside Chicago or really that would be North America honestly well now we're
starting to see a little more I mean it's not gonna be everywhere but we're
seeing some more stuff spreading out with Pokemon go there's gonna be an
event that coincides with the Taiwan Lantern Festival from February 6th to
the 9th there will be a Safari zone event in St. Louis from March 27th and
29th Liverpool will get the Safari zone event as well in April and then there
will be a Philadelphia Safari zone from May 8th through May 10th Harry Potter
Wizards unite will also be having another fan festival they had one last
year in I think it was Indianapolis it was somewhere I would have never thought
like a big but that's where they did it they have not said the date or the
location yet for Harry Potter but they're just saying we will be doing
something again and then of course for Ingress Ingress has their own events as
well they have what's called the perpetual hexathlon that's happening on
February 29th I'm not going because I have a conflict I think the closest one
to here you can either go nine hours south to Tijuana or you can go nine hours
to the east to Salt Lake City although most people I know are going to San
Antonio for that so weird but okay that's the city they're going to which
is fine when that's happening on February 29th lexicon hexathlon is
happening on April 25th what that's gonna be in San Francisco so that'll be
easy for us to go to and then there will also be the requiem anomaly in Munich on
May 9th which I would like to see more anomalies as opposed to hexathlons I get
that Ingress is trying to do some different things but I'm very
disappointed to see there's only one anomaly in the first six months of the
year and it's not even in this country and it's just like it's completely not
something I'm gonna be able to attend so that's a bummer but that's happening on
May 9th also some of the economic information about how these events have
been doing 249 million in tourism for revenue across Chicago Dortmund and
Montreal for some of the events have taken place maybe it's quite a bit yeah
that's a lot of money so pretty cool so Niantic's real-world events will
continue to grow I am sure so all right and hack def says come to Tijuana I
would have given it some serious thought but again I already I that is
that conflicts with the Star Trek cruise sadly so I will be completely out of
that event and that's that's what happens is these real-world events
sometimes they're just the wrong fucking day so I can't do them even if it was
like right here in my backyard so all right anyway moving on
Dark Sakura with an interesting video game story well and you know me I like
to tie things in on you know the real world so there has been an application
to the FDA for a video game to be prescribed and the video game
specifically is marketed for kids with ADHD they haven't gotten a green light
on it yet they filed in 2018 the startup company is Akili interactive labs and
they submitted for a game they're making let me see about getting the name on it
here project project Evo is Lisa's what it yeah from an early version of the
game it's supposed to help with helping kids focus there I don't this is taking
a very long time for it they haven't gotten any any momentum on it but
they're thinking that it's gonna be something that's gonna help a lot of
kids in need so I hope so it would certainly set interesting precedents
wouldn't it kind of game is it let's see it's played on a tablet and it sends
players through landscapes like lava river or a snow scape rewards you with
stars and points as you finish tasks so it's to quote this here it's the video
game as a delivery system for targeted algorithms that can activate certain
neural networks in the brain so it's meant to trigger I guess neuron building
is it pretty interesting and they're hoping that once that it's been approved
that they'll be able to again market it as a I guess a prescription subscription
I've never heard of like the idea of video games through prescription though
it's I mean it makes a lot of sense it's just like it's it's not for me it's not
something to pick up on Steam it's not something to go just get a store it's
like it has a very specific purpose which is like adjacent to edutainment
but I think that's also a really unfair thing to compare it to but I don't know
what out what other bucket to like put it in well another ADHD specialist who
is not associated with the company at all and says that there's a great demand
for non non pharmacological interventions and this quote says a
product that can help to remediate cognitive issues that children with ADHD
are experiencing would be I think very helpful and popular families really
trying to go through cognitive therapies instead of just drugging kids yeah Bobby
Blackwell actually points out that there's another game that is available
via prescription I never heard of this there's a VR game that you can get via
prescription it's called and he mentions the name is changed to vivid vision and
it helps fix lazy eye it is only available by prescription for amblyopia
I'm sorry I hope I'm saying that right lazy eye yeah lazy eye basically so
that's fascinating I never knew that I knew like video games obviously because
we've had the stories on the show before about how video games are used as like
treatment in some cases especially we've heard like with children I mean hell
we've heard about like DDR and PE class right which isn't necessarily to treat
anything but you still have like the games being used you know to to help with
certain things but I've like to go so far as to say via prescription that's so
fascinating to me yeah and honestly there is a link I mean we'll just I'm
gonna throw this out there how they say that playing video games helps with hand
eye coordination all of that is built in the brain you know that muscle memory
included that's one thing too but the brain builds those pathways that are
gonna create that muscle memory and create the instinct that the body is
gonna have and that is all based on visual cues and acting upon them this is
no different huh and I I had no idea about this but Bobby says the dude who
made vivid vision was partially inspired by my article on vog because Bobby's
talked about this before some of his stereo blindness issues and how that's
worked with the 3ds and you know some some of the early VR stuff and so I'm
one of those articles he wrote got a little bit of traction on some of those
communities so he said he even mentioned that article early on impressed stuff I
think he even commented on the article at vog well that's really your impact
that's no it's really awesome good it's not just variety articles anymore yes
yes not just variety articles hype mayhem has a good question if a game is
prescribed by a doctor will insurance companies cover it well I'll tell you
this insurance companies don't cover every medication when I had to take
pro vigil when I was having like the bad fault passing out at my desk problem it
wasn't covered by my insurance I know it was and then when new vigil came out
that wasn't covered by my insurance so there are still new therapies like I'll
give you another one when I was diagnosed with minor sleep apnea before
my surgery I had to use these no stickers that were 70 bucks for a month
to keep my nasal airways open and no not breathe right they go they're
little nets that go in your nose I'm pointing at my nose like people can see
it they go in your nose with a sticker around it that wraps over and it
actually just keeps the the knees the nasal passage held open but it whistles
so I'd wake myself up whistling through my nose but at any rate those weren't
covered by my insurance I still paid 70 bucks a month for him for two months and
then decide I wasn't into it again yeah I worked in insurance for 14 years I
don't anymore so I can talk a little more openly about it actually I'm sorry
it was more like 18 years those two different companies but usually like if
you were to go to a doctor's office or a center to play the game it would
probably be considered part of the therapy there and would probably be
covered like that but if it's something where it's like you have to buy it and
take it home it'd probably be viewed akin to like a textbook in a class and
you wouldn't it wouldn't be covered by the insurance but don't take my advice
for it call your company if you have any suggestions I can only tell you based on
my experience this is the likely turnout sorry there's another thing about this
though is that they didn't really see there was a marked improvement for
people that were playing the game but it wasn't a big enough improvement the
researchers that the researchers wanted to see and then when they did their
control testing they had a sham game versus the real thing and people that
played the sham game as well they they did well too the so really in general
it's the games having a kid sit down to focus on the game increase the child's
attentiveness in general so it the he kind of set himself up for failure this
way or the company set itself up for failure this way hmm I mean and they're
trying to market this in a pharmacological setting not necessarily
as a technological one where I think that if they I mean there's not really
anything new that they're doing you know a kid even with a short attention span
can usually sit and play a puzzle game or something because the thing is that
these games are offering enough dynamic visual information that I think it can
make things easier to focus on when you've got a lot more stimulation going
on in front of you than just looking at words on a paper and listening to your
teacher drone you know just saying yeah all right well we're gonna move on as I
as fascinating as this is and I love hearing stories about video games being
used just outside of like you know entertainment and its impact on the real
world but moving on we got a couple more stories for you guys before we get to
calls so Loki your turn all right so we have news about acquisitions so Tencent
you may remember who you know owns a good share of Riot games epic supercell
Ubisoft parallax or paradox I'm sorry I and frontier they are now looking to
purchase acquire full ownership of fun calm the makers of Conan exiles age
Conan anarchy online in the secret world and apparently they're already largest
shareholder of the company at 29% as of today but they are they're looking to
acquire more purchase more shares from fun calm current holders to make that
acquisition it says we have a great relationship according to fun calm CEO
we have a great relationship with Tencent as our largest shareholders so
far we are excited about this opportunity we will continue to develop
great games and that people all over the world play and believe that the support
Tencent will take fun calm to the next level so we'll have to see what happens
there's a lot of concern out there that Tencent is taking over too much yeah
because they have a lot of stuff so I mean this is just another one in the
pile there so I mean it's interesting because most of the company's Tencent I
feel like has been kind of investing in our most for the most part the smaller
stuff but then I think like well but riot games Tencent has a big we saw then
they are getting to be really really big there so they're although I mean they
don't all come together as like Tencent it's still like they're more like a
holdings company I guess in some ways it's kind of interesting so I guess
we'll see if that has any further impact on the industry as time rolls on hmm
alright moving on one more story for you guys and it has to do with video games
becoming movies and one movie I think people have been looking forward to is
the Uncharted movie well that has been delayed to March 20 March 5th excuse me
2021 and that's just because there's so many production hiccups going on they
can't fucking find a star I think is still the problem they're having because
I don't think Tom Holland is still in it right or I don't even know maybe that is
happening I don't know I get yeah the last thing it says the cast led by Tom
Holland and Mark Wahlberg is apparently settling so maybe that's no Mark Wahlberg
Mark Wahlberg should never be leading any cast now hiring Mark Wahlberg. He's not playing the main
character he's not playing Drake so Tom Holland ever happened to what's his name
playing Nathan Drake everybody wants him to play Nathan Fillion yeah no he did
that fan movie and then I think for the most part he's probably considered too
old for the part at this point I don't know but no come on I'm not saying
they're still making Indiana Jones movies I mean I think shit man man anyway now
there was a loss of a director so Travis Knight was the director attached to this
and he just recently had left the project so that's probably I mean
completing an uncharted movie that hadn't even started yet and having it in
theaters by December that was gonna be rough and I think even a March date
seems pretty I mean that's thinking there's not gonna be a lot of effects or
things like that in it I think I bet this gets pushed back again this ends up
being at least a summer movie for 2021 and that is assuming they find a new
director like now like next week we have an animated movie or something like that
or now the way to go is a Netflix series my god do you know how big the Witcher
is it's it's like one of the biggest series like ever now but I think it's
also well I think it's also important to note Netflix is global most TV shows
like let's say Game of Thrones on HBO not global in the same way especially
all at once so it's just it's interesting so anyway uncharted movie
delayed but it wasn't something I was exactly like gonna go running to the
theaters to see anyway so I'm not that torn up just think we're only three
weeks away from the Sonic the Hedgehog movie right oh I saw a billboard for
that yeah locally shit I thought of tiger I dropped something sorry I
thought a tiger claw while I was driving down cuz on 80 outside Dixon they have a
giant billboard and it has Sonic on it and it says if you were this guy you'd
be there by now we laugh we actually have one locally in Rancho Cordova on 50
oh really I haven't seen that one yeah yeah I have to go drive out that way so
where is it it's be it's between sunrise and hazel oh I'm usually not out that
far so okay that makes sense but interesting interesting all right well
anyhow let's move on and we're gonna open up our discord at vog network comm
slash discord to take some calls and I see somebody is already in the green
room ready to go so let's bring them on hi you're on orange launch radio who's
this hey what's going on everyone it is Rama great to hear from you Rama how
you doing not bad I just finished doing like several loads of laundry and now I
gotta get ready for the work we can kind of you know get back to this thing it's
it's the Sunday thing to do to catch up on laundry and things around the house
and that's kind of where lazy Sunday comes from even if you're doing chores
but me I was up until 3 a.m. last night and then got home at like 2 o'clock and
had to set everything up for the show tonight so like cranking out the show
roll and that that b-roll for Bayonetta like finished as Bobby show was starting
that's how late I was running tonight but we're done I understand there are
those times I go out Saturday night don't home to about four or five because
of the subway wake up around 11 12 dragging ass around the house trying to
figure out what all I have to do today you know I didn't realizing I got this
I got that I jump into J let me just run through this and I can't miss my Sunday
night gaming dates or else yeah I'm gonna get fracked well we always
appreciate you being here so what's on your mind tonight what you want to call
in about I appreciate that well I want to talk about this whole issue with
everybody has with streaming services and so forth Oh talking about like how
paradox is coming up with their own and all maybe and all this stuff yeah I look
at it this way just because they have exclusive shows you are not obligated to
sit there and subscribe to it there are ways around it yes people are going to
pirate I read an article where piracy had gone up since all these streaming
services came out and I said well it's not like it never left any reason to
save a buck but now as somebody who was watching the whole peacock presser and
all that stuff I can say this what Comcast is doing is giving everybody a
free subscription to peacock which I think is a good idea because that's what
AT&T is doing with their HBO max I really feel if some of these streaming
services can align themselves with certain providers and giving it away for
free or reduced price it can it could help you know yeah I have to say and
even though I have CBS all access for Star Trek and stuff I think it's really
silly of CBS to not have their television shows on a free version of
the platform I think you can go to their website and watch some of it but like it
should be mixed in with the CBS app that's there like if I want to watch
survivor from this week or something or what else is on CBS the undercover boss
is that still a thing I don't know if I want to go watch one of those shows I
should just download the app and be able to do it for free commercial support it
or whatever but then well the premium stuff then I have to pay for it I guess
well actually you can still do that to a certain extent because every cable
provider gives you a login you can make multiple logins and let's say you happen
to miss survivor and it's not on the DVR you can go to the website punching
your login credentials and you can watch it whether it's from the browser the app
or something yeah it's Xfinity and that stuff lets you do a lot of that so not
to endure I'm not endorsing anything but it is interesting how like if I want to
watch television on my second computer monitor that system does let me do it
and I will I will give it kudos for that it's probably the only reason I've kept
cable well same thing with Verizon I mean you know but unless I just I'm
sorry I have to read this comment from Jack's I think it's really good Phoenix
7726 says something also just occurred to me for those that want to see per
card and don't want to pay wait for it to come out on DVD or blu-ray and check
it out at your local library many have extensive video collections that's a
brilliant suggestion and yeah I think the first season of discovery did come
out on DVD and blu-ray and so and I think like orange is the new black on
the Netflix side a lot of these shows do the stranger things as well they do come
out on DVD and blu-ray eventually so you won't get to see it now but you'll see
it eventually I think that's a brilliant way to do it and you're not pirating
you're you're doing it the fairway I mean not for nothing I have Netflix I
did buy the first two seasons of Voltron legendary defender because there are
those times where you know yeah you can pull it up at any time but sometimes
this is a lot quicker to walk over to your shelf grab the disc and pop it in
and play and quickly sorry act up to saying the Picard series is on prime
video in Mexico yeah um so it's the in different regions they end up on
different services so Picard is on a thing called CBS all access and I think
that service actually only exists in the States maybe Canada but um yeah so like
a Star Trek discovery is on Netflix everywhere else but in the US it's on
the CBS thing and then Picard VPN well and that's that's neither here nor there
Picard is on the CBS thing here in the US then everywhere else it's on prime
video I say everywhere else but I think Canada is an asterisk because I think
discovery was actually on some Canadian service there sorry I don't remember off
top my head because it doesn't apply to me but I remember Delvin or one of my
Canadian friends telling me about this so Canada may not actually be the same
way but this happens a lot this is how the shows make extra money they sell the
rights in different countries like there's a show on the WB called Black
Lightning in the UK that's on Netflix now I'm like wow but let us not also
forget remember you can do your own team streaming whereas one person has Netflix
one person has Hulu one person has crunchyroll one person has Funimation
and a lot of these sites a lot of these services allow you to have multiple
streaming at the same time trade accounts and so forth you know that also
else yeah I've done that like I'm not gonna be you know try to lie and say but
I I have definitely shared the login like traded like oh you you want my CBS
cool can I get your Hulu and you know I've definitely done that before and you
know I think a lot of companies are thinking about cracking down on that but
yeah for right now I think a lot of people are doing the sharing thing it
because it let's be real if they try to crack down on it it they'll watch their
sales go up a little bit and then it'll probably sink back down because people
are starting to realize well I'm only gonna watch for certain things and call
it a day yeah well we'll see how this all pans out and you know we'll see if
peacock strategy you know since they are coming in this a little late to the game
although coming in late certain certainly didn't stop Disney Plus so
we'll see if maybe this strategy of being a little more free for some of the
stuff is gonna really help it out we'll see it's just matter of time and I and
I tell you this the couple of key points is the fact that what they're gonna live
streaming of sports events and none of their competitors do live streaming so
that's gonna be interesting and I've also found this out yeah I know there
are people who enjoy watching The Tonight Show and no lately late night
with Seth Meyers all of that if you get peacock you can watch that a couple of
hours before anybody else oh interesting yeah cuz they taped that stuff earlier
in the day yeah I can say this Fallon is taped around six and Seth is taped
around seven interesting but you know what's interesting living on the west
coast you know back when satellite was all the rage that was how we saw The
Tonight Show early is because oh we're watching an East Coast feed thanks to
satellite so we get The Tonight Show at 11 or excuse me at 830 now also kind of
mess with my head cuz I've traveled to my travel in the different times I'm
just like wait why is this an hour early is my watch wrong and I miss up
something you know time zones are crazy especially East Coast versus West Coast
and I know a lot of you East Coasters are listening and probably think it's
such as yourself Rama and probably think it's crazy that I'm telling you it's 830
here the night is still relatively hung but that's that's why we do the show
when we do it so that you know we have time to go home and decompress and you
know get ready for a Monday on the workday whereas for you East Coast folks
I know you stay up past midnight sometimes to listen to the very end of
the show so it's just fascinating how the world works like that and that's
well that's just West versus East Coast I'm not even considering some of the
folks in Europe that have listened Japan and so forth and those are real
crazy time differences I know Akuma JP listens to us on Monday morning I used
to work at Starbucks I made sure my Sunday schedule is set so I could be at
home to listen to you guys okay well we appreciate no matter where you're at and
that's that is truly why we stew podcast the show as well is because that way you
know for those of you that can't be here to do to whatever time restriction
you might have you can still participate with the show throughout the week in
doable all right all right my friend I'm gonna let you go so we wrap up the show
but thanks for the call buddy hey no problem love it listen in participating
all right take care buddy take it you did bye bye all right I think with that
we're going to shortly wrap things up I do want to check on last-minute stories
though from either of my co-hosts yeah I was just gonna mention this is kind of
funny in the world of DLC that we have nowadays it's so refreshing to see that
there's companies still putting out cheat codes and one of those is actually
for a Super Monkey Bowl banana blitz HD on PC apparently there's some cheat
codes where if you type in the word cube triangle or star on the character
selection screen it will change the ball into a cube a triangle like a like a
pyramid type thing and then some multi-point star like shape so and it
makes the game a lot harder because you know cubes don't roll very well cubes
don't roll very well how about that yeah that's I think I'm gonna stay on
Facebook for a while until people are done lifting up a racist a rapist sorry
I am I remove the app from my phone you'll be back on it tomorrow no I
really don't think I am because I'm getting really pissed off at all these
people now that someone is dead and like oh he was God's gift to everything he
raped a woman and cheated on his wife take the app off your phone it was the
best thing I ever did all right anyway um that's it we're gonna wrap up the
show and throw it all in for tonight we're done but not until we go running
get everybody's final thoughts I yeah I'm excited to be back here in seven
days I'm very thankful so many of you tuned up in here tonight live because I
know like the Grammys are going on right now and like I'm so over the Grammy
really Alicia Keys though what is amazing there'll be highlights on
YouTube so it's some of the fashion was really good but I will appreciate seeing
you guys I appreciate seeing you guys here in light of all the other stuff you
could have been doing tonight so I just wanted to acknowledge that and say I
really appreciate it and yeah that's that's it thank you guys so much if you
enjoyed what you heard here at orange on radio tell a friend help us spread the
word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice but if the voices
aren't here to air oh we can't have them but it looks like it's growing cuz I see
more of you watching tonight than in previous weeks so thank you so much for
being here really appreciate it I hope you'll stay a little while so let's go
around and get everybody's final thought I will start with Loki tonight your
final thought my final thought is this game that popped up on my Twitter looks
it very much like Legend of Zelda the old Legend of Zelda inspired yeah it's a
game called dawn thorn it looks very much like Legend of Zelda but pretty
cool though all right dark soccer your final thought um uh I hate my new
schedule see if I can get it changed fingers crossed later let it light some
candles sacrifice chicken my final thought tonight is I have been showing
great restraint in not ordering that burger time arcade one up machine still
we'll see if that survives another week we'll see we'll see all right that's it
we're out of here for tonight thank you guys again so much for watching the show
we really appreciate you guys being here or listening on the podcast feed
wherever you were participating with the show tonight thank you thank you
thank you we will be back in seven days to do it all again quick programming
note for those of you that are live Bobby black wolf will not be here next
Sunday there is a annual football game that a lot of people get really into and
for some people it's a big social event and I know for that it is that
celebration of owls yes Bobby is into it for the social aspect and all that good
stuff so it's a chance for him to see his buddies and you know what sometimes
we all deserve a week off so Bobby's taking next week off we will still be
here live at six o'clock Pacific sharp nine o'clock Eastern to wrap up the
weekend gaming news so happy gaming everybody will see you in seven days
here at orange lounge radio goodnight you've been listening to orange lounge
radio orange lounge radio is a production of olr studios to join us for
a live show tune into fog network calm Sunday nights at 6 p.m. Pacific 9 p.m.
Eastern the views and opinions expressed in this program do not necessarily
reflect those of the staff of orange lounge radio or fog network but you know
they were all still true
see you next week
you