Orange Lounge Radio
With your hosts, DarkSakura, Skie, and Loki
Nearly three decades later the game with no conversation dialogue
The original quarter eater Dragon Slayer is going from movie video game to video game movie
I'm hoping for a space age successor
This is just one story, join us for the rest starting right now on the show where every gamer has some space
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet and welcome back to another week of the show where every gamer has a voice
It is Orange Lounge Radio live tonight with episode number 813 of our program for March the 29th of 2020
My name is Rob Roberts and as we talked a little bit about last week
And as I'm sure you're well aware with everything going on in the world
I am all alone in the studio this week as we are practicing social distancing
Which is a pretty good idea in the state of the world today
Pretty good thing to be practicing
Not joining us at all tonight though sadly DarkSakura or Jamie Summers
Talked to her yesterday a little bit via text because her voice is not holding out so well
She was having kind of a rough night last night so she decided to bow out of tonight's show
Just to let her voice recover a little bit
Completely understand if you've been listening to the last couple weeks
She's been battling something kind of nasty
We don't know what it is because is it the big one? Don't know because testing is not there for it
But regardless we're wishing her well
I did check in with her about an hour ago
She said she was doing a lot better today but still wanted to rest her voice for the night
Which is certainly understandable
Who knows she might pop in to our chat room at some point throughout the night
Because we do tape live every Sunday night at the voice geeks network
vog network dot com that's vog network dot com or on twitch twitch dot tv slash vog network is where we tape
Every Sunday night at 6 o'clock pacific 9 o'clock eastern ish right after the Bobby Black Wolf show
Even though DarkSakura is not here tonight I am joined via discord by tech master Loki
Hello Loki
Hello I'm here
You are here how are you how are you holding up after how many days is it that you've been in the house now
For me it's coming up on 14 days tomorrow
Um yeah because I was working from home as a week from last Monday so yeah it's been two weeks
Yeah so yeah pretty much the same so well glad you're hanging in there
Hopefully a chance to play some games and maybe get caught up on writing your own game
Um I would have let no I've had time no time to do either of those
And the reason for that is I've been dealing with PC issues
And so I my laptop does not want to cooperate with two monitors I have
And so it's it keeps crashing I've been just dealing with that all week
And so because it clearly is not working and I think the graphics card may be going out on it
It works fine by itself so I got a replacement coming
All right well glad you at least have a replacement coming hope it makes a decent amount of time
Because I know they're prioritizing the essential stuff right now so it's
Oh no it'll be here like tomorrow
Well that's good that's good I'm looking at some of the chat room comments over at twitch.tv slash vog network
Where fifth dream today is saying the mouse is looking at me plushplosion
Okay so those that are watching live on twitch have the visual
And I haven't plugged this in a while so I should say if you are a subscriber on twitch at vog network
Which you can use your if you're an amazon prime person you get you may not know this but you get one free twitch subscription every month
So if you want to use that on vog network you get access to our video archives
The podcast audio version is free just as it has been for over 18 years
Or not quite over 18 years over 17 years coming up on 18 years like I'm getting at that point where I forgot my own age
But anyway the point is is if you're watching the visual whether it be live or via your twitch subscription for vog network
You can actually see see usually it would be myself and it would be loki on camera
DarkSakura sometimes on camera when she feels like it because you know it's her choice if she wants to get on camera or not
But without loki here I'm a little lonely so some of the various plushies that I have
That actually Alan freaking won some of these on that crane site
Torreba I think is the name of it I don't know what it is it's one of those freaking crane game sites
I shouldn't even give it a plug because he wasted so much time on that site and they're not paying me any money
But he did win this little hamster thing in that master ball looking thing but captain pikachu and I go way back
I've had this life-sized pikachu for a long time so I have to have something to fill in for loki when he's not here
Maybe next week I'll get some round table breadsticks those will remind me of loki
Maybe we'll see
It might be a few weeks that we're on this system of doing OLR
I think it's important that we continue to do OLR to the best of our ability
But the reality is we're not exactly going to defy the governor's order
So once that is lifted and changed then we'll consider getting back together again
Which if what we just heard earlier today in the national news is any guideline it's going to be at least till the end of April
But you know gotta keep people healthy gotta make sure we squash this thing flatten the curve
Try not to spread it around to people that don't need to have it myself included
So yeah we're just doing what we have to do
That didn't stop my neighbors from having their motorcycle party earlier today
What is up with that? We've been having neighbors that have been having parties too and I'm like you guys are missing the point
You're just gonna you're ruining it for everybody. It's horrible
Maybe they watched Tiger King and decided to bring their well I wouldn't even say it's their inner redneck because it's kind of their whole persona
But you know amp that up a bit
Have you been getting obsessed with Tiger King?
That is all everybody is fucking talking about on Twitch
It's Animal Crossing and Tiger King
I'm surprised the two haven't come together yet
I have watched the whole thing though
Of course you have
It seems like the type of thing your wife would be into
And she was, yes
Of course she was
No I've held off on Tiger King thus far
I am finally trying to finish Love is Blind
So I'm a few like and that was the big thing everybody was watching in February on Netflix
So I'm a little bit behind
So what is that? Is that because I sort of remember a show that was on the soup or something
Where they have like people in like a dark room talking to each other and they weren't able to see each other
Is that that show?
Yeah but the soup has been off TV for years
Love is Blind is a newer show
But they can only, they're in these like pod things and they can only talk to each other and they can't see each other
And then, but it's weird because like the first three episodes are that
And then the rest of it is, haha now let's see if it works
Or if they become a hot mess and surprise
Some of them are total hot messes when they get together in person
I mean I'm sure we're all shocked at the type of people that go on those sort of dating reality shows
That you put some, you mix them up in a room and there's drama, surprise right?
Yeah
Alright anyway, let's get into actual video game chat
I mean we could sit here and talk Netflix
I mean I guess we could talk about like Castlevania, Ingress anime
Or there's that other Netflix thing I bet is on y'all's mind
Yes it's in the news, we'll get to that a little later
But first while we get to tonight's kickoff topic
Loki, what are we starting off with tonight?
So they have the Nintendo Direct, or surprise Nintendo Direct I guess
That was earlier this week talking about some indie games and some other like additions to current Nintendo games
So for example they talked about their progress in Xenoblade Chronicles Definitive Edition
They announced that some 2K games are going to be coming to the Switch
Including the Biostock Collection and Borderlands
Those are going to be coming
I think that's, oh wait just real quick
I think that's great about Borderlands and Bioshock
But I don't know, this seems to be like the Switch's MO or something
How old are these games at this point?
And it's just now getting to Nintendo's console
It's not a read, it's not a dis, I understand
There's some people out there that are going to be very excited with the portability of a game like Bioshock
But I don't know, I feel like those are games that are better experienced on a big TV
Which yes I know the Switch can do, but you know the high end graphics and all that stuff
I don't know, I feel like those are little scraps that the Nintendo fans are getting tossed
Don't get me wrong, I love my Switch, I'm super jazzed about other stuff that was in there
Maybe it's just one of those not for me dot com type of things
It's probably just pretty easy to port that stuff over I guess
I guess, maybe, just maybe the engine they're built in or whatever
It doesn't take a lot of man hours to port that over to Switch
I don't know, I just always feel like those are kind of scraps
And then they have the XCOM 2 collection as well
So that was something that was announced there
Burnout Paradise Remastered was another game that's supposed to be coming to the Switch as well
And then some of the other things they talked about
There's the final piece of DLC for Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3, so it's a fantastic 4
They talked a little bit about Animal Crossing New Horizons
That's going to have their seasonal event Bunny Day
Which that bunny is super creepy
But that's going to be taking place
Too bad it wasn't the bunny from Silent Hill
It pretty much is
Can you do the reskins maybe?
Can you design the bunny an outfit and make the bunny wear Silent Hill costumes?
I don't know, but Zipper is looking pretty creepy
I mean, think about how fucking crazy business Animal Crossing is doing right now
Animal Crossing is probably bigger than it's ever been
And it's because in large part of what's going on in the world
We don't have our real lives to talk about
So what are we talking about on social media?
Our fake ones in Animal Crossing
I think this game would have done fine as it is in a normal world
But now especially that we're all shut in
And we can't go out and fish for real
Or go out and do things out in nature for real
We're all sharing it through Animal Crossing
I don't know about y'all's social media
But my social media is filled with Animal Crossing stuff
And I just feel like
And the reason why I say all that is that this game and this franchise has never been hotter
In my opinion, with what's going on in pop culture and stuff
This just seems like the time for Nintendo to really let us tweak it even more
Let us design some of our villagers
I would love to have villagers that imitate Pyramid Head and stuff
But maybe that is exactly what Nintendo does not want to open the flood gate to
If you could draw your own patterns for the villagers
I guess you could always give them shirts and things
But I feel like if you could totally reskin the villagers
Somebody's gonna do Nudzu
Somebody's gonna do Nudyzu
And it's gonna get awkward
I saw someone
Then you're gonna have Tiger King
Then you're gonna fucking have Tiger King
Well I saw somebody though actually on Twitter
And I want to say it might have been Mayor Marvel
But I thought it was
They did a dress that had a butt on the back of it
Oh yes, oh my god I saw that
Somebody had a dress pattern
But they drew a butt on it
So it just looked like the person's butt was hanging out of the back of the dress
That was great, I love it
Yes, it already happened
Oh you creative people
Oh and through the QR code and generate your own pattern sites
Anyway, people are putting all sorts of filthy things
But funny things too
Like I found online a shocked Pikachu painting that I have now
I have an N7 logo up
What else do I have?
I have
Oh a friend of mine sent me Rocky Horror Picture Show related ones
So now I have a throne scene with Frank N. Furter and friends all up there
Okay
Yeah so it's just all this crazy stuff you can get with QR codes
So aside from the Bunny D event which of course they're gonna be hiding eggs
And they have special crafting things
There are some other games that they are talking about
One called Good Job
It looked pretty cool
And then some new
They're gonna have a demo for Bravely Default 2
As well as they're saying that Star Wars Jedi Knight Jedi Academy
And the Panzer Dragoon remake
Those are all announced as well
And then the Bravely
No I was gonna say the Bravely Default 2 demo came out with the day of the Nintendo Direct
So I didn't get around to playing it but some friends of mine played it
I'm hearing kind of mixed reviews on it
Some people are really into it
You know those that probably really enjoyed the first Bravely Default
I'm hearing a lot of criticism about some of the character design
And some of the voice acting
I guess there's one character in particular
That's like please stop
Please stop this now
So don't know we'll see how it goes
Okay so and then we also had Clubhouse Games
51 Worldwide Classics
That's been announced
That's coming on the Switch on June 5th
I wanna just say I wanted that freaking franchise to make a comeback
Yeah
Well I was so
And then oddly enough
Games that no one ever asked to be ported to the Switch
Star Wars Episode 1 Racer
It's coming to the Switch
Why?
Because the pod racing was the only thing cool about that
I don't know maybe it's another one of those like
It was fairly simple to port so we did it
I guess porting games is the new shovelware
Perhaps
Anyways and then of course
New Fighter announced for the Smash Ultimate DLC
And that new fighter is Arms
Now I don't know if that's all of the different characters in Arms or just
One of the characters
You're kind of half right
They just announced that the next character
Would be from Arms
But they didn't say who it would be
And I know a lot of people are hoping for Twintelle
Just because she was a kind of standout character from Arms
But the thing about Twintelle
And the reason why I don't think it's going to be her
Is that Twintelle actually uses her hair
Not her arms
Like she's the one with the big braids
So I don't know if she'll end up being the character or not
I don't really play Arms
I've tried to play it a little bit
And I'm going to be honest
I didn't care for it
So I kind of wonder why Nintendo is trying to make Arms happen now
Because they did that
They're doing the free play weekend or whatever
Okay
But I guess other people were into it
Sure, but I wasn't a big Arms fan
So I'm kind of meh on this news
Yeah, I remember they were trying to position
As like an eSports title
Almost
That was kind of the trend there
Where everyone wanted to be an eSports title
And it just wasn't going to happen
Yeah
No, it didn't happen
Maybe eSports has
Got a new focus on it now
Because of this whole stay at home stuff
And how it's affecting
Some of the programming on television and stuff
But that seems a little too
Like I don't think Nintendo
Is putting Arms in Smash
Because suddenly due to Coronavirus
They sense a rise in eSports
That is too calculated
And would have taken more time to plan
Than the reality of this situation
No, I don't think that's at all
I'm just saying
I don't think eSports even around Arms is ever going to happen
But
I was going to say the last bit of news
In addition to
Ring Fit Adventure
They're getting an update which adds a new rhythm game mode
They have songs from Super Mario Odyssey
Splatoon 2 and Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild
Which is pretty cool
Man, if only we could get some pop songs in there too
Like that would be great
I have not played that mode yet
I've seen some tweets from people who've been playing it
And I've watched some of the YouTubes and stuff
So it kind of looks like
Just instead of the notes falling
From the top down
They kind of come in more of a
Well shaped thing
Like Guitar Hero
Because I guess we learned all those years ago
That Konami actually has the patent
On the notes falling from the top
Of the screen down
So that's why all the music games now do it
Where it's coming at you
Because Konami doesn't have the patent on that
That patent has run out already
I don't know
But for whatever reason
Nintendo is doing it where it's coming out at you
And you can see the motions with the controller
With the ring controller
Like it might squeeze on a certain bit
Or you might kind of tilt it left or right
At a certain point
And that is all dictated by when the notes
Get to the front
It looked interesting
I want to try it
It probably shows
I haven't really played Ring Fit
Since quarantine started
But I have been snacking
I probably should be playing Ring Fit
Some folks in chat talking about
Arms
AJ Twist is asking
Isn't there an Arms character that is a trophy in Smash already
I do believe you are correct
And they're talking about Spring Man
Act F says I totally forgot the name is the armed guy
AJ Twist says Spring Man
Yeah I think they're kind of like
Mascot guy that's like on the box
I believe he is some type of assist
Trophy already in Smash
Not that
Assist trophies and the like
It has stopped characters from becoming
Full blown characters before
I feel like
There was something that got upgraded
Along the way but
It escapes me in the moment
Man what are we getting Geno? Seriously
Well you've got four
Four more
Characters after this one
So you never know what might happen
Bobby Black Wolf says it has stopped Waluigi
Hey never say never
Until that tenth character is announced
Not that I want to give false hope but
I don't know I feel like they
Weren't originally planning to do a
Second set of DLC I feel like
And now they're doing it so they've had enough time
To hear the fan feedback and they might do it
Who knows but I think
If Waluigi does happen it will be the very
Very last one
Act F says Little Mac was an assist trophy
In Brawl before he became a full character in
Smash 4 yes I knew there was like one
That like got upgraded but I guess that
Wouldn't have really been within the same game
So was that everything
From the Nintendo Direct Loki?
Yeah pretty much So what did you think overall
Of the Direct and what you
I mean if you didn't watch it the highlights I guess
I didn't really watch it
I mean
I don't know
It's alright there wasn't really anything
That was super exciting about
Unfortunately I'm not a huge fan of Clubhouse games
I'm sure it's a great game
Don't really care that
Bioshock Infinite and all that says to be important to
The other system I have it on green systems already
So it's like eh I don't really
Need it
I don't know
There's nothing super exciting coming out of that
Unfortunately
Well it was a mini so you know it wasn't
Like I guess I don't know what the difference is
It was still 30 minutes they could have just called
It a regular Direct and it probably would have been fine
For me the Xenoblade stuff
That remake looks hot
I'm definitely going to buy that when it comes out
They definitely kind of took a deep dive into that
A little bit because I don't know if we'll get
Maybe there will be a special Direct
I guess before June there ought to be another Direct
Of sorts so they'll probably show even more on that game
But I'm definitely going to pick that up when it comes out
And otherwise
Yeah like the 2K games are a little bit like
Okay I already kind of have like all of the
Things I want on Playstation already
But I guess cool for the Nintendo exclusive folks
Or some folks are saying in chat
If you really want to play it in a portable setting
Which isn't for me
But maybe it's for you so cool
And then some of the
Clubhouse games obviously I'm a very big fan of
So those were some nice little surprises
It wasn't like an oh my god
Type of thing but it was some nice surprises
Nice little treats
Especially when there's a lot of shit news in the world right now
It was kind of nice to have something a little bit like
Oh I have this to look forward to that's a nice thing
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says
I hope they just did a mini
Just to shut up all the Twitter trolls
That beg for a Nintendo Direct every time
Well I don't think they did it just for that reason
But clearly Nintendo had a few things
That they just wanted to like drop on people
Because what they put out that Bravely Default 2 demo
They put out Panzer Dragoon
Came out day and date
They started taking your money
For clubhouse games
So they kind of had a backlog
Maybe a small backlog of things
They just kind of wanted to get out there
And make sure people knew about
So I think it kind of served its purpose in that regard
So
AgDef says if it was a big Direct
There would be like a big announcement
And they probably would have given you more time too
They probably would have said we'll do one tomorrow
Instead of
Did they say later did they drop one the same day
Or did they give you a days notice
I don't remember
Yeah
So those are some of the comments from our chat room
Oh interesting AJ Twist says
Maybe it was called a mini Direct
Because there was no human host
That's an interesting thought as well
Is that they didn't
Yeah they didn't have anybody
From Nintendo either Japan
Or America or anyone really
Talking us through the different announcements
So that is a very very good point
Maybe that's one of the differences between
A mini and a regular Direct
And perhaps in this era of social distancing
Where many Nintendo people
Are working from home
Maybe they weren't able to get all the footage they needed in time
Although you know many of these Directs
They filmed that stuff way in advance
So you know
The world has changed very fast
In the scope of two to three weeks
And I would bet they already knew what was going in this Direct
Like a month ago
For the most part they knew this Direct at least a month ago
If not even further back
I would bet
E3's Direct or I'm using my quotey fingers
E3's Direct
The inevitable June Direct
That Nintendo I guess can drop at any point they want to now
That Direct
They probably already at least have their outline
Of what's gonna be in that
And they're probably starting to script that out
And then they'll shoot that bit by bit
That will have live talking faces with that
So
Anyway, alright so Nintendo Direct
A nice pleasant surprise from Nintendo this week
So let's talk a little bit about the types of games
That we have been playing this week
Since Dark Soccer is not here tonight
We'll start with you Loki, how was your gaming week?
I didn't play much of anything
Aside from
Just
Forna
Because I've been trying to fix my computer
So
Didn't get around too much
I have started working on
Putting StepMania in the DDR cabinet
Because we have been using it a bit more
I just haven't really been playing too much
But like literally right now
I have the PC for that cabinet
On my desk here
I've been copying songs over
Probably should
I need to get everything loaded in
So that I can test it
But it's almost
Probably pretty close to being ready to go
I just need to mount the PC onto
Like a board or something
So I can set it in there
Figure out how to wire it up
So I can switch between the PC
And the
Actual System 573 board
That's in there
Yeah I was gonna say I saw on Twitter
Or Facebook or something I saw a video
Of a Dance Dance Revolution machine you have in your garage
So did that kind of awaken
The I want to do something else with this
Machine sort of part within you
Well I just had
A lot of time where I wasn't able to
Work on stuff or we
Didn't have to go anywhere so I had a lot of time to
Kind of
Put all that together and earlier
We got redownloading packs and everything
And then I finally found all the
Download packs that I had and I was like
Oh man
I just have to
What I'm doing now is I'm kind of setting it up to test it
I was originally wanting to make my own
Theme and everything for it
But I think I'm gonna put that on the back burner for now
Until I just want to get it
Running and get it going and then
I'll do themes and all that stuff
Later but I have to sort out
How I want to sort all of the songs
That are in there
I think I want to kind of do it more like extreme
Where has it kind of by
Mix that's come out and then
Of course
I think A.C.E. might be the
Dance System Revolution A
I think they have it
Organized somewhat similar
I want to do it like that
Probably the theme I'm going with
Is it's a fan made theme
Called Supernova 3
It kind of looks like the old
Supernova or even like
Extreme setups with the song wheel
And everything
It seems to be pretty lightweight
I'll probably do that
Cause I mean it should be pretty fast
I think I had originally tested it with the
A.C.E. theme on there
But we'll see
When I end up doing mine it'll be much fancier
And probably a little bit more unique
Ok alright adventures in Loki's
DDR machine
So for my gaming week so I've been playing
A lot cause you know video games help pass
The time sadly for discussion
Purposes I've been playing a lot of the same things
I usually play like continuing to play Final Fantasy
14 games like that
And MMO's are a great like social
Thing right now and you can't really like go outside and be
Social so I think that's why I tend to
Sink a lot of hours into something like Final Fantasy 14
Been trying to play the
GPS games on those rare occasions
I go out and walk like obviously
You know I can't really go out and do anything too crazy
But like last night we
Drove to a restaurant to get pickup food
And I was like Alan can you drive
So I can play Orna while you drive
So he agreed to do that
So that was kind of nice so I was able to get some GPS gaming
In there and I do a little bit on my walks
As well but haven't been doing anything too
Crazy with that for obvious reasons
Still continuing on Diablo 3 as well
I did make sure to play
A new game this week because
Since I do have
All this time and I have
Xbox Game Pass along with
Many other ways to play a variety of
Different games such as like the free games they give
On the Epic Store you know
And giveaways here and there and everywhere
There's no shortage of games in the backlog
To play so one of the games I decided to
Check out this week which is on
Xbox Game Pass although apparently it's
Going away soon because it does say it's
Like a limited amount of time left so
I don't know if I just started this game in time for it to
Leave at the beginning of the month I don't know
But it's a game called Kingsway
So what this game is
It's like an RPG
But the RPG it's like a
Classic you know swords and sorcery
Type of RPG like a Final Fantasy
English thing but it's
Framed around
An operating system
And it looks like an
Old operating system like a
Windows 3.1 operating system
From like 1994
Or something where you
Like double click on the world map
Window to bring up the map
And as you click where to go
You see your little character move and a little progress bar
And you can hear like it really emulates
Like a little disk drive going
Making the little noises the disk drives would do
And then like different windows will pop up
Like if you run into a monster a window will pop up
And you have to like fight it and so you
Do your inventory management through
Windows so it's really
Clever how they
Kind of built this concept of
We're going to do an RPG but it's going to be based
Within an operating system so it's
Like Windows the RPG but it's
Kind of clever and I
Think people who probably grew up
Around that era like I think of
Somebody like Bobby Blackwolf and I know
He's a big fan of these types of old
MS-DOS games back in the day
I think he would really get a kick out of this game
But I'm not sure a lot of
Folks like let's say
By the time you were born
Uh you know modern
PCs and Windows XP and all that
Stuff was already kind of the norm by the time you
Were a child I don't know if there's
Going to be as much here for you because it's not
Going to be the same type of nostalgia trip
But I think the nostalgia trip for
Gamers of a certain age is kind of
Fun so it's one of those games that's worth
Checking out especially if you have Xbox
Game Pass anyway
I don't think it's on Xbox
It wouldn't make sense why it would be on Xbox
The console because obviously it's very mouse
Driven so it's the type of thing that strikes me as
Very like a PC thing so if you have it
You might as well check it out if
You can it might be leaving
Game Pass very very soon
I believe so
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says
If it's in the leaving soon
Area of Game Pass then it goes away on the
31st well I guess I'm glad I played
It when I could I've been eyeing
It says Bobby I remember seeing
It all the PR for it from adult
Swim games yeah it's published by them
As shown under Matt says
Yeah I could play at home too I just need to get out
Move around being inside is
Maddening I know oh that's a response to something
It was Act F was saying in chat
Yeah it's
You got to find that right balance of
Going outside I haven't been going outside enough
Quite frankly but I kind of get sick
Of the same old walk like since
I live like right and without giving away my
Address here on the program
Since I live right in the heart of
Suburbia it's like within walking
Distance is a park
And if I want to walk a really
Long distance I could get to a couple other parks
But that's a
Long and it's like it's like a commitment
It's like if I walk all the way to one of the other parks
Then I got to walk back so
I mean I guess I could get in the car and drive
Somewhere but then you get into all these problems
Of well if you drive to the
Park that everyone wants to go to
Then it's too crowded and it defeats
The purpose that was a problem they were having
With the beaches and stuff right
So you got to find that right balance it's tricky
But luckily thanks to things like
Pokemon Go and Ingress
And the other GPS things I've played over the years
I have a pretty good sense of
Where all the big parks are in town
That don't get too crowded
So I guess that part is kind of nice
So that's good
And there's always like the river
I have been tempted to go down
To Capitol Park do you think they'd throw people
Out of Capitol Park I don't think they would
It's still very wide open you can keep your space
From people there as long as it's not swarming with people
But I don't know like I don't want to be
That person you know
That's setting a bad example so
Or just putting myself at risk quite frankly
But yeah I miss those really
Dense Pokemon places like Capitol Park
Would be fun so
Anyway well that's enough for my gaming week
So a lot of the same old stuff but I'm trying
To squeeze in at least one new game a week
While I'm here at home catching up
On the backlog a little bit I already know what game
I want to play for next week except
I forgot the name of it but it was another game
On Xbox Game Pass that totally looked like
It looks like it's Devil's Crush or Alien's Crush
Or something like that like it's another pinball game
And I think it's even called like Demon something
Somebody in chat will yell it out I'm sure
But that is the game I wanted to get around to it this week
But I didn't get to it so that's the game I definitely
Want to check out for next week so
That game looks really cool so
Alright
See a Tiberian chat talking about
The beaches stuff
It's interesting how the social game
Swarm what Foursquare originally
Was is now not
Awarding as many points if you're going outside
Of a home area and when you choose
To do something that's not like a housing
Development it pops up and says
Stay home that's kind of an interesting use
Of some of those GPS things
It is interesting seeing how a lot of those things have had to
Adapt things like Pokemon Go
Have kind of had to change how the game works
A little bit
To get beyond Minecraft Earth
Did something similar I heard this week
Have you checked that out?
I heard Minecraft Earth did something
Yeah so they did this thing
I checked it out for a second and I saw
It's turning very much into
A regular mobile game
So what they added is
These runes that basically
If you play Minecraft Earth
So part of the game is just collecting
The tappables that are on the screen to get
All the blocks which really if you
Just drive around you're going to have a ton
Of stuff
So they have it like
Parks there's these things called adventures
Where you can get additional blocks
And you also get experience
And other things
Then they have this AR interactive
Thing that you do so
What these runes do is they
Cause you to spawn and adventure
Like
Wherever you're at
So they give you one for free
To be able to spawn one of those
Adventures
It's only the taste that's free
And then after that you got paid for it
Use your rubies
Or whatever they're in the game
But you earn those pretty quick
I didn't see where I could actually spend those
To do that
And ever since I haven't played the game
In a long time so now it's just like
Full of like different
XP boosts and different
Food boosts and HP boosts
And I'm like oh my god
This is way too
Just like demanding of
Your money it's just like come on
Pay pay pay pay
That kind of really turns me off from playing that game
S2100 Matt says
Demons Tilt was the name of the game I was trying to think of
Yes that is it you got it
Interesting S2100 Matt says
Waze yells at you when you open it up asking if you really
Need to be outside right now really
Because I've been a good boy
And following all the rules I haven't seen all the apps
Doing these things so that's very
That's really interesting
Interesting how these apps have had to adapt
Let's just hope it doesn't go on
Forever and you know
If we happen to have some folks
That are working
In the healthcare industry and really on the
Front lines of what's going on right now
Thank you for what you guys are doing
I know it really can't be fun right now
So thank you so much
Hell grocery store employees
And Costco employees that really
Can't be fun either right now so
A big thanks to everybody that's
Really stepping up in this time
Of I can't believe
It's actually happening this
Alright anyhow let's move on
Back to video games and traveling
Around the globe
Checking out the latest and greatest in gaming news
Because while folks are still working
From home and while the world is getting used to
What's going on right now there is still
More gaming news
Such as Loki starting us off
Kind of a follow up
To something from last week kind of sort of right
Yeah so we talked a little bit last week
About how GameStop is considering them
An essential
Retailer and
That they need to stay open during this whole
Corona outbreak thing
However they're not the only
Game company to have done that
So there's another retailer by the name of
Game Exchange
Let's make sure we're hating on everybody appropriately
Let's make sure we've
Saved enough of our internet rage for other
Asshole companies
Yeah so they're looking mostly like Texas
Arkansas like the southern east
Or southeast of the US
And apparently
They have done something
Similar so they're doing the curbside
Pick up options as well
But
There's not really
The precautions being taken
They've basically said that
Yes they're an essential retailer
And that they're providing
Them with
Sanitizing products and stuff like that
But much like the whole GameStop thing
That's not necessarily
Being available
And it's not necessarily happening
Like they're describing
So some of the employees are very frustrated with that
Basically saying that they don't want us to
Close at all
If any employee chooses not to work
Then they're told that they will not be paid
Since they are not working
This even goes for salary managers as well
And then of course they're saying
We've got the order to shelter
In place today from the county judge
I hope that the higher ups would do the right thing
And not put up a fight
And put their employees at health risk
But it appears that they have no interest
In closing the doors as the pandemic has progressed
Corporate has declined
To stop practicing
Stopping the practice of accepting
Trades
Our location is located right next door to a medical clinic
That takes walk-ins
In a time where there's a global pandemic
Keeping the specific location
Open next door to a place where there are patients
With illness is madness
Funny enough actually
So along with this
I saw a follow-up talking about
The GameStop practices
And what they're instructing their employees to do
As far as
That delivering to the doorway
Type thing
So they're literally telling them to
Take
A GameStop plastic retail bag
And just put that around their hand
As a glove
To be able to hand games
And payment methods
Back and forth to people
It's ridiculous
You really
Shouldn't be exchanging things like
Credit cards and money right now
Unless it's at a truly essential business
Like a grocery store
Even then
Now is the time to check out Apple Pay
Or Google Pay
The contact type transactions
Tap to transact type thing
Yeah exactly
It's ridiculous
Apparently
They feel that they need to
Do this in order to stay open
I don't know if it's necessarily just
Capitalizing on it or the fact that
A lot of these independent retailers
Even though this is a pretty sizable one
Aren't doing that well
If you can think about GameStop struggling
And they have direct relationships
With all of these publishers
Game companies or retailers
Like Game Exchange
They have to purchase their distribution
I know because we used to sell to them
So
They have it even worse than GameStop
As far as being able to get product
On time
The cost keeping that low
And having these special incentives
To get people to come into their store
So that's even harder for them
And if GameStop's
Literally running
Their business to the ground
In fact I think they're closing another 300 locations soon
Then
It's just gonna
Hit them even harder
Still shouldn't put employees in danger
Because of that, that's ridiculous
But it's
A very complex situation
That really they should be sending those employees home
Especially since GameStop did that now
To a certain extent
If you're thinking of the profits
Before the employees
Then obviously you're a problem
And also
What's the pay cut
And I say this every time
Or the CEO
We never hear the talk about that
Well actually I will say
In non-gaming related things
We are starting to see that more and more
Like I think we're seeing those articles around social media
That there are some companies
And of course now that I need to recall them in the moment
I can't think of who
But there are some companies that are
Like the CEO, I was reading one about some CEO
That was dropping his pay to 10,000
This year
To try to use the extra money
To make sure they're taken care of and so forth
And yes, good job
That is what CEOs should be
A $10,000 salary
Heck, he could take maybe a little more
A reasonable salary is fine
But use that extra money
When you're the type of CEO that's making millions
To give back to your employees
I think that is
All we would like to see somebody do
Bobby Blackwolf in chat says
Devil's advocate
What if they're not necessarily thinking of the profits
They're just thinking about staying operational
With all
And that's what I think that they're doing
Is trying to stay operational
But at the same time
Everybody's thinking about that
But you can't put your employees in danger
To stay operational
You just have to
Reduce the number of stores you have
A responsible upper management team
Has a plan
Has a pandemic type of plan
Or a contingency plan
I can tell you every company I've worked for
I haven't worked for a lot of companies
Because I was with one for 14 years
But the companies I did work for
Always had a plan for
What if we get in a situation
Where all the computers go down
Or what if we get in a situation
And I distinctly remember
The first company I worked for for 14 years
Which was a major health insurer
Because of the fact they were a health care insurer
And people are going to want to use health care
They had specifically a pandemic plan
Granted I haven't worked there in several years
So I have no idea if they've actually
Enacted that same plan or what
But they actually have these types of plans
So it is kind of your responsibility
As the upper management and the board
To be thinking about these types of things
You should have had a plan for curbside pickup
And all this type of stuff a long time ago
Now I realize
There's infinite combinations
Of things to plan for
And not everything's going to be perfect
And nobody could have truly predicted this COVID situation
I do understand all of that
But don't you get the sense
Aren't you kind of feeling like
Nothing was planned
Don't you kind of see those two extremes
In this scenario
Yes
At the same time I do see that
And I think it's more
They may have been
Looking at well GameStop doing it
And we can do it as well
And that's a lot of the sentiment
I used to get with a lot of the independent
Retailers that I dealt with
Was if GameStop for example
Was breaking the street on a title
Then they feel well it's fine if we do it then
So I think
That's kind of what they're looking at here
They're basically saying that
Oh
Well if they're doing it then we can do it
Alright
Anyway it's a tricky
Scenario but I kind of think ultimately
The reality of what's going to happen
In light of all these
Stories that are coming out and things
I think this might be the situation
That pushes more people to go digital
That hadn't considered it before
I don't think physical is going away
I don't think my opinion has really changed on that
Whatsoever but because
Just CDs and music
That is primarily digital
At this point but there are still
Collectors and collectibles
You can still find
Those CDs and so forth they're not as easy to find
As they once were but you can still order them
I kind of think that is a direction
That gaming is kind of headed in
Eventually and I think this kind of
Accelerates that a little bit
Than maybe what we were thinking before
We were kind of already thinking
That gaming was kind of going that way anyway
And I think these two months
Of people don't really want to go out to the store
I mean there's this
GameStop and GameExchange
They got their plans on how to stay open
But the reality is
Speaking for myself
I'm not going to a fucking game store right now
Either I'm going to get it on Amazon
And just wait a few extra days
An extra week if I need to
Because it's something that's not essential
Or maybe even longer than that because it's a game
Or I'm just going to buy a digital because
You know what that's my other option right now
It's not the way I prefer to buy games
But if it's something that I have to play
Right now like Final Fantasy 7 Remake
Then I'll just buy it digital
Even though that's not really what I wanted to do
Anything else can either wait or you know whatever
So
Well yeah and I think a lot of major releases
Anyways are being pushed back
Because of this whole situation so
I don't think there's a whole lot of stuff that we have to
Jump out and run out to get right now
Yeah so Lady Gaga pushed
Back her album so you know that was
The thing I'm sure you all were waiting for so
Now that has been pushed back
So yeah I think really
Like as far as gaming goes I feel like
The Final Fantasy 7 Remake was the only
Big thing I was hearing about for April
I don't know what April looks like for like triple A titles
Maybe some of you guys in chat know more
But you know I think
I think it was really we're getting
I don't think we know a lot of the big stuff
Yet because we're in a new console year
So I feel like we're still waiting on a lot of the big
Console stuff oh is Last of Us 2
An April game
That's the other one that's escaping my mind
Right now was Last of Us 2 an April game
Or is that like later does he keep pushing that one back
Um I thought
I thought that got pushed
I thought that was a June game
Ok Act F says May
I know that I was like what's Playstation got
Oh yeah lots of difference
Alright well anyway let's move on
Let's talk about this story which has to do
With kind of a
Social media trend gaming
Companies coming together to start this
Campaign with
WHO the World Health Organization
So it's kind of interesting to see
Official government entities that are
Right in the midst of this whole thing coming together
With gaming companies to create
This awareness of what they're calling
Hashtag play a part
Together and that's kind of a play on the
Word apart because it's
Playing games across a distance but
You're also playing your part by
Staying home and not spreading this
Horrible disease so
The World Health Organization
And the industry have come together to
Launch this awareness campaign play a part
Together it encourages physical distancing
With special events, exclusives
Activities, rewards
And inspiration for different
Popular games. Some of the companies
Participating, Activision Blizzard
Zynga, one of your favorites I'm sure
Big Fish Games
Let's see Kabam
Pocket Gems, Riot Games is in on this
Snap, Twitch
Is actually taking part in this because I think
Twitch just did their big marathon yesterday right?
They had a big thing
Going on yesterday
The city is also in on this too as is
YouTube so there's lots of different types of
Elements of gaming that are in on this
Trend of
Hashtag play a part together
And it's interesting
Because some journalists are
Noting the World Health Organization
Just last year was talking
About gaming disorder
You know people that play too many
Video games whereas now
It's a little different. A spokesperson
The United States ambassador to the
World Health Organization Ray Chambers said
In a statement that during this
Time frame of COVID and everything
He applauds what's
Quote the ingenuity of partners from
All sectors who are stepping up
To assist efforts to combat the
COVID-19 pandemic
So the World Health Organization is trying to get the global
Gaming industry to get millions
That's another thing to note it's global
Gaming is global right? Riot Games has a huge
Presence in Asia
Many different Asian countries
Not just China where we know that
COVID is kind of I don't want to say it's
Taking its course but we know that the curve is
Starting to come down in China but we got all these
Other countries like I think I'm not sure
Where Taiwan is at
Or you know some of these
Other places Japan I think was just
Well I don't know if Riot Games and League of Legends
Is as big there but
You know there's just there's other countries
Where you know these some of these companies have a big
Presence it's not just the US
That needs to work on flattening the curve
As this virus is spreading around
So
Also trying to encourage
Game players and so forth
To follow hand hygiene
And physical distancing and
So forth so it's kind of
It's kind of a neat little awareness campaign
I'm very curious to
See what these companies start
To do like in games and so forth
But because they're talking
About like maybe like rewards
And things to get people to play games online
But we'll see as that
Develops right now
So
I'm kind of also curious
For those of you out there in the chat room
And Loki maybe you have a piece to say on this too
It seems like gaming
Is just becoming
More and more prevalent in these times
Anyway like I see a
A sizable number of people on Facebook
Starting to stream
Jackbox games that's a company
That's really thriving in light of what's going on
Like it's weird to talk about
Like oh your company's doing great
Because of this horrible situation going on
But it is what it is
Like I feel like so many people are learning
About Jackbox games right now
Because more and more people are playing
That on Zoom meetings
You know with streamer mode
And things like that people are getting together to play
Jackbox
Like my cousin who I didn't even think
Ever played video games was posting
About this earlier today trying to get people together
To play Drawful or something
On a stream and so it really does
Seem like video games are a great
Way for people to be and of course Animal Crossing
We talked about earlier in the show
Video games have been a great way for people to
Still interact even when they're
Staying at home
Loki have you kind of noticed an upward trend
In social media or have you been invited or seen
Any of this like online gaming stuff that didn't
Really exist previously
I mean obviously we've seen a lot of
Stories about different
Boarding
Entities going to their
Esports kind of equivalent
And doing stuff that way so I think we're going to see
A big
Especially if it takes off you know
A lot more popularity with esports
Because of this whole having to
Stay away from everybody
Yeah definitely I mean I've seen
A lot more people playing stuff online
I haven't been invited to do anything but
That's fine
I've just been noticing
A lot of people doing that
In chat PodCulture says you can play
Cards Against Humanity online now
Yeah I got I mean there's all sorts
Of like Cards Against Humanity like Sims
There was one Zizzix it's got a really weird name
Somebody invited me to play that the other night
So I was playing that for a little bit and that was fun
I had the most points too when I left just saying
And then that reminds me
That same group has been playing Dungeons and Dragons
You want to go old school
Maybe not so much it's not so much video games
But you know tabletop
Even have their place right now
And I know friends that do
Like a weekly or is it monthly
They do like a monthly tabletop gaming meetup
And so since they couldn't do that this month
They did it online and they were playing like
Dominion and Catan and those types of things online
Because there's a lot of sites where you can
Do that so it's kind of interesting to see
How people are playing through that
Oh and Bobby Blackwolf points out tabletop
Simulator even works in VR
See Bobby we need clubhouse
Games more than ever see by the time clubhouse
Games comes out hopefully we're on the other
End of this curve and everything and we're
Talking about getting back to some sort of normalcy
We need clubhouse
Games right now dang it so
Act Def says the game
Show games like Wheel of Fortune
And Jeopardy and things like that
Good call good call
And SHO 100 Matt talking about you know
The increased what are the sports channels
Doing sports broadcasting networks
Are starving for contact and they're turning
Or content excuse me and they're turning to
Wrestling and sports movies
Esports time now to get
All the eyes on it yeah and
I feel like Twitch there's just so many more
People broadcasting on Twitch all at once now
Too just because
You can't go outside
Right now so it's just interesting to see
How that's all taken off so anyway
Play a part together
Interesting awareness campaign for the world
Well let's move on with some more news Loki
Yeah speaking of more
You know campaigns for
The whole
COVID-19 situation
We have games done quick
Tackling
Some relief for COVID-19
With their brand new Corona
Relief done quick
It's going to be an event that's going to be online
Of course from April 17th through the 19th
And the
I'm assuming all durations
Or all donations are going to direct
Relief for COVID-19
And then of course they're saying that
The summer games done quick has been postponed
As well it was
Originally scheduled for June 21st
But now it's being pushed back
To August 16th instead
Probably
A good idea in light of everything going on
Yes
So
Yeah be interesting to see
You know what
I want to see what they're going to be running in that
Yeah and it's going to be interesting to see how that
Yeah and it's going to be interesting to see how that's going to all be set up
With the social distancing as well
Although I believe that channel
Has done plenty of speed runs
When there's not
A hotel convention type of thing going on
And they just
They do like a remote like they're
Hosting somebody else's stream essentially
Or maybe doing it through Skype or Discord
Video feed or something like that
So I'm sure there's plenty of ways to do it
So it'll be kind of interesting to see
How well received something like that is
And it does do very well
And then of course I'm sure everybody will be
Very much looking forward to getting back together in person
And it's funny because
Bobby was talking about this a little bit on his show tonight
Because as many of you know
He applied this year to be one of the hosts
Which is very
You know we're rooting for him
But if he weren't to get it we would understand
Because there's tons of people that are
Applying to be hosts of these things
But he was kind of talking a little bit about
You know well if they can do this online
There's going to be some people that would say
Well do it online all the time but at the same time
It kind of loses something like it's
There's something about being all in the same room together
You know and hearing the big cheers
And things like that and
I kind of replied to that I was like sounds familiar
Because it kind of reminds me of like OLR
Like we're able to do this show over Discord
But it's
It's more fun when it's in person and we can play off each other
A lot easier and the laughter is more contagious
Than it is over Discord
You know so
Looking forward to being back to normal soon
That's for sure
And Bobby Blackwell points out
Games Done Quick they do remote speedruns every week
They do entire weekend marathons completely online
Yeah I figure like I stumbled on one of those marathons once
So the
Corona thing
The speedrun they're going to do for
Corona virus relief
Efforts and so forth is not going to be
Probably a technical challenge whatsoever
Hopefully they can get lots of eyes on that
I'm sure they'll get support from Twitch though
Some front page love and things like that
And just general awareness on social media
And so forth that they'll get some
Good donations for that
And Questbuster talking about what's
Going on overseas
The ESA not to be confused
With the E3 people this would be I think it's
European speedrunning association I may have got
The acronym wrong but essentially that's what it is
They just hosted a UK
Speedrunning event that finished today and they're
Planning an online only week of runs in April
As well so
And since you can participate globally why not
You can check that out too as well if you want
So best of luck to everybody involved
With games done quick with the Corona
Relief efforts
Let's talk a little more about Animal Crossing
Since it's what a lot of people are talking about
Right now but actually what I want to talk
About is Animal Crossing Pocket
Camp yeah that's not the current
One the current one is New Horizons
Pocket camp is the cell phone game
Remember that one you would think a lot of people
Have thrown that app in the garbage now that
New Horizons has come out but that's
Yes it's hot garbage
But that's actually not the case
Pocket camp is apparently more popular
Than ever maybe because
With all this talk of
Animal Crossing on social media
Not everybody has a switch
So maybe some folks are turning to the mobile
Version to get their fix a little bit
Apparently players spending on March
21st a single day
Came in at a quarter of a million dollars
That was spending in one day
That's not bad the game's best day
Since March 2nd
The game has generated approximately
3.6 million dollars for the month
Downloads rose by 150
Percent and
670,000 installs the week
Of March 16th which is when the
Shelter in place started for many many people
So that's pretty
Interesting how that game has been getting some
Speed but I would bet it's all the people
That are like what's this about
And they don't have a Nintendo switch so they
This is their easiest way to check that out
Is through pocket cap
Which is a very different Animal Crossing experience
I wasn't really into it
But that's just me DarkSakura loved it
I was not into it it sounded good on paper
Animal Crossing on a cell phone
Sounds awesome and it was garbage
I didn't care for it but again
I have other friends that are super into Animal Crossing
That love it and I consider myself
Like an Animal Crossing fan
But I just didn't care for this one
I just prefer the Nintendo console based ones
And some folks
You know in this
Interesting day and age of all the different
Work from home things
You got some people that are using Zoom to work from home
Or maybe something like WebEx
To get people together or Adobe Connect
There's many many different ways to try to bring
Co-workers together in this day and age
Some people are using Animal Crossing
I think this is maybe meant to be
A little more parody and not that serious
But there was a
Japanese company that was posting some of the pros and cons
Of working remotely through Animal Crossing
And the pro
No voice chat
Because they have no network features whatsoever
Well you can voice chat through the Nintendo app
Technically
Actually I will give a shout out to the Nintendo app
It is proving to be useful for the first time ever
Well I don't know maybe some folks thought
Splatoon's tie-ins were pretty good
But
Excuse me
For Animal Crossing
The fact that you can use the keyboard
In the app is very helpful
As well as the QR code reader
To get different patterns in your
Town from the internet, that's very useful as well
So if you're playing Animal Crossing and you haven't looked at the
Nintendo app
You might have forgot that was a thing
Get back on that because it is pretty useful
But some of the cons
The Japanese company says about working from home
Via Animal Crossing
Can't send files
Can't speak about confidential matters
Meetings are constantly interrupted by talk
Of Animal Crossing
And no one is using their real name
You know it's funny because I was in a work meeting
The other day and people actually asked
Like what is something that's making you happy
During this time and I actually brought
Up Animal Crossing and I was like well a new
Animal Crossing game came out and I really love that
Game, nobody got it
Nobody got it
That's unfortunate
That is unfortunate because I bet a lot of them would really love it
If they saw it
I wasn't going to take the time to explain it
At this particular juncture
So
Bobby Blackwolf in chat talking about
Zoom and Fortnite
I saw a meme where people were using
Fortnite and said that the pros over
Zoom was that it was more stable voice
Chat and you could shoot your co-worker
If they were being annoying
I like that idea
That's very good
Alright
And Bobby also says I was using Zoom for
Four years I'm a Zoom hipster
You know what's so fascinating to me
My knowledge
Of those types of tools
From playing Ingress
Is coming in really handy right now
Because like when we had the big anomaly
Here we were doing a lot of planning
Stuff with Zoom
And so that's a tool I've been using
For a long time
Because there were other things that had
To do with Ingress and meeting people even before then
And
Slack I've used before
And now my company is talking about using
Slack in this interim while we're working
From home and so I'm like
I've used it I can answer some questions
Well Slack also is supposed to be
Integrating with Microsoft Teams as well pretty soon
So you can actually
Call somebody on Slack with
Microsoft Teams or vice versa
We've all jumped on the Microsoft Teams
And
It's alright
Slack's okay
I wouldn't want to see our company use it
Permanently but it's a nice little like
Stand in for now while we can't really see each other
I suppose so
Anyhow let's
Move on with some more stories
Loki
Yes so this is kind of a random thing
They have a brand new
Kind of advertising campaign for
Sega now
You may remember back in the 90s
They had the whole
Sagata Sanchiro
Who was their mascot
For the Saturn
Well now
For Sega's 60th birthday
Celebration they have
His real life son
Mito Fujioka
Playing
The same character
Which is pretty funny
So they have this whole thing
For Sega's 60th
Birthday
It's great we should get more
Advertising like this for
Companies
It's very Japanese
I just generally miss the
Mascots from all the gaming
You know all those commercials in the 90s
And maybe early 2000s
Where like what was the guy that worked
For Playstation that was in all the commercials
For a while
Was kind of the mascot
Yeah I don't remember his name
You know obviously Sonic was a bit of a
Mascot for Sega for a while
But that stuff isn't as strong as it used to be
You know
We need the mascots. Kevin Butler, thank you Act F
Yes Kevin Butler
He was the greatest fictional vice president
Of Sony ever
I guess the closest thing we have is
Flo from Progressive
I guess
But that's not gaming
We need those gaming mascots
To come back like that
Questbuster in chat says
The Sagata Sanchiro commercials were great
That actor's son is taking up the banner too now
Well you know sometimes those things
Kind of stay in the family. I'm thinking of
That social media thing that went around
With Mel Brooks' kid
And then Mel Brooks was actually in the
Bit too but the kid
His kid is in his 40s
He's probably older than me
Was kind of doing a little comedy bit about that whole
Thing and that was really great
Isn't his name Max?
Oh I didn't realize that
Bobby Blackwell says his kid wrote World War Z
Really? I didn't know that
Interesting
Well let's move on. Let's take a trip down memory lane
Let's look at those classics
Shall we? In a segment we call
The classic game of the week
Where every week on the show
We like to take a trip down memory lane to visit
A classic game. Usually Dark
Sakura would take this on and step into
The gaming vault and find a game that she thinks
Hey you guys should be checking
This game out
But she's not here tonight
So I'm gonna actually take over for tonight
And talk about my classic game choice
I think this is one you might like too though
Loki. I'm not sure
I don't know if this was up your alley but it should be
This was actually one of my
Favorite arcade games from back in the day
It is a game called
Ramparts is the game
Do you know this game Loki?
I do but I'm not a fan
Really? I love this game
It's from the year
1990 okay
It's based on that specific
Atari arcade hardware
Games like 720 and stuff were done on
I remember
Was it the Nintendo
Or Super Nintendo version?
They did. There was a Super Nintendo version
That used mode 7 if I'm not mistaken
And there were two Nintendo versions
A lot of people don't know this
There was the US version
I think Jellico did it in the US
And then Konami actually did it in Japan
And Konami kind of changed the game
A little bit because the game
Is kind of like castles and pirate ships
Sort of theming
And in the
Konami NES version they
Changed it to like samurai
And things like that
And I think maybe that's because they were
A little more limited in the graphics
They didn't really do the ocean as a thing
I don't know it's very interesting how they were different
But part of what makes Rampart kind of unique
Is
Rampart they say
They were credited anyway with being kind of a precursor
To tower defense games
Because essentially that's what it was
You were protecting towers
As they were being attacked by little peons
That would come try to attack them
The peons were coming from these ships
That were also attacking your towers
With cannonballs
And so the game was split up into different phases
And for those of you that are watching along on Twitch
You can kind of see these different phases play out
One is you place the cannons
Within your forts
One is it's a free for all battle
Between cannonballs
So you're firing on the pirate ships
They're firing on your castles
The next phase after that is
Put back together your castles
And so it's like a Tetris kind of style
You have Tetris like pieces
And you have to be able to surround
At least one of your castle buildings
With a bunch of Tetris pieces
If you can't do that it's game over
So you'll notice on the Twitch stream for those of you watching
This guy right now is trying to surround
In one bit and he did it there
And he's got another one that's a little smaller
So you can see he's kind of trying to build that together
For those listening on the podcast you'll just have to imagine it
But it's very easy to find gameplay of this game if you're interested
And yes it's playable in MAME
Which I know a lot of people
Check out their arcade games out that way
But it is a neat little game
In the original game there are six different levels
Where you're attacking different ships
And then trying to repair the damage
And it's built into those different phases
There is a multiplayer version of the game
At least the arcade version has it
Not all of the home ports have it
But some of them do
Interestingly enough I believe Konami's NES version
Is one of the ones that has it
Sounds like it's one of those cases where the Japanese
Port of the game was a little bit stronger
If you are playing with two or three people
The arcade version had blue, red, and yellow teams
It was a rare three player arcade game
Except instead of fighting against ships
You're fighting against each other
Your land is separated by a river
And you're trying to blow each other's stuff up
So that's kind of fun
So yeah some of the strategy for this game
It's easier to capture an unowned castle
Than try to repair the wall around a starting castle
But if you kind of build close to the water
You can have better aim
So there's lots of little tricks and techniques
To go into this
I was never very good at it
I just thought it was kind of fun to try to build
The biggest surrounding piece of land I could
Where has this game been ported?
Everywhere in the 90s
It was on the Super Nintendo, the Master System
The Mega Drive, Genesis, Atari Lynx
PC, Macintosh, Commodore 64
Amiga, Atari ST, Game Boy, Game Boy Color
There's a lot of different ports
And if that's not enough for you
It was also included in the
Midway Arcade Treasures compilation
So if you have a Midway compilation
That was either on the GameCube
The Playstation 2, the Xbox, or the Playstation Portable
This game is on it
And if you have the later
Arcade Origins series
That was on Playstation 3 and Xbox 360
This game is on there as well
And
I mean they've done this game a lot haven't they
If you bought Gauntlet on the Game Boy Advance
This game was there as well
It was kind of like the B-side
Like when they did Final Fight
And Magic Sword together
And I was more about Magic Sword
But it was kind of the B-side
So Rampart was available in Gauntlet
On the Game Boy Advance as well
There's also some open source games
That are basically clones of Rampart
Kajani Combat and Castle Combat
Are two of the names of those
So kind of neat
And yeah I really
And they say this is kind of an influencer
Of the tower defense genre
So yeah one of my very favorite
Kind of like puzzle games
I don't know like it does
Get a little bit old after a while
But it is kind of like it's so unique
That I can't help but if I actually
Find one of these machines
I don't think they made a ton of these in the arcade
So I don't see them very often
But if I do see one I really have to play around
For it so there you go
Dark Tetsuya says
I think there's a Japanese Famicom
Version of this too
Yeah I was mentioning that a little earlier
Is that Konami made the Japanese version
Whereas Jellico made the
US version
So it's kind of like Tetris
Where there was two different versions of it on the NES
Questbuster says
My castles are fugly because I had no idea what I was doing
Same though
And Questbuster says I loved watching someone else play it
So I could see the cannons in action
Especially if the arcade cab had its volume up
Oh and something that really should
One thing I need to mention about this game
Before we close up
It ran on a trackball
So you're placing all these pieces
You're firing all the cannons
They sold conversion kits for this
I think it would run on an old 720 machine
Or I'm trying to think of the other
Trackball Atari games
From around this era
But yeah it was actually a trackball game
And I think that's important to say because if you do end up playing a clone
Or whatever it really helps
To have a mouse
So when you are playing it on Super Nintendo
Or even regular Nintendo
You're not really able to play it with a mouse
Or did this game support
The mouse peripheral
I don't think so
I think it was an NES game
I'm pretty sure
It was on both
Because the Super Nintendo one had mode 7
Where you could actually see your land
In mode 7 and it was kind of cool
Because it was like ooh I built that and I'm seeing it in mode 7
So that's kind of neat
Anyway there it is your classic game of the week
One of my old school faves
From the arcades in the 1990s
Rampart
There you go my pick
I know that Sakura wasn't here to pick tonight
But hopefully she'll be back next week
And we'll get a pick from her
Although next week will be April
So she might do a pinball game
Stay tuned we'll see
For now let's move on and travel around the world quickly
With some rapid fire news of what's going on in the industry
Loki
So since we're getting a lot of people watching Netflix
It's I guess appropriate that we have some Netflix news
So there's I guess
Information going on saying that
Netflix is looking to develop
A series
And they're looking to have Ryan Reynolds
Set to produce and star in
I don't know if it's going to be a series or a film
But at the very least something
So
Interesting to see
I'd like to see that
But I don't know
Live action is going to lose some of its
Charm I think
But whatever
I guess we'll have to see what happens
I thought I had heard that it might be a half and half thing
Even though the Dark Sakura is not here
I had to throw out a Xanadu reference
For her
As long as we get a Netflix adaptation
Of Brain Dead 13 then I'll be good too
I guess Space Ace will have to do that as well
And then of course
Speaking of Netflix
Castlevania the animated series
Is getting a fourth season
So that's pretty awesome
And then
Of course
And then of course
So that's pretty awesome
Apparently
I guess the third season just came out
At the beginning of this month
So no date yet
When the fourth one is going to be coming
But I'm glad to see that it's doing well
I have not really watched that series
I think I may have watched an episode of it
But I mean it sounds like it's been
Doing pretty well
Yeah most people that have been watching it
Have said good things about it
So it's one of those things
But speaking of time sinks
You know what else got renewed on Netflix
Which is really exciting
It has nothing to do with video gaming
But it's a game of sorts
The Circle got renewed for seasons 2 and 3
So that is really exciting news
As did Love is Blind
Got renewed for seasons 2 and 3
Both those shows are crazy
Tiger King
Isn't Tiger King like a documentary?
Maybe they can't do a season 2
But I'm sure they'll try to figure out a way to do it
They found a way to do more seasons of Making a Murder
So we'll see
But
Yeah so there's those
The Circle also has
If you're really into that show on Netflix
The Brazil one just came out
And because Netflix is international
You can watch The Circle Brazil
With English subtitles
So it's kind of like having another season of The Circle
And apparently there is a French one coming to this
The Circle France is coming as well
If you're a fan of that crap
Like me
Alright anyway
Bobby Blackwolf says they're doing a season 2 of Tiger King
It's going to be scripted
Kate McKinnon is in it
She's playing the woman
No way
Isn't that just something they're talking about on Twitter
Because like Dax Shepard is saying
Like he has to be the main guy
In the movie version
Or the inevitable version of this
And then what's
Edward Norton wanted to fight him for the part
It's like crazy
Oh that sounds ridiculous
Yeah anyway
Wow he's linking me
He's bringing the receipts
He's linking me to a Deadline article
Apparently there is a Joe Exotic
Limited series starring Kate McKinnon
You gotta be
shitting me
Oh because this all got rolling
Back in November
And now interest in the project
Is picked up again because of what's going on
With the Netflix series
Interesting
So it may not necessarily be tied to Netflix though
But it probably will end up there
We'll see
Alright well anyway
On to other rapid fire news
Let's talk about Streets of Rage 4
Because I know some people only care about
Streets of Rage 4 because they want to hear new
Yuzo Koshiro music on the soundtrack
I don't say I can blame you
I'm in a very similar position
And the good news is you will be able to get the soundtrack
Or if you're a vinyl hipster
Which is completely understandable
You can get the vinyl in summer of 2020
And that will be a lot of fun as well
So yes it has been confirmed that Streets of Rage 4
OST will get a digital release
On the same day as the game launches
What day is that?
We still don't know
They're just saying it will be the same day
Soon
That's right
Last week we talked about the Humble Brag
Which was the Humble Bundles version of Nintendo Direct
Yeah I checked that out
It happened
And what did you think?
Well let me quickly mention
Some of the things they talked about
Their publishing arm is going to be getting
One Step from Eden on PC and Switch
Fae Tactics as well
And then they talked about some partnerships
Including Wildfire which is a stealth game
Ambition, A Minuet of Power
Which is a roguelike
Proteus, not to be confused with Parodius
Which is a sci-fi first person shooter
Ring of Pain, a roguelike
With card game pacing
And The Iron Oath
A turn based RPG in a dark fantasy world
You actually watched it Loki, what did you think?
It was okay
I've been interested in Proteus a bit
I was kind of disappointed that not everything
That they were showing was stuff that's right around the corner
But
I mean it looked okay
I thought they were going to have some
Really amazing announcements
But it was alright
More Proteus footage is good
I think we're definitely going to see more and more companies
That are kind of doing this
As time goes on, that's for sure
Alright
Well let us move on and talk about
World release dates and what is coming out
In a country near you very soon
So starting with the US?
Not a whole lot, but we've got Bubble Bobble 4
Friends on Nintendo Switch
Persona 5
Royale on Playstation 4
My friend
Pedro on Playstation 4
And then last but not least
Resident Evil 3
On PC, Playstation 4
And Xbox One
Alright, traveling to Japan
And checking out the releases there
On the Playstation 4
Biohazard 3
Which of course is Resident Evil 3
That remake is getting its release on Playstation 4
On April the 3rd
That is a regular version and a Z version
Is coming out there
Shovel Knight also getting its Japanese release
This week, so that's kind of fun
I'm guessing that's a localized version
It may have already come out digitally
But this is a physical version
That's coming out as well
Over on the Nintendo Switch, also seeing
Shovel Knight as well
Kotoba no Puzzle
Is a game as well
I don't know what the hell this is
Pika Pika Nurse Monogatari
Now I know you might think
That that is some type of Pikachu thing
But it's not, it's like a
Nursing simulator type of game
So, and that is
It's like Nursing Mama
Basically, so, yeah
Because you get to actually examine patients
But it's all cute and chibi
So, interesting
So that's out this week
And then there's a brand new Nintendo Switch Lite
Color coming out in Japan
A Nintendo Switch Lite Coral version
Is out, so
Fun fun
Okay, Logi
In the UK we've got
Onanaki, that's coming out on
PlayStation 4 and Switch
Zombie Army Trilogy
On a Nintendo Switch
Persona 5 Royale
On PlayStation 4
Super Epic on PlayStation 4
And Switch
Resident Evil 3
On PlayStation 4 and Xbox One
And that's it
Alrighty
Let's move on to our mailbag
Every week you guys send us emails
Participate at OrangeLoungeRadio.com
And we read some of our favorites here on the show
Although I'm sad to say yet again
It looks like our mailbag was kind of empty
So we don't have any emails to read
But I will go to our Twitter
Account because we do
Field your tweets as well
At OLR over on Twitter
And we do have a tweet coming in this week
From Flaco Jones who tweeted us
Saying, we haven't heard from Flaco
In a while. Hello Flaco, I hope you're well
Flaco says, hey OLR
My wife has been spending the bulk of her gaming time
During the pandemic lockdown
Playing Wind Waker HD
And she just talked to
A certain someone very special
To your show
And attached is a gif image of
Tingle
You can't even see that, whatever
Sorry, I was holding it up to the camera
Tingle has made an appearance
In Wind Waker HD
Good choice to catch up on the gaming backlog
You know, speaking of Zelda
I know several people that have kind of
Restarted or picked up again
Their Breath of the Wild games
Because you know, talk about a game that you sink a lot of hours into
That's another big one as well
Loki, any thoughts on
Wind Waker HD and
Tingle appearance?
I already made my comment on that
Oh, what did you say? I missed it
I replied, dislike
Dislike, whatever
Don't be a hater
Alright, so anyhow, there you go
So in lack of
Emails this week, at least we got a tweet
And I will be encouraging more folks to send us
Tweets for future weeks, because
If we're going to continue to have an empty mailbag
Then we're going to change this segment
A little bit, I'm not sure I'm going to delete the
Mailbag, but we're going to
Kind of open it up to other
Feedback mechanisms as well, so
Mails and tweets, I suppose
Don't make us go
Late 90s, early 2000s
Participate or die
No, no, I mean
You know, the reality is
Less and less people use
Email, because more and more
People use social media
And I think this is just one of those, maybe we have to
Evolve type of things, because
People just aren't really using their email accounts
Like they used to, but it's very easy to send a tweet
And you know, I
Probably should dust off the Facebook
And try to get some more posts on there
It's hard for me to put together this show
And be the social media guy, so
You know, we'll see, we'll do it again
So, alright
Dark Tetsuya says, just do what you did with
FUs, make it as needed if we do
Get any. The difference between this and FUs
Though is that, you know, this is the show where every gamer
Has a voice, and especially right now
Where we're having to use Discord to do the show, so we're not
Really doing calls on Discord
And we weren't really getting a lot of those
Either, I think we just need to rethink
Some of the ways that we're letting people participate
And so, you know what I need to do
I just need to open an Animal Crossing
Town during the show, and you can participate
By coming to visit and saying
Your message is there. That's staying
On top of trends, right? So, anyway
Hey, I'm open to ideas
If you think there's a way we should be
Getting more folks to interact with our show that we're not doing
Tweet me, email me
Anything, text me
If you know my number, I'll take anything
So, alright
Ooh, so
So, you want to talk about participation
Bobby just got some late-breaking news
For himself, Bobby said
In chat, breaking news
He has Tommy Tallarico coming on his show
Next week
From television, yeah
So, when are we going to be starting the show?
Like, 8 o'clock at night?
Do we get a show next week, Bobby?
Have we been bumped?
I don't know, no, I'm kind of
Serious, what happens now to OLR
Because he's not going to hold
Himself to an hour
We're going to have to figure that out
I did see the new video that he posted
About the Intellivision
With the new game series showing off
And stuff like that
In the controller
Showing off Missile Command, I believe
Yeah, I saw the Missile Command video as well
I think they're very committed to that idea
Which is, you know
Some may say is the wrong idea right now
In the time of Coronavirus
But hopefully by the time this thing is out
Coronavirus is a memory
God, let's hope so
And I think maybe more than ever
People will want to hang out in person again
Because they're going to realize how much they missed it
Because I will say
Even though the games are not
Packing the oomph
In processing power of something like
Nintendo Switch or Playstation 4
What have you
It seems like the ideas they've committed to
They're executing fairly well
Like the fact that the controller works on your phone
As well as the
You know, regular Bluetooth controller
Like that looks like it's
You know, that Missile Command game they were playing
The foreplayer looked very fast paced
And it looked like it was doing very well
So it's kind of interesting
Yeah, it looked pretty cool
Yeah, so I'm looking
Some folks in chat, OLR starting late
OLR cancelled next week
Bobby says
I'll try to wrap it at an hour
We'll figure it out
We're just joking
Well, here's the thing too
Honestly, if there's any time
To screw with our times
What else do we have going on
The nice thing is
Loki and Dark Sakura aren't driving
To get here at a certain time
So if we do end up with a 6.30 start time
It's not the end of the world
We'll talk about it offline
But I'm excited for you
That'll be a fun interview
Alright, let's move on
Loki, you have another piece of news for us
Yes, so
As we were kind of alluding to earlier
With all the sports
Being kind of
Postponed right now
So NASCAR is another thing
That's now going to be
Kind of like an eSports coverage
So they're gonna
Do their first NASCAR
They had their first NASCAR
Virtual race over the weekend
And now I guess
Fox and NASCAR have decided
That they're gonna broadcast a whole season
Of it on TV
And this is kind of similar to I guess
What Formula One's been doing
We talked about that last week
So it's gonna be the E-Nascar iRacing Pro
Invitation Series event
Interesting
I mean, like I said
This is kind of neat that
eSports is kind of gonna be a thing
That's coming more mainstream
With different sporting
Events going to
Their kind of electronic equivalents
It's also fascinating to me that you have
The professional sports players for being able to
Do the physical sports that are kind of
Transitioning to the eSports side of things
When it comes to these, you know, very
Intense simulators like iRacing
You know, because that's supposed to really
Simulate the kind of NASCAR experience
Versus the other kind of
Traditional eSports athlete that learned
To play said game
Because maybe it's not based on some
Well, even, I would say even something like Madden
Falls into this category
Madden is based off a sport in the real world
And some might even call it a simulation
But it doesn't really
Play like it, if that makes sense
You know, like they're very, very different
Whereas I think when we talk about something like
The iRacer, there's probably a lot
That goes into it
I'm not familiar with it myself, but I imagine
It's like the Microsoft Flight Simulator
Of car racing where every, you know, nut and bolt
Is kind of represented there
You know what I mean, whereas in Madden, it's kind of
Has to be dumbed down
And I'm using my quotey fingers, I'm not saying that
In a negative way
For a controller, you know
And the fact that you're not
Exerting physically in the same way
If that makes sense, so
But yeah, Bobby Blackwell says iRacing is what
The drivers use to train when they can't get on a track
As Joe and Hunter Matt in chat over at
Twitch TV slash VOG Network says
The NHL is simming the rest of their
Season, I almost said slimming, but it's
Simming the rest of their season
In NHL 20, complete with
Players of the day and stat updates
The team Twitter accounts are getting into it as well
What else can you do
Because, you know, when you don't
Have games, you don't
Have the visibility
You don't have the shirts
And the merchandising and that stuff
Necessarily selling at the same pace
I'm sure there's always going to be diehard fans
That are looking for that stuff, but it's not going to be selling at the same pace
So it's like anything that you can do
To get people to be like, hey, remember
Hockey, like, it's
Going to be something they're going to try
So, be interesting
It's just, it is
Going to be so fascinating, the
Economic ripple that this is all
Going to have, and I'm not trying to say it in like
A doom and gloom type of way
But I mean, look at
Like Disney parks being shut down
For six weeks, that's
Which is what we're looking at at this point
I haven't officially said the reopening date
But that's like crazy and unheard of, right?
So like Disney
Disney's going to lose like six weeks
Of park income, do you know how much money that is?
That's a lot of money
It's a lot of fucking money
Now a company like Disney has multiple
TV networks, movie studios and other things
To kind of like keep them afloat
So I'm not worried like, oh my god, Disney's going to go under
But it's going to be like a rough transition
I think for a lot of companies
Anyway, I don't want to burden us too much
With the real world stuff, but I would just say
When we get back to the real world
When it's safe to do so
It's going to be like driving on a road
That hasn't been paved in a little while
You'll get to the destination
It's going to be a little bumpy
There's going to be some potholes
It'll be interesting
Yeah, Act Efton Chat says
We're not talking millions, we're talking billions
Yeah, that's true, that is very true
As Joe and Hunter Matt points out at six weeks
For domestic parks, some of the international parks
Have been closed for months now
So, we shall see
Alright, anyhow
Well, one interesting
Case of gaming worlds
Hopefully reflecting
What might happen in the real world
Is that right now
House evictions are being halted
In Final Fantasy XIV
And I play a lot of Final Fantasy XIV
So let me kind of tell you what this really means
Because player housing is very highly contested
In Final Fantasy XIV
Because there's only so much of it
It's kind of a problem that's been facing the game
For a long time
There's a lot
There's the different areas
And then there's so many housing wards and plots
In every area
But it can be hard to get a house
Sometimes you have to just kind of camp out
And hope that a plot becomes available
And try to snatch that up as soon as you can
Because what happens in the way that plots become available
Is that if somebody doesn't log into their account
Or doesn't visit their house
I believe it's in 45 days
I think there's a timer that starts after 30 days
And if you go like another 15
Your house is basically demolished
And your plot goes up for sale
Because you basically abandon it
You get some of your investment back
And any furniture you put in there
You can go talk to an NPC and get it back
But you've essentially lost your claim to the land
So you get bounced for not having visited it
And so the housing is
And somebody will be there trying to buy it
When that happens
So I finally got my house
Because I went to a new server
And I finally bought my house
Because somebody abandoned the land
And I just happened to be in the right place
Right time and I got the house
Well, because not everybody is able to conduct their lives
With the same pattern that maybe they were before
Not everybody is necessarily logging into Final Fantasy 14
With the same, you know
And especially probably people
That are working on the front lines
In places like healthcare and so forth
Probably aren't thinking about things like Final Fantasy 14
That they used to
So, the automatic demolishing system has been suspended
So, and they've said
In a statement from Square Enix
Quote, taking into account the worldwide spread
Of COVID-19 and the economical effects
Of various cities going into lockdown
We've decided to temporarily
Suspend automatic housing demolition
Now that I'm saying this out loud
This could also very much be
For the sake of other countries
Maybe not so much the US
But other places where cafes
And that kind of pay in advance game time
Is like how you play it
We have to remember in the US culture
Playing at home and that stuff
Is very much how you do it
But there's other cultures where Final Fantasy 14 exists
Where you go to an internet cafe
To play and log into your character
And all that stuff
So I would bet for the sake of those places
That's why this is being
You know, and it's kind of one of those
It's easier to push the button for everybody
Than it is for just some places
So there you go
No more evictions in Final Fantasy 14
Until this is figured out
So hopefully something that reflects
The real world because I know there's a lot of people
And I'm thinking of a lot of friends of mine
Who have been displaced from work
I'm sure there's many of you out there listening
Because of what's going on in the real world
And I'm glad to hear
They're doing things like
Unemployment benefits
Like the stimulus package and so forth
I think we know
It's just the first of many things
That need to be done
So that we don't have just this complete
Catastrophe of people not being
Because where are all these people gonna go
So hopefully the government
Is able to
Put a stop to people
Unnecessarily getting kicked out of
Their places
So we'll see what develops
Over the next few weeks and months
Alright, well Loki we have a few more stories
Before we wrap up the show. Loki, you first
So
Capcom has decided to cancel
Their Capcom Pro Tour
At least the first half of it
Due to the COVID-19
Pandemic and they made their announcement
Via the Capcom Fighters
Twitter page basically saying that
Currently the Nobel coronavirus
COVID-19 is projected to continue
For several more months or longer
Across the world in light of this situation
Concerning the health and wellbeing of our players
Staff and visitors, all tournaments
Scheduled to be held in the first half of
2020 Capcom Pro Tour
Season have been removed
From the schedule. We apologize for any
Inconveniences may have caused players
Fans and tournament operators and production
Teams. The second half of the Capcom
Pro Tournament is scheduled to resume in
July, but we will continue to monitor
The novella coronavirus
Situation and we'll adjust
The schedule and rules accordingly
I mean it makes sense that it was gonna
happen. Yeah it's just kind of another
One of those up just add that to the list
Of things that are put on hold for a little bit but
It is the right thing to do so
We just you know I think now we're just all kind of
Wondering like when's where's that
Line gonna be of things that get
Canceled and things that don't get cancelled like when
You know the government is
Talking about April 30th maybe
We can start to relax some social
Maybe maybe
Does that mean we're gonna be able to have conventions
Again I don't know if it necessarily means
That we might start to see what probably
Will happen is that maybe they'll still like
Allow you to go to restaurants and things but they're
Still gonna say to limit gatherings to a certain
Amount of people like you know what I mean and then maybe
Like May or June we start to
See some of that come back as the line gets flattened
Even more hopefully so
Yeah I think it's gonna happen is they're gonna
Basically kind of scale it back
Kind of like how we saw it progressively
Get more restricted it's
Gonna kind of go the opposite direction
SSU 100 Matt points out
The Olympics was the big one that being shut
Down since a huge presidents yeah and that is not
An easy thing to move and you know and I think
I think I mentioned this last week when we heard about
This Olympics getting pushed back
Thing was kind of starting this puts that
Mario and Sonic at the 2020
Tokyo games that game that
Puts up in a very interesting predicament of
Being a licensed property
For something that didn't happen
That's not necessarily true
Because it will happen
But it's specifically
It's not called the Tokyo games
It's called the 2020 Olympic games
So yes yes it's fine
You all want to get me on a technicality
Well it will happen in 2021 yes I understand that
But the game is still the 2020
Another game they can make a second game
So what I was gonna say is
I mean it's not the most ridiculous
Property that's been created
Or no tie in
You may remember there was a Spy
Hunter game that's starring
Vin Diesel that came out
Or I think it was Vin Diesel
Somebody some action star that came out
And then the Spy Hunter movie never came out
Oh right
Yeah I remember they were working on a Spy Hunter movie
And then they just kind of stopped doing that
Now Bobby is saying that the branding is still all gonna be
Tokyo 2020
Well that is gonna be interesting alright then I guess maybe it doesn't make that game
As special as I thought but
If all the branding Oh yes thank you
It's The Rock I knew it was one of them
But The Rock was
One of those Fast and Furious
Guys one of them
One of them was in it
Well Vin Diesel had the other one too
There was another one though with Vin Diesel
It was
I don't remember what it was about
But it was another car driving
Type game not like
Fast and the Furious or something but there was another
Spy thing with cars
That he was in as well
Tiger Claw says The Wheelman
Yes that is thank you
That was also supposed to be a movie
Alright
Well moving on and after this story
We're gonna take your questions
And comments from our chat room
As we move into the listener round table
So if you have any questions or things you want us to bring up
That we haven't gotten to yet
Maybe we'll hit on in a last minute story
But twitch.tv slash vog network
Or vog network is the place to leave some comments
Meanwhile
We have news of a Nier
Remaster coming out
So Nier is hitting its 10 year anniversary
And there's going to be a
Remaster Nier Replicant
That's coming out for the PC, Playstation 4
And Xbox One
Now originally Nier Replicant
Was on Japan on the Playstation 3
But in the West it was called
Nier Gestalt
Which then came to Japan on the Xbox 360
There were different
Protagonists in the games
But if you have a game and I know I have this game
On the Xbox 360 that's just called
Nier, it's that, but with a different
Protagonist
So essentially it's a remake of that older Nier game
That was that, it's just some
Little changes there
But I know a lot of people are pretty excited about that
So it's coming out for Playstation 4, Xbox One
And Steam
Just in time for the 10 year anniversary
I'm a little surprised they're doing this
And not an all new Nier game
But maybe
It's one of those things where a new Nier game
Is going to take a little time
Again, this is coming out on Playstation 4 and Xbox One
Maybe a new Nier game is something
They're plotting for Playstation 5
And Xbox Series X
And so it's going to take them a little more time to cook that up
So, understandable
Fifth Dream Today says
Best Music
Yeah, the
Raid in Final Fantasy that's based off Nier
Has some pretty amazing music in it
I gotta say, it's really cool
Act Deft also points out
Nier Automata is coming to Xbox Game Pass
On April 2nd
Yay, I'll finally get around to playing it
After all this time
So, I will make it a point to check that out
I've heard nothing but great things about the Nier games
So I need to check that out for sure
So, alright
Well, we're going to open up the listener round table
If you guys have any comments or questions
Or so forth
Act Deft in our chat says
Rob, the Mario and Sonic game is still special
Because it has Waluigi doing gymnastics
That is true
Waluigi participating in those events
Is always going to be a special thing
Shehulk10 with a question for us
Do you guys have any
Old games that you liked
But not really that popular
That you would like to be given
A current gen remake
Or makeover
Mine is Jaws the Revenge from 2006
Where you play as the
Shark
Oh my god, I forgot about that one
Do you remember that game? The Jaws but you're the shark
I thought they had one that was just like that
Not too long ago
It's another Jaws game
I think it's Jaws
Man Eater
Yes, it looks
There's a lot similar there
It's not out yet
But that is something that's coming
So that's a good one
One that we bring up a lot on this program
Is the Guardian Legend
Which is honestly one of the greatest
8-bit games on the Nintendo
It was kind of a hybrid of a shooter and Legend of Zelda
And if you've never played the game
I really urge you to go check out some YouTubes
Unfortunately I think it's one of those
Who owns the rights now
That we probably are not going to see this game
On Virtual Console or anything like that anytime soon
Although I would be so giddy if we ever did
But I would love to see
That come back
But it has to be the right studio
That does it
And I would really want to see a company like WayForward
Because weren't they the ones behind the Blaster Master Zero?
Yes
Because that was done right
That Blaster Master relaunched it
And they even had the sequel as well
Which was kind of like a sequel that didn't really exist
Which is kind of awesome
That I would want to see come back
But it needs to be like
As good as Blaster Master Zero was
I would be very sad
If it was kind of crap
Like they kind of
Like that other Blaster Master game
That was on the Wii
Which was not that great because they tried to like redo too much
And then the physics felt off
And it kind of ruined the game
BobbyBlackWolfe points out WayForward
Also did DuckTales Remastered
Which was also very well done
Very good point
Some other folks in chat are answering this question
BobbyBlackWolfe says
GuttaruMan
Very good answer
ActDeft an old game I would love to see get a remake or make over
Uniracers
Repcycled in chat says
StuntRaceFX
Which I'm sure is going to lead to the inevitable
Loki answer of ExciteBike
ExciteTruck
ExciteTruck get it right
Sorry my bad
We've seen ExciteBike get remastered a few times
But not ExciteTruck yet
Yes I'm all for that
I'm all for an ExciteTruck
Yeah
Repcycled saying StuntRaceFX
In a way I feel like ExciteTruck
Was a StuntRaceFX
A little bit
A little bit I don't know
So those are some answers there
Loki any last minute stories
While we wait and see if chat has any other questions
Or comments for us
Yes I do have one so
Apparently there was a push notification
That went out
Just tonight saying that
HQ Trivia is back
Apparently
I think that was the trivia game that you can actually
Win real money
That thing was like all the rage
For like a month and then everybody quit
Yeah and if you saw their last episode
It was great go look it up on YouTube
Because they were drunk and they didn't
Give a fuck
They were swearing and doing all this stuff
They were probably high
They were just like we're closing tonight
Whatever it's the last one
And the guy put up a prize of $5
Of his own money
It was great
It was like total
They're coming back tonight
So
Alright cool I guess
You know maybe it's one of those things
Where it's like now is the time for that
Maybe they see an opportunity where it's like
Everybody's stuck at home
Let's try this again
They must have had a financier step in
And be like now's the time
An anonymous investor
That's what it is
ActDeft in chat
Says question for Robin Loki
Have you seen that Twitter tag meme
To post four games that defined you
Well what are yours
I have seen that meme
I just held off on doing it
Because I don't like tag memes
Because then it's like I have to tag people
That probably won't do it and then it's like
Why don't you tag me
That's basically an email for no thanks
There's a lot about those memes I don't really like
But let's take the
Because the question is still good
So let's take the question out of that
Four games that define you
This is tricky
I'd have to really think on this
But in the moment I'm gonna say
One of the obvious answers is Dance Dance Revolution
Without that game I wouldn't know Loki
I wouldn't know any of you
Because I wouldn't have had this show
So that's at the top of the list
Other games
So I'm gonna try to let that be the music game representation
I would say the original Legend of Zelda
On the NES
Just because that was the game
That really turned me into a video game nerd
Because that was the one where other kids
Who used to bully me would then
Secretly want to ask me questions about
So how do I get to the fourth dungeon in the second quest
Yeah right stuff like that
So I would say that game was very definitive
Two more
Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo
Because of the
Fucking crazy amount of that I played in college
I think that's really all I need to say about that one
And that was kind of like the PlayStation
I almost said Final Fantasy 7
But then I was like no you know what PlayStation game got even more time
Was Super Puzzle Fighter 2 Turbo
And then a fourth game
Probably some sort of MMO
Maybe I will say
Final Fantasy 11
Again I'm not really giving this a lot of thought
I'm kind of answering this spontaneously
But those are the four that come up spontaneously
But I feel like an MMO needs representation in there
I had an MMO based podcast for many years
And that way the Final Fantasy franchise gets represented as well
Which I've always been a big fan of
Alright Loki what about you
Four games that define you
So I have to say
Final Fantasy 7
Dance Man's Revolution
I mean probably the whole series
Because they can't really
I guess fourth mix if we had to pick
A game
Third mix plus Korean
Is mine
Okay
And then I would say
Grand Theft Auto 4
Because I played a ton of that
Let's see
I would probably have to say
Final Fantasy 11
And
Yeah probably The Legend of Zelda
Because that was one of the first Nintendo games I got
Driver 3
I didn't play enough Driver 3
Saints Row
Okay yeah I did play a ton of Saints Row
She-Hulk 10
I like this answer
Pac-Man Asteroids
Halo Mass Effect
I'm really surprised I didn't put
Mass Effect the trilogy on my list
See that's a my bad for not thinking
That through further but
You know I think I don't know if I would say
Mass Effect defined me
As much as
I really fucking liked
Mass Effect
Because I kind of feel like there's a difference
You know what I mean
I'm not critical of how anybody else
Wants to answer this question I'm just saying when I answered it
Things that I'm thinking of are like
Like this podcast
And the many many many hours
Would not exist if not for DDR and so on
Kind of the different reasons I gave
But like as far as like
Things I really enjoyed I would really have to
Probably put Mass Effect on that list
As well so
Really good question I like that I guess that's a good one
To end on so any other last minute stories
Loki before we wrap up
Yeah so
Couple more
I talked about GameStop closing 300
Stores so it's actually about 320
Stores in 2020
This was due to their 2019
Investors call
Apparently they're saying we're continuing to
Focus optimizing our global
Store fleet in fiscal 2019
And closing that total
Of 321
Stores inclusive of
333 closings and 12
Openings and in fiscal
2020 we will continue our efforts
To de-densify the store
Base and focus on
Maximizing product
Productivity of the entire fleet
So
I mean this was as of a call
Last week
So who knows the toll that
Other real world stuff might take on this
But they were already planning to close 300
They were already doing that like I already
Like I said my local store is
Closing I know that he
The guys there were
Promising me some stuff but I know
That they haven't been in the store for
You know a week or so
So I don't even know what that's doing
To their closing because they were
Doing like closeout stuff but they still have a ton
Of product in the store and
I mean if they're not open I don't know what that does
For them if they're just going to postpone the closure
Of them until they can open again
Or what the case may be
I was thinking
Going back on that four games question and I can't
Believe I didn't fucking say Ingress
Just because of like
I've traveled to cities I wouldn't have gone to
Otherwise if it wasn't for that game
Yeah so there's
I have to really sit down and think about that one
Long and hard there's a lot of good answers
For that I think so
Anyway
Because somebody else said Pokemon
It made me think Pokemon Go and then I was like oh yeah
Ingress I should have said Ingress because I've been playing that way too long
Maybe Ingress
Just slipped my mind because I haven't been playing
It the past couple weeks I wonder what
I mean a little
Bit like when I walked
30 minutes to another
Park I played it at the park
And then walked back but that's like it
Like I'm not playing it nearly
At the level I was playing it before
So interesting
Yeah SG100Matt says Rob didn't say
Super Metroid either
No I didn't because again
The question was the games that defined you
Not which games do you really really really really like
I think there's a difference
You know it really is
Anyway
So that's it for last minute stories Logie
I was going to say there's one more
It's kind of silly
So Crash Nitro
Field Racing
Or Crash Team Racing Nitro Field
They had a funny
April Fools
Day
DLC that they're putting out
So apparently it's free
Which is good and so what happens
Is if you smash some of these
Benox crates scattered throughout the tracks
You can actually
Unlock a hidden crate
Cart
So the hidden
It's like a
A benox crate
Is the driver of the cart
One of the smashing crates
From Crash Team
Huh interesting
That's a little silly
I kind of like though that they
Are doing an April Fools
Something along those lines because I think a lot of us
Are going to be really tired of April Fools
Day this year for all intents and purposes
April Fools Day is cancelled
Just don't
April Fools Day? Don't
Not this year, not today Satan
There's too much other stuff going on in the room
But I think cute things
Like this
Ready for it
Extra things, sideshow, okay
Okay we can do that
But that's about all we can tolerate right now
No jokes
Anyhow
Alright I think with that we will go ahead and wrap things up
I know it's a little bit shorter of a show
But we didn't have Jamie tonight
We're on Discord so I think things will be a little bit
Shorter just in the interim
We still filled a good about two hours or so
Nonetheless
Almost two hours
We want to thank you guys for being here and tuning in this week
Whether it was live on Sunday night
Over the Voice Geeks Network Twitch channel
Or if it was on the podcast feed
Really appreciate that
If you enjoyed what you heard here at Orange Songs Radio
Help us spread the word because we are the show where every gamer has a voice
But the more voices we get here on Sunday nights
And on our podcast feed
Throughout the week sending us tweets and things like that
The more we can get your voices out there
So tell a friend or two about the show
Help us spread the word
Auto hosts on your Twitch channel go a long way
Please consider adding VOG Network to your host list
That would be super awesome
And then just you know sharing on social media
The Spotify link or things like that whatever
Those things come in very very very very handy
Really appreciate those of you guys that do that
That's going to do it for this week
We'll be back in seven days to talk all again
And hopefully Dar Sacro will be back with us
And can talk about other stuff
We'll probably still be remote via Discord
For a little while but that's okay
We'll talk about whatever's going on in gaming
Loki I guess we get to final thoughts
Any final thoughts from you tonight?
Yes I've been staring at a black widow
That's been in my
My
monitor arms
And it's just
It's crawled up inside there now
And now I have to somehow take this apart
And go kill it
I think you're going to be burning your house down later
Honestly and I
That's the reason to do it
So
And then my final thoughts
Tonight is
Just keep staying inside
If I can do it you can do it
And enjoy the games
Catch up on your backlog
You'll have some near on Xbox Game Pass this week
You've got plenty of other free games out there
And stuff in your backlog
So check it all out this week
Have fun and we'll see you
On Twitch and on the podcast feed
In seven more days
Have a great week everybody
Good night
Orange Lounge Radio
Orange Lounge Radio is a production
Of OLR Studios
To join us for a live show
Tune in to vognetwork.com
Sunday nights
At 6pm pacific
9pm eastern
The views and opinions expressed in this program
Do not necessarily reflect those
Of the staff of Orange Lounge Radio
Or VOG Network
But you know they were all still true
See you next week
Thanks for watching!