[SPEAKER_10]: www.orangeloungeradio.com
[SPEAKER_10]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 204 for this, October the 15th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if this is your first time listening to Orange Lounge Radio, don't forget that Orange Lounge Radio is podcast twice a week, so you're actually listening to the second half of a show already in progress.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you want to catch the whole thing live when it broadcasts, you should listen to Orange Lounge Radio live on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_12]: or there's always our rebroadcast that plays on All Games Radio, Monday nights at 5 o'clock Pacific Time and Tuesday mornings at 9 a.m.
[SPEAKER_12]: Speaking of All Games Radio, our buddy Bobby Blackwolf, who does a show over there Sunday nights as well, just before we do, he's going to be doing some type of trivia contest at the big video games expo, which I wish I was going, but sadly I'm not.
[SPEAKER_12]: The VG Expo, if you're within traveling distance, unfortunately, when I talk about going, now we're talking about a plane ticket.
[SPEAKER_12]: But for those of you on the East Coast, it's probably very drivable from lots of different spots.
[SPEAKER_12]: VGExpo.com
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, such is life that we would have more news about Halo 3 at some point and at some point it's going to be Halloween.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, the spooky holiday will feature some brand new news about Halo 3 and yeah, that's about all we know is that there's going to be news.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's news about upcoming news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Halo 3 is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's going to be the big news.
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you think as we theorized previously, because you had that whole report talking about Halo 3 is likely to be coming out in April or May, do you think this could be where they drop that bombshell?
[SPEAKER_12]: Could this be the big bombshell that's coming out?
[SPEAKER_12]: It would be aptly timed, but probably not.
[SPEAKER_12]: You think it's more something along the notion of gameplay?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know this is time, though, to take a little bit of Sony's thunder from PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_12]: to get people talking about Halo 3 amongst the PlayStation 3 and Wii chaos that's sure to be going on in November.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, I guess currently right now they're showing Halo 3 to a select group of magazine journalists, not websites, but a handful of magazine folks, and yeah, it looks like they're going to be having some sort of event, and they're inviting game journalists from the U.S.
[SPEAKER_11]: and Europe to visit their studio and show a quick single-player
[SPEAKER_11]: Demo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, you know, I would say go out and buy the magazine to see the news, but it's going to be all over the internet the day it comes out anyway, probably before it lands in your mailbox, so just read the internet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of things that are at least being said around the internet and other places, Sony's talking some crap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, to be specific, that would be Nobuyuki Ide, who is the
[SPEAKER_06]: former, um, uh, wasn't he the former CEO of Sony?
[SPEAKER_06]: He's actually their current chief corporate advisor.
[SPEAKER_06]: So when he was asked about the Xbox 360 being the PS3 to market, he said Microsoft is not a technology company.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, they make lunchboxes.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, and Nintendo makes cards.
[SPEAKER_12]: at least they used to back in the day but you know yeah they made Hanafuda cards doesn't he used to run brothels too?
[SPEAKER_06]: I really don't know but this I just think that's funny because this guy was responsible for a lot of damage to Sony's profits back in the day but you know I think that it would be in Sony's best interest right now not to be throwing mud you know that's what I would be doing you know
[SPEAKER_11]: Concentrate on getting your console out instead of saying, our console's better than your console.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, except our console's not out yet and yours is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Sony pisses me off even more because they're discontinuing the AIBO.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love the AIBO.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but the AIBO is useless.
[SPEAKER_06]: The AIBO is their little robot dog.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that if they're going to do anything, they should make the AIBO a peripheral for the PS3.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would sell more units.
[SPEAKER_12]: That might actually happen.
[SPEAKER_12]: That might sell me one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd buy one.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's just what I need, my PlayStation 3 to bark at me and play Blu-rays.
[SPEAKER_11]: Brilliant idea, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_11]: After all, I mean, after looking at what was the Eye of Judgment set up that they have at G... I don't think that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought it would lower your blood pressure.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'd rather have a barking PlayStation 3 in that Eye of Judgment.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_06]: It wouldn't bark.
[SPEAKER_06]: It would hook up to the PS3 and you would play, like, instead of having Nintendogs, you'd have a real dog sim because you'd have your robot dog.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's like Rob the Robot.
[SPEAKER_06]: But only, like...
[SPEAKER_06]: Only good for more than one game.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, I always wish they would... This is why you're on internet radio, Jamie, and not in a boardroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: My ideas would sell money.
[SPEAKER_06]: People should hire me.
[SPEAKER_11]: They need to create Rob the Robot, like, as in... I always wanted, like, a miniature version of it for, like, the DS or something like that, that would sit next to your DS and do the same little thing and just re-release Gyromite or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, actually, one of the good things, though, about the AIBO is it actually was a very inexpensive...
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty, you know, interestingly complex AI, you know, in the little system that you could afford better than, like, a human-sized robot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lot of AI developers and robotics experts were actually buying AIBOs for experiments.
[SPEAKER_12]: Drunami in our chatroom is suggesting that here on Orange Sounds Radio we could replace Loki with an AIBO.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be cute.
[SPEAKER_12]: That would be pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I bet the AIBO is a lot cuter.
[SPEAKER_06]: AIBOs are really cute.
[SPEAKER_06]: It'd go well with my new Mac.
[SPEAKER_06]: When I get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Speaking of Sony, before Loki has a chance to give a counter-argument there, speaking about Sony executives who are sitting in boardrooms eating crayons all day when they ought to be working, this executive, Michael Ephraim from Sony of Australia, you know, he made this crazy comment earlier in the week that was essentially insinuating that the Wii and the 360 were too pricey.
[SPEAKER_12]: The maker of the most expensive console...
[SPEAKER_12]: for the next gen says the Wii and the 360 are too pricey.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, he further clarified his statements later in the week, but this is what he said.
[SPEAKER_12]: Quote, sorry you didn't have the opportunity to buy a PlayStation 3 this year, but I'm sure it beats lining up in a queue for hours on end only to be told the store has sold out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: No doubt in response to the delays over in Europe and some of the other countries.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, yeah, too bad you didn't have that opportunity to do that now.
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't worry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Your opportunity is coming soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: This just goes, look, again, I'm sure the PlayStation 3 is going to be a just fine system.
[SPEAKER_12]: Give it a little, it's like a fine wine, it'll age just fine.
[SPEAKER_12]: But Sony executives, seriously, gag order.
[SPEAKER_12]: Seriously, Sony, if you're listening, you need all these people to STFU.
[SPEAKER_12]: You need to get a public figure that, you know, is not going to be a laughing stock of the internet, such as Reggie Miyamoto over there, or Major Nelson, Peter Moore over here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sony needs somebody like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'll tell you what, it's not this guy, it's not the giant enemy crab guy, who, as I hear, has suffered so much embarrassment from that, he doesn't do public appearances anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I feel bad for him, almost, in a way.
[SPEAKER_12]: His bosses probably made him do that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And Kaz.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I'm sure they, like, leave giant enemy crabs at his desk and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know that game's just never going to come out now.
[SPEAKER_12]: or if it does come out, that'll be on the big sticker.
[SPEAKER_12]: It should be one of those things like the movie Showgirls where at this point it should just be self-aware of the joke that it is now and just market itself as, hey, we're that historically accurate game with the crabs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe they could just say the game caught crabs.
[SPEAKER_11]: He goes to his doctor for a physical.
[SPEAKER_11]: I've got bad news for you.
[SPEAKER_11]: You have giant enemy crabs.
[SPEAKER_11]: Poor guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now when I play a PS3 title...
[SPEAKER_11]: I simply can't depend on having a single friends list so I'm going to go manage the master list which should have presence in every PS3 title and X-Fire will be a plugin that some publishers integrate into some games and some won't.
[SPEAKER_11]: That means gamers can't depend on finding their friends in one place.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he goes on talking about more other stuff and talking about how X-Fire is going to cost money because they're licensing it and stuff and what's that going to do with the whole service and the fact that we haven't really heard much about
[SPEAKER_11]: and their online service.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, so who knows?
[SPEAKER_12]: So some fair equal time type stories here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Microsoft's doing some of the smack talking too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe should be leaving the PR to folks like Major Nelson and maybe some of the underground communities, the huge Xbox fan communities out there, some of our other friendly podcasts such as Gamer Tag and XBL.
[SPEAKER_11]: But there is some other interesting stuff though.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is funny because as soon as they ran this, that of course someone had to come to Sony's defense and that they did.
[SPEAKER_11]: And actually, they were talking about some of the information and they also posted in their blog saying there's some bad information there responding to the blog post that I'll get to in a sec.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it was interesting to me in...
[SPEAKER_11]: X-Fire Friends List Online President Smed
[SPEAKER_06]: Welcome to Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: Eat this crayon.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Look, let's go from all these smack-talking executives to you guys smack-talking us in our mailbag.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: We haven't gotten a lot of hate mail recently, have we?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, that's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm glad you guys have been nice and polite.
[SPEAKER_12]: We appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can send us an email.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: And every week, Dark Sakura suits up.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com Send us more.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the first email actually comes from Orko4, basically saying that in Hickory, North Carolina, there was a restaurant called Tallywhackers, me bringing up how they should make peckers as a thing to Hooters, and that the owner wanted the waiters to be shirtless and wearing Speedos, but they couldn't for health violations, so they wore really tight-ass shorts and tank tops.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yeah, I remember you talking about the male Hooters a couple weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder why.
[SPEAKER_06]: and the last line says, keep up the great work and I can't wait to hear the Doctor Who website of the week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's not Doctor Who this week, so it's Torchwood.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a spin-off.
[SPEAKER_08]: I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Next comes from Mike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_06]: The other day I saw a Nintendo presentation on game trailers.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that how it really started off?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_12]: Suddenly it's that little fairy that follows you in The Legend of Zelda.
[SPEAKER_06]: Listen!
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey!
[SPEAKER_12]: Listen!
[SPEAKER_12]: That's how I want you all to open up your emails from now on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, listen!
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, to continue.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's said that the price points for the virtual console, 500, 700, and 1,000 points are actually worded as starting at points.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, does this mean that we could be paying $15 for a Nintendo 64 game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wanted to hear your thoughts.
[SPEAKER_11]: Possibly.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wouldn't be behind him.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what I was just thinking about, though?
[SPEAKER_12]: If Ocarina of Time does come to Virtual Console, why would I get that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I have the little GameCube disc that had it on there.
[SPEAKER_12]: It has a limited release, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought that Nintendo 64 was going to be $10.
[SPEAKER_12]: I thought it was $5 for NES, $8 for Super Nintendo, $10 for Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_12]: Another email from Michael.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is HeySky, Loki, and DarkSakura, and maybe Drew Nami, who is not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's in our chat room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stop that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop what?
[SPEAKER_12]: Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, Jamie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Rob, only you can see this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Loki can see it too, but it's aimed toward you.
[SPEAKER_12]: I see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that your IQ?
[SPEAKER_12]: One?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mail?
[SPEAKER_12]: Email?
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, I'd like to say that I love your show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: and I've been listening on the podcast stream for a year and a few months and I most recently listened live last week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Speaking of which, I was the one who called in and hung up Tasete Purim, I guess I said that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's Latin.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't take Latin, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think he's actually renamed himself in chat to just call me Mike.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we'll call him Mike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Mike.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I forgot to mute the live stream while using Skype.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oops.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, earlier on Xbox, what's up with me?
[SPEAKER_06]: On episode 203, sports games came up.
[SPEAKER_06]: Most of the hosts on OLR aren't sports games fans.
[SPEAKER_06]: You said that sports games are just a roster update.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, the same can be said about music games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, games like DDR have a few very marginal new innovations, but for the most part, the games are just the same damn thing with new music.
[SPEAKER_06]: And to some idiotic gamers, they just hear weird Japanese techno and they think it's the same damn thing with the same music and a new number after the title.
[SPEAKER_06]: While I disagree with both arguments, I think that both make a valid point.
[SPEAKER_06]: So here's my call to the game developers and producers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't make a new game until it's ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure, your game can have all the songs of players in the world, but don't put it out until it is better than its predecessor.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's exactly what they're doing at 3D Realms.
[SPEAKER_04]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: Duke Nukem Forever.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're making sure that it's ready.
[SPEAKER_11]: Is the email done?
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: This goes for all games, not just music or sports games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take the Halo franchise, for example.
[SPEAKER_06]: Halo 1, a masterpiece.
[SPEAKER_06]: Halo 2, an Unreal Tournament skin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't get me wrong, I play Halo 2 almost exclusively.
[SPEAKER_06]: Halo 2 has pushed out the door too quickly, and just for live experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: Halo 2 was an unsatisfying game that could have been even better than the original.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then the master of re-releasing a game, whether it needs to be or not.
[SPEAKER_06]: Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love Metal Slug.
[SPEAKER_06]: It rocks.
[SPEAKER_06]: but when it's been pushed toward me on every available medium with no new features it makes me never want to buy a Metal Slug game again even if it has every feature in the world I love Metal Slug anyway game developers need to realize something sure you release the sequel to a good game it sells well but what if you want to make it a trilogy is it accepted or is it looked on as milking the franchise it makes sense in the short term but in one of the worst options in the long run
[SPEAKER_06]: Soon gamers will get smart and realize they are being scammed by buying the same game every year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've been trying to tell this to anyone who will listen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sadly, I think it's too late.
[SPEAKER_06]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry if I'm sending you this email again.
[SPEAKER_06]: It said the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah, I didn't get the first one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, I thought it was a pretty clever comparison, the whole roster update versus the music games.
[SPEAKER_12]: But I think...
[SPEAKER_12]: For that, it really depends on what you're into.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, I don't hate sports games.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just recognize that that's not what I'm into.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I'm sure for most of them, maybe dance games isn't really what they're into.
[SPEAKER_12]: And so they wouldn't recognize the fact that the new dance games do go through interface upgrades and usually there's a new mode in them somewhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: And certainly the entire list of songs gets refreshed with
[SPEAKER_12]: and so on and so on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm not going to bore you to death with the comparisons.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's an interesting analogy, but I think us being fans of dance games, we don't see that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You or other sports games fans, you don't see the comparison.
[SPEAKER_12]: That either, that the rest of us just see the roster update or whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually, I think it's exactly the same thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: In fact, that neither of the games have, you know, very, you know, huge improvements.
[SPEAKER_11]: Granted, sports games go through, you know, graphical improvements and stuff and roster updates.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, this is even coming from people, you know, reviewing, you know, the brand new EA lineup or whatever that they aren't really adding anything new and it really just is a roster update.
[SPEAKER_11]: But, you know, that's something that they need to prove in both, you know, dance games and, you know,
[SPEAKER_11]: Sports Games, and probably a lot of other games.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, like, what, God of War 2?
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, that looks basically like kind of an update, you know, to God of War 1.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know, look at... Oh, a lot of games are like that nowadays, you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jeremy Todd 1 in our chat room has an interesting point.
[SPEAKER_12]: Roster updates don't really change the gameplay all too much.
[SPEAKER_12]: New music and music games do change gameplay a bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have to learn new steps and that sort to the new songs.
[SPEAKER_12]: You don't really change much for roster updates.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well,
[SPEAKER_12]: But, you know, even the sports games do get some new modes, you know, for their respective games just once in a while.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just like the dance games, you know.
[SPEAKER_12]: For instance, we know that in the new Xbox ones, we're going to have the non-stop mixes and things like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's my thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we also got another email from Rini.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it's a fairly long one, so just to sort of paraphrase a bit, it's going into...
[SPEAKER_06]: More innovation in the DDR series of games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I'm going to start from here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, I want to read the first one just because it was really nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Good day to OLR and happy belated episode 203.
[SPEAKER_06]: May you have another 396 more at this point and beyond.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was really sweet.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So to continue on toward the middle part of this letter, there was some discussion going on in the Aaron in Japan and DDR UK forums that started to see what users had in mind
[SPEAKER_06]: for some realistic and reasonable feature additions that can be added to DDR.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll try to make things brisk with a few suggestions made by the community.
[SPEAKER_06]: Preview background mode and steps at the song wheel and maybe at the modifier screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Challenge steps for every song in the sense that they would not only give something for expert players but would also bring out the full potential of the song according to Konami so that we don't have the boring as hell licenses from the arcade supernova that has gaps of nothing for no reason.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wave Break, 0.25 and half speed, why hasn't Konami put these in?
[SPEAKER_06]: If Vulture Mix 3 allows 0.5 speed and phantom modifiers, then why can't the PS2 versions have them?
[SPEAKER_06]: Custom courses set on a home version can be used at the arcade with the ability to include any song available on the arcade machine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also should have a maximum of 4 songs on non-stop mode to allow modifiers and a max of 5 songs on challenge mode that disallows modifiers for these courses.
[SPEAKER_06]: Trade edit data online and at the arcade.
[SPEAKER_06]: Submit arcade score data online through a home version by way of memory card.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are some good suggestions.
[SPEAKER_12]: They are, you know, they are good suggestions and certainly we've thought, you know, through the show, many years we've been doing the show, a lot of you guys when you've called in said very similar things.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: I would think that maybe we're going to get another arcade release.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think either way it's inevitable we're going to see Supernova 2 or something like that next year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Because with the leftover songs that you didn't get from the arcade this year at least.
[SPEAKER_06]: I am going to put this one up on our site, but there is a last paragraph on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And by the way, the emails that I post are going to be on the live show discussion area on our forums.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well...
[SPEAKER_12]: Fake Boobs in Playboy OLR's enemy, G4, is finally mostly gone Yes, I know the words G4 are banned from OLR but for now we might not need to talk about them much anymore
[SPEAKER_12]: This is all I'm going to say on this because you're right, those words are banned from this network.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think a lot of people are saying it's definitely the doom and gloom of the network.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's more the doom and gloom of the network as a gaming network.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: That channel has not been a gaming channel for the past 18 months.
[SPEAKER_12]: Where have you been?
[SPEAKER_12]: This is still not news.
[SPEAKER_12]: So what they're doing a corporate restructuring around there.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not going to save them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Flush that shit down the toilet and be done with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a quote on here, though, that I knew it from the get-go.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do agree with the vision.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is actually a quote from the Ian Stile chief, Ted Harbert.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do agree with the vision of going after young men more than going after gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gaming has been demonstrated as being too narrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Narrow my ass!
[SPEAKER_06]: There are a lot of gamers out there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Text email, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just more... No offense to the men listening and the men in the room, but stupid men.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway.
Well.
[SPEAKER_06]: I didn't mean you guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys are fairly liberated in your mental states, and so are our listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kisses.
[SPEAKER_12]: Is that all the email?
[SPEAKER_12]: No!
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, well then get to the next one.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're out of time here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, my voice is running out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_06]: This, by the way, comes from Kenji.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I just picked up Clubhouse Games for the DS, and I cannot emphasize this enough.
[SPEAKER_06]: It is definitely a must-buy if you've got a hookup to the Wi-Fi connection.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though the bowling physics are awful, you can't go all in, and you can bet yourself out of a negative chip score.
[SPEAKER_06]: Playing 9-ball is similar to playing the game underwater or in space, take your pick.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can't deny the infinite replayability of this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, you can pick to chat via Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_06]: It can only be, however, on matches with your friends.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, of course, you can pick to via local wireless play and chat with your present messages on WorldFi Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, DMN lied to us last week?
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course, he had the game before most people.
[SPEAKER_12]: He had the game before most people, so he probably didn't have friends on Wi-Fi yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_11]: That makes me want to buy the game, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why?
[SPEAKER_11]: Dirty Wi-Fi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Dirty Wi-Fi chat?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, that would be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway...
[SPEAKER_06]: It is because of the awesomeness of this game that I come to you with a request, nay, a favor.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wanted to make an OLR Clubhouse Games Night where we all exchange friend codes, make a date and time, and basically play the night away.
[SPEAKER_06]: Perhaps you'd all like to participate, you being Jamie, Skye, and Loki, and you also being the rest of the people listening.
[SPEAKER_06]: At long last, Picto-chatting Drop 4 Biatch can become a reality, but only with your help.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've left a post in the forums for anyone who's interested.
[SPEAKER_06]: As always, love the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kenji.
[SPEAKER_12]: Just so you know, I did see that post earlier in the week, and I actually just moved it to the OL Army forums because it's kind of fit a little more with that because we try to create teams in certain games that will follow the cardinal rule of the OL Army is don't be a dick.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we just want people to join up that just want to have fun and not try to have that elitist attitude or like, you know, my plus four sword can beat your plus two sword.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_12]: Get in the game and have fun with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Put your plus four sword in your pants.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's exactly right.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I actually moved that post over to the OL Army and I posted my code there.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you want to add, that would be cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: And certainly we could set up a night for gaming.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe it could be a tie-in with one of the live shows that we do during the week because a lot of people don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: There are shows we do on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: We don't podcast because we like to be a live radio network.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura has her thing on Tuesdays and I have a show on Wednesdays and there may be more shows coming soon.
[SPEAKER_12]: We know Loki's got something in the works and there's something else I'm trying to get on board.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also coming from GS191, we got a really long email but I thought it was very cool and have posted it on that thread that I mentioned prior on there so I'd
[SPEAKER_06]: You'd love to get some discussion started up on that.
[SPEAKER_06]: The other emails that I was going to post up to you will be coming.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's just been, like I said, I've had a sinus infection the last week, so I haven't really done much of anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excuses, excuses.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Would you like the sinus infection?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would love to see you on erythromycin.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, and I would really love to see you on erythromycin.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just, you know, he who shall not be named.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else for emails?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_12]: God damn, we got a lot of emails this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: They love us.
[SPEAKER_06]: One more.
[SPEAKER_12]: Last email, we gotta keep moving.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is the one that came on through Myspace.
[SPEAKER_12]: Ah, okay, yes, I remember this one.
[SPEAKER_12]: This is a Myspace message.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gally from Breakdown Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, Gally here from the Breakdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a big fan of the show and you guys rock soars big time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry I didn't send this to your mailbag, but I think I'm being yelled at by the boss right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Damn the man.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, with all this talk of the Wii 60 going down, do you guys think it's a smart move on a personal level?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you guys already have 360s, but try and look at it from the perspective of a gamer who has neither yet?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think it would be a wise move to do the Wii 60, stick with one of the two, or is the last alternative, which I highly doubt because of Sakura's crayon-eating references, holding out for the PS3?
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: But if you are not rich and you only have the choice, you know, do I want to get a PS3 or do I want to do the Wii 60 thing?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or hell, can I really only pick one of these?
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, you really have to consider what games do you want to play.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I think especially right now between Wii and Xbox 360, there's vastly different games available on the two systems.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you really have to ask yourself, am I wanting to do the wavy controller, Elebits, Zelda, WarioWare type of game?
[SPEAKER_12]: or do I want to get online and play Gears of War and soon Halo 3 and maybe some games like Enchanted Arms or NFL, NBA type games that are available on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: You really have to consider.
[SPEAKER_12]: And then the way PlayStation 3 works into it is that even though a lot of games that we're hearing are kind of the same things we saw on Xbox 360, i.e.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oblivion and so on, they are going to have their own games eventually that stand out.
[SPEAKER_12]: My personal mindset is that you don't need to get a PlayStation 3 right out the gate, but I say that because for me, there's no games on this yet that I have to have.
[SPEAKER_12]: A year from now, I'm probably going to feel a lot differently.
[SPEAKER_12]: By the time Final Fantasy XIII, Metal Gear Solid 4 start hitting the market, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm probably going to be Sony fanboy all over again.
[SPEAKER_12]: But as far as the launch goes, I'm not really sold.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if you think you're going to have some money now and then more money in a year and PlayStation 3 doesn't have the lineup for you right now, do what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Buy the Wii now so you have your Wii 6 because I bought the Xbox 360 six months ago so it's spaced out enough where this isn't a huge financial impact.
[SPEAKER_12]: Buy the Wii when it comes out and then buy the PlayStation 3 later down the line.
[SPEAKER_12]: but you know again it's up to you and what games you want to play and there's no real clear answer we can give we can only tell you based on what we play but there's going to be so many fanboys that say no you have to have one of these on launch because you have to have Lair and Warhawk and Six Axes for Life and yada yada yada but it's all about what you want well from my perspective I'm getting them all anyway so I'd say if you can get them all get them all that way you're not limited
[SPEAKER_12]: Actdeft says I've said it before and I'll say it again I'll get a 360 just to play Uno you might be being sarcastic but you're really wasting your time if that's all you want because you can play it for free on Zone MSN or hell Clubhouse Games has something just like it so if now you must have strip Uno with the webcam well I suppose the 360 is the only place you can do that I don't know Rama says PlayStation 3 will be bringing it back to the store after it breaks in 20 minutes hey you know what
[SPEAKER_12]: That's something to be said, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe you don't want to get a first-generation worth of console.
[SPEAKER_12]: I learned my lesson with the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go back and listen to some episodes around February when I bought my Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_12]: The damn thing broke when I bought it, and I was pissed.
[SPEAKER_12]: And I was going to go torch down Microsoft, but since then they fixed it for free, and I've been a happy boy.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did also want to make an announcement, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_06]: For Pump Up the Volume, actually, this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your Tuesday show, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_06]: There will be a delay on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It will be starting around 7.30 to 8 this week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just wanted to go ahead and make a mention that I am doing it.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: So come listen to the other live programming on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: All done with the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Moving on to more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a movie called 8-Bit under development.
[SPEAKER_12]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_12]: According to VH1's Game Break, quote, this movie is about how games affect our culture, how the genre crosses the culture to influence music, art, and the way we think.
[SPEAKER_12]: In 8-bit, artists invade the online shooter Counter-Strike to add messages of peace on walls with paintball guns.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_12]: It's kind of weird that I've never heard of any of this stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I mean, I've heard of the music, certainly.
[SPEAKER_12]: We know a lot of those bands, but I haven't heard of any of those other art projects, so that might be worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've heard the Game Boy one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, yeah, yeah, the Game Boy music one, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: We've also had bands that use the type of... I'm talking about like the Counter-Strike, Grandpa and the Fire thing, and the whole... those sort of things.
[SPEAKER_12]: I've never heard of that before.
[SPEAKER_12]: That might be interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, shooting paintballs into a wall does not make for a winning team.
[SPEAKER_12]: But when it's, you know, it's an interesting kind of art form when it's done in a game, huh?
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_11]: It's very unique.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it's also kind of neat, and it's one of the rumors that's going to be coming soon, and you might actually be able to watch 8-Bit on this, that Microsoft might be adding Xvid and DivX support to the 360 in the fall dashboard update.
[SPEAKER_11]: Now, no idea whether it's true or not, but the news actually comes from
[SPEAKER_11]: A developers conference that was going on actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some Dutch colleagues from xlife.nl were invited to a training session for shop employees and basically kind of just talking a little bit about technology and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: And one of the questions that was asked basically at the event, they had a talk with the host and asked him whether there's going to be DivX or Xvid support in the future or other codecs.
[SPEAKER_11]: And he said that it was something that Microsoft was working hard to implement and a firmware update is expected within two months.
[SPEAKER_11]: So we'll have to see.
[SPEAKER_11]: That might be rumor for now.
[SPEAKER_11]: But it would make sense if they supported something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know if they will, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Something that's not a rumor is a new multiplayer mode for Red Steel is going to be called Killer Mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a special multiplayer setup, so you'll use your mission brief via the speaker in the Wiimote.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, this is a B.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I was hearing something about this, that, like, basically, like, I think the Wiimote is supposed to ring, and so you put it up to your ear, and it'll actually whisper, like, you know, This is Snake.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, you need, no, it says something like, you need to kill player four and do not kill the other players, or something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Like, it gives you your mission in a little speaker so the other people don't know what your mission is.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is damn innovative, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_12]: That's pretty fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's innovation.
[SPEAKER_12]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: XBOX LIVE ARCADE
[SPEAKER_11]: And this, I think, is going to be kind of very similar to that.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're going to be talking a little bit more, I think, about releasing games.
[SPEAKER_11]: Like, you know, you see some of the stuff, not necessarily old games on Xbox Live Arcade, but newer games that are small, maybe for that kind of setup.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I don't see this really replacing the current distribution we have now.
[SPEAKER_12]: But it's interesting because, you know, you've heard a lot of talk about this whole digital distribution moving on into the next gaming area, especially on PlayStation 3 as well.
[SPEAKER_12]: There's a quote here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me read this real fast.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this is from, I believe this is from Nintendo themselves.
[SPEAKER_12]: Beginning in Spring 2007, Nintendo will apparently begin the Wii Compact Software line of games which will allow players to download certain Wii titles to their console rather than purchasing a disc.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pricing and storage details, as well as what software will be made available, not provided.
[SPEAKER_11]: and New Cables and Whatnot.
[SPEAKER_11]: So anyways, there's some interesting stuff also coming out about the Wii, and I know one of the stories that was run during the week when talking about how Sunlight was causing a problem with the Wii remotes where it was interfering with the IR field that the actual receiver and emitters were putting out.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, apparently Nintendo has commented on that, and they said that it's not a major issue.
[SPEAKER_11]: It says, our testing thus far shows no great risk of light interference while playing a game that relies on the pointer and sensor bar.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so, you know, granted, that's going to be about as much interference as having, you know, bright light shining on your TV or something like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: That won't really interfere with it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm, you know, kind of on the fence with this.
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess we'll have to see when it comes out.
[SPEAKER_11]: But you know what, though?
[SPEAKER_11]: If there's anything to be learned from this, especially from the eye toy and from the Xbox Live Vision camera, my house is always too dark.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I don't think too much light is ever going to be a problem.
[SPEAKER_12]: JeremyTub1 in chat says, Who gives a shit if sunlight affects it?
[SPEAKER_12]: You aren't playing outside.
[SPEAKER_12]: If it's shining through a window, close the freaking blinds.
[SPEAKER_12]: Minini283 says, Everyone plays games in their basements anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I play in my living room.
[SPEAKER_06]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it was a joke about nerds there.
[SPEAKER_06]: This website of the week was actually one given to me by our dear friend and listener, Rob with two B's.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll spell it out.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's theca.com, which is for the Entertainment Consumers Association.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Entertainment Consumers Association is a non-profit membership organization established to serve the needs of those who play computer and video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Formed in 2006, the ECA is an advocacy organization for consumers of interactive entertainment.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can actually sign up for their site.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have things to win.
[SPEAKER_06]: They also have lots of information.
[SPEAKER_06]: Links to game politics, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seems that there's a little bit of an affiliation there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just lots of really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: FAQs, news, just things that are going on as far as our legal rights as gamers.
[SPEAKER_06]: In fact, there's another blurb on here.
[SPEAKER_06]: It says, Today, more than ever before, gamers need to stand together to defend against political activity that is threatening the creation and publishing of video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: On behalf of the gaming community, the ECA lobbies legislators directly as well as launching grassroots digital initiatives to preserve our rights as gamers.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was that link again?
[SPEAKER_06]: It's T-H-E-E-C-A dot com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, check it out boys and girls.
[SPEAKER_06]: Definitely, I'll be linking it in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, well, GameTap is a service we've mentioned a few times on this show, and it's, you know, still getting a little steam, a few more subscribers every now and then.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they have launched a 500-player beta of Uru Live, which you might know also as the Myst Online Project.
[SPEAKER_12]: And this is a pretty big deal, because what happened is the project was abandoned, and then GameTap has kind of picked it up and ran with it, so it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Gay Gamer recently ran a report on this, and they said this, quote, GameTap has improved the game with new sound support and a new physics engine that makes it much easier and faster to interact with others, something that bogged down the original game.
[SPEAKER_12]: And if things go as planned, Uru Live may begin to incorporate content generated by its incredibly creative player community.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I hope they keep doing more stuff like that and supporting smaller games and maybe helping in
[SPEAKER_11]: Some PC games get published and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think what's kind of neat about that too is that you're paying essentially the GameTap fee for access to all this.
[SPEAKER_12]: So if they get more MMOs, it's kind of like you're paying one fee for all these MMOs.
[SPEAKER_12]: And GameTap is relatively cheap.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's the same price they're charging for Phantasy Star Universe.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't want to sound like a commercial because I've already been accused of being on their payroll.
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually pay the $10 a month for GameTap, which is sad because I rarely ever use it because I'm just so
[SPEAKER_12]: I check it out like once every other week or so to see what's new.
[SPEAKER_12]: But this is something I definitely will check out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm very curious.
[SPEAKER_12]: Obviously I can't get into beta, but when it's released.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, this week Unfettered Blather, a blogging site, actually ran a top ten list of the top ten things about next gen that are annoying.
[SPEAKER_11]: So let's go off the list here.
[SPEAKER_11]: The big highlights, of course, number one,
[SPEAKER_11]: Sony's alternate reality.
[SPEAKER_11]: No matter how you spin it, we just want a game console first.
[SPEAKER_11]: Go push your format war somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_11]: Number two, dual price skew nonsense with the new next-gen console.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what, though?
[SPEAKER_12]: If you read those stories about people who are pre-ordering the PS3, some of them were doing it because it's a cheap Blu-ray player.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know if number one has as much validity as people think.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: Cost between consoles and computers vanishing.
[SPEAKER_11]: $60 games, expensive peripherals, consoles being released at $600 price points.
[SPEAKER_11]: Chasing Nintendo says you just can't ignore the changes in industry, but sure fun watching these two megacorporations scramble to keep up with Nintendo's ideas.
[SPEAKER_11]: And other fun stuff, they're also on there.
[SPEAKER_11]: Mainly repeating the $60 game thing, and name changes, like they're saying the Revolution was a better name, and
[SPEAKER_12]: That $60 game thing should have been number one.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the most annoying, if anything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_11]: $60 would have made my list.
[SPEAKER_12]: We haven't really seen that whole Gran Turismo thing, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't think we've really seen what exactly is going to come of that.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_11]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, if you have more annoying things, you could maybe write this guy and maybe he'll do an extended list in the future.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, in other news, in regards to, you know, we had brought up there was going to be a Castlevania movie, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's going to be written by Warren Ellis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty cool, huh?
[SPEAKER_06]: But also, it is going to be direct-to-DVD.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: Direct-to-DVD, that's not good.
[SPEAKER_06]: There have been some good things put direct to DVD.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, it kind of seems to be one place the movie industry is going.
[SPEAKER_12]: You have all these god-awful sequels going direct to DVD.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why not, you know, something kind of, you know, new, unique?
[SPEAKER_12]: Unless you saw Van Helsing, which was kind of Castlevania the movie in a way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not really, just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, at any rate, there's a quote on here saying, for an entity currently known only as Project 51's productions, a production blog will follow on the official site.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: We just keep our eyes on it to see what happens.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, I'll rent it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll put it in my Netflix queue.
[SPEAKER_06]: But having him write it, that's like fangasm right there.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's supposed to be the... By the way, it is the animated Castlevania thing that we were talking about before.
[SPEAKER_11]: So animated movie, that wouldn't be too bad, I guess.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is not live action.
[SPEAKER_11]: After all, they are making BloodRayne 2.
[SPEAKER_11]: I mean, God, do we really need more video game movies like that?
[SPEAKER_11]: But I don't know.
[SPEAKER_11]: It should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: He worked on, he basically was a comic writer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did some work for, I actually did remember that he did work for Excalibur because I've read Excalibur from its beginning incarnation on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did DV8, which was a Gen 13 spinoff, Stormwatch, The Authority, did some stuff for Vertigo, Transmetropolitan was one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also, did, was working on the Counter-X line of titles for Marvel.
[SPEAKER_06]: X-Men, X-Force, Avatar Comics, Homage Comics, South Park
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: I do want to point out, I watched this week's episode of South Park, and for those folks that heard my review of the WoW episode of South Park last week, that satire I said was missing, that was in this week's episode.
[SPEAKER_12]: This week's episode of South Park was freaking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_12]: I laughed my ass off.
[SPEAKER_12]: I just have a fucked up sense of humor.
[SPEAKER_12]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_11]: Don't you think that they probably did that stuff on purpose, or just didn't really give a crap?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm pretty sure they did.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, bathroom.
[SPEAKER_11]: So then there's another wonderful rumor going around the interweb this week.
[SPEAKER_11]: That would be that the sword featured in the actual episode of South Park was a real sword.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sword of the 1000 Truths is supposed to be winnable in the arena matches in Burning Crusade.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some people think that it's an obvious Photoshop, but who knows?
[SPEAKER_11]: I guess we'll see when Burning Crusade hits stores.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's kind of interesting, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: It actually wouldn't surprise me if that were true.
[SPEAKER_12]: I actually don't think that's a fanboy thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think that could actually be true because that episode of South Park felt like such this huge infomercial.
[SPEAKER_12]: It would be the perfect tie-in.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, it was funny, though, because some of the stats were a little bit different from the actual cartoon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course, it says 197 to 296 damage, 88 damage per second, plus 21 stamina.
[SPEAKER_11]: Requires level 70.
[SPEAKER_11]: It says equip improves hit rating by 8, improves critical strike rating by 14.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why don't you go post that on Wikipedia, you damn nerd?
[SPEAKER_11]: It doesn't match what was in the show.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, they already posted that on Wikipedia.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I see.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, that'd be interesting to see if that's going to actually be coming out.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Jeremy Todd 1 in chat says, looks like those WoW nerds during the correcting needs a clue.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got a clue.
[SPEAKER_12]: I got a raging clue.
[SPEAKER_12]: My clue is over there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let's go there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my, clue goo.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's a raging clue.
[SPEAKER_12]: I get it.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's a joke about the South Park from this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good job, listeners.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: You are on an internet radio program about video games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're black.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_06]: I calls them as I sees them, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, you remember my allusion to the Phantom earlier in Part A?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pay attention, listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was giving foreshadowing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they actually are starting to sell something for Phantom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't that funny?
[SPEAKER_06]: They have been showing off this thing called the Phantom Wireless Lapboard and Phantom Wireless Laser Mouse.
[SPEAKER_06]: The two together are basically just a way to sit on your ass and browse the internet with a keyboard.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like Web TV, only with a swivel keyboard thing and a piece of hard plastic underneath it.
[SPEAKER_12]: So is this the next generation of gaming?
[SPEAKER_06]: My ass.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like I said, Web TV, we've had this shit before.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I...
[SPEAKER_06]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_12]: The Get Well Gamers Foundation, it's another nice charity that was posted about a little bit earlier this week on GayGamer.net, quote,
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_12]: and this is the pretty cool thing is that you can actually donate your old games.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, you know, games you might think are old and outdated and you're never going to play anymore, like instead of throwing a Nintendo 64 in the garbage, you could donate it to a charity like this.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey, listen, if you've watched fucking Mind Mancia, you would know that nobody wants a Nintendo 64 anymore.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would just like to point out, in this picture, on this site...
[SPEAKER_12]: There is a child, a sick child, you're playing a Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_12]: Haven't he suffered enough?
[SPEAKER_12]: You heartless bastard.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, hey, I still love Pokemon Snap.
[SPEAKER_06]: Me too.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Mario 64 is the shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: I also threw away a PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I've done that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a stack of five of them in my back room.
[SPEAKER_06]: You heartless both of you.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't work.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_12]: If it's broken, then it's broken.
[SPEAKER_06]: One of our old ones, it will still sort of work.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to tilt it sideways at a 45 degree angle for it to read the discs right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe I'll donate mine to this charity.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't really play my Nintendo 64.
[SPEAKER_12]: My Nintendo 64 was broken.
[SPEAKER_12]: It was all blurry and the polygons were simple.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, now you're making it up.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now you're just making stuff up.
[SPEAKER_06]: If I'm going to play Nintendo 64, I'll play my DS.
[SPEAKER_12]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyway, just admit you're a bad person and get to the next story.
[SPEAKER_12]: I am a bad person, and I have no problems with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're a bad, bad man.
[SPEAKER_11]: Listen, if it comes, I'm getting my Wii, and I ain't donating shit.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my Wii.
[SPEAKER_11]: They're gonna, whatever, I'm not gonna say anymore.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're gonna get cancer.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just what's gonna happen.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's karma.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're gonna die in a fire.
[SPEAKER_11]: You know you really want a 64DD?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think we really need to go to the next story at this point.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, look, we've got one foot in hell, so let's please go to the next story.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, because in hell, if you throw water on the ground, you're going to get steam.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's my transition, because steam is getting a lot more cool games coming to it.
[SPEAKER_11]: And one of those games is a fan favorite, Psychonauts, and that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_11]: and, of course, other things that you're going to be seeing on Steam other than Psychonauts.
[SPEAKER_11]: And Psychonauts, by the way, is just going to be about $20.
[SPEAKER_11]: You're also going to see such wonderful games like Call of Duty 2, as well as some other Activision titles, Call of Duty, Call of Duty United Offensive, and Gun.
[SPEAKER_11]: Those are also going to be coming, as well as the brand new game that will also be coming to Xbox Live Arcade someday.
[SPEAKER_11]: Rebel Blitz is also making its way.
[SPEAKER_11]: So...
[SPEAKER_11]: Lots of fun stuff for Steam.
[SPEAKER_06]: They should do a game called Call of Booty.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: They have World of Porncraft.
[SPEAKER_12]: They should definitely have Call of Booty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, speaking of World of... You know what?
[SPEAKER_12]: I should... Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: I have this great entrepreneur idea here.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to share with the entire internet.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_12]: Patent pending.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's mine.
[SPEAKER_12]: Trademarked.
[SPEAKER_12]: You steal this, I sue you.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, here it is.
[SPEAKER_12]: Make a porn company that does nothing but video game tie-ins like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think there's an audience out there for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: And we could do both gay, straight, lesbo, whatever, everything.
[SPEAKER_12]: Trisexual, it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_12]: Furries, sure, we'll find something for you guys too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Pokemon or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe like Banjo-Kazooie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: Porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: FinalFuckX, who doesn't remember that one?
[SPEAKER_12]: That was a great Japanese import.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, we need some good domestically made... Really good cosplay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bring me your whores and your sluts and let's put them in some video game porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll make them stars and make a lot of money in the process.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, strippers are people too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Naked people.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, next story, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Back to the world of SomethingCraft...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, it's the chat room.
[SPEAKER_12]: Finish your story, then I'll go back.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, just tell me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sailor Moon and the Seven Balls.
[SPEAKER_06]: I saw that at a store last week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now they're going off on all these movies that we could make here.
[SPEAKER_12]: We have DMN says Super Princess Penis.
[SPEAKER_12]: DMN says Conker's Bad Furry Day.
[SPEAKER_12]: Mantic says Crash Bandicunt, DMN says Elite Beat Off Agents, and Bandit says simply Paris Hilton's Gem Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's basically porn anyway.
[SPEAKER_12]: You guys are awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, back to my story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Dirty-minded listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Chrome Horse.
[SPEAKER_09]: Good one, Travis.
[SPEAKER_06]: Travis, yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: No more porn, no more porn, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: They finished the first step of the character transfer and paid everything on the credit card.
[SPEAKER_06]: They said it would take 12 hours to move it.
[SPEAKER_06]: They checked again, 12 hours again, 12 hours later, they checked again, and still another 12 hours.
[SPEAKER_06]: And people on the forums were bitching up a storm.
[SPEAKER_06]: And actually, there was a...
[SPEAKER_06]: They were basically putting the same old cut-and-paste response on the forum.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blah, blah, blah, this is normal, working as intended, my butt.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, that type of thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they said no one could resolve it by working with their customer service.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was suggested canceling the transfer and starting again, and no one else had any luck with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: and it was redoing it over and over and over.
[SPEAKER_12]: So they encouraged them to retry it, yet it was withdrawing 20 euros every time.
[SPEAKER_06]: It looks like it was retrying it on its own.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it wasn't charging credit cards, like I said, but it was charging debit accounts and draining people's bank accounts.
[SPEAKER_06]: So Blizzard hasn't...
[SPEAKER_06]: They said that it hasn't worked for about eight days and Blizzard finally came out and said something about it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But there has not been a statement issued by Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_06]: There hasn't been an ETA as to when they're going to get that fixed.
[SPEAKER_12]: As I understand it, though, this is only screwing over the Euro banks, not American transfers.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's what I'm seeing right here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: But they can't just be so closed-mouthed about this.
[SPEAKER_06]: They have to be
[SPEAKER_06]: They are going to lose so much freaking business.
[SPEAKER_06]: On top of that, there's any type of number of suits are going to come up over just how much money they've taken from these bank accounts.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've really screwed themselves with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you see it happening, you stop the service.
[SPEAKER_06]: You do it right then.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, would you watch a movie called Slut Caliber 3?
[SPEAKER_12]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_12]: Blackboy says Super Monkey Ball, touch and roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: That sounds fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: I thought that was a game.
[SPEAKER_12]: Super Monkey Ball, touch and roll.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but it could be a porn, too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, I promised we wouldn't do any more of the porn.
[SPEAKER_12]: But some of them are just so damn funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: What can I say?
[SPEAKER_12]: Skype line's open.
[SPEAKER_12]: You can call us.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go to orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_12]: Click on Interact With Us.
[SPEAKER_12]: The username is OrangeloungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or you can pick up the telephone and call 916-226-9067.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, in the meantime, some quick last minute stories, some things to squeeze in there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did want to mention this.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you're a fan of the game In the Groove, you can now, this latest update they've done on the machine, you can do your own custom MP3s and steps.
[SPEAKER_12]: So basically now you have, In the Groove has basically come out and legitimized itself as Step Mania in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's only one problem though.
[SPEAKER_11]: What are they going to do for audio licensing?
[SPEAKER_11]: Since I'm sure they didn't address that, since the game is not, you know, these are not licensed on the machine.
[SPEAKER_11]: And usually the machine will cover the licensing for the songs that are in the game.
[SPEAKER_11]: But now that place, say if the RIA comes in and hears someone playing, you know, Christina Aguilera or something like that on the machine, they could sue them.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sorry, chat room is correcting me and saying it's actually OGG files.
[SPEAKER_12]: We are starting to get some calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll come back to this in a minute.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, this is Sephiroth1215 here.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Sephiroth1215 here.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm pretty much fresh off of Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_12]: How was Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_12]: Tell us a little bit about this.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, the first time you get in there, it looks kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's nice and big.
[SPEAKER_01]: So much to see, but it's really not that great this year.
[SPEAKER_12]: Really?
[SPEAKER_12]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_01]: You had some good things.
[SPEAKER_01]: You had some...
[SPEAKER_01]: Maybe a few gaming booths, depending on what you like, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: Now, Digital Life is not exclusively a gaming show, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: There's lots of stuff there.
[SPEAKER_01]: No, there's plenty of stuff there.
[SPEAKER_01]: Probably a lot of the space, though, was from MLG and another gaming league of some sort.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was Sony the best booth there?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Sony's booth was kind of small.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to mention it was right next to Microsoft's booth.
[SPEAKER_01]: Really?
[SPEAKER_01]: Did you get your hands on the plate?
[SPEAKER_01]: I got to play the PS3.
[SPEAKER_01]: And?
[SPEAKER_01]: And it played very well from what I got to see.
[SPEAKER_01]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played a little bit of Resistance.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, that's something they didn't have at E3, I don't think, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: What did you think of it?
[SPEAKER_01]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was more so looking at the graphics and the movements of the characters...
[SPEAKER_01]: More so than the gameplay, though.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did this sell you on the game?
[SPEAKER_12]: Or on the system, I should say?
[SPEAKER_01]: It proved to me that the system can be more solid than I originally thought because I thought maybe everything was going to be kind of blocky or it wasn't... I don't know how to explain it, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I guess just to compare, I got to play the Wii a bit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played Elebits, and oddly enough, there were problems playing that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, what kind of problems?
[SPEAKER_01]: The controls were off.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, you had to stay to the left, and it had the same kind of problem that Sonic did, where you go a little bit, and the cursor goes far off into the screen.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was it just maybe miscalibrated?
[SPEAKER_01]: It might have been.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm not quite sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: It was only a demo of the game, so it could change later.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to mention the loading time was way over a minute just to even start the demo.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wow, so that's interesting.
[SPEAKER_12]: Kind of a different reaction than we heard from E3 where everybody was buzzing about the Wii and not so buzzing about the PS3.
[SPEAKER_12]: What do you think was the best thing you saw at Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_01]: Honestly, the best thing at Digital Life was the DDR booth, which is where I was working all weekend.
[SPEAKER_12]: What was there?
[SPEAKER_12]: What was at the DDR booth that made it so great?
[SPEAKER_01]: There's tournaments going on all weekend long.
[SPEAKER_01]: Not to mention we were the only booth that had the best giveaways.
[SPEAKER_12]: What kind of stuff was being given?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that's right, because they do like the $1,000 tournament there or something, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Like big, big money.
[SPEAKER_01]: Overall, it was about over $8,000 worth of prize money and prizes.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm kind of pissed I missed New York City by a week.
[SPEAKER_12]: I would have loved to have been there.
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, honestly, it's all right because...
[SPEAKER_01]: From what I hear they're having talks about, it's not completely official yet, so you can't take my word on it, is next year, because there's no more Big E3, there's also going to be a Digital Life in LA.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: We might have to check that out.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to be at Nintendo World Store Saturday at noon?
[SPEAKER_12]: Because I'm going to be there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not to put you on the spot or anything, but if you're not there, I'm going to cry.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: I might have some CDs.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't know you were going to be there Saturday.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, did you not hear the part A?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I'm going to be there Saturday at noon.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'll be there.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, we'll see you then.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anything else you want to say for the listeners?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, not really.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll go to some more calls.
[SPEAKER_12]: Glad to hear you had a good time at Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_12]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_01]: You too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_12]: Legend of Zaku
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm going to let you in on a little radio secret here, okay?
[SPEAKER_12]: Sometimes we pick up the calls a little bit before I'm ready to acknowledge that you're actually on the line just because it makes for a smoother transition that way.
[SPEAKER_12]: So until we say, Orange Lounge Radio, who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Shh, be quiet.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Saku, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yo, I was also there too, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was also at Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_12]: I had a feeling you'd have something to say on Digital Life.
[SPEAKER_02]: As a matter of fact, I competed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I competed in freestyle on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_02]: And how was it?
[SPEAKER_02]: What I'm about to post right now in the chat room is a link to the actual, to my routine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Granted, it was a bad routine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, you get the get it joke right there.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hold on, I'm actually looking at it right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was a bad routine.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're looking at the screen!
[SPEAKER_12]: How long did you practice this?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was totally unprepared for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: This was an improv all the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: I was like, yeah, you got some cool alarm movements there, but yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Saku, you're looking at the screen too much, buddy.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I know, but it's alright though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wouldn't care less right now because I had a good time and I have no regrets for that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you see somebody left you a comment to go dance on some landmines?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, the internet's mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: I also played the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, what did you think of the Wii?
[SPEAKER_02]: On Elebits, definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was hot.
[SPEAKER_02]: You liked Elebits?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, it was fun for the fact that you could actually aim and move stuff around.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't miscalibrated for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, it was a little jerky, but I had to move a little bit back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because when I moved up closer, it wasn't even engaging.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the more further away I was from the screen, the more better the controls were.
[SPEAKER_02]: What about PS3?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did you get your little hands on the PS3?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, the lines were pretty long for that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I managed to play Guitar Hero 2 as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: What did you think of that?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's kind of like the same thing, it just has more difficulties.
[SPEAKER_02]: You can select characters and guitars.
[SPEAKER_12]: Here's another last minute story involving Guitar Hero 2 now that you brought it up.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, about the controller.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, hey, who's hosting this show?
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, man.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry about spilling the beans, as you were.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, you might as well finish your thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: Why don't you go, Zaku, why don't you play OLR Reporter here and tell us this story about Guitar Hero 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: From what's being said is that the demo version is not allowing you to play third-party controllers.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, in other words, this company that essentially made its name on making third-party controllers has locked third-party controllers out of its next game.
[SPEAKER_12]: According to the demo, if the demo is any indication.
[SPEAKER_02]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right now I've got to go, but I'll let you know
[SPEAKER_02]: I have some free swag for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_02]: What's going on?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why do you have to go so fast?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nah, I got some stuff to take care of.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll let you know if any free swag helps.
[SPEAKER_02]: The cops are there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, Zaku, go tell the cops we said hi.
[SPEAKER_11]: Worst call ever.
[SPEAKER_11]: This is the part in Mr. Robinson's neighborhood that we learn about the word of the day.
[SPEAKER_11]: The word of the day is fire escape.
[SPEAKER_11]: Kids, do you know what a fire escape is?
[SPEAKER_11]: Cabbage patch, kid.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lodge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, Ocean.
[SPEAKER_12]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_12]: All the New York City listeners are trying to hammer like mad to get through tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Let me guess.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you go to Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I did, and you did say last week you want all the New York callers to call in, so we did.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: How was Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yesterday, I didn't get as much swag, but today I got there early, got plenty of good stuff, mostly t-shirts.
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you get to play PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even bother.
[SPEAKER_05]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_05]: They had NBA Live up there, and it was like, everybody else was around there, like, drooling over NBA Live.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm like, it's just a game.
[SPEAKER_05]: I pointed at the $600 brick, laughed and walked away.
[SPEAKER_05]: Played the Wii.
[SPEAKER_12]: You're cutting out a little bit there.
[SPEAKER_12]: You said you didn't play the $600 brick, but you played the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_12]: How was the Wii?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was a little bit new to me.
[SPEAKER_05]: Played Elebit.
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_12]: Was Elebit the only game they had there or something?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, they also had Madden for the Wii, but EA shut that down for some odd reason.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: So, what did you think of Elebit?
[SPEAKER_05]: It was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, it was...
[SPEAKER_05]: I didn't even want to get off the machine.
[SPEAKER_12]: I walked over there, but it was so crowded, so I just watched.
[SPEAKER_05]: I just hung out with Zaku and Sephiroth for a bit.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, hell yeah, dude.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'm telling you, get in touch with me Friday night for dinner.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll email you with the real itinerary a little later.
[SPEAKER_05]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's the only thing I'm publicly saying I'm doing is the Saturday noon thing, but I'll tell you a little more about what I'm doing later.
[SPEAKER_05]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, anything else you want to share about Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_05]: Man, it was fun.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I remember talking before about how it's going to be the next E3, but it's more of a tech expo than anything else.
[SPEAKER_12]: So you're saying because of the fact it's a little bit too broad in its tech specs that it may not have the power to be the next E3?
[SPEAKER_05]: I don't see it happening anytime soon, literally, I don't.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Especially if there's a Digital Life LA, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, Ranma, thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_12]: We'll see you on Saturday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Maybe Friday, if you're lucky.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_12]: That was Ranma here, another New York City listener.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: Gravings Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hello, buddy.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_12]: You made me force me to get a Wii order.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on, hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Sit tight for a minute there.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_03]: No, you've been talking about, you've got to get a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: You've got to get a Wii.
[SPEAKER_03]: When did I say you've got to get a Wii?
[SPEAKER_03]: But that's what is going through my mind.
[SPEAKER_03]: You're like, Wii, like 200?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, because I want a Wii really badly.
[SPEAKER_12]: But that's me.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know, as I said earlier, I referenced what I told that email bag thing earlier.
[SPEAKER_12]: You really have to make decisions based on what's best for you.
[SPEAKER_12]: And what's best for me right now?
[SPEAKER_03]: I figured your logic too.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm going Wii 60 all the way.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so how was your experience pre-ordering?
[SPEAKER_12]: Where did you go?
[SPEAKER_12]: How was it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Actually, it wasn't that bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: The mall I didn't go to was jammed.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, God, I'm glad I didn't go there.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the one in Atlantic City was nice.
[SPEAKER_03]: I stood in line for an hour and 40 minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was like this woman, her car broke down.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But her kid wanted the Wii so bad.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was eight people, and they were all nice.
[SPEAKER_12]: Wait, it was eight people that all came together, or it was eight people in the line?
[SPEAKER_03]: Eight people in line.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, that doesn't seem... Whereabouts are you from?
[SPEAKER_12]: Atlantic City.
[SPEAKER_12]: That doesn't seem very long, all things considered, for a town like Atlantic City.
[SPEAKER_12]: Only eight people in the line.
[SPEAKER_12]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: We're a small town.
[SPEAKER_03]: The only thing we do is gamble.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, but I bet the Vegas GameStop lines were long.
[SPEAKER_03]: I bet.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, one of the best places to go for cheap electronics is pawn shops in gambling towns.
[SPEAKER_06]: So go to your local pawn shop, find a Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a good suggestion.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, so what did you pre-order with your Wii?
[SPEAKER_12]: Did you just get the Wii or did you get any games?
[SPEAKER_03]: I just got the Wii because I know I have to have it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Orange Lounge Radio episode, I can't remember, for the 19th.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, yeah, I don't know what number it is either, but it's going to be an interesting show.
[SPEAKER_12]: Our buddy DMN is actually going to be here in-house.
[SPEAKER_12]: So we're going to have our Nintendo QA guy actually here in-house, so it'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, one more.
[SPEAKER_03]: I actually went to a McDonald's for a way port, and it works pretty good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Alright, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: And you got a vision camera.
[SPEAKER_03]: Now we can have a Rob Astey.
[SPEAKER_03]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not happening.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not without proper compensation.
[SPEAKER_12]: Alright, freak, I'm hanging up on you now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's so weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, who'd want to see that?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who'd want to see my ass on Xbox Live?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's disgusting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Rob, you know everyone wants to see your ass.
[SPEAKER_12]: Not until I work it out a little bit, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: I think they want to see your wee.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, they ain't going to get that.
[SPEAKER_12]: One more call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's Dark Teeth.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, what's on your mind, Dark Teeth?
[SPEAKER_12]: Dark Teeth?
[SPEAKER_12]: No, Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_12]: Dark Tea, short for Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shut up and let the man talk.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have iced tea.
[SPEAKER_12]: He's one of our hardworking staffers.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: I had a few FUs.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have FUs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well... Are they gaming related?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, then we'll take them.
[SPEAKER_12]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you heard about Konami's link issue thing on Supernova?
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I guess they officially declared that link mode ain't happening this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, this week the official press announcement went out or whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_12]: At least DDR Freak ran it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Link Mode is not happening in Supernova.
[SPEAKER_12]: That makes you mad?
[SPEAKER_12]: A little bit.
[SPEAKER_12]: Were you looking forward to making custom dance steps to songs such as... I don't even know what the hell songs are in Supernova.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fascination Max.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had it planned.
[SPEAKER_07]: Any other FUs?
[SPEAKER_07]: Gaming related?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, just that my local arcade hasn't got Supernova yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: What is up with lack of Supernova machines in Sacramento?
[SPEAKER_12]: I know.
[SPEAKER_12]: I guess we're just not a real town.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're just some cow town in the middle of nowhere.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, someday, Dark Tetsuya, someday.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hey, did you do any of the Wii pre-ordering or PlayStation 3?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not yet.
[SPEAKER_12]: Are you going to be getting any of them?
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably get a Wii for Christmas.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, you're hoping Santa will bring you one.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have you been good this year?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, then maybe Santa will bring you one, so that'll be cool.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or he'll give you a spanking.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or some coal.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, if you've been bad, though, you'll get a six-axis, and that's all you get.
[SPEAKER_12]: You just get the paperweight of a six-axis.
[SPEAKER_12]: You guys aren't on the afterbirth, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, we're on the actual podcast show.
[SPEAKER_13]: I've never been on the podcast before.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Extrofer is one of our other personalities on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_12]: He does the Wednesday night show with me.
[SPEAKER_12]: And what else would they know you from?
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, other than that, I really like Supernova.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_12]: Do you like the home release of Supernova?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_12]: Top three songs, quick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Centerfold, Battle Without Honor, Humanity, and Gumland a Couple.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_12]: Of course you'd say that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Guacamole Del Taco, right?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thanks so much for the call.
[SPEAKER_12]: Have a good one, all right?
[SPEAKER_12]: You too.
[SPEAKER_12]: Later.
[SPEAKER_12]: One of our hardworking staff members there, that Dark Tetsuya.
[SPEAKER_12]: We appreciate him.
[SPEAKER_12]: All right, that's going to do it for phone calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: If you didn't get through, so sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Try again next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Any other last-minute stories?
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_11]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_11]: We talked earlier about video game movies and there being a movie called 8-Bit the Movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, actually, there is another movie coming out.
[SPEAKER_11]: For your PSP, you can download the entire movie.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's called Killing Time 24-7, and it is available online, actually.
[SPEAKER_11]: for full download to your PSP, which I think is kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of like a Hitman movie, basically.
[SPEAKER_11]: The main character who kills people and in his spare time hangs out with his friends and goes to arcades and whatnot and stuff gets a new assignment and his new hit is his father.
[SPEAKER_11]: And so it's kind of based on that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's actually pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: The download itself is about 300 or just over 300 megs and you can actually find it
[SPEAKER_11]: To download, and I'm pulling up the website.
[SPEAKER_11]: Actually, right now... Thrilling Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, but anyways... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_11]: I believe it's KillingTime- Yeah, it's KillingTime-24-7.com If you want to download it.
[SPEAKER_11]: Free download for your PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's it?
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all I had.
[SPEAKER_11]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_11]: That was good, that was one sentence.
[SPEAKER_11]: Tony Hawk's Project 8 gets some pretty awesome multiplayer on the 360.
[SPEAKER_11]: PlayStation 3 does not have any multiplayer whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I think that was two sentences, but that's all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_11]: Semicolon.
[SPEAKER_11]: Was there?
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: Microsoft launched a new website to browse Xbox Live Marketplace.
[SPEAKER_11]: Ah, I actually saw that.
[SPEAKER_11]: And that was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: I thought, so you made it two sentences?
[SPEAKER_11]: I was, I was dealt the story.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: And the website is Xbox Pipeline or whatever that's called?
[SPEAKER_12]: Xbox Live Pipeline, something like that?
[SPEAKER_12]: Something like that.
[SPEAKER_12]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're so informative.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, there's some website.
[SPEAKER_12]: I couldn't tell you what the name of it is.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, okay, here, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: I will tell you the exact website because I am awesome like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Anyways, the actual website is XboxLivePipeline.com, so go check it out if you haven't already.
[SPEAKER_11]: It has the look and feel of an Xbox.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's kind of nice.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I have some news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki is officially very funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: Last night we went and ate out at a buffet place.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm sorry, this doesn't have to do with games.
[SPEAKER_13]: We killed people on the way because we were racing there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that good enough?
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, Loki asks the waitress or whoever she was serving us or whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: He asks her if they're serving any popcorn shrimp.
[SPEAKER_13]: and she goes, and he looks at her and he goes, okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And everybody's like, did you understand what she just said?
[SPEAKER_13]: And Loki's just very calm.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't understand anything.
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, it was just so funny.
[SPEAKER_12]: Give it up for Extra Furnace.
[SPEAKER_11]: Farewell performance here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: One thing I did want to mention, I read this week on the PlayStation 3 online web browser they were talking about,
[SPEAKER_11]: that it has is for text entry.
[SPEAKER_11]: If you don't have a controller or whatever, it has that crappy text entry that they have on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_11]: Isn't that stupid?
[SPEAKER_11]: Just wanted to mention that.
[SPEAKER_11]: Some other fun stuff I was going to say.
[SPEAKER_11]: I remember, well, Japan's getting a brand new Wii Classic controller plus 5,000 point bundle, which is nice because we'll never see that here.
[SPEAKER_11]: And I think that was all I had.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, PlayStation 3 Oblivion was supposed to be getting exclusive content for it, but it actually is going to be available for us as well.
[SPEAKER_11]: So, on the Xbox 360 and PC.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, a new Prey content for online.
[SPEAKER_11]: Multiplayer maps and stuff.
[SPEAKER_12]: I really haven't played much Prey.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: People who are fans of Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: They've brought out a new download service for $12.95 a month for the Ultimate Collection, so you can get different games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They actually have, for $6.95, access to the Essential Collection with 90 games to choose from, including Prince of Persia, Hitman, Contract, Splinter Cell, Pandora, Tomorrow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of different stuff coming up on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_11]: but I would recommend going on to their main page and taking a look at it if you want to play Java NES games on your PC at work instead of working you can go to vnes.thatsanderskid.com and they have a whole Java thing for playing Nintendo games alright this is too much news for one night it's time to wrap up the program let's go around and get everybody's final thought Extifer your final thought dare I ask
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki, will you marry me?
[SPEAKER_12]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: No.
[SPEAKER_12]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh yes, I forgot The Grudge 2 opened up this weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who wants to go see it with me?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not me, that's my final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Extrovert will go see it with me, won't you?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh damn, I wish we were on TV.
[SPEAKER_12]: No, I totally won't.
[SPEAKER_12]: You should see the way he did that, he kind of did this whole little thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, no.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's not you, DarkSakura, it's the movie.
[SPEAKER_12]: You know what, no, I will see it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just want to see Sarah Michelle Gellar die.
[SPEAKER_12]: I do too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh my god, spoilers.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, she doesn't die soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: I saw a really good movie this last weekend though called The Departed.
[SPEAKER_13]: I want to see that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was so great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Great, great, great.
[SPEAKER_13]: Guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_12]: What?
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay, see the problem is folks who didn't listen to the three hour show when the grudge came out don't understand why you make that weird ass noise.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why are you making that weird ass noise?
[SPEAKER_06]: I remember the episode when I did that almost the entire thing.
[SPEAKER_12]: Two quick, quick things that came out.
[SPEAKER_12]: One thing that's being reported in our chat, like literally right this second, Bubble Bobble for the DS is broken.
[SPEAKER_12]: Players cannot pass level 30.
[SPEAKER_12]: This has been confirmed by Codemasters.
[SPEAKER_12]: Way to go, Codemasters QA.
[SPEAKER_11]: Loki, your thing real quick.
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, I was just making fun of this thing.
[SPEAKER_11]: They ran a report on Gizmodo about...
[SPEAKER_11]: Stuff that you can buy that looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_11]: There's a Mame Cabinet costume for Halloween.
[SPEAKER_11]: I just thought it was funny because the joystick, which is abnormally large, is placed right next to where his penis would be.
[SPEAKER_11]: And the coin door, which has two slots right where his balls would be.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's just the college humor in me.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_12]: And on that note, we're going to call it a night for Orange Lounge Radio this week.
[SPEAKER_12]: Remember, we will not be live on Sunday next week.
[SPEAKER_12]: We're pre-taped because both DarkSakura and I are traveling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Remember, YowieCon.
[SPEAKER_12]: Or New York City, Nintendo World Store.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or Nightmare Before Christmas at the Metreon on Friday night.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, I do it a lot better than you do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can I just unplug that microphone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, there we go.
[SPEAKER_12]: See, now it's unplugged.
[SPEAKER_12]: Thank you for supporting independent internet radio even when it's crappy like tonight.
[SPEAKER_12]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_00]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_00]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_00]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week.
Thanks for watching!