[SPEAKER_04]: Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_04]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 203 for this, October the 8th of 2006.
[SPEAKER_06]: If this is your first time tuning into Orange Lounge Radio, remember, or hear for the first time, that our show is released in two parts every week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We tape live on Sunday nights and then split it up and release it to our podcast feed twice a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: So if you want to hear all the news we talked about in part A, you've got to go download part A. But now it's time for part B, isn't it, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: and, uh, as we mentioned in Part A, uh, Final Fantasy XII.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been pirated to the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not too surprising.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games have been pirated before, but it's 30 days before the game is, you know, set to release in the United States.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, uh, that's pretty interesting that it's pirated.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so anyways, the ISO's leaked to torrent sites and, uh, various news group sites.
[SPEAKER_07]: None of which I'm a member of.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and it's apparently legitimate from the people that have it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You should spend your money on the actual game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't steal, because pirating is bad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll review you next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now wait, what I'm curious about is, you know, sometimes when albums get leaked early, like, I don't know, like, didn't the Eminem, his last album, get released early?
[SPEAKER_06]: And so they had to actually bump up the street date of the CD.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that might happen with this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if the game's already done and in the can, what are we waiting for?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's play it!
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a review copy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what got leaked, is a review copy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ouch.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what else has been leaked to the internet?
[SPEAKER_07]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_07]: In the Groove 2 beta.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: The gaming companies need to keep a lockdown on that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They do, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: All the journalists are going to be hurting.
[SPEAKER_07]: No one to blame but themselves, because these are their copies that get leaked out.
[SPEAKER_07]: What could they do to stop this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Put serial numbers on them somehow, or what?
[SPEAKER_07]: They could make them so they're only able to play on dev kits, and hope that the reviewers have dev kits.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, I mean, honestly, are you really going to have to fish for good reviews for Final Fantasy XII?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you could do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Watermark them.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, each individual copy, although I know it's going to be pretty difficult, each individual copy is watermarked so that you can check a certain, you know, byte signature or whatever and see, oh, Bill over at such and such gaming site leaked that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to kill him.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to sue him for $11 billion.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, my take on this, you know, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, great, you get to play three days early.
[SPEAKER_06]: ESRB Don't Play Games
[SPEAKER_06]: Aaron Ruby, the Underground Gaming Culture spokesperson, has a score to settle with the ESRB.
[SPEAKER_06]: The ESRB has been independently applying and enforcing ratings and guidelines on online privacy since 1994.
[SPEAKER_06]: The writer stated in his opinion column that the system applied to rating games should be different from those currently applied to TV and movies, which I disagree with.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if you want parents to know what the ratings are clear as day, make them the same as movies.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, well, oh well.
[SPEAKER_06]: So anyway, how do they give out ratings anyway?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, they read and watch.
[SPEAKER_06]: What happens is the game developers fill out a questionnaire on what the game's about and the game developers submit it with footage of the most extreme scenes from the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: There are three trained raters, not expert game players, if you check out the website you'll see this is true, from the board and then they hand out the rating based on what they read on the form and see on the videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: So according to the writer, quote, I find it alarming that the ESRB does not bother to base its ratings on the entire experience of playing a game, instead relying far too much on submitted clips.
[SPEAKER_06]: Which is interesting because that doesn't surprise me because I remember, and I'm not going to say who this was, but I was at a conference, or I should say a media show once, and I overheard a developer saying about a game that featured a lot of cleavage in it, you know, and a lot of, you know, female...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: but there's huge fines for lying and stuff as the makers of Grand Theft Auto are finding out, although I still to this day say they weren't lying, they were just careless and thinking they took out a portion of the game that they didn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's gotten so ridiculous now where they're, you know, rating content that doesn't exist in the game, you know, like Oblivion, you know, where they're rating it M because, yeah, underneath the virtual clothes there's virtual nipples, so I don't know, I think it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: But some other interesting stuff, speaking of virtual nipples.
[SPEAKER_07]: Playboy, you know, they've been doing this thing for the last couple years now, releasing the Women of Video Games spread in their magazine.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, virtual naked women to oogle over.
[SPEAKER_07]: And both Fleshbot and Kotaku have actually been running a preview picture of it, and we've got a list of the people that are going to be featured in there, as well as...
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, let's see, such wonderful people as Sarah Morrison from Tabula Rasa, two of the women from the Scarface game, and we've got two women from God of War 2, and Alicia Claus from Bullet Witch, Dr. Yasmin Lin from Timeshift, and Erika from Splinter Cell Double Agent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bunch of babes I've never heard of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, a bunch of games that aren't out yet, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: I see.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, very interesting, and that's supposed to be coming out, I guess, later this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you look at the spread?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nice boobies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Virtual boobies.
[SPEAKER_07]: The one chick I thought, you know, when I first looked at it, I'm like, why did they put Blood Ring in it again?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, you know, I don't play a lot of PC games, so, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess if you're into that stuff...
[SPEAKER_07]: If you're into boobs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, if you're into this, like, you know, virtual... Aren't they all fake boobs in Playboy?
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all airbrushed and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, what's the difference?
[SPEAKER_06]: Virtual boobs or airbrushed boobs?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: These are probably more real than some of the pictures that are in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very early pictures still, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be a... They're going to have a two-page fold-out in the final version.
[SPEAKER_07]: and 6 pages of gaming content.
[SPEAKER_06]: And how many pages of boobies?
[SPEAKER_06]: Lots of boobies.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, Playboy is a lot of ads and there's not that many boobies in that magazine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Will you be picking up this copy of Playboy for the articles or for the research material?
[SPEAKER_07]: I did last year, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your wife probably took it from you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think she did.
[SPEAKER_06]: For those of you that haven't met Loki's wife, she's hilarious, that's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_06]: She's had cameos in this program.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was something else I was going to mention, because this was also on Fleshbot, linked to the same story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh dear.
[SPEAKER_07]: There is a Nerdcore 2007 calendar out starring Sherry Roberts, and there's one picture... Oh my god, my sister!
[SPEAKER_07]: Bad joke, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, there's one picture, though, that I thought was funny, and I showed Rob this earlier...
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_06]: and if maybe chicks wearing gaming accessories aren't your thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you think that's hot?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess it could be, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you think your wife will think it's hot?
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably she'd think it's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: But anyways, it says it's a limited edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're going to have 2,500 copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're $25 each.
[SPEAKER_07]: Features 12 months of girls with a complete daily calendar grid and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're pretty big and...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: GameDevelopersConference.com
[SPEAKER_07]: Talk Like a Pirate Day, Tokyo Game Show, The Transformers, The Movie, Opening Day, and other flagship nerd videos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's putting this out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Slashdot?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, totallynerdcore.com is where you can purchase this calendar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I gotta say, you know... Damn it, we need to get them on the show and get one of these models on the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wouldn't that be awesome?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that'd be totally awesome to have any model on this show.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know what else to say so let's move on from boobies to violence!
[SPEAKER_06]: All the great games have either boobies or violence in them.
[SPEAKER_06]: Violence, violence, violence.
[SPEAKER_06]: This story coming from GamePolitics.com, our friends over there.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it has to do with a question and answer session with the Dean of the School of Social Policy and Practice at the University of Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_06]: His name is Richard J. Gellis.
[SPEAKER_06]: And there was this interesting quote.
[SPEAKER_06]: The question was, Excuse me, sir, but what is your opinion on video games and the lack of parenting to control the ever-increasing teen violence?
[SPEAKER_06]: Answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: Video games play almost no important role in teen violence.
[SPEAKER_06]: Teens with a predisposition to being violent may be drawn to violent video games, but overall, other factors besides television, music, or video games are more important risk factors for teen violence.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, that quote from Richard Gellis, the Dean of the School of Social Policy and Practice at the University of Pennsylvania.
[SPEAKER_06]: Also the Director of Center for Research on Youth and Social Policy.
[SPEAKER_06]: So this guy does know what he's talking about.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's actually going to be pretty much the same kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've got your Brain Age score and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So imagine Brain Age minus the touchscreen and on your PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of big news.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Because this guy, he was doing the DS stuff, and those games are huge in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: And now he's kind of defected in a way to the PSP.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think Nintendo's going to slow down their Big Brain series anytime soon, but kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I wonder what possessed him to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Money?
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's more brain training games coming out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What is that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think Majesco has two coming out in November.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like Brain Wave, I think it was called.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now it's just going to be like all those crappy Nintendogs knockoffs we got a while back.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: November is the month for Nintendogs knockoffs.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've got the whole dogs, cats, hamster life, horses.
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh-oh, I showed her to think what might be possible in a hamster life.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, let's move on and get some feedback from you guys, the listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Every week we invite your emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: And DarkSakura is typically here to read through the email.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as you know, she's not here tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I'm going to instead borrow her asbestos suit and put on the gloves and dig into our mailbag.
Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, so this first email comes to us from Deekman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deekman writes, Hey guys, just thinking about the new next-gen consoles and had these thoughts.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, the cost of the Wii at $249.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they chose to set it at this price not to make money, even though it is selling it more than it's worth, but for the simple reason that Nintendo doesn't want you to get any other console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just think for a second, with a $150 to $200 console, an Xbox 360 sounds mighty enticing to go with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: But a $250 console plus games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Suddenly that extra $360 doesn't look as good.
[SPEAKER_06]: To back this up, I remember hearing a quote posted on Kotaku by Reggie that said something along the lines of, and I'm paraphrasing here, quote, I've heard of the Wii 60, but our users buy our consoles because they want a different experience.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they want something else, they can get a DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, I'm paraphrasing, but it sounds like Nintendo is being smart with the pricing, if only to cut out the competition.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think of that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, that sounds pretty accurate.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, it's an interesting theory, but I don't think that was a factor in the price point they chose.
[SPEAKER_06]: was because it makes the 360 sound less appealing.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think if they could make it cheaper, I think in the long run it's which system costs which.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think your average family is only going to get one console unless they have some hardcore gamers in the house, if even that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, I mean, it's a good thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, it's a good theory, and it may be right, but I just kind of think there's a lot of other factors that come into play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Deekman also writes this, too.
[SPEAKER_06]: Region-free PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_06]: Not as elaborate as the last theory, but what if the reason Sony is making the console region-free is quite simply to combat mod chippers?
[SPEAKER_06]: A strong case, and the one most used in courts, especially in Australia so far, is that people mod their systems to play import games.
[SPEAKER_06]: What if this is simply a way to nip the next-gen mod chippers in the bud before they start?
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think of that, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Could be.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think mainly...
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the whole HDMI being added to all the different systems and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that kind of ties in with it because now they can do the digital flag on all the movies.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they might be able to do that with all the games now, too, if they have HDMI on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I guess, you know, since they do give the option not to use the HDMI, that might not be the case.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, region-free, I mean, I don't see why they don't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, when you think about it, because a lot of games, I mean, if you're going to import them, that's more sales for them anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: So...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see what the big difference is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, granted you get stuff early, but it's not going to be, you know, it's only, it's not going to be translated for over here unless it already comes in both languages anyways, which why wouldn't you release them in both territories?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Keep up the good work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Still listening, Dekeman.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as Canada goes, you know, it's a nice thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'd love to maybe retire up there, but just for right now, there's too much going on for me here in the States.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I definitely will be taking another vacation up there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Probably next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Our next email comes to us from Malice, the artist formerly known as Stupid Baka, or so his signature says.
[SPEAKER_06]: You folks still are awesome and I really like the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I love sitting in my room and doing my homework or talking to friends with the podcast in the background.
[SPEAKER_06]: I also like your guys' quirky attitudes and witty remarks from time to time, especially those that belong to DarkSakura and Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: You guys make my day.
[SPEAKER_06]: In other words, Loki, sorry, you suck.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, thank you, seriously, for the words.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know this is a recurring theme of discussion on the podcast, and I was just wondering what you guys thought of this.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm a member of my school's mock trial team and have been since last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: This year's case is People vs. Campbell, in which a student that is being bullied allegedly created a time bomb to blow up his school.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's being charged with acts of terrorism, intent to murder, placing an offensive substance in a public place, and possessing a violent video game.
[SPEAKER_06]: All the mock trial cases have pretrial arguments in which we argue to a judge about certain aspects of the case before it occurs, specifically in regards to evidence, the Constitution's Bill of Rights, and whether it shall be allowed during the case.
[SPEAKER_06]: The defense in this pretrial argument will argue that video games are protected speech under the First Amendment, which is something I agree with, as do you guys, I assume.
[SPEAKER_06]: This seems to be echoed as all the cases that they have given us that are relevant and have precedent
[SPEAKER_06]: are all in favor of the defense.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is definitely a change as most of the cases each year, especially in pre-trial, are made so that they aren't one-sided and can be argued both ways, ensuring for an exciting trial based on how good each side is, which is why I'll most likely be on the prosecution this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just wondering what you guys have to say about this as I know that you three are very vocal and have a lot to say about this issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a nice three-day weekend.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, it's not three days for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have to work tomorrow even if it is Columbus Day.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lucky you guys that get it off.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, I don't know much about the specific case that you're citing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just based off of other cases, I think you pretty much said what I feel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would agree with the fact that
[SPEAKER_06]: Video games are a form of art.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not talking about art as in a classic sculpture you might see, but it is a form of expression.
[SPEAKER_06]: Expression is art.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's no different than a movie or a CD.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think, therefore, it should be viewed at very similarly by the public.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: There are the people that criticize violent movies, and they probably do criticize violent games, but you can't say that a kid...
[SPEAKER_06]: played a video game and that's what caused him to go crazy because what about the R-rated movies he might have seen?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or what about the dirty music he might have been listening to?
[SPEAKER_06]: But more importantly, what about the parents?
[SPEAKER_06]: What about the home life?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where was the love?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where was the hug?
[SPEAKER_06]: Where was the how was your day?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's more important than the CDs, movies, or video games combined, in my opinion.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, anything you want to add to that?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it's basically just bad parenting.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Black Boy says, Dirty Music?
[SPEAKER_06]: Next email comes to us from Mr. Wonderful.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys and lady.
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, thanks for putting on the show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I emailed Sky earlier but figured that I should be thanking you all.
[SPEAKER_06]: I recently graduated college and got a great job right after graduation.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: I've got to agree, though, that you really should play Pinball Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Even though she's not here tonight, I'll make sure she sees that part of the email.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sure she will appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I will make her play Pinball Quest.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anyway, forgive me if these questions have been asked, but I'm still making my way through the backlog.
[SPEAKER_06]: On to a few quick questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: First off, if you guys have the power to resurrect one franchise for a well-done remake...
[SPEAKER_06]: What would you go for?
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's just the recent re-release on GBA talking, but I've got to think a Wii Bionic Commando would do the job pretty nicely.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thoughts?
[SPEAKER_06]: If it was 3D, maybe.
[SPEAKER_06]: What game would you like to see Wii made?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I know Kid Icarus is the obvious answer that most fanboys, I'm sure, would be foaming at the mouth for.
[SPEAKER_06]: And that would definitely be my number one answer.
[SPEAKER_06]: But as far as a GameCube game that I'd like to see on the Wii, I want to see F-Zero have another shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I'm sure there will be some type of F-Zero on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I really enjoyed the GameCube one.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think it was a little bit underrated in part because the arcade version had one key flaw.
[SPEAKER_06]: and that was the fact that there was really only the one model which was very expensive because the car moved around a lot and the fact there was only six tracks in the arcade and you can unlock them all in the home version.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think there was a lot to still be discovered with that concept that I think unfortunately in the execution kind of fell apart.
[SPEAKER_06]: But the whole driving with the Wii stick might be kind of interesting in F-Zero or something.
[SPEAKER_06]: At least even with the slightly souped up graphics and sound, I would like to see that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And the sound coming out of the controller.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm really looking forward to a new F-Zero game.
[SPEAKER_06]: And online, please.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything, Loki, you can think of?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of hard.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know.
[SPEAKER_07]: What could we do that would be really awesome?
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Drunami says Capcom seriously needs to put Okami on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's not a remake, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: DMN says Kirby's Dream Course.
[SPEAKER_06]: That might be kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could actually swing the ball.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a fun game on Super Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'd say just remake.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make a good...
[SPEAKER_07]: Even like a Castlevania would be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: A good Castlevania for 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: Make it like a first person shooter would be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to see them do the 2D.
[SPEAKER_07]: I got excited by the 2D news last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can have a 2D Castlevania too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just maybe Blaster Master maybe?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, that's hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to the next email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey guys, it's NeoDude.
[SPEAKER_06]: Belated congrats on 200 and all that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I just wanted to talk about the Sonic demo on 360 for a moment and why it sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh my god, I played that actually now.
[SPEAKER_07]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just like horrible controls.
[SPEAKER_07]: I couldn't even make it over the first jump because...
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just veering off to the side when I had tapped the button to the side.
[SPEAKER_06]: The email continues from NeoDude here.
[SPEAKER_06]: The big thing was the camera sucked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sonic has always relied on good camera control and it's not here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Plus, the demo gave Sonic everything he had at the end of Sonic Adventure 2, including the bounce bracelet, which leads to many unexpected deaths, especially when you're trying to light dash in the air.
[SPEAKER_06]: If they include a window that tells you what the X button does at any time and fix the camera and maybe take out the bounce bracelet, everything else should be alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Catch you next episode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I hope they change something.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know they've been getting negative feedback around the web, and who knows, it may result in a delay of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, but it would be nice to see them go back and change things.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think what they should do is have an option when you're running straight to be able to strafe a little bit.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need a strafe button in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, like, when I'm running straight, you know, ahead, I'm not, like, going to, when I try to, you know, be a little off on the rings there, I'm not going to all of a sudden veer off to the side.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they need to fix.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, this one, last email tonight comes to us from Laser123454321, and he writes this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Sky, Loki, and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_06]: I first want to thank you for giving the Bomani community its first podcast as well as your general game coverage.
[SPEAKER_06]: Read, you rock.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like all the politeness, like the fluffing of the egos in the first paragraph of all our letters tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, seriously, we love the fact that you guys are so receptive to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_06]: Second, I would like to get your in-depth view of the new DDR Supernova for PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just to tell about some of the experiences I've had, the new Stellar Master Mode far outshines the Dance Master Mode of DDR EX and EX2, as the majority of the unlocks can be done just by completing the first few trials in each Stellar joint and then facing the showdown.
[SPEAKER_06]: I personally play Controller Controller Revolution.
[SPEAKER_06]: We call it Button Button Revolution, but that's fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I like to face the Diamond EX Showdown or EX Showdown in each joint.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything you want to say additional about DDR Supernova, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: I haven't played it yet.
[SPEAKER_06]: I did play it a little bit, and I agree.
[SPEAKER_06]: I gave my fuller review on last week's program, so you can go back and download that in Part A.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I definitely think it's a solid entry into the series and will give you lots of new songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like the song list and I do agree that Stellar Master Mode is an improvement on the mode they had last year.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I didn't despise the mode they had last year so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: I felt it's okay to have the really, really hard songs kind of tricky to unlock because they're extra, they're bonus.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're supposed to take a lot of effort to unlock.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I think they did do a little bit better this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Other questions.
[SPEAKER_06]: One, what do you think about the song list as compared to the other US releases?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it's a pretty good song list.
[SPEAKER_06]: I do too, but Max 2 is still my favorite overall.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just, you know, as an old school DDR fan.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do think it was better than Extreme 1's song list.
[SPEAKER_06]: Two, what are some downfalls with the game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Link mode disappearing was an interesting thing that was a bit of a downfall of the game, I think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: Other downfalls for the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, the fact that they got rid of a lot of the videos.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't like the whole dancer in the custom-generated background or whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing I liked about DDR was some of the art backgrounds they had, and I always kind of looked forward to seeing some of the ones they came up with for new songs.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's kind of not there in Supernova.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a stupid request, but one I made before I went on Extreme 2 is not being able to put in edits on...
[SPEAKER_07]: for the eye toy stuff, like you can't put in hand things on your edits.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would have been cool if you could do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Granted, hardly anyone actually uses it, but how hard would it be to put that as an option for your edits?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Three, what do you think about Konami bringing back Battle Mode?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it should be more prevalent in their next release.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they should really explore what they can do with versus mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: I used to say this way back when the show was strictly about Bomani games and we had the three hour show.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think the future of DDR was in a versus mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: I would like to see more competitive style play and options.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I think it's a good step in the right direction but I'd like to see that option more fully researched in the next release of DDR and do more with it.
[SPEAKER_06]: So just a thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: What is your opinion on the online controversy?
[SPEAKER_06]: For those that don't know, the game features a few songs that are online only.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is, you cannot play songs that are exclusive to online play in the free dance mode offline, even after having played them in the online mode.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some have speculated that when Konami shuts down Supernova online play, like they did for Extreme 2, that these songs will be lost.
[SPEAKER_06]: Others believe that when this happens, Konami will reveal an unlock code for the songs for offline play.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think it's the doom and gloom most people are shouting about.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's something extra.
[SPEAKER_06]: And what if you have an Xbox that doesn't go online?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's many great songs that you're missing out on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, granted, I see the difference because you can download those songs and play them offline whenever you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I would speculate that if there's a Supernova 2 or whatever's next, which I would find it hard to believe there's not going to be at least one more PlayStation 2 game next year...
[SPEAKER_06]: I would bet almost anything you're going to see those five songs in the default song list for next year's game.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't know anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just speculation.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, I mean, it would make sense.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then people wouldn't complain about repeats so much because they didn't really have them in the last game.
[SPEAKER_07]: What if they're just going to be unlocked at a time unlock type thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like they're going to be unlocked...
[SPEAKER_07]: on a certain date, say, when the other games come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: I seriously think this is it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think they're ever going to be unlocked.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think online only is online only, and I think that's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's until someone puts out a code for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Someone might hack a save.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to be honest, the content is there, so true.
[SPEAKER_06]: So who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, lastly, and finally, for those involved in the Stepmania community, Loki might want to read this.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: have expressed interest in doing a Supernova theme, and Takuya will start work as soon as he has rips from the Supernova disc.
[SPEAKER_06]: I believe K Eternal is waiting for StepMania 4.0's theming engine to be finalized before he starts work.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not that hard to rip stuff off that disc, and to be honest, it's funny how I mentioned in the Groove 2 beta had already been leaked.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've already made tools to basically re-skin it, re-put songs in it for your own stuff like they do in the Groove 1.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, it's going to be possible pretty soon just to do all that stuff pretty easy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, hell, they've already automated the whole ripping of In The Groove stuff, you know, off of this once the game comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to be honest, I'm just not that big on playing DDR on my computer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: With the Indigroove rips that you can do in the editing, you can actually either, if you have a modded PS2, you can dump it to a disc and actually play it on the PlayStation 2, or if you have a hard drive like mine does, you can dump the ISO to the hard drive and play it off of that, and you can actually play your DDR on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's going to do it for the Mailbag this week, and lots of great emails this week again.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry to those we didn't get to tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you want to send us an email, it's Mailbag at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, excellent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, the big story this week is, well, one of the big stories, Mark Raine is basically saying that the second-gen game, Gears of War, on the 360 looks better than the first-gen PS3 titles.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, he's sort of right on some of those, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Sony says their next generation starts when they say so, I say bullshit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And basically stating that the next gen will start when that game comes out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Whatever, big talk, but we'll see.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sounds like people just kind of whipping it out back and forth.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: Typical PR, trying to slam the other guy type stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, speaking of the Xbox 360, of course, when Doom came out, a lot of people were like, where's Duke Nukem?
[SPEAKER_06]: If you're going to bring us Doom, you need to bring us Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, there was an interesting post by a staff of 3D Realms.
[SPEAKER_06]: Quote, you'd be surprised what they've turned down.
[SPEAKER_06]: Don't just assume MS will want it just because you like it and it's popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hate to sound defeatist, but it's not as easy as send it to Microsoft and get it on there.
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: They can release two games in one day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have a hard time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Their schedule is so book solid when things keep getting pushed back and we have to get things like, you know, the Project Gotham deck for Uno to hold us over.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, if they're so booked, why don't they release something else that's ready to go?
[SPEAKER_07]: Release two games in one day.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it going to kill the server that much?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I think they're afraid that one game would outshine another.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's why they don't release like 10 or 15 at a time because they want all the games to have a fair shot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does that make sense?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it doesn't make sense.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Duke Nukem 3D
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't see what the big deal is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think what the big deal is, they don't want to work on it because they're not fucking done with Duke Nukem Forever yet, and to be honest, just put the damn thing out.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's never going to be perfect.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're never going to finish it.
[SPEAKER_07]: The generation of hardware is just going to get better and better each time you're about done.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it's never going to happen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some other interesting stuff, though, like Duke Nukem 3D, you know, had pretty good multiplayer.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, another game that has really good multiplayer...
[SPEAKER_07]: Lost Planet, and we will be seeing a multiplayer demo this winter, which is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yeah, looking forward to that, probably in November sometime, would be my guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, I wasn't that big on Lost Planet when I played it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, I'm not sure what all the hype's about.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe it's just not my kind of game, but maybe a multiplayer would change my mind, if I had a lot of fun with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you more excited about this game?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you enjoy the first demo that came out?
[SPEAKER_07]: I liked the first demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure if I'd buy it, though, right away.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: I think about that time I'm going to be busy with the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not sure if I really want to buy this game right away.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it was a cool game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't get me wrong.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks really good.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really don't need to be buying that many games now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, let's do another story here.
[SPEAKER_06]: This one is regarding Full Auto 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be releasing some PS3 online details.
[SPEAKER_06]: Apparently the developers behind Full Auto 2 actually released some of the details about what online is going to be all about.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it was on this Radio PM podcast.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Full Auto 2 producer Mike Gallo from Sega of America talked about what was going on.
[SPEAKER_06]: and OPM asked, so when you go into Network Play, you'll see sort of a browser and they say when you first turn on the machine, it logs you in automatically.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you can change that in the settings.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have a user ID and an online profile that's set up through the PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_06]: We don't have anything to do with that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all done through the PlayStation Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: When you log in and as long as you have an ID and you're an active online member, when you go into the online mode, you get a menu option.
[SPEAKER_06]: You get to pick ranked or unranked play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Then you'll see what games are available and then jump into one of those.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's more information.
[SPEAKER_06]: As far as stat tracking, is it all within full auto?
[SPEAKER_06]: Is that outside?
[SPEAKER_06]: When you play Ranked Play, your stats, pretty basic set of stats, wins, losses, will get uploaded to GameSpy.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll be able to see, I think we have it sortable by, it's worldwide and monthly or all time, so you'll get to see who's ranked where.
[SPEAKER_06]: You'll be able to access it from our website as well, so you can look at those stats independently of the game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Achievements are big on 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you guys think about throwing in that concept for PS3?
[SPEAKER_06]: We actually do not have that in Full Auto 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's a feature we had to regrettably not support.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of it was just because of that moving target with the development timeline.
[SPEAKER_06]: We had to make sure our online modes and network play was solid before we added some of that other stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Unfortunately, that was one of the things we had to drop.
[SPEAKER_06]: Kind of interesting, though, if that means that there's not really going to be achievements like we know it on the 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just going to be on whatever games that they want to support it on.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of big news, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess they could patch it later.
[SPEAKER_07]: That might be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we're going to go now to a new segment, which is a new game.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're going to play a new game tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: So, Loki, you know I'm going to sucker you into playing this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ready for it?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, you'll like this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: and we thought we'd bring on a contestant of our choosing tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Caller, are you there?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi, and who is this?
[SPEAKER_01]: This is Bobby from Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Bobby from Atlanta.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, is this the same Bobby that does his own show on Sunday nights on another network?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know it is.
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, now there's a reason why I invited Bobby to be the first one to play this show or to play this new game here on the show is because, you know, there's been a little bit of smack talking in the past between, you know, Loki and
[SPEAKER_06]: and Bobby and Chromehounds, which never happened, and these whole, you know, oh, we're going to play each other at these games, and it never really happened.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I decided we here at Orange Launch Radio would provide an opportunity for there to be a great podcast war, if you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: So are you ready, Bobby?
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you going to kick Loki's ass?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I will.
[SPEAKER_01]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: He sounds quite confident.
[SPEAKER_01]: Two words.
[SPEAKER_01]: Shenanigans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Shenanigans.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, we're going to play a brand new game and it's called the Video Game Showdown.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's horrible music, dude.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have no reason why we're using the Press Your Luck theme for this, but I just wanted an excuse to use the Press Your Luck theme at some point during the program.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Video Game Showdown is a brand new game here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here is how it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: First things first, no fair using Google or the internet to cheat at this game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Some of you people can do your research mighty fast, so no fair.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're on your honor.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, Bobby, I want a fair fight.
[SPEAKER_01]: Am I allowed to at least write things down?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, you can write things down.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's certainly acceptable.
[SPEAKER_06]: You just can't research.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have to be on your own here.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so this is how it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to read you a list of ten items in a category, but only five of them actually apply.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you have to guess which five are the correct answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's tonight's category.
[SPEAKER_06]: Tonight's category is, per the website Video Game Charts, five of these games are the top five best-selling worldwide DS games to date.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: So tonight's topic is the top 5 best selling worldwide, keyword there, worldwide DS games to date.
[SPEAKER_06]: You ready for the list?
[SPEAKER_06]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, here we go.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's your 10 options.
[SPEAKER_06]: Animal Crossing Wild World Brain Training Mario & Luigi Partners in Time Mario Kart DS Metroid Prime Hunters New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nintendogs, Super Mario 64, Tetris DS, and WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_06]: Again, of those ten I just named, five of them are the best selling worldwide DS games to date.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here it is again one more time real quick and then we'll get the answers.
[SPEAKER_06]: Animal Crossing, Brain Training,
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario & Luigi Partners in Time, Mario Kart DS, Metroid Prime Hunters, New Super Mario Bros., Nintendogs, Super Mario 64, Tetris DS, and WarioWare.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, you about ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am ready.
[SPEAKER_06]: You're ready?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's the five you're going to pick, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: The five I'm going to pick, Animal Crossing, Braintrain, Mario Kart DS, New Super Mario Bros., and Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby, which five are you going to pick?
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, my five are Brain Training, Mario DS, New Mario Bros., Nintendogs, and Super Mario 64.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, there they are.
[SPEAKER_06]: So very similar lists, only one difference between them, and that could be the make or break.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now here's what happens, if we have a tie, and Bobby and Loki have the same amount correct...
[SPEAKER_06]: Then Bobby can either change one of his own answers after I tell him how many he has right or he can force Loki to change one of his.
[SPEAKER_06]: So that way we prevent a tie.
[SPEAKER_06]: So let's first check the correct answers and see if we have a tie tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it looks like we do not have a tie tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, we'll start with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You got four right.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: 4 out of 5 right, not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: Brain Training is correct, Mario Kart DS is correct, New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: is correct, and Nintendogs is correct.
[SPEAKER_06]: Those are 4.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Loki, that bastard got all 5 of them right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hell yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was concentrating on Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you cheat?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I wasn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I concentrated on thinking about what was popular in Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The top five selling games of all time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Animal Crossing, Brain Training, Mario Kart DS, New Super Mario Bros., and Nintendogs.
[SPEAKER_06]: And because they also packed in New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, actually, no they didn't.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it wasn't a pack-in.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I was a good guess from Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, it's a trick though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mario 64 was actually number six.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it was really close.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, my reasoning was just because it was one of the few games out when it launched.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, no, it was a good guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess Animal Crossing, yeah, was kind of a surprise, but, you know, the game was really big.
[SPEAKER_06]: Pretty much around the world.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, they're making a movie based on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Come on.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's got to be pretty big.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, good job, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: You did really good.
[SPEAKER_06]: Four out of five is not bad.
[SPEAKER_06]: And who knew that Loki had this superhuman power?
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess I should have guessed, you know, since he works in distribution, you probably know something about sales figures.
[SPEAKER_01]: I cry in shame.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm sorry, Bobby.
[SPEAKER_06]: But you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we'll give you a chance to plug your show.
[SPEAKER_06]: You have something you want to share about what's going on on the Bobby Blackwolf show this week?
[SPEAKER_01]: The Bobby Blackwell Show
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_06]: We've got newbies.
[SPEAKER_01]: and community chats and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, what nights are those on?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do we have a set schedule for that yet?
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, XBL radios on Tuesday, Evil Avatars on Wednesday and Game Addict Oddlines on Thursday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very nice.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, congratulations to those guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: We're happy to see them on board and we'll be looking forward to that over at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, thanks so much for playing our little game tonight and next time I'll do a topic, you know, maybe about like video games in Atlanta or something that Loki couldn't get.
[SPEAKER_01]: There wouldn't be five things in that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wait, I thought Atlanta was like one of the top five cities for gaming, like right under Seattle.
[SPEAKER_01]: It is, but you know, it's like in terms of video games being based here, I think like Midnight Club 3 was here and that's about it unless you count like sports games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I guess they just sell a lot there because you guys have to stay indoors because it's so damn humid outside.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's not the heat, it's the stupidity.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bobby, thanks so much for playing our game tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, all right?
[SPEAKER_06]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mr. Bobby Blackwolf, ladies and gentlemen.
[SPEAKER_06]: from AllGames.com does his own program over there Sunday nights, 5 o'clock Pacific Standard Time.
[SPEAKER_06]: A lot of our live listeners actually listen to his show.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like a bit of a warm-up before they come over to Orange Launch Radio, so that's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: That is pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's go back to the news.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we were talking about games being leaked out early and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this has to do with mod ship and HD loader programs out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, well, actually, some of the major ones were actually...
[SPEAKER_07]: Nailed for over $9 million recently.
[SPEAKER_07]: The ESA announced that a federal court in California ordered a group of defendants to pay over $9 million in damages for violations of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the violations were against Divinio, the maker and distributor of mod chips for all consoles, French resident Max Lohm, and Canadian resident Frdric Leggett.
[SPEAKER_07]: for trafficking of mod chips and software circumvention device called HD Loader.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yeah, it's basically, of course, the HD Loader, for those who might not know, was a device that was available on the market for a while, allowing you to dump games to a hard drive built into your older PlayStation 2, whether that be one that you provide or the official Sony hard drive, and you can put games on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love my HD loader because it allows me to play import games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And it just loads things faster, too, on the HD loader.
[SPEAKER_06]: It does load things faster.
[SPEAKER_06]: I like just not having to switch out the discs and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know how a bachelor pad looks around the TV?
[SPEAKER_06]: There's discs everywhere outside of their case because they're all too damn lazy to put it back in the right case.
[SPEAKER_07]: What I like using it for is when I used to, before I got my 360, when I used to take my PlayStation 2 to work to play games...
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't have to carry around like 50 discs with me.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all dumped to my hard drive.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I can just, you know, bring my PlayStation 2 and a couple controllers and the hookups and away I go.
[SPEAKER_07]: And plus the load times were a lot less.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, and DDR, it was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was just like instantly into the song.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, um, I don't know, but it's gotten worse since then.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, before, you know, when I first got it, you had a cap of 120 gigs.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, you can pretty much use now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now you can, it supports the two terabyte drives that you can hook up, um,
[SPEAKER_07]: via USB.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's so... I mean, you can literally put almost every single game out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, but you can also go rent games and then load them on your HD loader and then you have them forever.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, not that you'd know anything about that, would you, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I wouldn't.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm beyond renting games nowadays.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who needs to rent games when they're freely available on the Internet?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, Loki, Loki.
[SPEAKER_06]: There is a...
[SPEAKER_06]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: So just because it's releasing late in Europe doesn't mean you won't have an impact here in the United States.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, that's 500,000 PlayStation 3s that were expected to go to Europe at the end of this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, that's 500,000 less consumers to sell games to.
[SPEAKER_06]: So publishers are probably going to delay games that they previously were going to release this year to 2007 just to take advantage of the greater user base in Europe.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we all get screwed by this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Isn't this kind of what you were saying earlier?
[SPEAKER_07]: That's for a whole different reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's for the fact that they haven't gotten their dev kits in a timely manner, and so they're not able to finish the game, period.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm talking about earlier in the program, you were talking about how sometimes, or I should say, like say the Wii sells 9 million units, I think you said this in Part A, then that's 9 million available systems for people to want to publish for.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Isn't it the same logic here?
[SPEAKER_07]: In a sense, yes, but
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't really apply, like say if there's 500,000 units in the United States, that doesn't mean they're not going to release a game here.
[SPEAKER_07]: If there's no systems obviously in the UK, they're going to delay the launch of a game there.
[SPEAKER_07]: But just because Europe doesn't have their game system yet does not mean that they won't launch their US copies here first.
[SPEAKER_06]: So not only will Europe get screwed by the release of the system, but now all their games are going to be delayed six months because of this.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, they'll just come out when the PlayStation 3 launches instead of just, you know, being launched at the same time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, the same thing happens with, you know, different region games like Tomb Raider will come out in the UK first and then it'll come out over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: It does not mean, you know, if, for example, we could release, you know, PlayStation 3 games here first and then just wait to release them there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter because they need time anyways to, I guess, you know, print more copies.
[SPEAKER_07]: One interesting thing, though, I have to add to this, was that there was an interview with the Sony Computer Entertainment Europe World Vice President, Jamie McDonald.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he claims that Europeans don't mind that they have to wait an extra four months for the console.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they asked him, what would you say to consumers who like Sony and want to buy your product?
[SPEAKER_07]: but perhaps feel because they're in Europe they will always be last in line.
[SPEAKER_07]: And he says, European consumers have shown that historically they don't mind that because they end up buying as many PlayStations if not more than the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Japan.
[SPEAKER_07]: In Europe, it doesn't seem that the release of our platforms after the U.S.
[SPEAKER_07]: and Japan in the long run affects how consumers feel.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think some of our listeners over in the old country might feel a little different.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, guys.
[SPEAKER_06]: Is it just me or do you feel a little different than what this guy is saying?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, so, I thought that was very interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he's saying basically, well, since Europe usually gets screwed, you know, we're kind of used to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they're assholes stretched out now, it doesn't matter if we fuck them again.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, that's pretty much what it comes down to.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, anyway.
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow!
[SPEAKER_06]: Wow, um, damn.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki says the darndest things.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like kids say the darndest things.
[SPEAKER_07]: All we need now, we're just missing Bill Cosby and we've got another show all...
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to say this real quick before we get into the next story.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's something I wanted to talk about that for whatever reason isn't on the show roll.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was actually kind of a busy week for news with the whole GameStop conference and everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: The system's coming out soon.
[SPEAKER_06]: There was a story, an opinion piece.
[SPEAKER_06]: Does Sony need a figure like Major Nelson?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because, you know, Major Nelson is sort of like the internet guy for the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, he kind of, you know, in a way, he's kind of a viral campaign in a way.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you know, he starts buzz on his blog.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, he's a popular guy.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's on the system playing the games.
[SPEAKER_06]: People have run into him on Test Drive Unlimited and stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you go over to Nintendo and you have very charismatic folks like Reggie.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, we love Reggie.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Miyamoto, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: But Sony has...
[SPEAKER_06]: These guys, like, you know, as Jamie calls them, the crayon eaters and bike helmet, which, by the way, the photoshops in our forum that you guys did, fucking hilarious.
[SPEAKER_06]: We have the best listeners.
[SPEAKER_06]: Seriously, guys listening, if you've never visited our website, you must go to the forums just for this.
[SPEAKER_06]: The people doing the photoshops of the amazing crayon eaters over at Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: But anyway, Sony, you know, has these guys that make these crazy statements like this.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, does Sony need somebody a little more...
[SPEAKER_07]: What they need is Willy Wonka.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's going to take some fucking magic to sell those consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, some news about Oblivion on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we knew that there's got to be some catch to this.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're not going to be able to put Oblivion that we saw on the 360 on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no fucking way.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what we did find out, though, according to the...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Is any of it new?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or are they just recycled dungeons from the existing Oblivion?
[SPEAKER_07]: I have no idea.
[SPEAKER_06]: If so, I mean, what the hell is the point?
[SPEAKER_06]: It reminds me of those Game Boy Mortal Kombat games, which are fucking horrible compared to the console ones.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's like, you know, we had to take out half the moves because there's only two buttons and things like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, granted, the graphics for this Oblivion look kind of nice, but this is a game that should just simply be played on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or on a computer screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, I'm
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know, but... I will suspend disbelief until I actually get to play, get my hands on it and actually play it, but I worry about this whole concept.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, at least to... Why not like a little spin-off story?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do some slightly different dungeons and do like a spin-off story.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think that would be a lot more... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well... Wantable.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's... It's interesting, but I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: The game itself looks pretty.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, not as good as, obviously, the 360 one, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it looks okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: And like you mentioned, cutting out skills and stuff, 18 of the original game's 21 skills are going to be in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: A couple of them stripped out.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know, it's basically... Why don't they just release a 3D version of Diablo?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of like what this game is almost like, where you pick up items and just kind of grind at it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, I'm sure Diablo 3 will be something we're hearing about in 2007.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's just my thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: I swear I have not been ignoring you, chat room, over at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_06]: Click on chat.
[SPEAKER_06]: My mind just got distracted with trying to set up that game and everything a little bit ago.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it looks like Bobby Blackwolf is actually campaigning right now to be the voice of Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he'll get up there and be the voice of Sony.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll send you some Crayolas, Blackwolf, so you can start practicing.
[SPEAKER_06]: And then DMN follows up with, Nokia needs Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, the N-Gage needs a spokesman, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem with this, I mean, they...
[SPEAKER_07]: I really have trouble with them pushing games like the Eye of Judgment because it's going to take an elaborate setup to get to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: And to be honest, the Eye Toy didn't work all that great.
[SPEAKER_07]: And just a lot of the games that are coming out at launch, like Resistance, okay, it's a first-person shooter that takes place during World War II, which also happens to come out at the same time as Call of Duty 3, which is a first-person shooter that takes place during World War II, granted one's sci-fi, I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dragon Riding Game, Eragon, MotorStorm, EA Sports Games
[SPEAKER_07]: and Carbon.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, you first speak Carbon, which is actually a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Play the demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, and then the 2K sports games.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, like, as far as exclusive titles, I mean, there's not a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's, I think that's really gonna hurt them more than the fact that the console's three, you know, fucking expensive and that there's not that many units out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that there's, you know, people that are, like, actually gonna want, I mean, there'll be people that pick up the console, but a lot of people are like, well, I'm just gonna wait until some more games come out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sony fans, if you feel differently, send Loki an email.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mailbag at orange.radio.com Meanwhile, let's move on to something for the Nintendo fans, and this is a little bit more disappointment.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, we already heard about the consoles are definitely going to be region locked.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_06]: Eurogamer talked to a Nintendo UK spokesperson, and they confirmed that the Wii Virtual Console games will also be region locked.
[SPEAKER_06]: The Virtual Console games will also not be universal.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to play the original Metal Gear or Gartic Metal Gear here
[SPEAKER_06]: No, but the old school MSX, it was on the MSX before it was on the NES.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, and the true sequel to Metal Gear was not Snake's Revenge, but the true sequel to Metal Gear was only on the MSX.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I get, well, they had the whole PlayStation 2 secret thing, but whatever, I want it on the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gimme.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why I sound depressed, sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not too worried about it, I mean, big deal, I didn't play a lot of the import games on the NES, and whatever, I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's not like they were going to put all the games on there anyways.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, so, you know, do I really need a Japanese version of Zelda on there?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ranma speculates maybe you can get a Japanese Wii Connect 24 account.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blackboy says he was looking forward to Doki Doki.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Doki Doki Panic, the inspiration for Super Mario Bros.
2.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, well, the consoles themselves are probably region locked, but I'm sure you could probably like...
[SPEAKER_07]: Disable it or change that to something else, you know?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it's very easy to get a Japanese Xbox 360 account, so maybe that same logic.
[SPEAKER_06]: But at the same time, it's hard to pay for that, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, you can't really... Like, you only get the Japanese account so you can download their free demos and trailers, but you can't, you know, buy things on their store, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, luckily that there's no real money involved.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's basically the Nintendo points cards, or points, and you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You can still do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But what if the points cards are region locked?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Only the American...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, the points cards are just universal.
[SPEAKER_07]: And what's interesting, though, see, like, there is going to be some Xbox Live games that are exclusive to Japan, and I was going to buy them on my one account because you can actually play them on your, you know, US account, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I would download the demo on my Japanese account and register them on my US account.
[SPEAKER_06]: GS68 says, I want the Famicom version of Gradius 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: See, all these great games that really didn't ever come over here.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Nintendo, I think you ought to reconsider this.
[SPEAKER_06]: Or at least, if you're going to do this, please give the U.S.
[SPEAKER_06]: gamers a shot at some of these games they never played.
[SPEAKER_06]: I bet there's, you know, money to be made there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I think a lot of this, though, is going to be to eliminate confusion.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, if you're a normal consumer out there...
[SPEAKER_07]: What if you don't want to download the Japanese version of a certain game and you might accidentally do that and then you've wasted your money on it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, mark it very clearly.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's no amount of clear marketing that's going to stop stupid people from injuring themselves or downloading something they shouldn't be.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I'm done being emo.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's nothing more you can do, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some interesting stuff, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Reggie over in Tendo there is contradicting some of the info we've gotten about the pricing for the
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the web browser for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, his comments were basically, in fairness for the Americas, we haven't made the business decision for how and what we're going to do with the browser.
[SPEAKER_07]: We recognize for most people, browser is pretty standard.
[SPEAKER_07]: The concept of charging a significant amount of Wii points to get the browser is somewhat challenging.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to work through that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, basically saying, you know, we haven't announced anything yet about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: Wemo is an expensive piece of equipment.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's what, like $50?
$40?
[SPEAKER_06]: $50 it's retailing for?
$39.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: $39.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's very interesting that a third party is going to jump in and try to make their own version of the Wemo, but usually third party controllers aren't quite as good as first party.
[SPEAKER_06]: For me, I kind of go, uh-oh, if I were Nintendo, I'd be concerned about this because this is kind of like market saturation, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're the ones that have to approve it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I bet it won't come out right away.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's for sure.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Great, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo will sue!
[SPEAKER_07]: There's some controversy now, it's about the dumbest things too, about the light on the front of the Wii surrounding the disk drive, whether it's going to be on or off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And during the Nintendo Fusion Tour, there's actually, the light was completely turned off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And some people are like, well, hey, I want my light on, what the hell?
[SPEAKER_07]: So, here's my theory on this whole thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, what they've come out and said, the rep,
[SPEAKER_07]: was that the light's only going to be on when you put a disc in or when you turn the console on and that it's going to turn off later on.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there's either going to be an option to keep it on or the fact that probably those games that you were playing weren't running on that Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: They were probably running on a dev kit that was below the Wii and that the system just wasn't plugged in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, I was going to say, when we went to the Konami thing, didn't we see Elebits?
[SPEAKER_06]: The thing was glowing the whole time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_06]: But of course, that same logic could apply.
[SPEAKER_06]: It could have been hooked up to a dev kit.
[SPEAKER_06]: It doesn't mean shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they could have just had the console plugged in and turned on and so the light glows.
[SPEAKER_07]: But if it's hooked, you're actually playing off of a dev kit and not the actual system.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I mean, in theory, you could just, if you're limited on plugs or whatever for power, you could just not plug that in and just set that there because...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_06]: Our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio or you can always pick up the phone and call us 916-226-9067 Can't remember if I mentioned it last week but there is an 800 number coming soon because the number we have now is not toll free but by the end of the month we're going to have a toll free number which is very exciting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm very much looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_06]: and then we'll have a lot more folks wanting to call in, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll probably bring back voicemails of the week at that point because we think more of you guys might want to contribute if you have a toll-free number to use because most of you are just too lazy for Skype, I guess.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's up, guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_06]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_02]: Not much, not much.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was trying to record the last part of the show so I just got back from another anime convention.
[SPEAKER_06]: Another anime convention?
[SPEAKER_06]: Which one this time?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Manga...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's nothing but a convention about mangas and fans and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_06]: So no video games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, there were no tournaments, but let's just say older gamers like us would have cried tears of joy at the games that were there.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did they bring?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we saw a working Nintendo set up with Super Mario Bros.
3.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's pretty hot.
[SPEAKER_06]: Did they have Guardian Legend?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they didn't have that.
[SPEAKER_02]: The older guy that ran the game told them next year.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that works for me.
[SPEAKER_06]: Anything else you want to share about the con?
[SPEAKER_06]: What else?
[SPEAKER_02]: It was fun, and it was basically drama-free, because everybody just had to have a good time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Nobody bashing Orange Moms Radio to you this year?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, not this year, not this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love our anime fans that go to the conventions and then bash us to other people.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's lovely.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, I'm just teasing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's cool, whatever, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: People have their varying opinions.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's about 500 video game podcasts out there.
[SPEAKER_06]: If you don't like this one, go find another one.
[SPEAKER_06]: Just keep it independent is all we ask.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, anything else you want to share?
[SPEAKER_02]: There was a few Super Nintendo set up, a couple of Playstations, and yes, there was Guitar Hero on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: There was what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Guitar Hero on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, Guitar Hero on the big screen.
[SPEAKER_06]: How did that go over?
[SPEAKER_02]: That was pretty nice.
[SPEAKER_02]: That and DDR Extreme 2 were like the top, part of the top five.
[SPEAKER_02]: You also had Not Ultimate Hero 4 and Battle Station DLN are also popular.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well we're going to let you go so we can take some more calls, okay?
[SPEAKER_02]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, have a good one and we hope for some more old school gaming goodness at the next con.
[SPEAKER_05]: Damn right.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_06]: Later.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to another call here on our Skype line.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hello, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, this is El Mullet calling.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, we remember you.
[SPEAKER_06]: You haven't called into this show in a long time.
[SPEAKER_06]: How are you, El Mullet?
[SPEAKER_06]: I am doing just fine, Sky.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm doing just fine.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have you ever called into the podcast?
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't think so.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, this is my first podcast call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Your podcast debut.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know you used to listen to the three-hour show back in the day.
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was fun times.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, from what I mean, yeah, crazy random times.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, that's great.
[SPEAKER_06]: We love our history.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, you're getting married next week, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_06]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_00]: Is she a gamer?
[SPEAKER_00]: Slightly.
[SPEAKER_00]: I am learning her.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's good.
[SPEAKER_06]: There's got to be compromise in a relationship, right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Right, Loki?
[SPEAKER_00]: We're mostly DS playing.
[SPEAKER_00]: We do New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_00]: vs. We do Tetris vs. Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: What did you want to call in about tonight?
[SPEAKER_06]: What's up?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm basically wanting to say hi.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's your hand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you still doing your column over at Inside Pulse?
[SPEAKER_00]: Actually, I've quote-unquote left Inside Pulse.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's just been a lot of stuff going on.
[SPEAKER_00]: I see.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm trying to find work.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's obviously the marriage thing.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, things have just been...
[SPEAKER_00]: Lots of stuff has been going on, and I've been trying to catch up on everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: I understand.
[SPEAKER_06]: Lives go through chaos sometimes.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's fully understandable.
[SPEAKER_06]: What games have you been playing recently?
[SPEAKER_06]: Did you check out DDR Supernova?
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, yes.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've been having a blast with that game.
[SPEAKER_00]: There are a few songs I could have done without, but I like the setup of Stellar Master Mode.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really like the fact... I think it's the best...
[SPEAKER_00]: What's the word?
[SPEAKER_00]: Console licenses.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's the best lineup thus far, especially songs like The Other Side, Turn Up the Music.
[SPEAKER_00]: Um...
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you think the game compares to the other PlayStation 2 releases that are out there?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was just at Target the other day, and they had a DDR Supernova bundle right next to Extreme 2 bundles they still hadn't sold.
[SPEAKER_06]: So definitely options are still available to the new DDR folks that want to get on board with this.
[SPEAKER_06]: How do you think it compares to the other ones?
[SPEAKER_00]: Well, I definitely think that it's definitely on par with Extreme 2 as far as best US PS2 mix.
[SPEAKER_00]: There's definitely stuff in there that make me go, wow, this is much better.
[SPEAKER_00]: But then there are other things that make me go, hey, it was better in Extreme 2.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like I think the chorus mode, we got shafted with chorus mode this time.
[SPEAKER_00]: Because there's only one difficulty level on everything, whereas last game, you had two difficulty levels on everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: What do you think about how the new Xbox games are shaping up?
[SPEAKER_00]: I think they're shaping up really well.
[SPEAKER_00]: Your podcasts are definitely making them more favorable by the day.
[SPEAKER_06]: I appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll let Konami know you said that.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, seriously though, if you were still reviewing games for the website, how many stars out of 10 would you be giving DDR Supernova?
[SPEAKER_00]: DDR Supernova, well, that would be under the 10 category review system.
[SPEAKER_00]: I gave Extreme 2 a 7.5 and said that was the best one ever.
[SPEAKER_00]: which is like a 9.0 on other websites.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I would say that Supernova would range between a 7.0, 7.5 because there's stuff that's better and there's stuff that's worse.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it would be around the same score, I would think.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, what's up with that?
[SPEAKER_06]: You brought up an interesting point is that a 7.5, the way you would review games, and if I wrote game reviews, I would hope I would be very similar as well where like, you know, an
[SPEAKER_06]: Average game gets an average score in the middle.
[SPEAKER_06]: But it seems like most game websites, you're right, kind of skew it towards the high end.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's what I get.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, games that are reviewed on IGN, they'll have a score for each category and then a score that doesn't have anything to do with any category on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, for example, a game might score seven fives across the board on all the other categories and get a six overall.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like,
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, how the hell is that average out?
[SPEAKER_06]: Or I'm thinking about like on Rotten Tomatoes, like, you know, because they cover game reviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't do it quite as well as they do movies, but it says we only give a fresh rating if the site gave it a 7 or better because of the skewed, you know, people tend to give higher scores on game reviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why do you think that is, Emily?
[SPEAKER_06]: The problem is...
[SPEAKER_00]: The problem is that so many of these numbers are pulled directly out of their asses, and most of these numbers don't even correspond to what the written opinions are on the game.
[SPEAKER_00]: I've seen 7.0s on some sites, on some game reviews, and the bottom line is, don't play this.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's the way that Inside Pulse reviews games.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's out of a 10-category system.
[SPEAKER_00]: and it could really excel in some areas, but there are other areas that could bring the game down.
[SPEAKER_00]: A game could have a great story, but horrible graphics and sound.
[SPEAKER_00]: The game could have great gameplay mechanics, but it can only be fun for the first three hours.
[SPEAKER_00]: Basically, the games have to be really awesome in all categories to get 8 and above.
[SPEAKER_00]: But a game can be worth playing at a 7 or even a 6.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, yeah, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: I was going to say, I hope to see that you come back to the internet soon reviewing games and sticking to the more realistic scale that you started over there.
[SPEAKER_00]: You just might see a Supernova review before the end of the week, assuming I have enough time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Very cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Elmoled, I've got to let you go so we can get some more calls, but thank you so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_00]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_00]: You too.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: How exciting, a wedding, getting married and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_05]: Uh, Ultimate Gamer from Chad.
[SPEAKER_05]: Well, I'm currently not in chat right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, hello, Ultimate Gamer.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, yeah, I'm just, uh, thinking about the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_05]: Now it has a $200 HD DVD drive.
[SPEAKER_05]: And, um, uh, like, am I just gonna have to, like, should I just get a PS3?
[SPEAKER_05]: because since the Blu-ray drive is implemented into the PS3 and games are actually on Blu-ray discs.
[SPEAKER_06]: Gotcha.
[SPEAKER_06]: Okay, I see.
[SPEAKER_06]: This is where you're going.
[SPEAKER_06]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: Are you interested in just playing movies with this device, or are you going to be playing games as well?
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, I'm mostly getting the PS3 for games, but I know the Xbox 360 has some good games.
[SPEAKER_05]: Right.
[SPEAKER_05]: The PS3s are actually on Blu-ray discs.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think it really boils down to, you know, which console has the games that you want.
[SPEAKER_06]: And, you know, Microsoft gets a lot of heat usually because they overlook, or at least they have in the past, they don't have a lot of solid role-playing type games.
[SPEAKER_06]: They don't have a lot of solid action games.
[SPEAKER_06]: And they've been trying to correct that, you know, you got Blue Dragon coming out and they, you know, they had Cameo, take that for whatever it's worth.
[SPEAKER_06]: But, you know, Sony's always kind of excelled in that range.
[SPEAKER_06]: But on the flip side, Sony doesn't seem to have a strong lineup right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you have to kind of look more into the future at what Sony's got.
[SPEAKER_06]: And Microsoft is trying to correct themselves.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you kind of saw that with Tokyo Game Show.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're trying to take a more broad approach to different games.
[SPEAKER_06]: So you really have to ask yourself, which of these two systems is going to have the games I want to play?
[SPEAKER_06]: Because remember what we always say, the golden rule of gaming, a system is only as good as the games that are on it.
[SPEAKER_06]: And when it comes down to the whole... I guess here's another question I have for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where does the we stand in your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Do you not care about the Wii?
[SPEAKER_06]: So I would say take that same logic and put it on Xbox 360 versus PlayStation 3 because it's not really going to matter, you know, Blu-ray, HD, DVD, whatever.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's going to be really about the games in the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_06]: I've seen Blu-ray and HD, DVD side by side.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's really not that much different.
[SPEAKER_06]: The spec-wise, they're about the same, too, other than data.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I do understand what you're saying, is that Sony, and I do agree, this could be to their advantage in three years, is that Sony has the native Blu-ray support for the games, and while right now it's causing the system to cost your firstborn child, later on, when we get further down within the subdivisions of this generation, that could really benefit them in the end.
[SPEAKER_06]: XBOX 360
[SPEAKER_05]: It's just like, you know, having an HDTV will make the game high definition.
[SPEAKER_06]: True, that's true.
[SPEAKER_06]: But also, don't forget the other part I'm trying to say here is that, you know, doesn't it boil down to how good the games are, though?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not necessarily how they look, because, you know, being on Blu-ray, certainly they're going to look better.
[SPEAKER_06]: But if you're going to buy a Wii, then you must already be into that school of thought that it really is about the fun games.
[SPEAKER_07]: And granted that Blu-ray does have more storage available to it, doesn't mean though that they'll use it all, and also doesn't mean that the games that are on DVD-9s are going to look any less brilliant than, say, a PlayStation 3 game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at Gears of War and Resistance.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perfect example.
[SPEAKER_07]: They both look very good, and
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm just messing with you, but, you know, I know you're probably right now.
[SPEAKER_06]: You want one this year, and maybe you'll get the other one next year?
[SPEAKER_05]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_05]: I know I'm getting the Wii first.
[SPEAKER_05]: I mean, PS3, I get a couple months down the road, but, you know, I think, you know, the games, they should be like, you know,
[SPEAKER_06]: I think... But also good graphics.
[SPEAKER_06]: Right.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think you're on the right track then.
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, if the Wii is... It sounds like you really, really, really want the Wii, you know, then go for that, buy that, and then when you have enough money saved up for a second console, look at the games that are out and or coming out and make your decision at that time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thanks, really love the show, and great RSS feed.
[SPEAKER_05]: I listen to it on my PSP every week, and I get no buffering signs or anything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm glad to hear there's people still using OLRPSP.com, so Loki, go update it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know sometimes we give the PSP a hard time on this show, but it is a great multimedia, multi-platform system, and we're really glad to be able to offer our podcast on it.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_05]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_05]: All right, bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: That was a good call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, let's go to another call here.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: Uh... Oh, I... Am I on?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you are.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, sorry about that.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Legend of Zakum.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, buddy.
[SPEAKER_06]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_06]: Uh, Digital Lice next week.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know it is, and I'm not going... I'm missing it by a week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, it's... Wait, wasn't it this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, Nintendo's doing a lot of good things with the Wii, but then all the good things end up turning up sour, you know, when you really think about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The whole having to lock down, you know, region, regioning on, you know, the games and the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_10]: Isn't that going to hurt them in the long run?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I agree it sucks and all, but, you know, the NES was region locked too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, but that was easy to get, you know, it wasn't as hard.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was Zen.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, when you have the PS3 being region free, couldn't they just compete on that?
[SPEAKER_06]: I gotta be honest with you.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know the folks that listen to this show because the way myself, Loki, and DarkSakura are is that we are focused a lot on import gaming.
[SPEAKER_06]: And we really do enjoy a lot of the games that come over here from Japan.
[SPEAKER_06]: So from our perspective, yeah, it's really fucked up that Nintendo's not supporting the region.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you had a single version of a game without having to do any porting,
[SPEAKER_10]: Any extra work in trying to localize it to a particular country, you know, rather doing the language as a first time, would that make more sense than just releasing one copy?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's a lot of work, though, because you have to do all those different languages and things.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, if it's got to have French for parts of Canada, Japanese... But that's, you know, but just keeping that in the single source.
[SPEAKER_06]: Maybe, but here's... Okay, here's my other question for you would be then...
[SPEAKER_06]: About the Wii, what about the greater gamer culture out there besides just us, the rabid import gamers?
[SPEAKER_10]: Are they going to give a shit?
[SPEAKER_10]: Casual gamers won't give a crap about what we're bitching about.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, that's a fact.
[SPEAKER_10]: Casual gamers just want to play, period.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so what the Wii does is gives them that opportunity to just play.
[SPEAKER_10]: which is basically Nintendo's banking on right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're just banking on the casual gamers to pretty much dominate this holiday season.
[SPEAKER_06]: So my question is, in the big picture, will it really make a difference that they've region locked out?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: It would affect some, but then Nintendo wouldn't care because our niche minority is not their bottom line.
[SPEAKER_10]: Their bottom line is about everyone, the casual gamer included.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_06]: Interesting comment in our chatroom.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ari Massen says, I'm a large importer.
[SPEAKER_06]: I might buy two Wii's just to play both Japanese and American games.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Nintendo just won off you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, that's basically what people did when the PS2 first came out.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, that's what I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hey, Sony made it twice off me, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And, you know, who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: There might be a way to just crack the Wii like they did with the GameCube to play imports.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so you've got to give those opportunities time.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right, Zach, any other thoughts for our listeners?
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, New York people, Digital Life, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
[SPEAKER_06]: Where's a good meet-up spot at Digital Life?
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, I'm not really sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe in the front lobby of the Javits Center.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or maybe inside the DDR tournament area.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right, so Orange Loungers, be at the DDR machine Saturday at noon.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: The OLR meetup.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes, the OLR meetup right there with the DDR tournament.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_09]: It's Saturday at noon.
[SPEAKER_09]: Alright, have fun.
[SPEAKER_09]: Be there.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, later, Saku.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: One more call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Last call.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_03]: It's DMN.
[SPEAKER_03]: How's it going, guys?
[SPEAKER_06]: Goddamn, you get through every week.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know, and I keep paying you, you know.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well, what's up, DMN?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm actually calling with a... Well, now having heard that last call, I have something else.
[SPEAKER_03]: But the first thing is a little brief review of Clubhouse Games for the DS.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want Clubhouse Games.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally forgot about this game until somebody was talking about it in chat earlier.
[SPEAKER_07]: Dude, the only reason I want to get this game is because you can PictoChat over the internet.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, you can't.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not buying it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fuck you, Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what you get.
[SPEAKER_03]: You can PictoChat over local Wi-Fi while you're playing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I can do that already.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, you can't do PictoChat while you're playing a game, though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I can do it while I'm playing Ping Pals.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I'm sorry you bought that.
[SPEAKER_06]: No, it was a gift.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a very nice gift, but fuck that game, seriously.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry that that was bought for you.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's like, no, no, no, I mean, it was a very sweet person that gave it to me.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm not saying anything negative about the game, but seriously, it was like getting a fruitcake for Christmas, okay?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know Grandma loves you, but you got a damn fruitcake.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, well, Clubhouse Games is really cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: What's really awesome about it is, with the Wi-Fi mode, you can play all of the multiplayer games online, which is like about 36, I think, when I come back to it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, see, that's cool to me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and it's great because I'm a casual gamer as well as a hardcore gamer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I love playing, like, Checkers, Chess, whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: So this is fun for me because I can play with my friends all around the world, and at the same time, it's games I know how to play.
[SPEAKER_06]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now, what other kind of like features does this have kind of souped up with the games?
[SPEAKER_06]: You know, there's like 30 some odd games, which I suppose is a big selling point, but what are some other features that might sell this game to people?
[SPEAKER_03]: The fact that it's under the Touch Generations label, which is Nintendo's label for games anyone can pick up and play.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you could... Sorry, lost in thought there.
[SPEAKER_03]: You could pick up anything on this and immediately want to play it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um...
[SPEAKER_03]: and from what I hear, it might be affordable.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hear it might retail at the very most expensive $29.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hmm, interesting.
[SPEAKER_06]: Loki, do you know how much that's retailing for?
[SPEAKER_07]: What thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Clubhouse games?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you know how much that's going for?
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to say $19.99 or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a really good deal if that's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't remember off the top of my head.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you give me a second, I can check.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, well, you do that.
[SPEAKER_06]: What else did you want to say, DMN, while he's checking?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, now hearing about that whole Wii region lock...
[SPEAKER_03]: It could be very possible that sometime down the road Nintendo could release a firmware update to eliminate that issue.
[SPEAKER_06]: Why would they do that?
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_03]: Perhaps maybe Nintendo will realize the error of their ways sometime down the road and be like, oh, hey, these people want to play our Japanese titles.
[SPEAKER_03]: They can't ignore the fact that Oh and Don was one of the most imported games of 2006.
[SPEAKER_03]: True.
[SPEAKER_03]: and they said, okay, fine, we're going to give you Elite Beat Agents.
[SPEAKER_03]: But if there's an Owen Don game coming out for the Wii, I want it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't want to have to buy another Wii or crack my Wii open to play it on my American console.
[SPEAKER_06]: I totally understand what you're saying because it's as cool as Elite Beat Agents might be, it's not Owen Don.
[SPEAKER_06]: It's not the same song list which in a music game is everything.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So...
[SPEAKER_06]: And that's what DarkTetsuya agrees in chat right there, but Elite Beat Agents is an entirely different game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, did you find the answer, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_06]: What?
$29.99.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Blast.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's alright, $29 is not a bad price, really, for that many games.
[SPEAKER_06]: But I mean, they're not all like shitty clones of each other, right?
[SPEAKER_06]: Like, they're all like uniquely different, pretty cool games?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, they're all uniquely different, and... That's cool.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've already played a couple games of Wi-Fi, there is nothing like a good Wi-Fi game of BS.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_03]: and definitely nothing like a good Wi-Fi game of Speed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm totally going to be playing some of our chatters in Speed.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'll buy this game just for that.
[SPEAKER_06]: You could have just released Speed and I'd buy that.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's a great game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, well I'll be picking up the game and we'll post on the forums and get an OLR get-together on the Clubhouse Games at some point.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, cool.
[SPEAKER_06]: DMN, thanks so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a wonderful week.
[SPEAKER_06]: Bye-bye.
[SPEAKER_06]: Alright, that's going to do it for the Skyflying tonight.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_06]: Sorry to those folks who didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_06]: Try again next time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Any last minute stories you want to share, Loki?
[SPEAKER_06]: Of course I do.
[SPEAKER_06]: I know, you always do.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, some wonderful stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, one thing about the Wii, since we were just talking about it, the Miis that you create, actually, they're going to be popping up in different things.
[SPEAKER_07]: For example, in games, you might see the other Miis that you've created in the audience, or in the stands for certain games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, they will be possibly migrating to other Wii systems, kind of like Animal Crossing, so that's kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh, that's kind of neat, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: So it's not just your face in Wii Sports as the tennis wielder, you might just, you might start
[SPEAKER_06]: infecting other consoles.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some other cool stuff, Rainbow Six Vegas is going to be seeing a demo on Xbox Live on October 23rd.
[SPEAKER_07]: That game looked pretty amazing, so worth checking out.
[SPEAKER_07]: As we mentioned before with GT, that it was going to have a steering wheel attachment for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Monster 4x4 World Circuit, another Ubisoft racing game, will also have that same steering wheel attachment as well for the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Earthworm Jim
[SPEAKER_07]: And then there was a survey that went out for Guitar Hero that mentioned two games that are possibly in the works.
[SPEAKER_07]: Keyboard Hero and Drummer Hero.
[SPEAKER_07]: In no way, I'm sure, ripping off any Konami franchises with those.
[SPEAKER_07]: But interesting nonetheless.
[SPEAKER_06]: Oh yeah, I heard about that survey that went out.
[SPEAKER_06]: I don't know though.
[SPEAKER_06]: I think people might be reading too much into that whole thing.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: There was also a really cool product that was released called Connect360 that indexes your iTunes and iPhoto libraries to stream them to the 360, which is interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to check that out, it's www.nullriver.com slash index slash products slash connect360.
[SPEAKER_07]: So go check that out.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then some more adult content that is available out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: For Dead or Alive Extreme 2, you will be getting changing sequences.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, the girls will change.
[SPEAKER_06]: Like in Final Fantasy X-2?
[SPEAKER_06]: The girls will change.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, yes.
[SPEAKER_06]: I knew it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's not like... It says it will be anime-inspired, resembling a transformation sequence you'd find in something like Sailor Moon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Curious.
[SPEAKER_07]: Horrors of Warcraft 7.95
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's real people.
[SPEAKER_07]: This isn't Machima or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they actually also have a MySpace community if you want to join that, which is MySpace.com slash Hordes of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_06]: I should also mention Orange Lounge Radio has a MySpace community that's more worth your time.
[SPEAKER_06]: MySpace.com slash Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: But they have some chick that looks like she has elf ears.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Get your elf porn going on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: I have received a hot tip.
[SPEAKER_06]: from a trusted source that WarioWare for the Wii is going to be bumped up to a launch title and you will be seeing that very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, good, because I have that pre-ordered and it was only slated for January.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, it looks like you may actually get your WarioWare on in November.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: So take that as you will.
[SPEAKER_06]: I want to see Wii Play come out as a launch title too.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura will be back next week to keep us in line and to read the emails and give you her website of the week, of which there is none this week because she's not here.
[SPEAKER_06]: and next week as well we'll have more you guys in our chat room and on the Skype line and more news and hopefully some interviews.
[SPEAKER_06]: We are trying to get some interviews lined up for the rest of the month on through the year and thank you guys so much for tuning in to us and supporting Independent Radio.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, Loki, your final thought?
[SPEAKER_06]: My final thought is I have two episodes of my new show done already.
[SPEAKER_06]: Both an hour long.
[SPEAKER_06]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_06]: And you'll be, yes, Orange Launch Radio will be participating in November sweeps this year.
[SPEAKER_06]: That's all I can say.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my final thought will be, well, on behalf of Jamie not being here, I will say reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_06]: And my other final thought would be how in the hell did six bottles of Aquafina end up over on Extra First's desk?
[SPEAKER_06]: That's kind of scary.
[SPEAKER_06]: They're all like half empty.
[SPEAKER_06]: Actually, quite a bit of them are mostly full.
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell?
[SPEAKER_06]: What the hell is wrong with this picture?
[SPEAKER_06]: Such a waster.
[SPEAKER_06]: Waster of water.
[SPEAKER_06]: All those countries out there that are like, you know, dehydrated.
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you guys so much for tuning in to us.
[SPEAKER_06]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_06]: Have a great week.
[SPEAKER_06]: We'll see you next time here on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've been listening to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_02]: Orange Lounge Radio is an Orange Lounge production.
[SPEAKER_02]: For more information on our live and podcast programs, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com See you next week.