[SPEAKER_06]: Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream twice weekly.
[SPEAKER_06]: To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links to websites with listings of past episodes.
[SPEAKER_06]: Now the conclusion of this week's episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: And we are back here on Orange Lounge Radio on this episode number 202 for this October the 1st of 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can't believe the year is almost over at this point.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: Time just flies by.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well let's get back into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, let's start us off with the Zune.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Zune, it sounds like loon.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyways, Microsoft's brand new MP3 movie, you name it, player.
[SPEAKER_08]: They announced some details at XO6 about how exactly it's going to work and some of the online things.
[SPEAKER_08]: The 30GB version of the Zune will be sold for $249.99 when they're on sale November 14th in the United States.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says the price of music is in two choices.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can either buy a monthly pass for $0.99, which will give you hearing access to all the songs in the Zune marketplace.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there is a catch.
[SPEAKER_08]: You will not be able to listen to the songs once the...
[SPEAKER_08]: If you want to permanently buy any song, you can make it yours by spending 79 Microsoft points.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right, the same Microsoft points you would be buying Doom on Xbox Live Arcade you can be spending on music.
[SPEAKER_08]: And of course, 79 points is roughly about 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can either purchase the song for 99 cents, or you can pay, I guess, a monthly fee and listen to all the music for 99 cents.
[SPEAKER_08]: But you probably have to download it each time.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, it's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: Debit and all that stuff were practically there.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: One of the technologies they were showing off was a thumbprint scanner.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's basically a thumbprint scanner, and then you enter in your phone number, and you'll deduct money from your checking or savings account just using your thumbprint.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's pretty much going to be like the wave of the future.
[SPEAKER_02]: They also have this thing where they have a chip stored in a fake tooth that's fireproof, you know, bashproof pretty much, so that if you were to be horribly, say, horribly burned...
[SPEAKER_02]: In a fire, they can still identify your remains without DNA testing.
[SPEAKER_02]: You've got your tooth there with your medical records and all your information.
[SPEAKER_08]: Without having to play, let's name the burn victim!
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, to get back into gaming news.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep in mind, I was a big tech TV fangirl.
[SPEAKER_02]: For fans of Saints Row, there is a thing called the Thunky Fresh Pack.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's 100 Microsoft points, and it has clothes, tattoos, hairstyles...
[SPEAKER_02]: For use in single and multiplayer modes, you've also got tiger-striped underwear, bunny slippers, an eye patch, and a samurai helmet, medallions, and rattlesnake tattoos.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gee, do I spend the 100 points to buy this crap, or should I get a copy of London Bridge for my Zune?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think, uh... Some people like the customization.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some people like Fergie.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh my god, I had to listen to that CD yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: I characterize it as a pimp hat now, and it's dressed in really nice clothes.
[SPEAKER_08]: All purple, of course, because I've got to represent things for all colors in order to get the more, you know, I guess, points, you know, for missions and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, um, I don't know, this was kind of like the same thing we were talking about, you know, a while back, which was rumored to be coming to the kiosk at GameStop for free, uh,
[SPEAKER_08]: Robotron 2084 Microsoft Points
[SPEAKER_07]: on Xbox 360, Satan's Hollow, Sinistar, Spy Hunter, and Tapper.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, you can play those all online on Midway's website.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right now, if you want, it's midwayarcade.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, who needs Midway Arcade Treasures, huh?
[SPEAKER_07]: You got all that available for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Enjoy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_08]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: You gotta save money for those PlayStation 3 games, of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: And as we mentioned earlier...
[SPEAKER_08]: They are going to be retailing for about $59.99 for the most part, which is expected.
[SPEAKER_08]: Most current-gen games are peaking at about $49.99, most actually which are $39.99 now, and now the next-gen games are going to try to be getting $59.99 retail for most everything.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is pretty much confirmed by, say, sites like SonyStyle and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some games might not be $59.99 like Gran Turismo HD.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a surprise, I would say.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm still waiting for those companies out there to get greedy and start charging more.
[SPEAKER_07]: As long as those $70 and $80 rumors don't come true.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be honest, I don't think they are.
[SPEAKER_08]: If anything, they'll try to nickel and dime you on the back end with their online content.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what it's going to end up being.
[SPEAKER_08]: Instead of
[SPEAKER_08]: Charging $70, they can charge $900 and charge $50 for the game or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_07]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: Jamie.
[SPEAKER_02]: I win.
[SPEAKER_07]: Release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: UK release dates.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was the ferret translating.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Coming out on 1st October, VeggieTales, Larry Boy and the Bad Apple on Game Boy Advance and PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 6th, we have Barnyard for a bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have Capcom Puzzle World on PSP, Heroes of Annihilated Empires on the PC, Import Tuner Challenge on Xbox 360, Mage Knight Apocalypse on PC, the Nintendo DS browser on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was a bad joke.
[SPEAKER_02]: Open Season coming out on damn near everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: Put out by Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_02]: Wild Arms 4 on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have to say the Wild Arms series is a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have a friend who's absolutely addicted to that game, so Wild Arms 4 is good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did Wild Arms Ultra F ever come out over there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not a series I played.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, let me know if it ever came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: A few things coming up though in the months to look forward to is Power Stone Collection for PSP.
[SPEAKER_02]: English Training, Have Fun Improving Your Skills on the DS.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's actually pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Resident Evil 4 Platinum, Sims 2 Pets coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're getting Dragon Ball Z, Tenkaichi Budokai 2, and Metal Slug Anthology.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: The US isn't going to see too much this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some pretty good games there.
[SPEAKER_08]: FIFA Soccer 07, if you're a soccer fan, coming out in almost every single system.
[SPEAKER_08]: You do have also Star Trek Encounters coming out in the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: A great Star Trek combat game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very cheap.
$19.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, check it out if you can.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think, actually, it might even be $14.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know it's very cheap, but that's all I know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, another crappy game, Snowcross 2, featuring Air Blur Morgan.
[SPEAKER_08]: and, by the way, this game has been delayed for a year, so it's crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see, Mercury Meltdown for the PSP, which, you know, sequel for the first Mercury game, and I don't know if this is worth your money, but if you want, pick it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gangs of London, definitely a better game for the PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, on the PC, we have El Matador and Paparazzi.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, that's some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, how could I not forget, Scarface, PlayStation 2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, a lot of places are reporting that this is the 8th of October, but it's actually the 5th.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has a soft street date on it, so stores will be getting it on the 5th, but they cannot advertise it until the 8th.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, weird.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go bug your GameStops, because that's probably the game you're going to want that week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, over in Japan, we have some release dates for the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, not a whole lot coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of a slow week over there as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: NBA Live 07 and FIFA Soccer 07, both coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shinobido Imashime, also known as Spike the Best, is coming out over there this week as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And Dragon Ball Z Sparking Neo is coming out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Front Mission 5 in the Ultimate Hits Collection hit stores this week in Japan as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: And for you music game fans who have about $250 to spare, you can get your Guitar Freaks ASC arcade-style controller this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, as far as other releases for the UK going back to them, they're actually for fans who are football fans.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's Pro Evolution Soccer 6 coming out on PlayStation 2, Xbox 360, and PC on 27th October.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, not by Konami.
[SPEAKER_02]: PSP and DS versions will be coming.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are... They're actually stating that the 360 version is going to be noticeably improved.
[SPEAKER_02]: The AI, anyway, is... There will be...
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually specifically named it in areas like the AI players running into space.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's not going to happen.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also runs in high definition and widescreen.
[SPEAKER_02]: It will also feature new licensed clubs including Manchester United, Benfica, Sporting Lisbon, and Olympiasos.
[SPEAKER_02]: New kits and squads for Czech, French, Australian, English, Italian, Argentinian teams.
[SPEAKER_02]: Spanish and Swedish National.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, I know we've got some football fans listening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Goal!
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's so hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, he's up for doing more 2D Castlevanias, so maybe we'll see some exclusive stuff on the next-gen marketplaces.
[SPEAKER_07]: Please, some more 2D Castlevania.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or just, even just some, you know, you can do that subtle hints of 3D, kind of like if you look at Symphony of the Night.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, just make a real grand 2D Castlevania for the next-gen.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because, you know, your next-gen doesn't mean everything has to be 3D.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at a game like Beautiful Joe.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a great 2D using next-gen graphics.
[SPEAKER_01]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, if you still want to live in the current generation, well, this might be the controller for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is a controller that would be great for throwing against the wall.
[SPEAKER_07]: Everybody has a friend like this, somebody who gets so frustrated, or maybe a sibling, that they throw the controller against the wall, or they throw it at people when they get really frustrated with the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now you have a Nerf controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, there's a PlayStation 2 controller that's covered in Nerf,
[SPEAKER_07]: It's like this bluish color here.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's coming out for the PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's wireless.
[SPEAKER_07]: It comes in black, blue, red, or orange.
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be about $30 and comes out in November of 2006.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, the official Nerf controller.
[SPEAKER_07]: Perfect for throwing around.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although I wouldn't recommend it.
[SPEAKER_07]: You could still break the damn thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or somebody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's still kind of heavy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just because it's Nerf made doesn't mean it's safe to chuck at people's heads.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it at least would hurt a lot less.
[SPEAKER_08]: Speaking about breaking people, there was the Uwe Boll boxing matches going on recently, and as expected, you know, nothing's going to be fair when it comes down to Uwe Boll.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, actually, Richard Lotax Kanka was one of the people from Something Awful to actually be able to fight in this, and he kind of gave a little bit of a
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: and Oogaball doesn't like a fair fight.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, out of the four people, including one 17-year-old, everyone pretty much got beat the crap out of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is that legal?
[SPEAKER_07]: To beat the crap out of a 17-year-old like that?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I guess it was Canada.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe the laws are different there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess he signed a waiver.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe the parents signed a waiver as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: The video's out there on YouTube, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be honest, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the
[SPEAKER_08]: Richard Lotex, his whole thing is he didn't really hate Uebol before this whole thing, and now he does.
[SPEAKER_08]: He thinks he's a douche, basically.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wonderdog Harold sums it up in our chatroom and says, Uebol is such a pig fucker.
[SPEAKER_08]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, big deal.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you beat up some critics.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, you beat up critics that had no boxing training, and then one person that actually might give you some competition.
[SPEAKER_08]: You pussied out, you fucker.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't one of the critics that came out of this say that, you know, although the fight was kind of a joke, the new movie's not bad?
[SPEAKER_07]: Or something like the clips they saw from the new movie didn't seem that bad?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't see how they could mess up, you know, Postal.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it doesn't... That one I'm interested in seeing, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I think the new movie, in the name of the king or whatever...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh God, Robway linked me this article.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's aligning himself with the defense for some case.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just a bunch of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you'll notice I purposefully omitted that from tonight's show role because I didn't want to give him any more attention.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, the one thing that I think is worth mentioning for this is that it's probably something to likely get him disbarred in that state, so let's hope that happens.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, God, all this talk of Uwe Boll and Jack Thompson puts me in a foul mood, so you know what that means, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: FUs of the Week, DarkSakura My FU of the Week goes primarily, there are some exceptions, to straight men.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yes, just because I'm a woman doesn't give you the right to look at me, see me there, and then proceed to back into me and elbow me in the shoulder while trying to take a picture at the wax museum.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then it doesn't give you permission to just expect me to move out of the way when you're gonna open a door.
[SPEAKER_02]: I paid to be there.
[SPEAKER_02]: You are going to freaking respect my personal space.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: And your cock.
[SPEAKER_07]: But not literally.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: It goes to this whole attitude of I'm a man, you're a woman, you have to move, you have to do what I say, blah blah blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: The whole... I hate how...
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope you're not... this isn't... Well, I'm just saying, how did you know his sexual orientation?
[SPEAKER_02]: His wife was there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Does that mean anything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Trust me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have infallible gay darks.
[SPEAKER_02]: These people... The only way that I think that there would be any remotely gay vibe coming from them is if they were like, you know, bare leather daddies or something.
[SPEAKER_07]: All our listeners of the show are accepted from this, fuck you, right?
[SPEAKER_02]: We're gonna drink beer and go to Hooters
[SPEAKER_02]: We're gonna, to quote Margaret Cho, we're gonna order titties with ranch dressing and celery sticks.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's just... Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_02]: And no, like I said, this is not centered toward all straight men.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is just centered toward stupid straight men.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Loki, speaking of stupid straight men, Loki, you know they actually serve Hooters at Hooters?
[SPEAKER_08]: That might be worth, you know, a price of admission right there, but their food's actually
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, no, actually, ironically enough, fuck you, the stupid women drivers who can't fucking pay attention on the road because you're talking to your kids or talking on the cell phone or fucking around with something on your dash.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, I know I understand that those complex SUVs that you drive are so, you know, beyond you, but, you know, could you do us all a favor and stay at home so I don't have to bother, you know, driving behind you because you're too fucking slow or retarded?
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to remember we have... Mail drivers are worse.
[SPEAKER_07]: We have folks all around the world listening and not everyone knows what Hooters is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hooters is this eerie where you can order hot wings and that's about all that's decent on the menu and they're not even very good because it tastes like vinegar.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they're served by women wearing really small gym shorts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cheerleader outfits, essentially.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not quite, because they're not little skirts.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just this uber... They're the shorts that you can see ash cheeks through.
[SPEAKER_02]: And...
[SPEAKER_02]: and actually I read an article about a girl who went inside on Hooters just to try to find out what went on behind the scenes they ask you what your t-shirt size is and they give you one that's two sizes too small lovely and basically you're there for boobs which I have no problem with personally but I hate the whole mentality that spawned it and a question from our chatroom from someone from abroad who doesn't know better is there a male version?
[SPEAKER_02]: there should be when I was in high school
[SPEAKER_02]: One of my people who was in band with me that I used to march next to, she said that they should open a restaurant called Peckers.
[SPEAKER_02]: Where it's men in speedos that wear their aprons backwards.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you have any other FUs?
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just actually the Hooters, this is kind of an old FU, but FU the Hooters because their service does suck.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you might go there saying, oh yeah, we're going to go get served by hot chicks.
[SPEAKER_08]: The chicks are dumb and the service is awful.
[SPEAKER_08]: and they can't get anything right and it took them like two hours to serve like hot wings which is their staple food at this goddamn place and they can't prepare that even quick enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Then they, you know, jump around and dance and stuff and just act obnoxious and annoying the whole time.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's obviously not worth the trip, so go to a strip club if you really want to eat with boobs around you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_02]: What was that one strip club that you said had really good food?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it was Centerfolds.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you want to go?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure, why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: It'll be fun.
Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Don't... Well, Nellie will want to go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll all go.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll be at OLR, uh... We'll have a staff... Let's have a staff meeting at Centerfolds.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: That'll be excellent.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, we'll do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Our next OLR staff meeting at the Titty Bar.
[SPEAKER_07]: Um... Let's see, um... My F.U.
[SPEAKER_07]: of the week goes to Philips, the company that made my last television.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just over one year after buying the thing, it stopped working.
[SPEAKER_07]: You would turn on the TV, my nice new high-definition TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: You'd turn it on, then the image would get really bright, and then it would shut off.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it broke.
[SPEAKER_07]: The damn TV broke.
[SPEAKER_07]: But thank you to Costco, who's now my favorite store ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have the best return policy in the world.
[SPEAKER_07]: I took the TV back and got a new TV from a different company that hopefully will work for more than a year.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it has a red eye of death on it, like that 360?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, it did not have the three rings of death on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would shut off and then that little flashing green light would come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Flash, flash, flash, and that's all it would do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm tempting you.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have power, but I'm not going to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bobby's offering to fly out here for the staff meeting.
[SPEAKER_07]: You are more than welcome to attend.
[SPEAKER_07]: We can talk about all games business as well at the meeting.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be pretty funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: That just sounds like it would be lots of fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, um...
[SPEAKER_07]: We are going back into the news now, and this has absolutely nothing to do with titties, but it is a little foul.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you ever watch South Park, it's a little bit dirty, but in that way that we all love.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it looks like on South Park's season premiere, they're going to be spoofing World of Warcraft, and a little 15-second teaser hit the internet this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: and it says the World of Warcraft shows the World of Warcraft and then we hear that all too familiar voice yes that's right this Wednesday on Comedy Central that should be interesting World of Warcraft is gonna be hitting South Park yeah you know I enjoy South Park I've seen quite a few episodes it's one of my guilty pleasures
[SPEAKER_07]: and I'm sure it's going to be hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, they've spoofed games before.
[SPEAKER_07]: They've spoofed DDR and they've spoofed the Golden PSP.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember that whole episode with the Terry Shivo thing?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, so they've spoofed stuff before.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we thought it would be fun to bring back an old favorite segment of ours tonight and have a little fun with this topic.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to play Listless!
[SPEAKER_07]: Listless!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, the way Listless works is that we're going to come up with the definitive list of Orange Lounge Radio's top something with whatever category we're doing tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And as a follow-up to this story, the category we're going to do tonight is game that South Park most needs to make fun of.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, obviously, we can't do World of Warcraft and we can't do DDR.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the way Listless works.
[SPEAKER_07]: All of the hosts are going to go around and name their top three, and then we're going to go around and eliminate one off the list.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it gets a little vicious in here, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Now, usually this game is played with four people, but since there's only three of us here in studio, we've asked one of our frequent callers and emailers to join us tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Caller, are you there?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess you must be, smartass.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's your name?
[SPEAKER_07]: Introduce yourself.
[SPEAKER_07]: DMN, DMN, DMN
[SPEAKER_07]: And just for that smart-ass remark, I'm going to make you go first.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would be your number three pick for a game that South Park most needs to make fun of?
[SPEAKER_07]: Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Night Trap!
[SPEAKER_07]: Winner.
[SPEAKER_07]: The old Sega CD game starring Dana Plato.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a great one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're good at this game, DMN.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see if the rest of your list is up to par, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: But first, well, not yet, not yet.
[SPEAKER_07]: We've got to go to Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, you're number three.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would say Grand Theft Auto.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto, San Andreas, DarkSakura, Karaoke Revolution,
[SPEAKER_07]: Final Fantasy Xenoverse
[SPEAKER_07]: So far on our list, we have Night Trap, Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, Karaoke Revolution, and Final Fantasy.
[SPEAKER_07]: DMN, what would be your number two pick?
[SPEAKER_05]: Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_07]: Custer's Revenge.
[SPEAKER_07]: The old Atari 2600 classic, yes?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, where you can rape and pillage in very, very pixelated format.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be interesting to see on South Park.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, your number two pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Kart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Mario Kart!
[SPEAKER_02]: Just imagine, like, they throw, uh, what was the little, what was the ball-shaped kid's name?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_02]: The little Canadian.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Ike?
[SPEAKER_02]: Ike.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they throw Ike as a, as a thing, and then throw, like, like, Kenny's head.
[SPEAKER_07]: Didn't they have, like, a South Park game that was kind of like Mario Kart?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: A little bit, but they never really referenced it on the show, so I guess it could work.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, we'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, um, let's see, my number two.
[SPEAKER_07]: My number two would be, uh, Silent Hill.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to draw that now, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, seeing as we're on the topic of crappy games, I thought I'd say, hey, why doesn't South Park make fun of South Park?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting, interesting little play.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why doesn't South Park make fun of itself and its own crappy game that came out?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, good thought, good thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which one, the Nintendo 64 one?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, okay, good.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, Loki, your number one pick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't hate, but Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: Katamari Damacy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Did you see that commercial this week that was kind of inspired by Katamari Damacy?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, except they say the people who made it say it
[SPEAKER_07]: They were not inspired by the game in any way.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't watch TV, so I have no idea what it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's on YouTube.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the new TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, DarkSakura, what would be your number one?
[SPEAKER_02]: The Sims.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Sims!
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, that's a good one as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: Imagine they do have somebody controlling them walking around town.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good one, good one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, first, before I name my number one, let's go and look at some chatroom picks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's some things the chatroom are suggesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: OLArmyEddy says, Dead or Alive.
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68 says, Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Drunami says Africa.
[SPEAKER_07]: Meklar says Loco Roco.
[SPEAKER_07]: GS68 says Genji 2.
[SPEAKER_07]: Raven's Dolphin says Dead Rising.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blazer says Gradius.
[SPEAKER_07]: All very good guesses.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loco Roco would be funny with Cartman.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about Your Mom the Game last night?
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is in bed.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: My number one pick is none of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a game that desperately needs to be made fun of, especially after this week that I got my hands on it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sonic the Hedgehog for 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, so here's the list as it stands so far, and we're going to have to take one of these off the list, DMN.
[SPEAKER_07]: You've got to take one of these off the list, and unfortunately the chat room will not be able to vote for it because you've ruined their hopes and dreams to be able to vote for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's the list as it stands so far.
[SPEAKER_07]: Night Trap.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, Karaoke Revolution, Final Fantasy, Custer's Revenge, Twisted Metal, Mario Kart, Silent Hill, South Park the Game, Katamari Damacy, The Sims, and Sonic the Hedgehog 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: DMN, which one of these do you say South Park should not make fun of?
[SPEAKER_07]: Which come off the list?
[SPEAKER_05]: Um... Twisted Metal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Twisted Metal!
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, that was a little obscure, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Night Trap would be too obscure.
[SPEAKER_07]: Night Trap is too obscure.
[SPEAKER_02]: As much as I agree, either Night Trap or like Sewer Shark or something, nobody, unless they were in our, you know, age range of gamer, probably wouldn't get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: A lot, you know what, every pick that's left here is actually pretty good, so this is hard for me to take one off.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm going to take off, Jamie, don't hate me, I'm taking off Karaoke Revolution.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because since they already made fun of DDR, it's kind of close for me, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here we go, chat room, you now have the chance to vote on your favorite.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need you to give a number one and a number two, and here is what you get to vote on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, and DMN, you don't get to vote, because you already helped.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is, here's the list, and I posted it there in chat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Grand Theft Auto San Andreas, Final Fantasy, Custer's Revenge, Mario Kart, Silent Hill, Katamari Damacy, The Sims, and Sonic the Hedgehog 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Place votes now.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your number one and number two picks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Send a private message to Sky in the chat room with your vote.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember, it doesn't count unless it's over a private message.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll tally up the votes and reveal it shortly here in the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: DMN, thanks for your help.
[SPEAKER_07]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys have a good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, some interesting stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: This could also be, I guess, parodied on South Park, but the whole controversy with Bully.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, people were wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: It says, you know, Bully has been shown to, E3 was shown to very few press people, but now that it's almost out, actually in the next couple weeks, it's been shown to a lot more people.
[SPEAKER_08]: And actually, the game itself, which garnered a teen rating, isn't a
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, speaking of politically oriented things, you know, we love those guys over at GamePolitics.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just wanted to give a mention that GamePolitics.com has launched this week, and unfortunately it means they have come off of LiveJournal for their commenting system, but they have a fancy schmancy new website made in WordPress, so you should check it out, GamePolitics.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: We just wanted to give them a shout out.
[SPEAKER_07]: and DarkSakura is going to give another website a shout out right now because she surfs the web up and down every week.
[SPEAKER_07]: At work.
[SPEAKER_07]: At work, so she can find a pick worthy to share with the rest of you all.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's her website of the week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, we should really be using the Mr. Rogers music for this part.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe next week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: At any rate, my site of the week is actually one that another of our listeners linked to me when I did the Doctor Who site last week, but it's actually a very good Doctor Who fan site.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Doctor Who Online.
[SPEAKER_02]: The website address is doctorwho-online.co.uk and doctor is drwho-online.co.uk Oh my god, this site is fantastic.
[SPEAKER_02]: They actually have the Doctor Who Online WhoCast
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I'm going to be giving a try within the week.
[SPEAKER_02]: Lots of really good stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have a little area called Psychic Paper.
[SPEAKER_02]: References.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: Even an eBay link to a shop.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a really fantastic site.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I suggest going to it if there's a place to comment.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some orange on the radio sent you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Excellent.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well...
[SPEAKER_08]: Got some cool stuff here, especially from the folks that make Gears of War epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: Their thought on the whole Xbox 360 is you don't need to have an HDTV to be able to enjoy their games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so they are making sure by testing their game, Gears of War, on a bunch of small SDTVs
[SPEAKER_08]: Make sure that you can read the text in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unlike, say, Capcom, who couldn't give a flying fuck that you don't have a HDTV.
[SPEAKER_08]: So at least someone's getting it right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's awfully good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very reassuring.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, another reassuring news, actually, for anyone who's thinking that, oh, Wii's coming out, I don't have to keep my GameCube stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: The WaveBirds are apparently going to be able to be used on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_02]: and certain Wii games you will still need your receiver plug-in there's a slot on top of the console that you can plug that into but there's not really any word out as far as how well it's going to work with virtual console but it's apparently going to work with the Wii anyway so yay
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, well, I'm still trying to tally up the listless votes, so maybe we ought to just go on to our next story.
[SPEAKER_07]: We got flooded with, we have over 50 votes tonight for listless.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm trying to crazy tally them up.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry, Bobby, nice try, nice try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know, for anybody who is a bit of a snake charmer, you can play with your snake, in public no less, and not get arrested for it.
[SPEAKER_02]: There are already Metal Gear Solid 4 figures that will go out with the release of the game on the PS3.
[SPEAKER_02]: A 12-inch tall made by Medicom.
[SPEAKER_02]: Medicom puts out some really nice figures, by the way.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a prototype model up on GayGamer.net that looks pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snake's just really old, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: But the figure, though, is...
[SPEAKER_02]: They're stating that it may be something about 95,000 yen up to maybe 20,000.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do think the comment on the form here is Snake's got a great ass for an old guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Snake does have a good ass for an old guy.
[SPEAKER_02]: So Rob, how's Italian going?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm almost done.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's going to be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, you can always call us.
[SPEAKER_07]: The other free way would be to go on to OrangeLoungeRadio.com, click on Interact With Us, and get the information on Skype, username OrangeLoungeRadio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go for it, Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyways, as we like to do every week, we're reporting some stuff that you might not know yet because it hasn't been reported on the front of a magazine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, the first, of course, actually the only one I have this week is Call of Duty 2 on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dropdown to $39.99.
[SPEAKER_08]: So if you don't own it yet, might be a time to find a used one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, they should be even cheaper than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although, I mean, Call of Duty 3 is coming out in November, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a good game, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely worth the multiplayer, so check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some other fun news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo, there was a whole controversy about the Wii using the friend codes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, they're going to make it a little bit easier on you.
[SPEAKER_08]: They will be using the friend's code system
[SPEAKER_08]: However, they are going to only require that you have one friend code.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you'll be able to share that friend code and then be friended for all the other games.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that is good, you know, at least a good way to do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I swear I had that in the show role.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's crazy.
[SPEAKER_08]: My bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then there's some other stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was actually legislation...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's in the house right now to require the ESRB to actually play through the entire game before reviewing them.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's going to work because, you know, that would take forever.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would seriously delay the release of all games.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would delay games, and how would you do, like, MMOs or games that have new content added to them constantly?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's going to work.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's unrealistic.
[SPEAKER_08]: And why are they having, why is the government concerning themselves with this kind of stuff anyways?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_02]: What I think should be is that I think that on the websites there should be a parent link for any internet savvy parent to go online, get content warnings of the games more in depth.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the manufacturer does have a degree of responsibility to make sure that...
[SPEAKER_02]: They give accurate listings, but if they're really so concerned about it, then they can make it a requirement for the manufacturers to have more information made available.
[SPEAKER_02]: Or you know how when you buy food, it says for nutritional content, write into this address or go on this website?
[SPEAKER_02]: I think it should be the same thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: However, I think that it really is up to the parent to do the research before allowing their child to buy the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: As far as children, though, buying the games without their parents' permission, oh well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some other fun stuff, Rockstar announced a brand new series this week actually called L.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Noire, and more information should be coming out when the official trailer is released on October 5th, and if you want more information on that, you can visit rockstargames.com slash L.A.
[SPEAKER_08]: Noire, that's L-A-N-O-I-R-E, and looks like it's going to be a game that, of course, you know, kind of pays tribute to a lot of the film noir movies, much like, you
[SPEAKER_08]: LA Confidential, or even if you want to go really old, the Maltese Falcon.
[SPEAKER_08]: So that should be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kind of Grand Theft Auto-ish.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'm looking forward to that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then finally, some stuff on Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: As we mentioned before, Sierra is planning on releasing some games to Xbox Live Arcade.
[SPEAKER_08]: King's Quest?
[SPEAKER_08]: No, not yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: Damn it!
[SPEAKER_08]: The first couple of games that were announced, Assault Heroes, which is going to be another over-the-head...
[SPEAKER_08]: kind of shooter game that, you know, using two analog sticks, think, you know, Geometry Wars, but still pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then my favorite game, 3D Ultra Mini Golf, is going to be on Xbox Live Arcade, and that was a really fun mini golf game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I used to piss off people with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then, of course, Codemasters also announced the X-06 Sensible Soccer, which I think was announced even before that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And, of course, a very classic game should be making its way.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wanted to go to the chat room for some comments here.
[SPEAKER_07]: DNL, who, by the way, posted some great artwork to our LiveJournal community this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check it out if you're a user of LiveJournal or Community Orange Lounge on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: DNL says, in regards to the ESRB thing, on the back of the package it does say ESRB content rating, www.esrb.org.
[SPEAKER_07]: And also something I wanted to add on that whole ESRB thing is that when you play a game online, you always do get that, you know, warning that comes up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Warning, game experience may change with online play, do-do-do, type thing, so...
[SPEAKER_07]: Something to think about.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, I finally have some results for you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: You ready?
[SPEAKER_07]: My god, that was a lot of work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: The definitive list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Games we would like to see South Park make fun of next.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I gotta tell you, this list turned out really freaking weird.
[SPEAKER_07]: Considering we had so many votes, there were a lot of ties.
[SPEAKER_07]: So here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: The number one game you want to see South Park make fun of was a tie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Game number one, Silent Hill And game number two, Katamari Damacy Those games tied for first place Damacy Whatever And now what's interesting is so that takes us to third place And there was also a tie So we have two games tying for third place Because you know, you have first and second place basically tied there So for third place we have Grand Theft Auto San Andreas And Final Fantasy Are the two games that came in third place there
[SPEAKER_07]: So that is the definitive list.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys all for voting and giving me a lot of work there during that segment.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, we'll see if any of those actually make it to the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can say you heard it here first.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's go to the Skype line, boys and girls, and take some calls.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Raven's Dolphin.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, my friend.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_09]: I just want to say one news, Brian.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_09]: It's GameFly.
[SPEAKER_09]: Uh-huh.
[SPEAKER_09]: They actually did some more things with Gamefly.
[SPEAKER_09]: They now have four tiers now.
[SPEAKER_09]: Four tiers?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, now you can get one game for $15.99.
[SPEAKER_09]: You can get two games for $21.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now, they just added this.
[SPEAKER_09]: Three games for $30, or you can go for the Kin Kaboodle, which you'll lock yourself in your room forever.
[SPEAKER_09]: Four games for $40.
[SPEAKER_07]: Netflix does like eight games.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can do like up to eight movies on Netflix.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, you know, at least I think you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, so I'm not too surprised.
[SPEAKER_07]: They probably would let you do more if you really want.
[SPEAKER_07]: But damn, what do you need with five games at a time?
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you need with four games at a time?
[SPEAKER_07]: Two is enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: Two is enough so that you have, I mean, even, well, one's really enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: But two is enough so that when one's in the mail, you still have something to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they don't need more than that, in my opinion, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, if that's what you, it's your money, spend it how you want.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because I'm poor.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have to save up for a week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Are you a Gamefly subscriber?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, I am.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't use them.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think of them?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's not because I dislike them or anything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just, at this time, choose not to use them.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think of them?
[SPEAKER_09]: Actually, they got really better.
[SPEAKER_09]: Before, at first, they didn't ship my games for like nine days, and now it's coming to four.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blackwolf in our chatroom is commenting, you just had to be a member for a month before you got the third game option.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had three games from Gamefly years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: The four games is new.
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, they just gave it to me for 25 cents this month, Black Wolf.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_09]: I guess they're not nice to me.
[SPEAKER_09]: All right.
[SPEAKER_09]: Anything else you want to share with our listeners tonight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, one other thing.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_09]: What was it?
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I know.
[SPEAKER_09]: I just bought an iPod, so I'm now mad at Apple.
[SPEAKER_09]: Why?
[SPEAKER_09]: Because they just came out with the new Nanos.
[SPEAKER_09]: And it looks like a little mini iPod.
[SPEAKER_09]: Remember the ones with the black and white screen?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: The iPod Mini?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Now I got an old Nano, so I'm not mad at them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, you might... Well, I doubt you could do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because sometimes if they do a price cut, like a week after you bought it, they'll give you a refund.
[SPEAKER_07]: But maybe not with the old models versus new models.
[SPEAKER_07]: But you never know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Check their website.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Couldn't tell you.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm... And...
[SPEAKER_07]: That's about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, can you guys hear me?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, hi, this is Blue Monster from the chat room.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, what's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_10]: I just wanted to share two things.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first one is, congrats on the show, man, because seriously, it's something I look forward to every week.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you, I really appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_10]: A constant in your life, you know, as I was telling you earlier, DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyways, the second little thing I wanted to share with you guys is, I picked up Okami last week.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, that's a game I've heard a lot of great things about and seen a lot of good things about.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm a little tight on my gaming budget right now, so I haven't been able to pick it up.
[SPEAKER_07]: But, yeah, I'm really curious.
[SPEAKER_07]: What do you think of this game?
[SPEAKER_10]: That's what I actually wanted to call.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wanted to give you like a mini-review kind of thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a pretty good game.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very Zelda-ish, but the only thing I have against it is there's a lot of hand-holding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, the first dozen hours, I put all my 24 in it.
[SPEAKER_10]: The first 12 hours is like nothing but hand-holding.
[SPEAKER_10]: Like, they tell you everything the way you gotta stop it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So if you're looking for some hardcore Zelda-ish style of gameplay...
[SPEAKER_10]: You'll have a hard time getting through it, at least for the first half.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, Enchanted Arms, which is a game I have been playing lately, is very similar because every time you go into a new dungeon, it seems like there's some new environmental thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, press A to get into the cart.
[SPEAKER_07]: Press A to move the teleport.
[SPEAKER_07]: And they'll have to have this whole back and forth where the main character is like, how do I do this?
[SPEAKER_07]: and one of the other smarter people in the party says, well, you walk up to it and press A. But that's the answer every single time you walk up to it and press A. They could have just said in the beginning.
[SPEAKER_10]: They have a little tune that's like jumping up and down the nose of the wolf and he tells you all the time, oh, maybe if I should use my brush to cut this vine, which I've been doing for the past six hours, please let me do it myself.
[SPEAKER_07]: They should just have had a thing that says, hey, whenever you see new shit, press A. Exactly, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: But overall, it's a really good music, really good art style, the graphics are really good, there is a bit of slowdown, because there's a lot of stuff happening on the screen sometimes, but overall, it's a really good game, it seems long, because I've already put 24 hours in it, and the game actually just got started, and the hand-holding just now stopped, so I'm guessing...
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, long game.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's a good game to get if you're waiting for Final Princess, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Now one other question I have for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: For those that don't know much about Okami, I mean, maybe we've seen the graphics, you know, that it has that very unique hand-drawn style to it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What would you compare this game to?
[SPEAKER_07]: If you could compare it to any other game, you know, maybe half this and half this, what would you say it's kind of like for people that want to know if they'd be interested in this or not?
[SPEAKER_10]: Mix the world of Wind Waker and the style, cartoony style of Wind Waker, but also add a bit of a stench of Chester Radio or Chester Radio Future and maybe some beautiful Joe in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_07]: And all those games kind of have that same art style too, so that's kind of interesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: The thing is that Wind Waker is very clean looking, this is more dirty.
[SPEAKER_10]: The graphics are not that clean because of the brush thing and the whole brush theme that it has.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's more beautiful Joe-ish, but it's still really good.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's very Japanese, so you've got to be open-minded about it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's still a really good game, and I would definitely recommend it to anyone who's stuck on the game.
[SPEAKER_10]: And don't be scared.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's not as platformer as it seems to be.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's more adventure-ish and more pilot-ish, I guess.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm calling from Argentina, it's 1am in the morning over here What's it like in Argentina?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: You pay about 80 US dollars for a game, between 70 or 80, if you want the original copy, of course, because there's a black market here, like, you wouldn't believe, like, you can buy a game for 2 bucks if you want to, US.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: But, yeah, but if you actually want an original game, you gotta pay about 70, 80 bucks.
[SPEAKER_10]: and it's all games because you don't get the new stuff right away.
[SPEAKER_10]: And you got to take into account that a maid here, like a maid full-time maid here, maybe costs 200 US dollars a month.
[SPEAKER_10]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it's like basically a game is about half the salary of a maid per month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Gosh.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, hey, now your copy of Okami is legit though, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh, no, really.
[SPEAKER_07]: Uh-oh, uh-oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, we better hurry and end this call.
[SPEAKER_07]: We won't tell on you.
[SPEAKER_07]: We won't give out your full name or anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm glad you got to call in, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I'm glad I got to call in.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, have fun with the game, and we know that when you can't afford it, you will buy the legit copy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I already put it up there, so, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, good, good, okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Happy ending.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thanks for calling.
[SPEAKER_07]: See ya.
[SPEAKER_07]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_07]: We love hearing from people.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't say overseas, but over planet, because, you know, you're all the way down there right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just gotta keep looking south.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: SSJ100Math's going, happy ending.
[SPEAKER_02]: The thing is, is that I'm in massage therapy school, so I know what you mean.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_07]: You guys...
[SPEAKER_07]: Go play Uno.
[SPEAKER_07]: They cover that in massage therapy school?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, they don't.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't started school yet, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Go play Uno, you sick fucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, this is Eddie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hi, Eddie.
[SPEAKER_07]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I was just wondering if you heard about that thing, like a guy posted on the All Games forums that he was booted out of Uno because somebody saw that he was a black guy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I did read that post.
[SPEAKER_07]: That is so fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, somebody... Oh, that sucks.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't think I know about this.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, no.
[SPEAKER_07]: God, can we find the post real quick?
[SPEAKER_07]: This just made me so angry.
[SPEAKER_07]: Some people are so stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Swear to God.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see if I can find it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Do you remember what forum it was in?
[SPEAKER_07]: It was the...
[SPEAKER_07]: Let me ask you real quick, while I hunt for the post, is there any other topics you want to bring up tonight?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I had something related to that thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of the replies to the article was that that's why the me on the we thing is so good, because you can create your own avatar or whatever.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I was just thinking that it doesn't really solve the racism issue, since...
[SPEAKER_03]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: and it shouldn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: It shouldn't matter at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, in World of Warcraft, we play purple and green people and it doesn't matter, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, when they demoed the Wii, they showed them making Samuel L. Jackson the baddest motherfucker on the planet.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I would cower in fear if I was playing against Samuel L. Jackson, you know, because...
[SPEAKER_07]: He's a badass, but people are just so superficial.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I found the post.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I realize probably like 50 of you linked it in chat room, but I did find it on my own.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here it is.
[SPEAKER_07]: This was made by a post.
[SPEAKER_07]: The guy is named Five Fingers of Death, and this is on allgames.com's forums in the Xbox 360 section.
[SPEAKER_07]: Does Vision Cam hamper jump in Vision of Live?
[SPEAKER_07]: I was wondering if anyone else has experienced this I purchased my vision cam last week and hooked it up to experience a couple of multiplayer UNO sessions when I connected all three people I was paired with also had the camera I heard someone mention he's a black guy and then I was booted by the host as we know live has always had its racist comments but for the most part you could never really tell who you were gaming with for all we know David Duke could be playing with Louis Farrakhan and neither would be the wiser now being able to actually see the person how will this affect the live community just wondering
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I can't wait for me to get on the camera and have somebody go, That guy looks like a fag.
[SPEAKER_07]: Boot him.
[SPEAKER_07]: You wouldn't want to play with those fuckers anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's fucked up.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Put all those people on your ban list and warn them and damage them the best you can.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's so stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: They obviously don't want to play a good game, good old-fashioned game of Uno anyway.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it doesn't make it right at all.
[SPEAKER_07]: By any means does it make it right, but I guess...
[SPEAKER_07]: Until, you know, Microsoft steps in and I don't even know what Microsoft can do.
[SPEAKER_07]: What can they do?
Ban.
[SPEAKER_07]: So it's up to the community to police itself, I suppose.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Disturbing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anything else you wanted to say on that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, not on that issue, but take pictures of cookie box.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you can get them from Granville Island, one of my favorite places in Vancouver.
[SPEAKER_07]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Have a good one, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_04]: No, what I was training with the Marines, they were showing us the tapes of famous Marines on the tape.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, well, you know, I'm not going to say you're a liar.
[SPEAKER_07]: I just always thought that was an urban legend.
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't think that was true.
[SPEAKER_04]: That was the first time I ever heard it when I saw the tape.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I think I remember my brother telling me something about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, me and my brother actually just was released from the Marines.
[SPEAKER_07]: Firebomba says, WTF, Mr. Rogers is a camper.
[SPEAKER_04]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, you know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: On Wikipedia, that whole thing is filed under urban legends.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's what it says.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yikes.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe that's it.
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to give your Wikipedia to your friend.
[SPEAKER_02]: But he also was a Presbyterian minister and left the clergy to work with children.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, I just realized podcast listeners may not understand why we're suddenly talking about Mr. Rogers.
[SPEAKER_07]: We do a bonus segment when we tape live when we'll sometimes play things off of YouTube and such and that was the subject this week was Mr. Rogers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry, just for the podcast people's sake who maybe didn't hear that live.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyway, anything else on your mind, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: I've decided not to buy a PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why is this?
[SPEAKER_04]: I was watching, I was following like the Sony's podcast, livecast of the PSN and everything.
[SPEAKER_04]: Now they're doing their version of the virtual console.
[SPEAKER_04]: On that fact alone, I refuse to buy one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, okay, is it because you feel they're ripping them off or something?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean...
[SPEAKER_04]: They say imitation is the greatest form for flattery, but come on Sony's been ripping off people left and right with the PS3 But couldn't you say that the Virtual Console is a form of Xbox Live Arcade?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yes and no, but the thing is the Virtual Console has all these classic games by Nintendo
[SPEAKER_04]: Xbox Live Arcade Xbox Live Arcade Xbox Live Arcade
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But to not buy a system over it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, what if they did it better?
[SPEAKER_04]: Eh, I just can't see myself, you know.
[SPEAKER_04]: And no, Zarko, I'm not a fanboy.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just don't have 600 bucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, there's the realistic reason why none of us are getting a PS3 at launch.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least I think I can speak... Well, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess Jamie's getting one.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I know I can't afford 600 bucks.
[SPEAKER_04]: For 600 bucks, it better come with a lap dance.
[SPEAKER_07]: For 600 bucks, it better...
[SPEAKER_07]: Suck... Never mind.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm not going to finish that thought.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: You know what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, anything else on your mind, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_04]: I love you guys.
[SPEAKER_07]: Love you too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next month.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, bye.
[SPEAKER_04]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm coming to Orange... I'm coming to New York City very soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'll have details on where I'm going to be and when.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hopefully soon.
[SPEAKER_07]: I feel weird because now I think there's at least more than a handful of people that want to come meet up, so I feel weird about doing that at a store unannounced.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm trying to figure something out creative we can do.
[SPEAKER_07]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'll have to work with some people in New York.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'll be fun, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, are there any other last-minute stories that any of you guys have?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you guys, by the way, all of you guys that called in tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: And sorry to those we didn't get to.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're just running out low on time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have one quick story I wanted to share here from BamaniStyle.com has posted a list of elite beat agents, a song list, at least partial.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, again, because apparently it's being shown off on the Nintendo Fusion Tour, and they were able to get some of the songs from the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: YMCA by Village People, Highway Star by Deep Purple, Rock This Town by Stray Cats, Walkie Talkie Man by Stereogram, Makes No Difference by Sum 41, September by Earth, Wind & Fire, Skater Boy by Avril Lavigne,
[SPEAKER_07]: and I Was Born to Love You by Queen.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: If you want to check out what stages those are related to, check out BomaniStyle.com.
[SPEAKER_07]: There's a more complete list over there.
[SPEAKER_07]: And on that note, I guess we're going to end the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: So let's go around and get everybody's final thought.
[SPEAKER_07]: Loki, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I ran out of milkshake.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_07]: My final thought would be I need to adjust the sound on my new TV because it sounds like I'm playing Beatmania in a tin can and that's not fun.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, your final thought.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Julie's meeting us for dinner.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need some dinner.
[SPEAKER_02]: She has my house keys because she had to feed my cat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I need some big time dinner action.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to do that, we have to finish the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you so much for supporting independent internet radio even when the hosts stutter.
[SPEAKER_07]: and we'll see you next time on Orange Lounge Radio.