Orange Lounge Radio is taped live on Sunday nights and released to our podcast stream
twice weekly.
To listen to the first half of this episode, visit www.orangeloungeradio.com for links
to websites with listings of past episodes.
Now the conclusion of this weekís episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
We are back here on Orange Lounge Radio.
This is episode number 206, if you can believe it, for this October the 29th of 2006.
Remember if youíre listening to us on the podcast feed, Orange Lounge Radio comes to
you in two parts and if you want to hear all the news we already talked about, youíve
got to go to part A. If youíre thinking like, ìHey, why doesnít this podcast talk about
this?î Well, maybe we already did or maybe we missed something and you want to email
us and yell at us about it.
Mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
We love getting emails from you guys.
We got a whole crap load of them this week because we had a long period there with the
pre-taping of our show last week.
Bob is obviously not speaking for me.
What?
We enjoy getting emails from you guys.
Oh, no, I love getting emails.
Thatís it.
Bob is obviously not speaking for me.
Oh, you know what I mean.
I go in there too.
I peek.
I peek around.
Iím joking.
I like getting email.
Usually youíll share them with me anyway if theyíre really good or really bad.
I love the hate mail though.
I finally just told somebody off in the email and he was so retarded that his only response
was yawn.
Iím like, ìHaha, pwned.î Iím sure that person is still listening and just got a boner
hearing you say that.
Good.
Iím joking because I think that your hate mail is hilarious and really stupid.
So send your hate mail to mailbag at orangealmsradio.com so Dark Star Kara can make fun of it.
Weíll get to that a little later.
Weíll get to the mailbag a little later.
But for now, we need some news.
Loki, save us from this endless debate about hate mail.
Well, Toys ë Us did their wonderful pre-orders for Playstation 3 and the Wii on the 29th.
So that already happened if youíre probably listening to us now.
And yeah, it was a clusterfuck, much like the Gamestop EB pre-orders.
They actually were having lines of people lining up a day in advance.
So pretty crazy.
A lot of the Toys ë Us stores were getting anywhere from like, what was it, I think it
was four to eight Playstation 3s and like sixÖ