Tonight, October 22nd, 2006, new firmware is on deck to the PSP, a Nintendo DS game
releases with a major bug still in the game, and is EA watching your every move?
Hello, everybody, and welcome to another week of Orange Lounge Radio. We are that
video game podcast dedicated to gaming culture, gamer lifestyle, and what you, the
gamer, really want to know. Welcome to our show. We're pre-taping this week. We're a
little early. It is Wednesday night, October 18th, but this will be our week
show. That's because I'm traveling this week, and so is one of our lovely co-hosts
here, Dark Sakura, Jamie Summers. Are you saying that Loki is lovely? I suppose. In
his own manly way. And I'm moving. Yeah, that's right, you're moving this weekend.
So everybody's busy this weekend, so it's just a bad weekend for us. I'm going to see
see, uh, boy love. Oh, YowieCon? Going to YowieCon, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and.
And? Gonna see Nightmare Before Christmas in 3D! But see, by the time most people
hear this, that will have all already happened, because this this is still
going to air usually on Sundays.
We do have a small audience in our chat, a lot of our loyal listeners tonight here on
Wednesday night.
I just wanted to kind of lay that down up front just in case there was some developing
news, some of these stories changed throughout the week.
Keep your time frame in mind that we're doing this on Wednesday, so don't blame us if something
changed.
Don't blame us collectively, but you can blame Rob personally.
Sure, why not?
All right, so anyway, let's start it off.
How was your gaming week, Dark Sakura?
I had a gaming week.
My gaming week consisted of me being half asleep watching Dan play that crappy Mortal
Kombat game, going, oh my God, I hate the sound effects of this game, go to sleep.
That's what we talked about last week.
I know, but that wasn't, since my gaming week has been three days.
No, no, I know, but I'm curious, I thought it was okay, why did you think it was crappy?
I hate the music in it and I hate the sound effects.
And just watching him do the same crap over and over.
If I want to play a good beat-em-up, I could do that Tekken fighting mode from Tekken 3.
I actually haven't played Phantasy Star Universe yet, either, because I've been doing real
life things.
Well, you're in luck.
I heard the beta was extended, which, again, we'll do the Sunday listeners no good because
it's extended through Saturday, but that's what I'm hearing.
It doesn't mean no good.
Well, unless I want to play tonight.
I think you can play some tonight.
Yeah.
I'm actually gaming gaming tomorrow.
Like old-school D&D.
Like, no.
Roll D20.
Werewolf.
Oh, God, you nerd.
I game every other week.
Yes, everybody, not only am I a video gaming girl, I do tabletop gaming, too.
Which just, you know, further cement you as a hardcore nerd.
I know what a D4 is used for in second edition D&D, bitches.
Nerd patrol.
You can use it for a whip.
Nerd herd.
Loki, how you doing?
How was your gaming week?
It was short, I guess.
Well, I played Grand Theft Auto.
I didn't get to play any of the PlayStation 2 games that I have lined up to play.
I don't get to play a lot of games right now because I'm packing, and packing sucks.
But I am looking forward to playing The Warriors, which, you know, is coming out on the PSV
pretty soon.
Well, probably next year.
Yes, it was a movie, and it was an awesome PlayStation 2 game, too.
So yeah, lots of Grand Theft Auto, and I'm kicking ass in that.
And Zuma a little bit.
I'm on level 9 now.
I beat level 8 while Nellie was asleep because she couldn't get past it, and she was getting
frustrated.
But she says, you know, she has to beat it herself before or else it doesn't count.
I don't know.
So whatever.
And then I played a little Dig Dug, and I was trying to play some Luminous Live, but
it won't download for me because it stops at 1%.
Xbox has been having some wacky stuff today ever since their maintenance yesterday.
And what did their maintenance do?
It's just stuff for their website, from what I hear.
Well, we don't really know the full scope of things yet, so possibly they've done some
type of upgrade that's dormant until later.
They broke Luminous Live.
That's what their update was for.
I don't know.
Oh, and of course Saints Row.
Been playing lots of Saints Row, and that's fun.
I'm trying for the million dollar achievement right now, and once I get that then I'll kind
of move on.
Yeah, that's pretty much it for now.
Some comments from our chat room.
We do have a small crowd there tonight, a little smaller than our usual Sunday show,
but we say thank you to the loyalists who are there as always.
Jeremy Todd 1 in response to Dark Soccer being a hardcore nerd says, Tabletop gaming is for
people who aren't hardcore enough to play video games.
I did both.
That means I'm double hardcore.
SSJ100 Matt says, Jesus saves and rolls D20s.
Get it?
That's a roleplaying joke.
Did Jesus make a saving throw?
Let's see, My Gaming Week.
I've been playing more of the Phantasy Star universe beta.
I will say this, those of you guys that got frustrated with connection issues and things
of that sort and getting started, may not have given the game enough opportunity because
I'll tell you what, when I got in a party with some of my real life friends and we were
able to do voice chat, the game got like 5,000 times better.
I'm looking forward to the commercial release.
I'm definitely going to pick up the commercial release.
I'm still going to hold off on a full review of the game until I actually have a commercial
release in my hands to review, but we will talk more about Phantasy Star universe at
a later date.
Meanwhile, I downloaded Luminous Life today.
I was able to grab it this morning, I guess maybe before the masses were getting home
from work, school, and started downloading on Luminous Life, so I picked that up.
I want to warn you about something with Luminous Life.
The game's got microtransactions at the butt, and when I say that, I mean when you download
the game, you can play Xbox Live, you can play normal challenge mode with about, I want
to say it's about 12 skins, forgive me if I'm a little off on that number, but if you
want to buy more skins, like you want to get a pack of 20 skins, you're going to have to
buy those later in what's called an advanced pack.
Also, if you go in to play versus CPU, you only get one skin, and once you play that
for about 10 levels, it says, thanks for trying this, buy the versus CPU pack if you want
more.
Then in mission mode, you get about five missions, hey, if you want more missions, buy the mission
pack.
Yeah, what the hell's the demo?
I mean, seriously, if this is the actual game, then what's the demo?
I guess it's one stage of the game, so pretty much the game you're getting on Xbox Live
is just the skeleton game of the non-stop puzzle mode with about 12 different skins,
and the ability to play on Xbox Live.
Oh goody, but I guess they'll have 700 songs on Xbox Live at some point for a micro-transaction
of $100 each, then maybe I'll get the, I can have this go with my Gran Turismo HD.
It's hard for me to sit here and be critical of Gran Turismo HD for the micro-transaction
things they've been talking about, and not apply the same logic to Luminous.
I don't think that would be okay for me to do.
As much as I love Luminous, and I think it's an awesome puzzle game, I don't think it's
fair for folks to be picking up Luminous when they don't really know what they're really
buying.
I don't think Q Entertainment and Microsoft have been very upfront about what exactly
you're getting with this, and the fact that some components of the game are missing.
Are you getting a full game?
Yes.
Are you getting the same thing as you got on the PSP?
No.
The PSP version as it stands right now offers more than the basic skeleton that Xbox Live
is giving you.
I don't feel like I can give this game a fair assessment until I know it's real price for
everything else.
Would it have been a little bit different if the game were like $5 instead of $15 out
the gate?
Maybe, but again, I would take all that into consideration with how much is each little
component price.
For example, Test Drive Unlimited was kind of using that formula, basically putting out
a very cheap game and then having microtransactions, but the difference between Test Drive Unlimited
and say Gran Turismo HD or Luminous is you don't need to purchase those.
Granted, I bought this game because, well, I'm a cheapen point horror and it sounded
pretty easy, so hey, what the hell?
So what if I play a few stages?
I don't like the fact that there is only five stages because I think there should be at
least more, and then say later on you want to buy more songs on top of a full game's
worth of songs.
That's fine.
Oh, by the way, you want to progress later on, you're going to have to buy the levels.
I can understand the logic that, hey, maybe not everyone wants to play Mission Mode.
Hey, maybe not everyone wants to play Puzzle Mode.
Okay, but still you have to take the value of what you're paying out in consideration
with all this is that for right now, for a pretty competitive $29.99, you can get the
PSP version of Luminous, which offers more skins.
As it stands right now, better songs, as far as I'm concerned, even though, yes, some of
the songs in Xbox Live's version are from Luminous 1, some of the best songs on Luminous
1 are nowhere to be seen so far in Xbox Live Luminous, and when you put those values side
by side, how worth it is it to be playing Luminous on your TV?
I don't know.
Or if you have a PlayStation 2.
Or on Xbox Live.
If you have a PlayStation 2, just wait and pick up Luminous Plus for $30 when that comes
out, which is basically just a rehash of Luminous.
By the way, the Madonna song, any licenses whatsoever, nowhere to be seen yet.
I don't know if they're going to be in the Advance pack.
Rumor has it they're not.
I have someone who's had a peek at the Advance pack and tells me that there's just more general
Q Entertainment produced songs in there from the first and probably second games.
Nice bait and switch there, Q Entertainment.
So I don't know where Madonna is or any licensed artists for that matter.
That could change.
I'm assuming that's on Rumor there, but I'm assuming that will be another buy later on
if you want to have Madonna or what have you in your game.
So, interesting.
Yeah, well, I remember reading, I know, and I've got to pull this up because I pulled
up a different article, same type of thing, but they were talking about other additional
downloads beyond the Advance pack, and I want to say it was run on 1UP, but I can't remember
what they were showing, oh, here we go.
I know they had a ton of micropayment stuff, and of course they were talking about the
Advance pack, but they were talking about other things that you can download as well.
Let's see here, it says, oh, they were just talking about, I guess, the mission and puzzle
mode.
They're assuming that each one's going to be about the same price, so like $6 each or
whatever, or 600 points each for another 12, 100 points, or $15.
It says that adds up to about $22.49, and it says all of a sudden the game, after you
bought everything, ends up costing you $37.49.
So I don't know.
I have a hard time being able to say I recommend Luminous Live or I don't because I feel like
the whole game has not yet been revealed, so it really depends.
Ask yourself this question before you buy it, A, if you don't own a PSP, I do think
it's worth it.
I don't think it's one of the greatest puzzlers ever made, even if the music is not as good
as the PSP version.
I wouldn't go tell you to buy a PSP just for Luminous, so I would say it's worth checking
out if you don't have a PSP, but if you do have a PSP, yeah, so.
Anyway, let's get into some housekeeping real quick for tonight.
Tonight's housekeeping, first off, it's only going to be a one-part show tonight because
of the fact that we are pre-taping and usually those only end up being one part.
I do want to point out we will still be doing DDR previews tonight, even though it is only
one part, and remember we're not live, so if you've joined our chat room on this lovely
Sunday evening or whenever you used to listen to us live, keep in mind that we are pre-taped
this week.
I also do have a message from one of our lesbians, Kristen would like everyone to know, she says
hi.
All right, so you're hanging out with her this weekend, right?
Yes, I am.
It's a whole cluster of people going to YowieCon.
We averted a crisis, but she did want me to tell all the listeners hi.
All right, sounds good.
All right, we're going to start to get into some gaming news tonight.
We've got one more thing.
Oh, yes.
Oh, did you get the Battlefield?
I'm so sorry.
The Battlefield contest.
Who won?
We do have a winner.
There was lots of entries, but there could only be one.
There could be only one.
Your mom.
Drum roll, please.
And the winner of the Battlefield 21-42, I don't remember which year it was.
Get the game name right, please.
The Battlefield 21-42 contest is Jason Tryon from St. Petersburg, Florida.
Congratulations.
You'll be getting an email with your download code to download the full game with maybe
a few additional extras that we will be talking about a little bit later.
Yay.
Congratulations.
Wait, do I have my sound effect loaded here?
Hold on.
There we go.
Congratulations to you from us here at Orange Lounge Radio.
We actually have breaking news tonight.
I'm going to interrupt our usual show role here because here at Orange Lounge Radio we
try to plan our stories in advance.
We literally got breaking news about 15 minutes before we went live tonight, and for long
time fans of Orange Lounge Radio who listened to us back in our music gaming days, we know
a lot of you folks are still with us.
This is huge news.
Directly from OrangeLoungeRadio.com, there's a press release today on Roxor's website and
it was short and simple.
Konami Corporation, developer of the Dance Dance Revolution video game, and Roxor Games
Inc., developer of the In the Groove dance games, today announced the mutual settlement
of the litigation between the parties in the U.S. District Court in the Eastern District
of Texas.
Under the terms of the settlement, Konami has acquired the intellectual property rights
to the In the Groove dance game franchise.
It was further agreed as a part of the settlement that Roxor would respect Konami's intellectual
property rights.
Translation?
Pwned.
Yeah, so In the Groove dance game fans, not going to be too happy at this news.
I'm going to be honest, I'm hearing a lot of talk already about, oh, this opens the
door for Konami to make DDR versus In the Groove and all this other stuff.
Honestly guys, I think what Konami is going to do with this license, this newly acquired
license so to speak, absolutely nothing.
I think they've got their biggest competitor so to speak and they'll just crush it like
a grape.
It would be a DDR PC too.
Now granted, there may be more information forthcoming later, who knows?
Perhaps Konami will re-explore the PC market with the In the Groove franchise, who knows?
I mean, I'm not going to say for sure I'm the end-all, be-all, know-all of what's going
on but in my mind, that kind of makes the most sense for Konami.
Why dilute the market with more dance games, just make it all DDR?
Well, so they would put out that patch though for In the Groove if they didn't know that
they were going to be losing.
Exactly, and this is another good point that last week there was a patch release for the
arcade game that allows you to play any song you want in the arcade game if you know how
to load it on your USB memory card.
So I do believe now that was the final F-you from Rockstar getting the last cut in before
they went down.
I think they knew that was happening.
And now you have this nice relic on your wall.
I do.
We have a signed In the Groove poster, In the Groove 2 poster from last year's Digital
Life.
I'm looking for millions on eBay next week.
Yeah, right.
I'm kidding.
Millions of pennies.
Here's a little something else though for those arcade owners out there with an In the
Groove machine with this update on it.
If the RIA catches you playing a song that's not licensed, you can be sued for a lot of
money.
So keep that in mind with this wonderful unlocked machine if you want to.
I mean, you can get sued, so there you go.
What if the arcade has a jukebox license?
If they do, but not many do.
So most of them think, okay, I'm safe because the game's music is licensed.
That doesn't include stuff that people load on there.
Well, more to come on this as it develops here at Orange Lounge Radio.
We would like to open an invitation.
We know there are folks in the music game industry who listen to this program.
If anyone from Rocks or Games would like to come on the show, present their side of things,
the door is open.
If anyone from Konami would like to come on the show and talk about the future of In the
Groove now that they've got it, the door is open.
You can go to the contact us on our website.
We'd love to have you on the program.
That is awesome now that I have the In the Groove 2 beta for PlayStation 2 because that'll
never be released now.
Probably not.
Never say never, but probably not.
All right, back to the normal list of topics.
Anyways, speaking of stuff that we think will never be released, and that would be a working
firmware for the PSP, but the next big firmware update, 3.0, is coming and supposedly coming
tomorrow, or the 19th for most people out there.
Anyways, what does that mean to you?
Well, if this is the big old firmware story that we've been waiting for, it's going to
have the PlayStation emulation in there, as well as support for linking up to the PlayStation
3 for remote play, whatever the hell that is supposed to be, but I guess we'll find
out when the PlayStation 3 comes out, and it's not a big surprise that that is coming
out tomorrow, seeing as Sony is having their gamer's day for basically covering all the
PlayStation 3 stuff and PSP stuff, you know, on Thursday, so that's pretty cool.
And yeah, so lots of good, lots of big stuff, and I'm sure a lot more ways to stop you from
running homebrew software, so enjoy.
I'm sure this will be on the next Grand Theft Auto anyway, so it'll have to update no matter
what.
All right, well, something that's kind of interesting in the Sony area, now this isn't
really officially supported by Sony, but you know, we've been talking about, you know,
high definition, high definition is like the next gen of gaming, well, did you know that
you could do high definition with your PlayStation 2?
Yes, that's right, there is a boot disk that's out there, and it's from, let's see, it's
called the Exploder HDTV Player, and it's by a company called Silicon Era, or at least
that's the, I'm sorry, no, that's the website that originally ran the story.
It's actually Exploder, I think, is the company.
Exploder is the company.
It says here that what you can do is that if you have a 1080i supporting TV, you can
load this tool before starting the game, and then what you can do is inside the menus,
you can select which resolution you want to run the game at, and that this Exploder program
is going to automatically, I suppose, upcode your, you know, existing PlayStation 2 resolution
to 1080i.
No idea exactly how successful that's going to turn out, but if they're putting this product
out there, they must feel pretty confident.
You know what that strangely reminds me of, though?
Blamecast.
Kind of, but this isn't for a specific game.
Well, no, I understand that, but they were wanting to do something very similar to use
the better graphics processing of the Dreamcast to play other PlayStation games, too.
I think it's sort of along the same lines.
So I still don't know if this is something I would pick up, though.
It just seems a little too risky to me, and I don't know if the PlayStation 2 game was
not designed for high def.
It's going to be kind of funky in this transition, so I don't know if that's something I want.
Why?
The PlayStation 3 is doing the same thing.
Oh, okay.
Why not?
All right.
So, I mean, it could happen.
I mean, who knows?
Stranger things, I guess.
All right.
Well, since you brought up the PS3, there actually is a little bit more news about the
Blu-ray discs and the developers that are working on them, that they're actually close
to the 25 gigabyte limit for a lot of the games.
And there's a lot of talk that we're putting movies in there, non-interactive content,
and we pretty much have an admission on that from one of the folks with Sony.
Actually the one to speak with was Phil Harrison, who was the world studio guy.
But basically what he said, and this is a quote, is, I see nothing wrong with having
non-interactive full HD sequences as part of a game.
That's all part of the production value and experience you get when you buy the game.
I don't see that as a weakness at all.
It's a weakness if it's going to cut down on game time and playability.
I think it's a lot of the stuff is, because they are outporting the 1080p, a lot of it's
just higher res textures, or in the case you've got your high def video and stuff in there,
which some of that's fine.
And also they could be doing less compression on it because the Blu-ray drives are slower.
Because they are slower, well actually you would think they would do more compression
if they had slower Blu-ray drives, whatever.
I'm no developer, so what the hell do I know about content?
All I know is 25 gigs is a lot for a game, and it better damn looked good for 25 gigs.
That's all I got to say.
Wait until they have to deal with the 50.
What are we going to see then?
More movies?
Defective discs.
Hopefully a Playstation 3 that will take out my trash and do my dishes.
Then I buy it.
At launch.
New for PS3, Turbo Tax!
Anyways, some really cool stuff coming to the Playstation 3, and this is also coming
out of Sony's Gamer Day.
First off, their brand new e-distribution titles, or their Sony arcade, whatever the
hell you want to call it.
Some pretty cool stuff actually.
Very interesting ones, like for example, there's a new game that kind of resembles Geometry
Wars, which is kind of neat, called Blast Factor.
There's going to be Lemmings 2, which apparently is not a port of the original Lemmings 2,
but is a brand new Lemmings game, you know, updated graphics and whatnot.
Go Sudoku, because, god, there's just not enough Sudoku out there.
Swizzle Blocks, which I don't know what that is, but it sounds like a puzzle game.
Criminal Crackdown, and, well, Flow, because that was previously announced.
I saw some of the screenshots for some of these games, looked interesting.
I, Blast Factor looked pretty cool, and the graphics looked pretty pristine on it, so
I don't know if it's just a TV or screenshots that they're showing, but...
I'm hoping out of this Gamer's Day thing that will have already happened by the time most
of you hear this, we will see a little more, like, in the means of footage, and kind of
made, like, not so much screenshots, but actual footage, kind of what they look like in action.
You know what I wish they had is like a console that's just these mini-games, because that
would be pretty cool.
Well, what about one of those crappy plug-and-play joystick things?
No, I'm talking about, like, an online service or something where you can download, I mean,
I hate these, all these arcade things and stuff.
Isn't that what Phantom wanted to be?
Yeah, but the Phantom was lame.
So wait, so you're...
No, Phantom wanted to do full games.
Did you just say that you want the Phantom to come out?
I did not say I wanted the Phantom to come out.
Are you gonna run over to GameStop and reserve your Phantom?
The Phantom is just a really crappy PC.
Now, granted, the case looked pretty, pretty lame, but actually the case reminded me of
something that would be in, like, Half-Life 2 or something, and I liked the glowing light
on the front.
But that's all I liked about the Phantom, and I wouldn't touch that fucking lap board
with the 10-foot pole.
All right, well, for those that were worried that they may not get a hand on the PlayStation
3 this year, you should probably still be a little bit worried, but it is said that
they are on target to produce 1 million PlayStation 3s in 2006.
Sony has confirmed they are aiming for 1 million PlayStation 3s in North America by the end
of this year.
For day one, we're gonna have a total of 400,000 units for the launch period only for
North America, and we expect to have about 1 million units by the end of the calendar
year.
These are some pretty aggressive numbers, and that comes from Kazurai himself.
So those that were thinking that PlayStation 3 was gonna get delayed a little further in
the U.S., such as something I actually speculated previously on the show, I was wrong.
Yes, and I'm sure the PlayStation 3 is still launching spring of 2006, like they previously
said.
I do think the machine's gonna launch, but I think we're gonna see Xbox 360 shortages
all over again.
I'm not too disappointed.
I don't really need one at launch this time next year.
Yeah, I'll probably have one.
Honestly, the only reason I feel like I should own one of these at launch is because of the
show.
But I'll also go to Jamie's house and play hers.
We can see if that 1080p is worth a damn, since my TV will run it.
Yep.
You know what, though?
I think I'm still just gonna use it as a paperweight.
Well, we'll see.
We'll see.
Well, speaking of things to see, I do have a list of release dates for our buddies in
the U.K.
On the 26th is Anos 1701 for PC.
A bunch of other stuff on the 27th, and I'm not going to list all the systems they're
on because there's a few multiple releases, but there's Action Loop, Blade Dancer, Lineage
of Light, Dark Messiah, Might and Magic, Dragon Ball Z, Tenkaichi Budokai 2, Dragon Warriors
Volume 2, FIFA 07, Ford Street Racing, LA Duel, King of Fighters Maximum Impact 2, Metal
Slug, Metal Slug Anthology, Myst Ultimate Compilation, NBA 2K7, blah, blah, blah, Neo
Geo Battle Colosseum, Pipa Funnel, Pipa Funnel 2 on GBA, by the way, Pipa Funnel, Take the
Reigns, Prince of Persia Trilogy, Pro Evolution Soccer 6, Sudoku Master, Sims 2 Pets, Tiger
Woods PGA Tour 2007, Tom Clancy Splinter Cell Double Agent, Warhammer 40K, War of Dawn,
Dark Crusade, if you want to play Warhammer, just go buy the figures, Zoo Tycoon 2, Marine
Mania, and on the 31st Legend of Spyro, A New Beginning, although I'd just rather go
trick or treating.
Spyro's not that bad.
Spyro is an in-joke on Spyro's message board that I moderate on.
I'm going to be seeing Whoop 11 on that day, so screw Spyro.
Anywho...
Nerd!
I know!
Did you get any more nerdier tonight?
I'm going to go see a Trekkie band.
Are you wearing a pocket protector?
No.
Anywho...
I do have a chainmail bra.
La la la la la.
So there's going to be some good stuff coming out this week.
We've actually got some pretty cool stuff like, for example, Marvel Ultimate Alliance
will be coming out on Playstation 2, Xbox, and the 360, and I believe the PSP as well.
Some other fun games, Reservoir Dogs, the ultra-violent game, will be on Playstation
2 and Xbox.
We've got Splinter Cell Double Agent coming out on Playstation 2, Xbox, and GameCube.
Nicktoons Battle for Volcano Island on Playstation 2, GameCube DS, and Game Boy Advance.
And of course, Tony Hawk's Downhill Jam will be coming out on the DS and Game Boy Advance,
so that should be pretty neat.
And of course for you RPG fans, we've got Phantasy Star Universe coming out on Playstation
2, PC, and on the 360.
And other fun stuff, well these are a little bit way off now, and even more way off than
we mentioned last week.
I unfortunately have to give you guys the bad news that DDR Universe has been delayed
into March of 2007.
How do you know this?
From my work.
Alright.
It's from Konami themselves.
So, you know, I'm not surprised because all their other games...
Could they change it back?
It could very well change back.
I don't think it will change back, because that's a pretty large jump there, so yeah.
I would say March, because it makes sense, I mean it's just like Beatmania last year,
so no big deal.
There have been some price drops on some 360 games in case you're interested.
You know what though, I want to say real quick, for folks that were very critical of DDR Universe's
build at E3, that could actually be good news that they went back and retooled some things.
Because you know a lot of people were bitching about the interface on Universe and things
like that.
Remember when people complained about UltraMix 2, they went back and retooled it, and that
came out, in my mind, still the best DDR home release they've done yet.
So I'm not saying they are, I don't know, but that could be good news.
I'd rather them wait and get it right, you know.
Let's see, well anyways...
Or they're putting in the groove songs in it.
Just kidding, no.
A few price drops here.
We have Hitman Blood Money for the 360s dropped down to $39.99.
Every other version for Hitman Blood Money has actually dropped $10, so that's pretty
good.
Tomb Raider Legends dropped down to $29.99 for the 360, and all the other versions have
dropped also $10.
And finally, Condemned, which wasn't that expensive to begin with, and actually was
$39.99 for a while now, is now $29.99.
So if you haven't picked it up yet, probably a good time to do it.
Because it is the only Survivor Horror game, pretty much, on the 360.
Comments in our chatroom on Spyro.
Jeremy Todd 1 says, I remember I had a Spyro game for the GBA, and I got stuck on the 4th
or 5th world, and then I gave it away.
Separoth1215 says, Spyro is now voiced by Elijah Wood, I guess that's further proof
he's jumped the shark.
SSJ100Matt says, Spyro needs to end, it's time for him to grow up and burninate the
countryside.
There you go.
Well I was going to mention also, there was a game that actually came out last week, or
this week depending on when you're listening to the show I guess.
Splinter Cell Double Agent for the 360.
It is going to be one of the first titles that will support the brand new fall dashboard
update for the 360, and it will support 1080p.
So that's pretty sweet.
Well we'll have to see how sexy that looks on a TV that can support it.
Again, we'll be going over to Jamie's house.
Because she has to have all the big toys, because she's a nerd.
Hey, it's not just me, it's the fact that my husband has this, oh my god I need resolution!
I need a TV that's bigger than god!
Speaking of nerds, you have to be a little bit nerdy if you're importing your games from
Japan.
You know, I've imported a couple games from Japan, I wear that nerd badge with pride.
For those of you guys that are importing games from Japan, here's some games that are coming
out this week, or if you live in Japan, and you can just walk down the street and pick
up some of these games.
We have Nizu no Senoritsu 2, I'm sorry Senoritsu 2, which is coming out from Kid, it's an adventure
game, and of course it's the sequel to Nizu no Senoritsu 1, which is entering best hits
as well this week.
That all goes down on October 26th, 2006.
Princess Princess comes out from Marvelous Entertainment, it's also an adventure game.
I noticed the cover has these three anime looking chicks, who I would speculate might
be the princesses in this game.
Although there's two princesses in that title and three on the box, so, I don't know.
Also coming out from D3 is Mermaid Prism, another adventure game coming out October
26th.
And lastly on my list here we have Utaware Rumono, yet another adventure game, but this
one coming to us from Aqua Plus.
Check that out this week in Japan.
Sweet.
Is that Utaware?
Oh, probably.
Why do I do the Japanese releases?
I've never taken a lick of a Japanese class.
I think we need to.
I mean, I love our UK people, but I can trade.
I love them too.
Let me at them.
I love our Japanese people too.
Alright.
We'll talk that up behind the scenes, because you've actually had Japanese class, so I butcher
those words.
So.
I was just wondering.
I openly admit.
I can't see through you.
I just did the Japanese release dates because they were lonely and needed some love.
No one was talking about them anywhere, so, you know.
I took them into my home and I sheltered them, even if I did horribly butcher their names.
And releasing in Antarctica?
Nothing.
Sorry, guys.
However, being released in nowhere is actually, speaking of things that aren't actually going
to be making it out, I should say, the major UK retailers, Currys and Dixons, are not going
to be stocking Canis Canem Edit, which, for those of us in the US, is a bully.
One of their spokespeople said, we have no plans to stock Canis Canem Edit.
We are fully aware people will be able to buy this game elsewhere, but we feel this
game is not appropriate for Currys' family-friendly image.
Eat it.
It's Latin, right?
Okay.
I don't think I take Latin.
You do the Japanese words.
I'll do the Latin words.
Here we go.
Whatever.
Orange Lounge Radio.
We are high school graduates.
Anyway, it's going to be out October 27th.
It has a 15 rating.
It's not that bad of a game.
It got really good reviews and apparently the character at the end, spoiler alert, becomes
an upstanding citizen who gives more than he takes.
And makes out with boys as well as girls.
Is this true?
I think there are certain characters that you can make out with.
I need to quit this game.
No thank you.
The kid's what, 15?
Anyways, Grand Theft Auto IV.
Again, it's way off.
It's supposed to be coming out in October next year.
Like a year from now?
Yeah.
And I cannot wait.
But no, anyway, the PlayStation 3 is also getting exclusive episodic content.
Okay, listen now.
Rockstar, do you know what the word exclusive means?
It means one system, Getty, the other system, no Getty.
So you know what?
Maybe both Getty, some content, okay.
Anyways, so both of them will have online.
Don't ever read children's story time books.
Don't ever do that because you can't do it.
Shut up.
She can't speak Latin.
I can't speak Japanese and you can't read to children.
That's fine.
Anyways, so yeah, it's going to get episodic content, not a big surprise, and what might
be different is the content might be different for each platform, who knows.
My guess, no, because they are lazy, so it will be the same on both platforms.
I think you're wrong.
I think it's like Soul Calibur II, where you had one character on the, I'm not saying literally
this is it, but you know how you had Link on the GameCube and Spawn on the Xbox and
Heihachi on the PlayStation, and it was, you know, that was their exclusive content per
console.
What you're going to get in Grand Theft Auto is you're going to get like, you know, West
Island on the PlayStation and East Island on the Xbox, and the Wii gets nothing.
Rob, if you've ever played the multiplayer in Grand Theft Auto Liberty City Stories,
they're lazy.
They are not going to make new content.
We would be lucky if the original content works correctly.
If we had to wait a goddamn year for the game, I would think they have enough time to make
West Island and East Island.
West Side and East Side.
Exactly.
I was waiting for that.
Meanwhile, who won that Battlefield thing earlier in the show?
That was Jason from Florida?
Yeah.
I think that was his name.
All right.
Well, Jason from Florida, be careful before you install Battlefield 2142.
Something you might want to consider is that this letter that leaked to various gaming
blogs this week that basically says that there is IGA advertising technology in the game.
Now, the purpose of this technology is to deliver advertisements when you use the software
on the Internet.
It's basically going to collect anonymous information to measure what types of ads you
should be seeing based on, you know, where you live and things of that nature.
It's kind of anonymously looking at your IP or what have you.
And of course, everyone is going flipping nuts on forums about this, like, how dare
EA spy on me, how this is an invasion of my privacy, I was going to buy Battlefield 2142
but now I'm not, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Loki had some strong opinions on this.
Yeah.
It's retarded is what it is.
And the reason it's retarded is because this is retarded or the reaction, the backlash
is retarded.
And this is why.
It's for just those fucking dynamic ads that are in the game.
But all it looks at is your IP address to figure out where the hell in the world you
are.
So if you're in France, that the ads aren't in English, they're in French or they're for
products that come out in France, you know, stuff like that.
So it, you know, and also it's collecting information on how many views of said ad you
have made so that they can go and, you know, bill whomever, you know, their clients.
Our friend and pal and buddy VXChaseNXV in chat is jumping up and down screaming.
An IP address is not anonymous information, grr argh.
Get over it, people.
Seriously, it's not like saying we're collecting your credit card information.
We're going to be watching where you're browsing on the internet.
It's just a goddamn IP.
It's just figuring out where you are in the world.
I don't think EA is the first company to be watching you.
No.
War of the Warcraft.
Every time you sign into Xbox Live, Microsoft knows what you're playing and they track it
on the internet for your friends to see.
So War of the Warcraft, you know, they, you know, monitor your computer for spyware, but
oh my God, they can be monitoring for other things, you know.
It's just, whatever.
I used somebody's IP address to track down when I was being stalked.
Well, yeah, I mean, you could, I don't, they might be collecting your IP address, but they're
just using that for this.
I don't think they care where your house is.
Yeah, I don't think they're going to come knock on your door, sir, you've been playing
too much of our game.
Well, they don't care that, you know, you've been looking, you know, it's, you know, porn
all the day.
What they should have done, I guess, what would be the common, you know, the happy medium
here is have you sign up on their website or whatever, putting your address information
in there and then you don't have to have your IP tracked because they'll go off that address
and send you ads based on where you live via that.
DMN says, but this allows for date people in insert zip code here.
That shit's annoying.
Microsoft doesn't hit you with shitty ads.
Yes, they do.
Download our artist video of the month on Xbox Live this week.
Buy a Yaris from the Xbox Live Arcade because no one else is.
Buy a Sion.
I just feel sorry for people like in my home state having to see ads for, you know, all
kinds of, you know, heat hauling.
What about the official Xbox Magazine that makes you watch stupid commercials to unlock
points in their disk to unlock a further demo, which by the way is probably already on Xbox
Live Marketplace anyways.
What I think is interesting though, let's look at the bigger picture here.
Loki, what do you think of this?
The bigger picture that people are saying is bullshit, is that I'm paying, you know,
60 bucks, 50 bucks, whatever for a game that has advertising in it.
That's too much money.
If the game has advertising in it, it shouldn't cost me that much money.
Does it cost you anything to play online?
No, it doesn't.
You know why?
Because that money that they're making from advertising helps run the servers.
I'm just surprised that someone with such a philosophy is actually kind of supporting
this in a way.
It's kind of interesting.
I don't see a problem with it, and to be honest, so what?
There's fucking ads on billboards that are in this world.
It's not like, you know, my character has a fucking, you know, date hot people or whatever
in this zip code strapped to his body or something.
It's not like they're that obtrusive.
They're just on fucking billboards.
I don't notice what the hell are on billboards in the game, and if you're sitting there staring
at the fucking billboard, you're probably going to get shot or stepped on by a giant
robot.
So, whatever.
If you're really going to get your panties in the bunch for that, I don't want to see
you playing Battlefield 2142 anyways.
Go play another game.
VX Jason says, give me the ability to run my own server and fuck your advertisements.
You think people are going to end up hacking this game to take the shit out?
Sure, why not?
They've done it before with other games, so I don't see why they couldn't.
All right.
Well, all this talk of privacy and invading our privacy and, you know, ruffling our feathers
here.
It's, you know, the internet versus EA and what have you.
It makes us a little bit angsty, so that means we have to bring on the FUs of the week.
Yes, the antibiotic that they prescribe quite often for a sinus infection, so I guess it
really is rooted to my sinus infection that I'm still not, you know, done with.
But I would like to actually be able to digest solid food, please, drugs, hurry up and be
done with me so that I can actually eat a pizza without wanting to die.
Not love me.
F you to my head hurting because I have a headache right now and it's one of those ones
that's not really that bad, but it's in the back of my skull and that sucks because there's
no way to get rid of it, so I fucking hate that and I get them so often.
It's from your neck?
It's from a tumor.
It's not a tumor.
F you to the fact that I'm getting on a red-eye flight tomorrow night to New York City and
I'm getting sick.
I can feel my body getting sick.
I know this because I was cold in my office all day and I usually don't get cold unless
I'm getting sick, so that's just great.
I'm getting sick to ruin my vacation in New York City.
Yay!
Joint excitement.
F you to viruses.
New York City?
Sorry.
Shut up.
Get a rope.
Anyways, moving on.
Well, speaking of things that are moving at least, we've got a track listing for Elite
Beat Agents, so if anybody who is interested, and actually, again, the release for that
is going to be November 6th over here in the US, but the songs that are going to be in
it is Walkie Talkie Man by Stereogram, ABC, Jackson 5, Skater Boy, Avril Lavigne, I Was
Born to Love You, Queen, Rock This Town, Stray Cats, which is a great song, Highway Star,
Deep Purple, YMCA, Village People, September, Earth, Wind & Fire, Canned Heat, Jamiroquai,
Material Girl, Madonna, Lala, Ashley Simpson, you're the inspiration, Chicago.
You know I used to actually have that on a 45.
Nerd.
No that just meant it was the 80s.
Survivor, Destiny's Child, Without a Fight, Hoobastank, Believe, Cher, that's so gay,
Let's Dance, David Bowie, I love David Bowie, Jumpin' Jack Flash, Rolling Stones, Makes
No Difference, Sum 41, The Anthem, Good Charlotte.
Well, this will certainly ruffle the feathers of those folks that were expecting to get
more Japanese style music, but if that's what you wanted, import Oh and Don.
I thought they were expecting to get Japanese music.
Exactly, so this is certainly an Americanized version, it definitely is going to take this
series in a completely different direction.
You know what, although there's a couple of songs on that list that made me go, ugh, you
know any music game is going to have a couple songs that made me go, ugh, so I'm okay with
it.
I think it'll actually be fun, there's some kind of funny songs on there, so it should
be interesting to see it in this system.
I'm upset with this track list.
Why?
Because any time that Cher song is seen anywhere with my eyes, it gets stuck in my head, and
I can't get it out, and I also think of that Margaret Cho act too where she was talking
about it.
Yay, I know what game to play every time Jamie's over.
You know what, I know which ass to kick every time I'm over.
Yes, speaking of ass kicking, Red Octane or Activision have basically kicked the ass of
any third party guitar controller, because according to the official PlayStation Magazine
demo of Guitar Hero 2, they will not work, so if that's indicative of the final game,
your third party controller will no worky on the brand new game, so that kind of sucks.
At least this is based on the demo, right?
Based on the demo, but you know what, I don't know, how hard could it be to get a controller
to work?
I mean seriously, so, I don't know, we'll see, I'm sure people will find a workaround
for that, but as of right now, that's kind of poopy, seeing as Red Octane started off
as a third party controller manufacturer, and now they're just kind of saying, fuck
you all.
Yeah, so let me get this straight.
A company that got its start as a third party peripheral manufacturer has effectively locked
out third party peripheral manufacturers from their latest games.
It's a preemptive strike.
It's cutting out future competition for other third party.
It's interesting.
It's an interesting tactic.
I mean that's business.
You can hem and haw all you want about Red Octane or bastard people, they're hypocrites,
blah, blah, blah, but that's just business.
There was basically the official controller, they way it kind of recognized it was an official
controller is because they had the left button shorted out, kind of like how pop-in music
has that.
They have a button shorted out to be able to detect that it's the official pop-in music
controller.
What's interesting though is there's some speculation that this was to lock out those
third party wireless controllers because Red Octane was coming out with their own wireless
controller for the PlayStation 2.
Interesting.
Well, if guitars aren't your thing and singing is more your style, you already know the karaoke
revolution American Idol is coming out on the PlayStation 2 pretty soon and Konami is
going to be launching a tour to find the first virtual American Idol.
And if you win this and you are the virtual American Idol, you will win airfare, accommodations
and tickets to a taping of the real American Idol TV show so you can look at the better
singers.
Oh boy.
Even if you just participate, you'll still get, what is this, a contest t-shirt and a
coupon for $5 off when pre-ordering through konami.com.
If you win in your region, you do get a free copy of the game.
So this is going on tour around the nation and let's see, Loki, I want you to keep November
4th clear because we're taking a trip to San Francisco to go to the Stone's Town Galleria
because you know you owe it to the listeners to participate in this.
I am not doing this.
Oh yes, he is, folks.
No, I'm not.
And we're going to tape the whole thing for the future of the Ontario TV project.
I am not doing this.
Yes, you are.
It's fine.
I am not doing this.
I know.
You're going to play this little game here where you're going to say you're not going
to do it.
No, I'm not.
And then we're going to get him and then it's supposed to be a surprise, folks.
He's just being sheepish.
Don't worry.
We'll have him there and root for him if you're in San Francisco.
I am not playing that damn game.
Bring your Loki signs, like they have on the show, Loki is my American Idol.
You know who we should take to that?
Iguana Girl.
We should, but we'll take her to another city because I've got to have Loki win this one.
No.
Iguana Girl can go and be the real winner.
That's fine.
Oh, see, look, you're getting support from our chat.
Look at all the...
They're so excited that you're going to be saying, what song are you going to do when
you try out for Karaoke Revolution America?
I'm not playing that game.
I know, I know.
Yeah, that's right, Matt.
Keep telling yourself that.
I'm not driving down there either.
Anyways.
I'll drive.
It's fine.
No.
I won't even charge you for gas.
Jamie will chip in for gas.
We'll go and dutch.
With what money?
I'm poor.
Anyways.
I'll sell the ferret.
Oh, my baby.
If dancing is more of your thing, you'll be happy to know that the ever rumored, because
everyone wanted a DDR MMO, well, Dave Perry, who you might remember from Shiny, is creating
a new MMO called Dance, which is promising players will have a chance to create their
own unique dancers, and through variable styles, facial features, and clothing accessories,
you can also be able to actually play.
It sounds very similar to O2Jam or something like that, but it should be pretty interesting.
Obviously, when I first read the news on this, it sounds very similar to one of those popular
Korean music games, such as O2Jam, R2B, one of those types of games, kind of an Americanized
dish, you know, I wouldn't say it's an Americanized version of this, but that idea, that concept
in a localized MMO should be interesting.
I'll check it out if it's free.
I mean, it can't be free, right?
Exactly.
Will they be watching my IP, though, and delivering me in-game ads?
You betcha.
Actually, I think this was one of the ones that they were talking about supporting it
with ads, because it was going to be free, but it might have been another game, I don't
know.
All right.
Well, every week, you send us emails, and Dark Soccer writes down your IPs with a big
magic marker.
And then I lock them down to your zip code.
Sends them to the spam factory to say, no, I'm just kidding.
Of course, we never give out your emails, addresses, or IP.
We wouldn't do that to you.
We're not the man.
But we will read what you write to us on air.
Actually, I find where you live, and if your letter sucks, I leave Stinky Poo on your front
doorstep.
Oh, I see.
All right.
Well, hopefully, we've got some letters that did not earn a poo bombing this week.
Dark Soccer, open up the mailbag and pull some emails out for us.
The first one comes from, well, it doesn't really have a name on it, so I'm just going
to say Pendragon.
Actually, Aibo is not useless.
I've had this ERS-7 since they first came out.
He watches my house when I'm not there, and he has his own blog on the web.
Meet Falco at FusionCrew.org slash Falco.
That would be kind of funny.
I did want to get one at one point, but they're just too damn expensive.
I want an Eibo.
I'm in shock someone wrote us to tell us they have an Eibo that has a blog.
My Xbox 360 has a blog.
I want an Eibo that has a blog and that we'll be walking around because it randomly takes
pictures and stuff.
It's like, oh, look, there's people having sex on the couch or something like that and
posts a blog.
It would just get more pictures of your foot, but I'm going to start a PayPal account for
myself.
The donate to Dark Soccer's Eibo fund.
You do that.
Let's see if I get an Eibo.
Come on, chat room.
You know you want to help me get an Eibo to replace the ferret.
Sell your goddamn TV.
Then you can afford an Eibo.
I'll get an Eibo and I'll name him Ferret.
Anyway, this is when I get my wireless router working the right way again.
You can email Falco and he'll take a picture and email it back to you.
That's at ibofalco.comcast.net, so I think that's pretty funny.
By the way, he wants us to pick him for the drawing, but I think it's a little too late.
Sorry.
Maybe you should have entered your Eibo.
Dude, I want an Eibo.
I want an Eibo to win a contest.
We should have a world's sexiest Eibo contest.
I don't want one of those ones that actually look like dogs.
I want one of the old school Eibos.
You just need to...
They're really cool.
Anyway.
This one comes from Gomez.
Hey, Orange Lounge.
This is the first time I've ever sent you guys an email because I'm kind of an Orange
Lounge noob because I only started listening about episode 196.
Nice run on sentence.
Welcome to the show.
I'm glad you've decided to stick around.
I love the show and the praise you give Xbox 360 LOL.
However, my friends and I have been having some problems with the system.
My controllers now have a mandatory tape job on the back of them to keep the batteries
connected so the controller does not disconnect due to a loss of power, which makes me really
mad.
But this doesn't compare to a friend of mine whose Xbox broke just recently, but Microsoft
was generous enough to give him a new one, which within a week was also broken.
He had to endure another couple of months without an Xbox, even though he had just bought
NHL07.
Dude, you're like the king of run on sentences.
This is awesome.
NHL07?
Boo.
The system can be a hassle when it freezes on me or the controllers disconnect in the
middle of a game or battle, but nothing makes me more mad than the controller disconnect
and because of this my Xbox freezes.
Either way, I love my Xbox 360 because of the fantastic graphics and games, and yet
I hate the frustrations.
I guess I hate it and love it.
The other topic I had to say was to do with the new Phantasy Star Universe demo that came
out to the marketplace recently.
Since I've downloaded pretty much every demo I had to play, this one pretty much got me
hooked but not before some difficulty.
I originally made myself one of those robot guy characters and pretty much held the A
button through the whole tutorial while talking to my friend, which I later found out was
a mistake because I had never played these MMO games before.
So all I could do was walk around asking people, hey, how do you battle?
Or do you know how to get money?
And my normal response would be, no, go away you noob, you suck at this game, screw off,
and ah ha ha ha, yeah right noob.
No, yeah right what a noob, which didn't help me at all because I couldn't have any fun
with this demo and made my gaming experience go down the drain.
However, I remembered Sky on your show mentioned something about being a girl in World of Warcraft
and how he got lots of items and stuff for free, so I decided to give it a try.
I made a new account and made this girl human super hot with handlebars or pigtails or whatever
you guys like to call them.
And once I entered the world, it was entirely, hello, how's it going, oh wow, you're really
hot, let's go out.
And when I said, do you guys know how to battle, oh yeah, let's go, let me show you.
Gomez responds, and the guy showed me where to go and everything even though I dished
him once I got into the battling world.
I am now given free money and items in this group because I just have to say my mic is
broken so now I can just type everything I want to say to the players.
I never knew until how many Desperate Gamer guys there really are out there.
Sincerely, Gomez.
I love this email.
This email is fantastic.
Because someone actually took a suggestion of mine and ran with it.
You know what's funny?
I'm not playing a girl in PSO because, you know, you may be new to the show so you may
not have picked up on the fact that I'm a gamer who enjoys gamers of the male variety
if you know what I mean, right?
So I actually made a character who I would find attractive who is a male, like, you know,
tall and handsome type guy, right?
And that's the character I made.
But the thing is that luckily I had the PSO experience so I kind of was able to pick up
PSU pretty quickly.
Yes, a lot's different, but I had my friends to voice chat with and kind of figure the
things out.
So what does it say about me always making short, cute girls?
Nothing.
Because you're a short, cute girl.
And I have to say that the one male character I made back in PSO, though, was a femoral.
Just be careful, though, because, you know, I do have a friend who is, like, OMG a real
female that plays Phantasy Star Universe who's been playing the beta and she has a female
character in the game and people harass her on voice chat all the time.
And not only that, like, I was partied with her, I saw this happen.
Random guys will run up to her and do those little motions that'll make it look like they're
eating her out or trying to sodomize her and, like, all this stuff.
People are so stupid.
I can't wait for this game to go pay so that all these people will have to, you know, if
that's how they want to spend their $10 a month, then fine.
But you know, at least we'll filter out a lot of the lame-os that are just playing this
because it's free.
This should have, like...
Now, what I did mean to ask, though, you've still got your mags in that game, right?
No.
You kinda have.
Damn!
You have a house pet who apparently later can be an NPC that joins you, but it's a little
different.
And you feed it stuff kind of like you did the mags, but it's a little different.
That annoys us too.
Okay, I'm going back to PSO so I can use my oppa oppa.
No, no, no, no, no.
PSU is beautiful.
I want my oppa oppa!
The first time I dual-wielded sabers, I was like, oh god, I love this game.
Oppa oppa.
Unless I can make my pet an oppa oppa, then I'll be happy.
Okay, last email.
You can name it whatever you want.
Mine's named nothing.
I want mine to look like an oppa oppa.
It kinda does, so name it oppa oppa.
Okay.
Email.
Last email.
This is from Mark.
Hey guys.
You know what?
I think that that's sexist.
Okay, I'm just kidding.
Oh.
I'm kidding.
I thought that was the email.
I was like, what?
Explain yourself.
I'm just curious as to why you released the podcast in two parts.
Is it that you can't get it all edited by Monday, or is it that you hope to get people
to listen to the live broadcast instead of having to wait for the two parts?
To be honest, I will never listen to the live broadcast because I just don't have the time.
I hope you guys can change this.
Anyhow, great show as always.
Thanks, Mark.
Because we want to.
Nana nana nana.
Nana.
No.
We did it at first because we were a little afraid.
We didn't know how the server would handle a two to three hour program being thrown out
there all at once.
So we thought by breaking it up into chunks, it wouldn't be so bad.
On our old server, we used to have to worry about bandwidth a lot.
On this one, we don't have to worry about that so much.
Hugs and kisses to our webmaster, VX Jason XV, who makes all this shit happen behind
the scenes.
We split it up in the beginning, and that's just kind of worked for us.
For us, it's a little harder to sit down and listen to this podcast.
It looks like it's three hours long than it is to just get little bits and pieces twice
a week.
I don't know how we've looked at it.
I have two words that explain it for me.
Pee break.
Hypothetically, we could, when we break the show, just put a little like...
Bobby takes a break on his show, but he'll put a little noise in there.
He'll edit out his break and put a little noise in there.
Technically, we could do that, but I don't know.
It's just kind of what's worked for us.
We might change our minds later in the future.
I don't know, but for right now, it's kind of what we're doing.
Email us if you feel strongly one way or the other because I've heard from people that
kind of like the fact that they get regular OLR content.
You won't this week.
There is no second part this week, but a lot of folks like their regular OLR.
We're irregular this week.
Yes, that's right.
We're pregnant.
Is that it for emails?
Just because someone's pregnant doesn't mean that they have irregularity.
I'm just messing.
God.
It just means they don't need enough fiber.
I'm just messing.
Jeez.
I'm getting all angsty.
I already did the FUs of the week lately.
You're catching me midweek after I got off of work.
Any more mailbag?
No.
Send us more mailbag at OrangeLawnTrader.com.
Give this woman more to read next week.
Any more stuff and give me money.
Anyways, there was an unconfirmed rumor this week, as every other week, that there may
be a Blue Dragon anime series in the works.
This is basically coming from a toy hobby figurine page from a Japanese toy company.
It wouldn't be that far of a stretch because it is created by Hironobu Sakaguchi, who is
the brainchild of Final Fantasy, and Dragon Ball Dragon Quest creator Akira Toyayama.
Very strong ties to anime.
They'd be kind of neat.
But he also did all of the character designs for Chrono Trigger.
You said Akira Toyama, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah, he did all the character designs for Dragon Quest and Chrono Trigger.
There has been short anime series for each, or segments of anime.
They have existed in anime form.
Doesn't matter.
They have existed in anime form at some point.
So I guess we'll have to see because right now it's just rumor.
If Microsoft can have their Viva Pinata show here, why can't they have a Blue Dragon anime
there?
I'd rather have Blue Dragon.
Viva Pinata sucks.
I watched the thing on Xbox.
It wasn't the end of the world.
It is!
Horrible!
It was bad, but if I was seven years old, I'd probably like it.
Anyway, if I was seven years old, I might enjoy Bubble Bobble.
No, I'm kidding.
Actually, you can love Bubble Bobble no matter what your age.
It is a very cute game, though, aimed at children.
But guess what, kids?
Don't buy your kids Bubble Bobble Revolution on the DS or they're going to be pissed off
because apparently this game was not play-tested past level 30.
In other words, the game is supposed to have a boss show up at level 30, and the boss does
not show up, therefore rendering the game unplayable.
Every time.
A quote from the source, we have been looking very hard into this issue with Nintendo and
have now determined that all of the cartridges that have been shipped in North America are
faulty.
Needless to say, we are extremely sorry that this situation has arisen and would like to
apologize to you for this issue.
We have already started the process whereby a corrected version is to be manufactured
and will ensure that all customers have their copies replaced.
Unfortunately, this will take 8 to 10 weeks simply because of the time required to manufacture
new carts.
We will update you with what you will need to do to get a replacement game as soon as
this has been determined.
Hey, folks, over there at Taito making this game.
How about you tell us a little bit about what you're going to do for your QA processes in
the future?
Is it only the US one?
I'm not sure.
I think it's the only region this has been released in so far.
Has it?
I thought that it was a...
Maybe.
It's the only place with a problem showing up.
Well, you know what?
Apparently, they were too busy playing Rainbow Islands, which also, you know, was released
the same time instead of Bubble Bobble.
I mean, words cannot express what a fuck up this is on Taito's part.
I mean, it's...
So, nobody ever played through the whole game over in their testing.
You could use cheat codes to get through, I don't know, but somehow, some way, this
really, really big flaw was overlooked.
It will make me hesitate every time I go to buy a Taito game on the DS from this point
forward, until they say what they're going to do to make it better.
I guess, but then again, you know, perhaps they've learned their lesson, so to speak,
so I don't know, who knows, maybe their QA will get a lot better real fast after this
very embarrassing screw up, but not good, folks.
Not good.
Yeah, DMN says in our chat room, someone's getting fucking fired.
Well, I'm going to raise a good point, Squeenix owns Taito now.
Oh great, maybe Final Fantasy XII will be unplayable.
I doubt that, though.
There's lots of things to doubt, though, whenever anything that's involving them is, you know,
coming about, but never mind, I'm not going to be bitter.
Not going to be bitter.
Anyway, speaking of releases and things, we have some stuff from THQ for launch week for
the Wii 4 games.
The first, of course, this is the big one, is Kars, for all of our Pixar fans, one of
who has landed in San Jose today, who I'm probably going to be hearing about this all
weekend.
We know.
We all know.
What?
I'm just messing.
Oh no, no, I'm going to be hearing about it all weekend.
Anyway, also coming out is Barnyard, Avatar the Last Airbender, and SpongeBob SquarePants
Creature from the Krusty Krab.
So this just confirms Loki's list from previously, in other words?
Yeah.
I don't remember the Barnyard title, but then again, I wouldn't have remembered that.
It's been there, and it's just like, and you know, it's just so exciting because these
are all GameCube ports of like previous months.
She could have said three games are coming out for the Wii, whoop-dee and shit, and it
would have had the exact same impact for me.
I'm just sorry, not interested in any of these titles.
You know what's really sad?
I guess Kars might be cubed.
Some of these games that I thought were new are not new, like for example, GT from Ubisoft
is apparently a port of GT for the GameCube that came out a long time ago, and same with
Monster 4x4 World Circuit, it's a port of an Xbox game that came out a while ago too.
Or I think it may have been a GameCube game at one time too, but I know the Xbox version
came out in April, and so they're nothing new, it's just a lot of ports, and I actually
cancelled my pre-order for GT because of that, so I'm like, I'm not going to buy any fucking
ports no matter how cool that little steering wheel might be.
You can buy the steering wheel if you really want it.
They are selling it separately.
Use it on an Excite truck, which apparently has no online play.
That's very disappointing.
Rob.
No.
The chat room made me!
Don't even think about it.
The chat room made me.
Rob.
What?
Low key, please save this show from going down the toilet anymore.
Sorry.
We're stuck in the U-Bend.
Anyways, so crappy Wii games, hooray.
Some things that are not so crappy, though, and quite fun, actually, Mario Kart GP 2 is
coming to an arcade.
That's the arcade one, right?
Yeah.
Hot!
Yeah, that's the game that I played while I was drunk on my bachelor party.
Why isn't that video on YouTube?
Uh, because I haven't loaded it on there yet.
We're going to let that happen.
But basically, the game itself looks very similar to what we've seen before, although
I do see some things, though, that look new, like some of the characters...
I don't know who this is, and I don't know if you would know, Rob, but this character
looks very, very familiar.
Let's see here.
I think...
No, this is from Tomogachi or whatever, I think.
That character right there.
Yeah, that looks like a Tomogachi corner shop.
So that's going to be one of the brand new characters, a Tomogachi character, and then
it looks like you've got all your repeat characters, Wario, Mario, Luigi, Waluigi, Yoshi, Princess
Peach, Toad, Bowser, Donkey Kong, and then the ghosts, Pac-Man and Mrs. Pac-Man.
Very interesting.
There's, of course, a lot more stuff that you can put on your character or your screen
caps.
You know how they do the webcam thing?
Yeah, it's just my little finger up and put the princess hair over it.
That's why we got to put my video on YouTube because my screen cap was hilarious when I
was drunk.
We'll work on that, folks.
If you're too poor to purchase a Mario Kart GP machine, perhaps you're also too poor to
buy a Wii, even though there's a huge difference in price.
I don't know.
That's a good question I can think of.
If you are too poor to pick up a Nintendo Wii, you might get a chance at Toys R Us.
They're doing a deal or no deal promotion.
You get these things in the newspapers that are going to be coming out.
They call them weekly circulars, and when you get one of these circulars, what you can
do is you can cut out the suitcases and you can take a deal, which is 10% off any item
in store, which I would think could be used on the Wii for a nice little saving, or no
deal.
The cashier will scan the ticket and possibly you win a Wii console or you lose your 10%
coupon and get a 5% coupon instead.
No word on the banker or a very scary looking Howie Mandel coming into play here, but supposedly
25,000 Wiis are being given away as well as a $1 million prize and a trip to Los Angeles
to go actually see the show live in person and be frightened by Howie Mandel in person.
Good luck to any of our listeners that enter this.
I forgot to mention, since we don't have the video of my playing Mario Kart GP drunk on
YouTube, you can, however, download it for your PSP on OLRPSP.com under the download
section.
I assure the listeners it will be on YouTube by the time you hear this show.
Look for username OrangeLoungeRadio.
Well, speaking of other amusing things, guess what Xbox is going to be, guess what Microsoft
is going to be doing?
Charging me more microtransactions for luminous backgrounds.
Actually no, it's what they're already doing.
They're already in work on a successor to the Xbox 360.
Basically Chris Lewis, who is the EMEA for Microsoft, their VP, sorry, has been quoted
saying you can't sit back on your laurels in this business, the consumer won't let you,
the developer certainly won't let us, so that's happening now.
They said there's not anything they can really say on it right now, of course, but it's still
very, very early on.
So they're thinking ahead.
This isn't a surprise.
I mean, Xbox 360 was being worked on years in advance.
Just because they're laying down the preliminary groundwork does not mean the 360 is dead.
By any means.
These things take years to happen.
I think it's getting blown out of proportion a little bit by some of the gaming media out
there.
Guess what, folks, Sony is probably working on a PlayStation 4 and Nintendo is doing a
Wii again or whatever they're going to call it, I mean, more Wii 2.
Who remembers the Neptune?
How long did that take to eventually become the Dreamcast?
Oh, the dolphin, huh?
Yeah, I gotcha.
Alright.
Yeah, hopefully they'll, you know, maybe they'll pick a cool development name and stick to
it.
Remember how disappointed people were when Nintendo dropped that name Revolution and
went with Wii?
Although I think people are used to it now.
You know, I think people got the sand out of their vagina now over that whole naming
of the Wii.
I told you.
Revolution was a cool name.
Wasn't I right?
Simplicity.
Easy to remember.
Something people will talk about.
Well, we'll see when the damn thing goes on sale.
Besides, they need to save Revolution in case they come up with something really, really
cool like, you know, 3D holographic projection or something like that.
They tried that.
It was a game called Time Stalker.
Which was the big reveal on this show that Nintendo was supposedly putting in the Wii
console.
Yeah, but you know what?
Somebody is still working on it apparently because that was still a quote that one of
the game companies out there had the technology to do it, so, you know, unless PlayStation
3 is doing that, which I don't think so, but, you know, whatever.
I guess that would justify the cost.
All right, well, when I said something about Microsoft charging on Xbox Live for little
bits and pieces here and there, I wasn't joking, folks.
Now, to be fair, it's not really Microsoft that sets up these fees.
It is the developers.
Well, wait until you hear this one.
Electronic Arts is selling Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2007 cheats on Xbox Live.
In other words, you could just download for 200 points, unlock golfer, and unlock courses.
That's 200 each.
And you will open up all the hidden golfers and courses in the game.
Don't even have to think about, oh, I've got to play through and do this.
I've got to play through and do that to unlock it.
So you can still play through the game the old-fashioned way and not have to pay the
points.
But if you just want to unlock everything right at the start, just like that, pay 200
points for a simple unlock key.
Good idea, bad idea.
Why?
Because it takes, why hands, actually it's more of a reflection on the society.
So I don't want to say necessarily bad idea, just a sad idea that people are so wanton
to instant gratification, wanton it now that they can't freaking work for something.
That pisses me off.
But Jamie, I have to have this course.
My friends are coming over tonight for a Tiger Woods tournament.
I have to play this course.
I suggest you start playing the hell out of it now.
Sit your ass down in that chair and play your goddamn golf.
Loki, any thoughts?
Good idea, bad idea.
I think it's dumb just because, I mean, I guess whether they're trying to make sure
that when the next Tiger Woods game comes out, which is just going to have more courses
anyways and probably not be very different, that you'll be finished with this one because
you'll probably have already cheated by then or finished the game.
Is this a way for them to say, F you, game facts, F you, strategy guides.
Well, they tried the same thing before.
They had EA put out Madden NFL tutorial videos for some of the basic stuff and they were
selling them online on Xbox Live Marketplace, stuff that should have probably been included
in the game, like how to throw a pass.
Yeah, that might be useful when I play the game.
Jeremy Todd one in chat says, breaking news, they're going to add drivable golf carts in
Tiger Woods 2008 and you'll have to pay for the steering wheel so that you'll be able
to drive the golf cart.
I would love to drive golf carts in Tiger Woods and run over people.
That would sell the game for me.
All right, well, that's just about it for the gaming news tonight, but it's not it for
everything we've got to say because you know Dark Soccer, she has to surf the web up and
down and left and right every single week and find a site for your viewing pleasure
and it's featured here in the website of the week.
Dark Soccer, where should the kids be pointing their browsers right now?
I would suggest the site of false advertising, a gallery of parody.
It's at parody.organiq.com and it's got lots of neat little false ads basically, you just
scroll through the site and it's basically like one of them is star sucks coffee, drink
our coffee or we'll break your legs and radio shit, you've got money, we've got pockets.
So for those folks that like, you know, funny ha ha parody ads.
My favorite one on here is like the fourth one in, it's an ad for Prozac, it says you'd
kill them without it, it shows a picture of a family.
Do they have a parody ad of the whole, you remember it was controversial about two months
ago, they had the white PSP ads, do we have any parodies of that?
No, I haven't seen any so far, I've seen Calvin Clone dare to be the same.
Get working on that folks.
And Baby Gasp, next week I'll outgrow this, it's pretty funny.
Check it out boys and girls, Dark Soccer's website of the week.
One other thing we've been featuring here pretty weekly here on Orange Lounge Radio
are DDR previews.
We've been previewing new tracks of DDR games upcoming on the Xbox and Xbox 360 systems
and guys you know what, next week is the last week for this, cry, sob, well that's right
the games will be out soon enough.
We still have more songs soon enough, well I guess after what you've learned tonight
maybe not that soon for Universe, but we do know that Ultramix 4 is coming, so at least
we can give you a little taste of what you can expect in March, that's alright, March
is a slow period anyway.
Who releases games today?
March is actually pretty heavy.
Is it?
Yeah.
I thought it was April.
April got heavier.
No, April starts to die down again.
March is like the end of fiscal quarter months.
Well then I obviously don't know what I'm talking about so let's get to the music.
We have two new tracks tonight from DDR Ultramix 4 and two new tracks from DDR Universe, let's
start it off with a track from DDR Ultramix 4, no long versions tonight folks, sorry to
say, just have some short tracks for you guys.
This first song is from DDR Ultramix 4, it's by a group called Neuroactive and the song
is called More Serotonin, enjoy it here on the sneak peaks.
Thanks for watching, and I'll see you guys in the next one.
Bye!
I was neuroactive with more serotonin here on Orange Lounge Radio, DDR Sneak Peeks.
I caught myself doing the little head bob thing, Night at a Roxbury, during that song.
For a dancy-trancy song, not bad.
I like that.
This is a good edit.
If dancy-trancy isn't your thing, remember that these games keep a variety of music.
This one is definitely a unique sounding song, this next song we have coming up.
It's very interesting.
It's interesting.
It looked like someone cut a really stinky fart.
No, it's just different.
It was not what I expected when I first heard this song.
You guys see if maybe it's more your thing?
It's by Wave Group, featuring Scotty D. They did that Stompin' at the Gotham song last
week, which was awesome, that jazzy one we all liked.
See if you like this one.
It's called Bongo, here on the Orange Lounge Radio, DDR Sneak Peeks.
Bongo.
Hear that?
It's one of the most exciting sounds in the world.
Orange Lounge Radio, DDR Sneak Peeks.
That is Bongo, by Wave Group, featuring Scotty D, coming soon to DDR Universe.
See what I'm telling you?
It's a little different.
That song is growing on me.
I like the whole Austin Powers 60's spy theme vibe that song has going.
I think, with all due respect to the folks that wrote that and sang it, I think it's
the voiceovers that kind of bugged me a little bit.
I don't know.
It's a little weird and out of place to me, but it'll probably be...
Songs sound different when you're just listening to them than when you do when you're actually
playing them and dancing to them when they're coming out of your TV, so I'm sure I won't
even notice.
All right.
Let's go to a song from DDR UltraMix 4, and this one's pretty exciting.
This is by a group called Real Life.
You might remember, years ago in the 80's, they did that song Send Me an Angel, and they
would still play it in clubs around the nation, right?
So they have a song in DDR UltraMix 4, it's called Oblivion, and it was remixed by Nevaraka,
who did some of the other remixes in previous UltraMix games.
I didn't realize that they sung the original of that.
I have the Nevaraka mix, I just need to listen to the original.
There it is.
Real Life with Oblivion here on Orange Launch Radio, sneak peeks.
We are in my heart, I am running out of the truth.
I'm running out of the truth Whatever I do I never want to hurt you
When it comes to this I feel fine but I have to admit
Here in my heart I'm running out of the truth
Life goes on and the world turns round Yeah, life goes on and the world turns round
Cynthia, bring it on Cynthia, bring it on
I'm running out of the truth
Let's enjoy!
Orange Lounge Radio
Thank you for watching!