[SPEAKER_18]: All Games Radio is now broadcasting live from Sacramento, California.
[SPEAKER_18]: Up next, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tonight on Orange Lounge Radio, sadly we did not win the Mega Millions, so we're here, and not in Tahiti.
[SPEAKER_14]: But lucky for you guys, because it's been a very busy week in the Bomani news world, and we have a lot of stuff to cover tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: So stay tuned, or we'll throw you into the Hunger Games, and you'll have to kill each other endlessly, and complain about how you're in a rip-off of Battle Royale, even though the concept's been around since like the 20s.
[SPEAKER_16]: we'll be right back after this Orange Lounge Radio is presented in the TMI sound format Orange Lounge Radio
[SPEAKER_17]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_17]: Call me Daddy.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge may contain adult content.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge may contain many four-letter words.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge may contain a scene of nudity.
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge may contain plenty of... Just kidding.
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio will not contain any of that in this episode.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, isn't that special?
[SPEAKER_16]: Orange Lounge Radio Live is a fully interactive program via our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_16]: And now, here are your hosts for Orange Lounge Radio Live, DarkSakura, Sky, and Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are live!
[SPEAKER_14]: This is episode number 452 for this April the 1st of 2012.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're tuned in to the Be Money Scene's most fabulous radio stations of all things Be Money.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then some.
[SPEAKER_14]: My name is Rob Roberts, but you might know me as Sky.
[SPEAKER_14]: Joining me as always are my awesome co-hosts.
[SPEAKER_14]: First off, the happiest bunny on the farm, Jamie Summers, also known as DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: How are you doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: You have explosive diarrhea.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sorry to see that.
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or hear that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess if I saw that, that would be a really weird... I would wonder how you got in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_14]: In that corner, say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_14]: How are you doing, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm doing okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's up with this?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't see food out all over the table for you to see.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because I already ate it, and unfortunately the burger was non-edible.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had a burger, but I eat it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it was non-edible.
[SPEAKER_13]: I only ate about a quarter of it, and it was terrible.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sorry to hear that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stop going to McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have a rough life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: Feeling the love, talking about everything that's going on in the Bomani scene this week Which, oh my god, oh my god, it's been a busy week I swear, we've been doing this show for how long?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like for years and years we're sitting here going Nothing's happening in our DDR scene and we're really sad But tonight, it blew up, just like DarkSakura's butt Hey, my butt did not blow up So we're going to cover all that news and talk about how angsty we are That we didn't win the lottery Okay
[SPEAKER_14]: and I want to talk about... I didn't even play.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is really important.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to talk about reading because you guys... I fucking read a book this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can read?
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: I read a book.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to tell you all about that when we come back.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_14]: How was your week?
[SPEAKER_14]: When we come back after this music break...
[SPEAKER_14]: And I thought we could start off this music break.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to do underappreciated dinner songs this break.
[SPEAKER_14]: Underappreciated songs.
[SPEAKER_14]: The best of the worst.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll be right back after this music break with more of Orange Lounge Radio for April the 1st of 2012.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_00]: The body jacket, stuck to the sideline, the mic's a dead line, my test, they rewind, use them as guidelines I hit the bubble like bricks, sick, when in a mix, I skip, like a brick, I'm like a toothpick You can't get with dance, I'm in a wreck of power, my lyrics hurt to be like we can run a car, so don't swap Let's not move on Let's not move on Let's not move on
and many more.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_16]: Please listen to Orange Lounge Radio because real radio makes Captain Jack cry
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's a real feat because he's dead.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like from the great beyond.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like, what's that crying under the ground?
[SPEAKER_14]: Did someone bury a baby down there?
[SPEAKER_14]: Orange Lounge Radio Live, episode number 452.
[SPEAKER_14]: For those April the 1st of 2012, I can't help but feel there's something about today, like something special I was supposed to remember.
[SPEAKER_14]: But, oh well, whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, anyhow, we're here in studio, chilling out to Dynamite Rave, which always makes me think of your freestyle routine, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, the one I forgot.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was like, ah, fuck it, I'm walking off.
[SPEAKER_14]: You got up on stage, you just fucking froze.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I didn't freeze, I just like, I forgot it about halfway through, and I'm like, eh, fuck it.
[SPEAKER_13]: What did the judges score you on that, when you did that?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't even remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was like a three.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was like long ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Would have been better if you hadn't used Mirror.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, how are you doing, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: I want a burrito.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Instead, I'm going to have tea.
[SPEAKER_14]: I thought you were doing this whole fasting thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why I'm having tea.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, Alan is being kind enough.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tonight was going to be Taco Festiva here at Studio OLR, and he's been kind enough to postpone that until the show's over.
[SPEAKER_14]: I appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I mean, we're not going to talk about Frogger on this show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you miss the part about it's Bomani?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, I understand that, but, you know, they like to throw out those Frogger anniversaries.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're celebrating the 23rd anniversary of Frogger.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like, no one fucking cares.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe there will be a version of DDR where little frogs will show up on the little arrow pads and you can step on them to kill them.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be... I'd play that.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's like that spider stomp.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: and I have witnessed the spider stomp freestyle routine.
[SPEAKER_13]: That was interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: How did the spider stomp freestyle routine go down?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was Explicit that did it, I believe.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_13]: Was it Explicit?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't remember now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Was it an explicit routine?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I've seen some of those in my years of DDR festivas and so forth.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was something that came out when we went to play QZAR.
[SPEAKER_14]: How does a spider stomp freestyle work?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just like DDR, but spider stomp.
[SPEAKER_13]: Step on the glowing bubbles.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just remembering working in the arcade and having a spider stomp.
[SPEAKER_10]: Did you have a spider stomp at... We did.
[SPEAKER_10]: In Alabama?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wherever it was you were?
[SPEAKER_10]: When I worked at Cyber Station, we had a spider stomp.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was really good at spider stomp.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, ladies first
[SPEAKER_10]: So, uh, Friday, actually Thursday, I called my friend's new boss and said, hey, I'd like to work there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Friday, I went in for, no, no, that was Wednesday because I was at school.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thursday, I get a call back asking, how did you get the number?
[SPEAKER_10]: and send me your resume.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then I get a call back after I had my second interview for eHarmony and they're like, okay, can you come in tomorrow?
[SPEAKER_10]: So I went in Friday.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're like, we like you.
[SPEAKER_10]: So now I have a job.
[SPEAKER_10]: I start Monday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay, you got a job.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay, Kermit, yay.
[SPEAKER_13]: So eHarmony, when they're, you know, like for example...
[SPEAKER_13]: Checking out new candidates for job positions.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do they match them up with different levels of compatibility?
[SPEAKER_10]: Ironically, they actually go through a recruiting service.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe you're 80% compatible for this job and maybe only 60%.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry, you're homosexual.
[SPEAKER_14]: You cannot apply.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not true because they have a service called Compatible Partners now because they got sued into it.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, so I got to send them a rejection letter.
[SPEAKER_10]: The eHarmony people.
[SPEAKER_14]: How do you go about writing a rejection letter?
[SPEAKER_14]: Are you really supposed to be talking about what company you said no to?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure they don't listen to this show.
[SPEAKER_10]: If they do, sorry.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was like, I regret to inform you that I have chosen a more qualified position with another company.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, I said, they're paying me more.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's, you know, better work, more challenging, more what I'm looking for.
[SPEAKER_14]: Give me money.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry, we're not a match.
Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: You stood up, eHarmony.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, honestly, eHarmony, judging everything, they just seemed like a fantastic company to work for.
[SPEAKER_10]: The working from home thing would have been cool, but I have bills.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on top of that, I need to get out of the house.
[SPEAKER_14]: How long has the job dry spell been going on now?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's been a little bit, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been bad for a lot of people I got laid off November 2010 Oh wow So yeah, it's been a while But here's the funny thing I will be working with my BFF Becky We worked at the same last job That's not a recipe for disaster or anything No, because we know how to behave in a professional environment We're doing two different jobs on top of that It's going to be nice Very cool Loki, how was your week?
[SPEAKER_14]: How was your day?
[SPEAKER_13]: Mainly this week, it was just kind of, I don't know, back to work.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because last week I was off a couple days to watch Josh while Nellie was going to the doctor and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then, what else did I do?
[SPEAKER_14]: Slept.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't sleep that much, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it was pretty much...
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, we saw the Hunger Games last week.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think I already talked about that, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Nelly went and saw the Bodyguard in theaters.
[SPEAKER_13]: What?! !
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, because they had one night, it was the 20th anniversary of The Bodyguard, and so she went and saw it in theaters, and she said that the sound mix was horrible, that when they, I guess, remastered it, they remastered it in a tin can, and so it just sounded very tinny.
[SPEAKER_14]: Does this mean that they're coming out with a new Blu-ray or something?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, it came out on Tuesday, actually, and she wants that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Mark Wahlberg, Mila Kunis
[SPEAKER_13]: which is being written by Seth MacFarlane it's about a guy who wishes for his teddy bear to come alive on Christmas and then he does and so he has this walking talking teddy bear but now he's grown up and so there's this teddy bear that's with him that's just like this boozing prostitute sleeping with you know druggy teddy bear I'm like I'm not sure how I feel about
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_14]: I read a book, y'all.
[SPEAKER_14]: I read a book.
[SPEAKER_14]: I read a book from start to finish.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can read?
[SPEAKER_14]: I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I read a book.
[SPEAKER_14]: I read a book in like four days.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it only took me about four days.
[SPEAKER_14]: I read The Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm disappointed.
[SPEAKER_13]: Didn't I give you a copy of Ready Player One?
[SPEAKER_13]: No.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, then I'm going to give you a copy of Ready Player One.
[SPEAKER_14]: I want to read that.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, I'll read Ready Player One.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll give you both a copy of Ready Player One.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sweet.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I don't know why I read The Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, yes, I know it's a movie and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, my God, I heard.
[SPEAKER_14]: But all my friends are reading it and just raving and raving about it and won't shut up about what a good book it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm like, fine, I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll try it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And so I read the whole thing start to finish and it wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what did I do the day after I read The Hunger Games?
[SPEAKER_14]: Went and saw the movie.
[SPEAKER_14]: and seeing the movie with everything so fresh in my mind was it was easy for me to pick out everything that really bugged me about what they changed from the book and even Alan commented like I could tell every time they changed something from the book because I would just hear this deep sigh coming from over where you're at yeah but I think according to my wife she said that actually the movie is better than the book
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, they're different.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not going to say one is better than the other.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they were both good.
[SPEAKER_14]: They were both good in their own way.
[SPEAKER_14]: But because they moved, the biggest problem, quote unquote, with the translation is that because the book is first person and the movie's third person, there's a lot they have to do differently because you're not inside her head.
[SPEAKER_14]: So they have to use a lot of these other scenes to kind of explain what's going on because she can't do it in her head for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: So seeing these extra scenes was a little weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Battle Royale wasn't necessarily totally original either!
[SPEAKER_14]: Huh!
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just a little offended that you would read the book for the Hunger Games, but you didn't read Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_14]: I did try to read Battle Royale, but it was kind of boring.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was good.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I was telling a friend this, is that if I'm not in the exact right mood when I'm reading a book, then I'm going to squirrel, do something else.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like my ADD is so bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'll try to read Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_09]: That's because you can't read.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's because you weren't reading Ready Player One.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe that.
[SPEAKER_14]: so but I liked um of course I liked Battle Royale I'm not dogging on Battle Royale it's a fine movie and hell many years ago on this show we used to talk about you know didn't we start off one show with a paper plate Battle Royale one night I seem to remember it was really funny and stupid
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura is not in the room right now and I want to wait for her to get back so we can do the news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um...
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know I've been very kind of much a homebody I didn't get a new job this week I've been at the same job for 10 years but I like my jobs it's okay so I we went to the movies yesterday then we went out to Chinese food which was good this is great radio in that yeah
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you think maybe I should do a break song and then we'll come back and we'll talk about what's going on in the news this week?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we're going to do a quick break.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to come back and we'll talk about what is in the news this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot of stuff, so stay tuned, guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be right back with more of Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_04]: In the city where the sound sign shines, that person left a shadow and disappeared.
[SPEAKER_04]: Suddenly, goodbye, I loved you, I realized at that time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Memories are in dreams, I wake up when I forget them.
[SPEAKER_04]: Thank you for watching.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, we're back.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura's all better.
[SPEAKER_14]: She's back joining us.
[SPEAKER_14]: You didn't stink up the bathroom, did you?
[SPEAKER_10]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good.
[SPEAKER_10]: If you must know, iPad2P, thank you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, la la la la, TMI.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so news.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's lots and lots of Bomani news going on this week because Konami had a surprise Kisanera event, which, surprise, we weren't invited to.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a shock.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: which as you know is the name for it over in Europe but they've also used this in Japan before for artist exclusive games and they're going back to that like when was the last Dancing Stage game we had Dancing Stage featuring Dreams Come True yeah was it I couldn't remember if Dreams Come True or True Kiss Destination one of them was back in like 99 or 2000 what which for the record I found my copy of that
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: of course right so it just made sense that she's gonna get her own dancing stage game now we don't know all the songs that are gonna be in it but we do know Bad Romance is in it because that was the song that they demoed in the trailer which makes sense do you think Bad Romance would be a tough DDR song do you think that'll be like a seven or an eight or a nine or what
[SPEAKER_13]: I put it at a 7 I could see them doing some runs If I remember correctly, I believe the True Kiss, Destination, and the Dreams Come True stuff Those songs weren't that hard I think it was like 6 and 7 were the highest Because it's more of the casual
[SPEAKER_13]: Paragaga
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not going to do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm so on board with this idea.
[SPEAKER_14]: Paragaga, come on.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're not going to do something like that.
[SPEAKER_10]: Or how about the other game, Paraparagaga.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe if this one does very well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now what's weird is that they haven't talked about any home releases for this.
[SPEAKER_14]: So this is like an arcade exclusive thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's usually how it works.
[SPEAKER_13]: They'll have a home release later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: True.
[SPEAKER_13]: They'll just dump it into the engine of a Dance Dance Revolution game or something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now this is really weird because did the other Dancing Stage games have a couple songs from other artists, like a couple Konami originals in it?
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't remember because I found this really weird there is actually a Katy Perry song in this game too California Girls is apparently going to be playable in this game it's in the press release but it's only available in basic mode
[SPEAKER_14]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Something about Katy Perry is only basic.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's only available in basic.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_14]: It'd be a very casual, relaxed song, but I could definitely see some freestyle to that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I could definitely see Wendell busting out a California Girl.
[SPEAKER_13]: Perhaps they're going even so far as to say, you know how they did with some of the other mixes where they'll have a preview of the following mix?
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe they're previewing the Katy Perry version or
[SPEAKER_13]: I'd say seven.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just don't care.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, really?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, hey, more Dancing Stage DDR mixes are a good thing, I guess, so I'll give it a 5.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll give it an 11, because there's nothing in the world I love more than DDR and Lady Gaga, so there you go.
[SPEAKER_13]: What if it was RuPaul's?
[SPEAKER_13]: Dancing Stage featuring RuPaul's Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dancing Stage featuring ABBA.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're right.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would be a 12 if it was Dancing Stage featuring ABBA.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, didn't you say that you would get a PS3 when an ABBA game came out?
[SPEAKER_14]: And sure enough, SingStar ABBA came out and guess what I got?
[SPEAKER_14]: PS3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Did you ever pick up the ABBA You Can Dance?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, I did.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the best thing I've ever seen in my entire life.
[SPEAKER_14]: If we were hooked up to do it, I would play it live on air tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: But sadly, we're not.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, darn.
[SPEAKER_14]: What a bummer.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was seriously the happiest moment of my life.
[SPEAKER_10]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: Watching me play that?
[SPEAKER_10]: Watching you do the ballet-style stuff for The Winner Takes It All.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was the best thing I've ever seen.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, let's move on to the other big piece of news from the Konami Kisanera event that had to do with Bomani.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this kind of was a surprise because you guys know we've been saying this on the show for years.
[SPEAKER_14]: This...
[SPEAKER_14]: Series was really underrated.
[SPEAKER_14]: And a lot of people gave this series a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it was actually really good if you play it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, right.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, the game that is announced, Rock Revolution 2 has been announced.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_13]: I thought you were talking about a good series.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rock Revolution 2 was announced for consoles and arcade.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, I guess it's kind of like a reboot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I mean, if it's arcades, then they're probably just renaming Guitar Freaks to Armenia.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they're trying to Americanize it a little bit, or maybe they ran out of mixed numbers.
[SPEAKER_14]: Could be what they did.
[SPEAKER_13]: This is Konami.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think they'll ever run out of mixed numbers.
[SPEAKER_14]: But this is interesting.
[SPEAKER_14]: Konami is actually thinking outside of the box and doing something a little different here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rock Revolution 2, the console versions, will link up to the arcades using Konami's transferring.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you're actually going to be able to take your unlocks...
[SPEAKER_14]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: Could I play, would this allow me to play GWAR in the arcade, yes or no?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, maybe, it would probably be something more like, you know, you could take your ranked, like say you score something, like a high score on a song and you can take that to the arcade and take it home and that way it's still linked to your, you know, Konami profile or whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, you're awfully quiet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Does the prospect of a Rock Revolution 2 excite you?
[SPEAKER_10]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_10]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because I didn't play the Rock Revolution 1.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was too busy.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe it's time to catch up.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been too busy with Parapara lately.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anything new right now is just sort of like, but I want to wave my arms and wear pink and, you know, platform boots.
[SPEAKER_14]: And who doesn't?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that if they keep up with... I like the transferring element to it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That can make it exciting.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I still would have to wait for judging the final...
[SPEAKER_14]: All we have are these fluffy press releases and things to go off of.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I don't really want to get excited until I see something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, some folks in our chat room, which, by the way, I still have not plugged the chat room.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are no longer on Calibamani.com, so don't go there.
[SPEAKER_14]: You want to go to chat.orangelandreda.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: That changed recently.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're not on Calibamani.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's chat.orangelandreda.com, so check that out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Tigerclaw says, will Rock Revolution 2 have Kinect support on the 360?
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's certainly possible.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anything's possible.
[SPEAKER_13]: I can see it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, Konami's done some Kinect-enabled games recently, so why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_13]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now, I was curious what Harmonix was going to do in response to this, and it looks like Harmonix is cutting them off.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you notice this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Harmonix released this today.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you guys see this?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is pretty amazing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Product not yet rated.
[SPEAKER_02]: Time for our rock band party.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: No way, guys!
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got something brand new!
Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Rock Band Board Game!
[SPEAKER_18]: That's right!
[SPEAKER_18]: Rock Band Board Game is the newest game from Harmonix Musical Systems.
[SPEAKER_18]: Featuring all the fun and authenticity of rock band without the hassle of big bulky instruments.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, that seems like a dig a little bit at Konami.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like the whole, like, you don't need instruments for this.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a dig.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Board Game, who would have thought?
[SPEAKER_14]: Konami advancing technology with transferring and all this stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: Harmonix scaling back.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_14]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, actually, let me explain.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you see the dice?
[SPEAKER_18]: I got face screwed!
[SPEAKER_18]: The Rock Band board game has a larger song library than any other rhythm action board game!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: Setlist challenge!
[SPEAKER_02]: Draw three random song cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say it ain't so!
[SPEAKER_02]: Tubular!
[SPEAKER_02]: Again!
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Say it ain't so!
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I do notice Say It Ain't So, I end up playing that an awful lot in Rock Band.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hopefully they'll put out a patch to just, you know, it's not that I hate that song.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe you should pick another song.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think you've played this enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_18]: The Rock Band features you've come to love.
[SPEAKER_18]: The party will never stop rocking.
[SPEAKER_18]: Features like Character Creator.
[SPEAKER_14]: Auto-calibration!
[SPEAKER_14]: It was very interesting watching the different directions these two companies go in.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Rock Revolution 2, how amazing is this news on a scale of 1 to 10?
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: It all depends on how good it is.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, because it could be very terrible or it could be very good.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not ready to rate it yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fair enough.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just going to say a 6 for my excitement level.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'll wait and see.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to give it a nine because I'm just excited that Rock Revolution is coming back.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm very excited.
[SPEAKER_14]: And this whole thing sounds like it's going to be amazing and push technology forward.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, one more story we've got to cover tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: This did not come out of the event, but oh my God, it was like timed at the exact same time.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's crazy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I couldn't say anything about it either.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: What is up with that?
[SPEAKER_14]: You're supposed to be like our inside scoop to this.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had an NDA.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fuck your NDA.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I wanted to go to Las Vegas again.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here it is, you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR Freak Extreme has been announced.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_14]: A press release.
[SPEAKER_14]: J-Dog, the owner of DDRFreak.com, of course, put out a press release this week that simply said, we are starting over.
[SPEAKER_14]: and they are going to relaunch DDR Freak.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going to be DDRFreakExtreme.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: There will be an upgraded Machine Locations database that will have Google Maps integration with it, which I think that's smart, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Everything's on Google Maps now.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're going to have brand new forums because the forums were starting to be a little bit of a problem, right, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_14]: You were a moderate, yeah?
[SPEAKER_14]: So they're going to do brand new forums, and what they're doing, they're actually going to let random topics have their own sub-forums.
[SPEAKER_14]: So the Wolf Game is now going to have its own sub-forum, and Pornography Post will have its own sub-forum.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's actually a code written into the PHPBB that's going to allow any of those external sites that like to traffic through forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: They all just go directly there.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, that's great.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's their own forum.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, because when I think, where am I going to go to get porno links?
[SPEAKER_14]: DDR free.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, it's also for the Goat's Apex and the Bukkake and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_14]: Lemon Party?
[SPEAKER_14]: Will there be like a sub-sub forum?
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure there will be.
[SPEAKER_14]: Two girls, one cup reaction videos?
[SPEAKER_10]: But we have to have a moderator for that with a very strong stomach.
[SPEAKER_14]: I see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you know, how did you audition people for that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Who ended up getting that?
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: But the other thing that is actually going to be that I finally got the okay to talk about.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wait, is this like an exclusive?
[SPEAKER_10]: It could be an exclusive.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is DDR Freak Radio going to get pissed off because that might be a little weird because, you know, there's the two radio stations.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there was a little talk about they wanted to acquire us.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_14]: So, like, we're going to be the official radio station?
[SPEAKER_14]: What's going to happen to DDR Freak Radio?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, it's gone.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gone.
[SPEAKER_10]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Hell yeah, that'd be awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good idea to get the community back together.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's the other thing, too, that is kind of hush-hush.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay, ooh, I love exclusives.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR Flash.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's this?
[SPEAKER_10]: That works with a USB dance pad.
[SPEAKER_14]: So like integrated into the site?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can you do like your own music and stuff?
[SPEAKER_10]: That I don't know yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're still working on licensing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I see.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can actually browse the forums using the dance pad.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, that's cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_14]: Especially if you're looking at the porn forums.
[SPEAKER_10]: But they've actually done a Kinect hack as well so that you can navigate the site with your Kinect controller.
[SPEAKER_14]: There was the 1.5 release of Kinect on PC.
[SPEAKER_10]: And have full integration.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, DDR Freak Extreme, let's go around and rate the importance of that news on a scale of 1 to 10.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: Totally a 10.
[SPEAKER_10]: DDR Freak was the best time I ever had.
[SPEAKER_14]: Biased, biased, biased.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki?
8.
[SPEAKER_14]: We always need more places for porn links.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's true, that's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would normally give it an 8, but the porn forum?
9.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's very important, so 9.
[SPEAKER_14]: But...
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, and you know the other thing, too, is that for people who are offended, they just don't have to click on it.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Don't click it.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_10]: And they, oh, oh, I have to tell you about the other form that got added.
[SPEAKER_14]: What?
[SPEAKER_10]: A lolcat form.
[SPEAKER_10]: All little cats.
[SPEAKER_14]: How nice that they've evolved with the rest of the internet.
[SPEAKER_10]: I know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, it's great.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I'm so happy.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have to shut my mouth before I let out the whole grid thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Will the users that were banned last time still be banned?
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to make them their own forum.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like the troll grounds or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: We're going to call it Hall of the Band.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_14]: I like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a catchy name.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, well, don't go anywhere, guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have plenty more show to come.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have the cage match that's coming up in just a little bit, FUs of the Week, and we might just have to play match game.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so we'll be back after this with more of Orange Lounge Radio after a quick break.
[SPEAKER_14]: April Fools
[SPEAKER_14]: All the stories we talked about, sadly, were fake.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, really, the Konami Kissing Era event, please.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we made all that shit up.
[SPEAKER_14]: And DDR Freak is... People outside California don't know what those are.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some folks in chat generally got excited that DDR Freak was coming back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't be mad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't sue us.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm thoroughly glad I don't have to moderate DDR Freak anymore.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, you know what?
[SPEAKER_10]: I actually have to tell you about a realization that I had.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_10]: I went back and read on one site the graffiti that they found on the walls in Pompeii.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it made me think of the same shit I would see on DDR Freak, which proves to me that in the last however many thousand years, humanity has not grown at all.
[SPEAKER_14]: There were trolls even back in the olden days.
[SPEAKER_10]: No, there was one post that said, so and so, like...
[SPEAKER_10]: Did some girl in the ass here.
[SPEAKER_10]: And ran away with her brother.
[SPEAKER_14]: How naughty.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so anyway, yeah, everything we just did was bull.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we thought it would be fun for our... Especially because it's the 10th year of OLR and April Fool's happens to be on a Sunday.
[SPEAKER_14]: And look, we're never going to top the giggling lesbian gaming show that we did in 2006, which will always be the best prank we ever did.
[SPEAKER_14]: We thought we'd do that for our little April Fool's gag.
[SPEAKER_14]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyhow, let's get back into the real show because there's been a lot of stuff going on in the gaming world this week that we want to touch on.
[SPEAKER_14]: Big, big news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rumor news that I think Loki said might take the whole damn show tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're going to talk about that a little bit as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: First, though, the real version of what we do at the top of the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: How was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Talking about the video games we've played this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, you want to start us off?
[SPEAKER_14]: What video games have you been playing this week?
[SPEAKER_10]: I looked at that copy of Mass Effect and then Dan and I talked about it and then I got too busy to play because I was busy getting a job.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shame on you.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was busy getting a job.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fine.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess a job will be an acceptable excuse maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: I did play well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course you did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because you have an addiction.
[SPEAKER_10]: Dealer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, how was your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_13]: My gaming week was alright.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't play a whole lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: I played Call of Duty.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then I also played... What was it?
[SPEAKER_13]: The saxophone game that I posted.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's... God, I can't remember now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um...
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, so a little internet game.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was kind of fun.
[SPEAKER_10]: Was it Sax Maniacs?
[SPEAKER_13]: It was Epic Sax Game.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Based off of the Epic Sax guy from...
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's hilarious because it's actually a little music rhythm game and you have to learn how to play that little bit of music there and then you keep playing it over and over and over again.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know, it's fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot of songs out there that have epic sax solos in them, so hot sax all night long.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, this is specifically the epic sax guy.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Specifically.
[SPEAKER_10]: Have you ever seen the original that that came from?
[SPEAKER_13]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_13]: Eurovision.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was part of this Eurovision thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Was that that big competition they do that's like American Idol or whatever?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, sort of.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_10]: Never mind, I know what you're talking about.
[SPEAKER_13]: The guy wearing the blue pants and the red gloves who kind of looks like Duke Nukem.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hip thrusting to his Epic Sax solo.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's an awesome song.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, so that it for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_13]: That is all I played this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I've been playing that a little, little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Otherwise on the consoles, I'm still plucking away at Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I'm about halfway through the game from what Shane tells me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've picked up some of my partners and now I've got a few more.
[SPEAKER_14]: I did some events on a planet and it unlocked some more dossiers.
[SPEAKER_14]: For those of you that have played the game, you can kind of tell where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_14]: still loving the Mass Effect series the battle system has gotten a little better for me because you might remember last week on the show I was bitching about the battles in Mass Effect 2 compared to 1 but I'm liking it a little more now that I have more abilities I really like that you can kind of take an ability from one of your loyal friends
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been using that, but Mass Effect 2 is still awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's really about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I play, oh, no, one other game I've got to talk about.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is important.
[SPEAKER_14]: I haven't played this a lot, but I played it a little bit, so I'll talk about it a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kid Icarus Uprising.
[SPEAKER_10]: I played some of that, actually.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got on the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: On my friends.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah?
[SPEAKER_14]: What'd you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: It's cool.
[SPEAKER_10]: The 3D actually works.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, the 3D is great.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a gorgeous game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was really into the way that it's set up like Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: too.
[SPEAKER_14]: The menus and everything look just like Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_09]: I like the customizing your weapons thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I mean, there's so many little... I mean, you can tell it's designed... I mean, hello, I'm not stupid.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know it's the same people that did Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_14]: that did this.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it has all those same mini-games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like for Smash Brothers Like, you know, the machine where you put in coins And you can get like an egg You know, that has something special in it The grid of unlocks I mean, there's tons and tons and tons of stuff in the game And I love the air stages in the game It is so awesome It makes me think of Space Harrier Yes, it's beautiful to look at too And I love it when it's on rails and all this Then it gets to the ground stages And it's
[SPEAKER_14]: it's not that I dislike the ground stages but that's where and I think you know any of you that have been reading reviews about the game the controls are not good for the ground stages because you I mean just the way you have to hold the controller you have to move with the little circle pad you shoot with the L button and then you flick on the bottom pad left and right real quick to spin your character left and right and you use it to move your targeter
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's kind of a lot going on with that touchscreen.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have to hold it very awkward.
[SPEAKER_14]: And yes, Kid Icarus comes with that stand, but that kind of defeats the purpose of having a portable gaming system.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have to kind of like use that stand.
[SPEAKER_14]: So the controls disappoint me a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But otherwise, it's really a shame that something like that really screws the game in the way that it does because I love the storytelling and the videos and tutorial videos and all that in it because they break the fourth wall constantly.
[SPEAKER_14]: and all these in jokes like the game was made for people that remember the old Kid Icarus and constantly they're like you know oh it's been 25 years since we last saw Medusa and then it'll show like it says here's a picture of Medusa and it changes to that hideous looking thing from the eight big Kid Icarus and somebody writes Medusa in an arrow and it points at it like all these really dumb things and you know kind of some of those adult level jokes that kids wouldn't get but adults do and a lot of that is really funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: Going to our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com Game Girl says, is it worth it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was thinking of getting Kid Icarus Uprising.
[SPEAKER_14]: It really depends on how tied you are to this series and all that.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, I paid $30 for it, which I think is a fair price.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think Best Buy had a discount, so Amazon price matched it.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I got it for that price.
[SPEAKER_14]: $40 might be a little steep, depending on, you know...
[SPEAKER_14]: I wish there was a mode and maybe there will be one at the end where you could just play the sky stages because the sky stages are where this game is the best because you don't have to worry about turning pit and you just use the thing to move them and you use the touchpad to move the targeting and the game is fantastic and it's at its best in those stages and the 3D looks great but otherwise the ground stages kind of take away from the rest of the game for me
[SPEAKER_14]: but I still think it's a solid 3DS game I think it's definitely worth hopefully they'll put out a demo or something so you can kind of evaluate if it's for you I want it to do well because I like the idea of the Kid Icarus series coming back but I'm not going to sit here and say the game is flawless when it's not
[SPEAKER_13]: It's bad they couldn't patch it to use the Circle Pad Pro as, you know... Well, you actually can if you're a lefty.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because the lefty controls are using the Circle Pad Pro and then using your left hand for the stylus.
[SPEAKER_13]: I understand that, but I meant, like, you know, the second analog instead of the touchpad.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I want to say there was customizable controls in there too, so maybe there's a way you can kind of fix it and maybe kind of do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I can't see.
[SPEAKER_14]: The problem is if you did that, Loki, then you'd have nothing to use to target.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'd have to move and then pick up your stylus and target, and it would be kind of disjointed.
[SPEAKER_13]: You'd use the right analog to target.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, but then how would you turn your screen?
[SPEAKER_14]: You still have to use your stylus to turn the screen.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: First person shooters don't have that problem.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why does this have to be an issue with this game?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, so it's a little rough there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Uh, Porkchop in chat says, I've never played Kid Icarus ever, but Uprising looks awesome.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me talk about this real quick, because as a pre-order bonus, I got the Kid Icarus 3D Classics, which is the 3D version of the regular game, and it's actually really good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like, even though it's just the regular Kid Icarus, they put these backgrounds in every level, where the 3D is not just the back, like, the backgrounds themselves are kind of 3D, and
[SPEAKER_14]: and I think the game is based off the disc system version and not the cartridge because there's load and save files which only existed in the disc version and I want to say the sound effects were slightly different which I remember the disc system had a different sound chip than the NES did so some of the games had slightly different sound effects so that was kind of cool
[SPEAKER_10]: You should hear the music in the disc version of Castlevania 3.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I always hear that Castlevania 3's got a neat little... But yeah, Kid Icarus actually had a really good music on the disc one.
[SPEAKER_10]: And the sound.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shane in our chatroom says, Kid Icarus used to be worse for the 3DS.
[SPEAKER_14]: At E3, the ground stages were timed and you had to get through checkpoints so they at least fixed that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, thank God.
[SPEAKER_14]: That would have been really bad.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm glad they changed that because that sounds terrible.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anyway, the 3D Classic is actually really good.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I wish every game got this kind.
[SPEAKER_14]: I wish they would do this for every virtual console game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it's not that much that they did.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, they added backgrounds and the 3D is done tastefully.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think that's the best way I can put it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not like you've got one sprite layer here and then your background layer.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's more than that.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's multi-level of 3D and I think the effects are really good.
[SPEAKER_14]: And it kind of...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm really looking forward to seeing what else... Oh God, what's the name of the developer that did the 3DS versions called?
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like... It's not Akira, but... Akira or something like that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Did all the...
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_14]: AlphaCanadagram in our chatroom with a tip says, just an FYI, to people that have any 3D classic games on 3DS and didn't notice, you can go into options and increase the 3D density setting even more if it's not strong enough on max if setting is untouched.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, that's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: Not just the 3D density on the slider, but there's a 3D density within the game that you can adjust, which I think is a good idea.
[SPEAKER_14]: So...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Since we didn't get to say it at the top of the show because of our little joke tonight, a big thank you as always to All Games Radio where we do tape live every Sunday night at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern right after the Bobby Blackwolf show, although not tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bobby's on a little break.
[SPEAKER_14]: He'll be back on the 15th.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, so there's a big ol' fun rumor regarding the next PlayStation system.
[SPEAKER_13]: Apparently, there's sources that contacted Kotaku, or Kotaku contacted...
[SPEAKER_13]: Anyways, they figured out that the working title or possible name for the system is Orbis and that it's being planned for release sometime next holiday, so 2013 holiday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't Orbis a travel website?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, that's Orbit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't Orbis a drink that has these little gummy things in it that's the most disgusting?
[SPEAKER_14]: That was Orbit's?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh my god, it's like you were drinking herpes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, the name for the actual console is legit because you can pull up the dev website for PlayStation and typing in Orbis or slash Orbis or whatever pulls up the actual dev site.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just you don't get a 404 from it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they have it built in place, but they just don't have anything there yet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Kind of like with the Vita.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that's on Sony's site.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, orbis.scdev.net, their dev site.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, man.
[SPEAKER_13]: The name is real.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a working name or it's a...
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's real, at least.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, some of the specs, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're saying right now that they're planning on using an AMD x64 CPU, also an AMD Southern Islands GPU.
[SPEAKER_13]: And what they're saying right now is that it's supposed to be able to push a 4K HD, which is...
[SPEAKER_13]: Way more than most TVs can use, although newer TVs do support it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a 4096x2160.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's a resolution far exceeding most HDTVs.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then also they're saying it's capable of playing 3D games in 1080p, whereas the PS3 can only do that at 720p.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, I just want to say so far, I can believe it that they're pushing the technical limits because if you think about it, when PlayStation 3 came out, not everybody had adopted Blu-ray yet or even HD TVs.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that was the technology they went with.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I could kind of see that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the problem, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll cover what my issues are with the news in a sec.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, they're saying right now that select developers have dev kits already, which makes sense.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_13]: If it's a year out, obviously they're going to be working on games already.
[SPEAKER_13]: No backwards compatibility whatsoever with any PS3 games, also PS2 games.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would be assumed that stuff would be coming via emulators on the PlayStation Network since they have that right now with PS2 and PlayStation 1 games.
[SPEAKER_14]: But why would the dev kits be backwards compatible anyway?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, they're talking about the final product, not the dev kits.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right, but how would the... I mean, if this is being leaked from a dev, which is what I'm assuming because the dev website's out there and everything, if this is being leaked from a developer, then why would their kits have the backwards compatibility?
[SPEAKER_13]: They wouldn't have that, but the thing is they're telling them what the final specs are, what their specs are estimating.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it makes sense that they would cut out backwards compatibility because, one, you can still push PlayStation 3s, and two, they want to sell those games digitally because they can make money off that, and they also don't have to put... Putting the PlayStation 2 chips in there...
[SPEAKER_13]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_13]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_13]: However, much like PC games, it's going to be tied to your system, so you're going to need to have a PlayStation Network account and be online to even get the game started.
[SPEAKER_13]: um and then on top of that they're saying that if you decide to trade in your disc or you know loan to a friend or sell it or whatever um that the next person that gets it is going to have basically kind of a limited version of the game uh either going to be like a demo form or some sort of you know hindered version kind of think of like uh I guess the online passes or something like that but who knows to what extent and they're going to pay a fee to unlock or register the full game
[SPEAKER_13]: So there's that.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I guess we can talk about that first.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can we talk about that?
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so there's a few problems I have with the specs.
[SPEAKER_13]: First off, let's talk about the 4K resolution.
[SPEAKER_13]: That sounds good and all until you actually look up what 4K resolutions over HDMI are actually capable of.
[SPEAKER_13]: 24 frames a second.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you're looking for like 60 FPS games, you're not going to get that on this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, when you think about that, that's only compatible with HDMI, I think 1.4, which most TVs do not have.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, I would assume that there's going to be some backwards compatibility with like 1080p and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But let's just assume that maybe there's not.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_13]: And say they're going to be assholes about it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Then you're going to need to buy a new TV, new sound system, new cables, just to get this fucking thing to work.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then on top of that, like I said, 24 frames a second is not very... I mean, that's video.
[SPEAKER_13]: Video, that's fine, like watching the movie and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: But playing a game, I think you'd want higher FPS for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: At least I would think so.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then on top of that, I mean, let's see.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're talking about digital downloads for games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, that works okay for Vita games that are a couple gigs long.
[SPEAKER_13]: but we're talking fucking PlayStation 4 games I mean which are going to be pushing these 4k graphics with textures that are fucking huge you're talking like I mean PlayStation 3 games right now are upwards to I'd say I mean it's possible that they're up to 50 gigabytes on a dual layer blu-ray disc 50 gigabytes most of them don't take up 50 gigs it's most of them are about like you know
[SPEAKER_13]: 10 to 20 something gigs.
[SPEAKER_13]: But still, that's a fucking long time to download the game off of the internet.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plus we're talking, you know, all these companies talking about bandwidth caps and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: You're going to eat up your bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_13]: in no time.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they want you completely connected to the internet for some sort of back-ass words anti-piracy bullshit.
[SPEAKER_13]: So on top of that, we don't even need to cover why that's a bad idea because look at with the whole Ubisoft always on DRM bullshit.
[SPEAKER_13]: If their network goes down, PlayStation Network goes down for a day or so, bye-bye, can't play your game system for that whole day.
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do not see them.
[SPEAKER_13]: First off, GameStop is not going to let them do this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, because you think that... Didn't that one analyst who we always kind of tease on this show?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes, Michael Patrick.
[SPEAKER_14]: But he made a good point.
[SPEAKER_14]: He said GameStop is not going to sell these consoles.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, if basically, if they're...
[SPEAKER_13]: We'll get into why they wouldn't carry these consoles.
[SPEAKER_13]: Basically, if you're offering a system that has no used games whatsoever, it's impossible to sell a demo disc.
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's just say, worst case scenario, you can't play anything other than a small demo on this console.
[SPEAKER_13]: First of all, I think that's going to be a huge, huge incentive for hackers to try to fix that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because they're going to be like, oh, wait a second.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's your fucking disk.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can do whatever you want.
[SPEAKER_13]: Plus, tying it to one account is also kind of lame.
[SPEAKER_13]: But at the same time, it's just like, why?
[SPEAKER_13]: If they're not going to have any used game sales or whatever, then they're not going to carry it in their store.
[SPEAKER_13]: Much like they did carry a little bit of the PSP Go stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: because some people might have wanted it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But that offered really no sales for them other than PlayStation Network cards because it was all digital.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I just don't see them doing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But let's talk a little bit real quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Are you trying to say that GameStop had a hand in why the PSP Go failed?
[SPEAKER_13]: No, it was stupid.
[SPEAKER_13]: The PSP Go was dumb.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was a system that was digital only that was priced higher than the current model out already.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why would you buy it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me read some quick comments in our chatroom at chat.orangelandradio.com GamerGirl says, I have a feeling the PS4 is going to tank.
[SPEAKER_14]: Technus says, I doubt the game will run at 4K, maybe for full motion videos, but the games will probably run at 1080p at 60 frames per second.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember, a lot of these specs could be really overblown.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember back when they were talking about the specs of PS3, how they were saying, oh, 1080p and 120 frames per second for all games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, 1080p for all games and 120 frames per second.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're just going to go crazy with that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: And that never fucking happened.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, whatever.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's very possible that this stuff could be patched in later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because remember, the original, well, the Xbox 360 didn't always used to have 1080p.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was 1080i.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then it got patched in later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they could add it later on.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's possible.
[SPEAKER_14]: On this used game thing, is it possible that we're misinterpreting a system similar to what the Vita has to prevent trophy exploitation?
[SPEAKER_14]: No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it possible that it's tied to an account but you can easily remove it?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't think it's like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's just because... Well...
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm just going off what they said.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's all speculation.
[SPEAKER_13]: They said it's just limited.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe it is where you can remove it off of your system when you're done with it and then it becomes free to use for somebody else.
[SPEAKER_13]: I would hope that that would be kind of like what it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to express big reservations about this and the next Xbox, whatever it is, if the rumors are true about that as well, that Microsoft and Sony have joined together for some sort of dark pact where both these systems do not play used games.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well,
[SPEAKER_13]: Let me cover real quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so first off, and I gotta, this is Dennis Dyack.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, not a lot of you may be familiar with Dennis Dyack, but he's the head of development studios at Silicon Knights.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, Silicon Knights, the company that put out 2Human?
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: He's talking about a world without used games, new consoles.
[SPEAKER_13]: Because there are no used games, you could actually sell a game for a long time and get reoccurring revenue for quite a while.
[SPEAKER_13]: Reoccurring revenue is very key.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now there is no tail.
[SPEAKER_13]: Literally, you will get most of your sales within the three months of launch, which have created this really healthy... Literally, you'll get most of your sales within three months of launch, which has created this really unhealthy extreme...
[SPEAKER_13]: Where you have to sell it really fast and then you have to do anything else to get money.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then it also says, I would argue, and I've said this before, that used games are cannibalizing the industry.
[SPEAKER_13]: If developers and publishers don't see revenue from that, it's no matter of, hey, we're trying to increase the price of games to consumers and we want more.
[SPEAKER_13]: We're just trying to survive in an industry.
[SPEAKER_13]: If used games continue the way they are, it's going to cannibalize.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's not going to be an industry.
[SPEAKER_13]: People won't make these kind of games, basically saying the really high price games.
[SPEAKER_13]: So I think it's inflated the prices of games, and I think the prices will have to come down if there's a longer tail, but there isn't.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, so first off, this guy's so full of bullshit.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, really, he has nothing to go off because his games suck.
[SPEAKER_13]: It wasn't because of used games.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was because your games sucked that it didn't sell.
[SPEAKER_13]: But besides that, he doesn't understand how the fucking industry works.
[SPEAKER_13]: And sad considering a guy that is in the industry doesn't understand how it works.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you get rid of used games, you're going to get rid of the game specialty market, which is basically your game stops any game-specific store.
[SPEAKER_13]: Retailers that deal in multiple things like...
[SPEAKER_13]: You know, like a Best Buy or something like that, an apartment store that carries everything.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're not necessarily going to be affected by that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, first off, they don't really deal and use to begin with, but...
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: and really they can't make, you can't run a business with a 20% margin because you also have to pay your employees, your rent and utilities and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: And there's a lot of factors that go into it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they make up their money by used games, trade-ins and sales.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, the trade-ins obviously are also gonna drive new game sales because you're getting people that take their 2012 copy of Tiger Woods and they trade in for their 2013 copy of Tiger Woods.
[SPEAKER_13]: and you turn around and you sell the Tiger Woods or whatever game it is at an increased margin basically you're buying it for $20 and you're selling it for $40 and so instead of a 20% margin you have like a 100% margin now it's a lot healthier for these companies and now yes I understand that GameStop makes a lot of money in use but you know what that's how they run their business and that's how any game store is going to run their business they can't make they can't survive on just new games
[SPEAKER_14]: I think, honestly, if the Dark Pact is true and these companies are going to move towards used games, I think one of two things is happening.
[SPEAKER_14]: A, they're handing Nintendo the crown.
[SPEAKER_14]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_14]: When those soccer moms go to the store in 2013, what system are they going to pick up?
[SPEAKER_14]: The system that they don't really have the TVs to run anyway?
[SPEAKER_14]: And the systems where they won't be able to get used games?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or that the retailer might tell them you can't play used games on this?
[SPEAKER_14]: You can't rent games to this system?
[SPEAKER_14]: Or are they going to get a Wii U?
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to get a Wii U. Wake up call.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the same reason the Nintendo Wii succeeded the first time.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let me finish.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because if the Wii U somehow did this too, we don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nintendo could be a part of this dark pact.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't know the final specs of the Wii U. Let's hypothesize, and yes, this is being a little tinfoil hattie, but let's hypothesize that all three game companies are taking this stand against used games.
[SPEAKER_14]: I call video game market crash of 83 all over again.
[SPEAKER_14]: It will be that serious.
[SPEAKER_14]: The video game market will crash.
[SPEAKER_14]: Absolutely will crash.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they've been wondering how long is it going to take for it to crash again.
[SPEAKER_14]: This type of greed is going to cause it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think actually, I don't think it's going to crash.
[SPEAKER_13]: Why would I buy this system, Loki?
[SPEAKER_13]: Why?
[SPEAKER_13]: But that's the thing though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's what I think is going to happen is it's not necessarily going to crash.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's just they won't buy those new systems.
[SPEAKER_13]: No one's going to buy the new systems.
[SPEAKER_13]: And then what's going to happen?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, there's still plenty of people out there with the Xbox 360s and the PlayStation 3s and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that's still a crash because Nintendo and Sony and Microsoft would lose so much money from putting those consoles on the shelves that no one buys.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, I hope that's a big wake-up call then if that's the case.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, first... Sorry, it's really just not only the used games too.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, the fact that...
[SPEAKER_14]: What do these consoles really have to offer?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, yeah, okay, it's the technical edge, but a lot of us don't even have that technology yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I myself did not buy a PlayStation 3 until they were already out for like two years.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just... I really worry.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, granted, I have to take this all with a big-ass grain of salt because this is all rumors.
[SPEAKER_14]: All of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: All of it's rumors until it's on the show floor at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right?
[SPEAKER_14]: So maybe we're just getting a little bit carried away with the hysterics.
[SPEAKER_14]: But I hope to hell...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: for a new game, and $20 for all this download content, and then block out used game sales.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a moment, especially in this economy, which isn't going to be fully recovered by next year, where the consumers are going to say, enough.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have taken our money.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're not going to give it to you anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're fine with
[SPEAKER_13]: And on top of it, they're not even really claiming that you own the disc.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's your licensing content from them anyways.
[SPEAKER_13]: There is no industry out there that doesn't have used car sales.
[SPEAKER_13]: Do we see car sales suffering because of used car sales?
[SPEAKER_13]: No!
[SPEAKER_13]: It's never fucking happening.
[SPEAKER_13]: So why do you fucking think that you need money, Mr. Developer of Too Human...
[SPEAKER_13]: for used game sales.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't deserve any of my money then.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the case?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, here's how it's going to work, Mr. Dynak or whatever, or Dyak.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't even fucking pronounce your last name.
[SPEAKER_13]: Whatever, Dennis Dyak.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's how it's going to fucking work.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay, let's cut out used game sales.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: and no one's buying it new and there's no used game market anymore so you know no one's buying it and then turning it over and saying oh fuck it I'm not gonna you know play this so what's gonna happen your game your brand new game is gonna have to drop in price in order to push some sales and it's gonna keep dropping in price until it gets gets down to the used game price that would have been then people are gonna buy new
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, there's no used games.
[SPEAKER_13]: People just wait till the fucking new games to get to the price of what the used games used to be before.
[SPEAKER_13]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_13]: They get all the full benefit of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can't justify a $60 game if there's no resale value.
[SPEAKER_14]: You're literally taking all of the value out of the game.
[SPEAKER_13]: And here's another fun fact here, Dennis Dyack.
[SPEAKER_13]: If your game system or the game system that you're putting your content on doesn't support used games...
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, we're just not going to carry it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they probably will listen.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, why would they just stop listening to them all of a sudden?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know we want to wrap up this topic to move on to other things, but I want to check in with Jamie because we haven't heard from her in a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: And as a collector, how do you feel about no used game markets?
[SPEAKER_10]: I think that's freaking ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_10]: I was just saying earlier in chat that I bought a PlayStation game two weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: A PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_10]: I still have PlayStations.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just saying that there's people out there that will still keep holding on to the older systems, like say they may have an Xbox and not a 360, because all they buy is used games.
[SPEAKER_10]: and you know that's that's their prerogative they can do that I think that if you take out the ability to sell the game back get a little money back in their pocket so they can go out and afford to buy a new game that they're basically going to be cutting out let's just say at least a good 25% of their market
[SPEAKER_10]: Just in the people that basically resell games so that they can buy a new game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, when you think about it, that disc will be worth nothing by the time you take it out of the shrink wrap.
[SPEAKER_14]: It is now worth nothing.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're literally saying, though, that you can pop it in your system, mark it as, oh, I own this, and then you can literally throw the disc away.
[SPEAKER_14]: But who has the bandwidth from Comcast or whatever your provider is to support that?
[SPEAKER_14]: You have a 250 gig cap.
[SPEAKER_14]: These games are going to be 17 gigs each.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's the other thing too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Another point that I brought up because I actually responded to that article is, okay, let's assume that you can dump this game to your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: How fucking big is that hard drive going to be?
[SPEAKER_13]: And how much is it going to fucking cost?
[SPEAKER_13]: Because, you know, the prices of these hard drives from... I understand, data storage is cheap.
[SPEAKER_13]: But data storage is not cheap when it's sold by a company in a proprietary format.
[SPEAKER_13]: For example, you could buy a 320 gigabyte hard drive or whatever from Microsoft and it's going to run you like 200 bucks.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I can get like a 2 terabyte drive for about the same price if I bought it for my PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: So...
[SPEAKER_13]: Unless they open that shit up like they do with the PS3, props to them for that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, why wouldn't they do that?
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, after all, these guys are so fucking hungry for money that, of course, they're going to take the opportunity to, you know, oh, hey, you need that two terabyte drive because you're going to have to store all those games that we're going to make.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can't take without giving back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um, I stand by my earlier statement that this is going to cause a video game crash, and it's going to drive the game market underground.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, not like, you know, not like, oh, the back alleys and whatever, but it's going to be, games will be sold at flea markets, and GameStops will sell nothing but used games, because people don't want new games anymore.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not worth shit.
[SPEAKER_13]: And also, when you think about, you know, technology getting the way it is right now, and how expensive consoles are getting, you know, meh.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe people will actually go to PCs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Hey, look at that.
[SPEAKER_13]: PCs.
[SPEAKER_13]: Where you can get games and actually own stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't have to worry about used game sales because there's just sales on video games.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's Steam and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: Could this be how the hacks are happening?
[SPEAKER_14]: No, I say no because I've never sold a hard drive back and I was hacked.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have all my drives I've ever had.
[SPEAKER_13]: And on top of that, I don't think it stores the actual credit card information on your hard drive.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's tied to your network account or your Xbox Live account and it's downloaded from there.
[SPEAKER_14]: But is it possible it's ever written it to the drive?
[SPEAKER_14]: Ever?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's possible that it might be in a cache file or something like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe that is possible, but
[SPEAKER_14]: Now Microsoft responded to the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: So let me read Microsoft's response because obviously this is important.
[SPEAKER_14]: Quote, we are conducting a thorough investigation into the researchers' claims.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have requested information that will allow us to investigate the console in question and have still not received the information needed to replicate the researchers' claims.
[SPEAKER_14]: So they're deflecting a little bit in the opening like we don't have the information yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: I somehow doubt that they actually wipe the drive with like zero byte writing but I think it's just like format
[SPEAKER_14]: That was not a 100% denial either.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did you notice that?
[SPEAKER_14]: That was not a firm, no, this is crap.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was a, we haven't been able to investigate it and it's unlikely.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that wasn't a no.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, maybe for legal reasons they can't say no because if they do say no and it ends up they were wrong, now we can class action lawsuit them, Xbox Live agreement be damned because this is on the actual hardware itself.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not scared God, I...
[SPEAKER_14]: I know I'm a total hypocrite saying this because my credit card info is on my Xbox, but if you haven't put it on there yet, I would advise you just don't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't ever give those damn things your credit card.
[SPEAKER_14]: Use the cards that you buy in stores.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's the only safe way to do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sad, but true.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, meanwhile, DarkSakura, what do you got for us?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, actually, I was answering a question from Nish, I guess, asking what my favorite console is of all time.
[SPEAKER_14]: from our chat room, yeah?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'd probably say the PC Engine Duo, Turbo Duo.
[SPEAKER_14]: Why is that?
[SPEAKER_14]: Dracula X. Super Nintendo for me, easy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Super Nintendo was the best console they ever did, I think.
[SPEAKER_10]: So anyway, you remember we had actually mentioned a rumor about Zipper being closed, Zipper Interactive, that created SOCOM, the developer of SOCOM?
[SPEAKER_10]: That was last week, yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Sony confirmed it.
[SPEAKER_10]: but other than that, bye bye
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I mean, I guess most of us kind of assumed last week's was probably true anyway, but it's unfortunate that it was confirmed, but... It doesn't... When you say a rumor, you should always give it some closure.
[SPEAKER_10]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_10]: They got the closure all right.
[SPEAKER_14]: If it's true that these new consoles are gonna lock out used games, I bet this is gonna get a lot more frequent.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's gonna be... If your company doesn't develop for PC, you're gonna be in trouble.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all I have to say.
[SPEAKER_10]: I wonder what the project was that was cancelled.
[SPEAKER_14]: SOCOM 5?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just SOCOM on the Vita?
[SPEAKER_14]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_06]: Eh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's travel around the world and check out some release dates and what is coming out near you soon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, the drought has begun again, so not a whole lot this week.
[SPEAKER_13]: Titanic Mystery on Nintendo DS and on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, to celebrate the release of the movie all over again.
[SPEAKER_13]: I know, it's talking about the Titanic 2 and how there's a bomb on the Titanic.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think we talked about this.
[SPEAKER_13]: Sounds like the plot of Speed 2.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's also, of course, Funky Barn from Ubisoft.
[SPEAKER_13]: 3DS game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Fallout and Oblivion are getting a double pack on Xbox 360 and PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: Connect Star Wars out this week as well as the Connect Star Wars Limited Edition Connect Star Wars Oh, that's finally out?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'll be damned.
[SPEAKER_13]: Connect Star Wars is finally out.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you happen to shop at GameStop or Nintendo online, Xenoblade Chronicles is out on the Wii this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: And... That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Finally, Xenoblade Chronicles.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's one a lot of people are looking forward to.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, gotta say that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, and originally it was going to be a Devil May Cry HD collection this week on PS3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: However, Capcom dropped the street date on that, so it's out now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like, canceled?
[SPEAKER_13]: They're no longer street dating it.
[SPEAKER_13]: So it was basically, before it was, okay, you have to hold your copies until Tuesday, then they're like, ah, just sell it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Maybe it got leaked or something?
[SPEAKER_13]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it got leaked years ago.
[SPEAKER_14]: Devil's May Cry HD Edition is not like one of those games like people have to have right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's like you already played it before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it doesn't look all that HD either.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's go to Japan.
[SPEAKER_14]: In Japan, not a whole lot coming out, but there are a few things.
[SPEAKER_14]: On the Nintendo 3DS, Puyo Puyo Kansatsu Niki.
[SPEAKER_14]: That is not Puyo Puyo, there's a big difference.
[SPEAKER_14]: Puyo Puyo, which looks like this big fat cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's not really Nintendogs or Nintendcats, although I guess it does actually look a little similar to that.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've seen that cat a bunch of places before, so I think it's like from a manga.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like a character or something.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, it does look a lot like Nintendogs or...
[SPEAKER_14]: That looks like Shermie.
[SPEAKER_10]: It does not look like Shermie.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shermie is not that fat.
[SPEAKER_10]: And she's not orange.
[SPEAKER_14]: A plus.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Going to... Let's check out the Vita.
[SPEAKER_14]: See what's coming out on the Vita this week over in Japan.
[SPEAKER_14]: There we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Unless you want a portable charger.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's an official first party portable charger.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, hey.
[SPEAKER_14]: on the Xbox 360 and the PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go to the 360 first.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're also getting Star Wars this week and the console.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it's not just America that's getting that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Japan is getting their version as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: And lastly on the PlayStation 3, Borderlands Game of the Year Edition comes out in Japan and Mahjong Dream Club.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yay?
[SPEAKER_13]: Is that tying in with like Dream Club?
[SPEAKER_14]: The anime?
[SPEAKER_14]: It looks like it, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: Like the chicks?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, it is.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is why you knew about this, Loki.
[SPEAKER_14]: Classy.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's ladies in swimsuits, if you would like, with big old boobies playing mahjong.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Titty-jong.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you know what?
[SPEAKER_13]: More people might be into mahjong.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's the sound the eyes make.
[SPEAKER_14]: Mahjong!
[SPEAKER_14]: How about the UK, DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_10]: On the third, we have Star Wars Connect.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have Devil May Cry HD Collection and Wheels of Destruction.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the fourth, Diabolical Pitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the fifth, Rhythm Thief and the Emperor's Treasure.
[SPEAKER_10]: And on the sixth, Shoot Many Robots.
[SPEAKER_14]: Many Robots.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shoot them.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, we're going to take a moment to go in the gaming archive and find a game that DarkSakura thinks, hey, you ungrateful little brats.
[SPEAKER_14]: Although tonight we were reminiscing about old times a little bit, so everybody was reminiscing tonight a bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But we're going to reminisce again, not with an old version of our show, but with the classic game of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, what did you pick from the archives this week as the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_14]: Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's no joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: No, that's true for the truth.
[SPEAKER_14]: Although Capcom fighting games have become a bit of a joke in recent years.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I figured with everything happening, I may as well just go right to the source.
[SPEAKER_10]: So let's talk about Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, it came out in 1987, of course by Capcom, and it was their first fighting game that they put out.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it was actually one of the first ones that had a six-button controller and had commands that had special moves.
[SPEAKER_10]: So this basically started the whole big thing for us.
[SPEAKER_10]: The version that came out on the TurboGrafx CD was called Fighting Street in 1988.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that actually came out on the Virtual Console in November 2009, and the same for the UK.
[SPEAKER_10]: So basically, you have one-on-one matches against the computer opponent, and then each matches three rounds, and you have to defeat each opponent in less than 30 seconds.
[SPEAKER_10]: If the match ends before the fighter is knocked out, then whoever has the most energy will make it to the next round, basically.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fighting Games do today.
[SPEAKER_10]: You have to win two rounds to win and move forward.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if the third round is a tie, then the computer wins by default.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, basically, this started the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_10]: This, you know, having the moves and everything, having... See, look, it's the Shoryuken, and he's fighting Sagat.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that also started the computer cheating every time, because that's bullshit, that if it's still a tie, the computer just wins.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, yeah, but actually in that case, that's actually somebody playing Ryu.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um... So there were, um... There was a deluxe version of the game that had an 8-way joystick and then two large mechatronic pads for punches and kicks.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it was basically, um... The harder you hit, the harder your punch or your kick was.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then the later version came out with the six attack buttons.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know, the three heavy punches and three... Oh, the three punches and the three kicks.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: There were all kinds of different moves.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, you had...
[SPEAKER_10]: The Psycho Fire, which was the Hadouken, and the Dragon Punch and the Hurricane Kick.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, they were all the same moves that followed over.
[SPEAKER_10]: So for the characters in this one, basically, you play as Ryu.
[SPEAKER_10]: And if you have a second player, then you play as Ken.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's why they had the same moves and everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: And he also, basically, the two-player mode is basically Ryu versus Ken.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you had different opponents in single-player mode.
[SPEAKER_10]: You had Retsu, who was a Kenpo instructor, Geki, who had a claw, and Joe, who was another karate guy, Mike, who, from what I understand, became Mike... I think was actually, if I'm right, he became Mike Bison in Street Fighter II, which...
[SPEAKER_10]: as we know over here he was called Balrog which was Vega's name and Vega was who was Bison over here and I've gone across side yeah that's how it works
[SPEAKER_10]: So we had Lee, who was Chinese boxing, and Gen, who was a professional killer.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Gen came back in Street Fighter Alpha, or Street Fighter Zero.
[SPEAKER_10]: And so did Birdie, who was the wrestler slash boxer.
[SPEAKER_10]: He also was in there.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then there was one named Eagle, who was a bodyguard.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then you had your...
[SPEAKER_10]: Your last two opponents you had, Adon, who was Muay Thai, and he actually came back for Street Fighter Alpha as well.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was the one with the very interesting hair.
[SPEAKER_10]: And Sagat, who was the boss.
[SPEAKER_10]: And now Sagat, of course, came back for just about every version.
[SPEAKER_10]: So it came out, it was produced by Takashi Nishiyama, who we've seen as Piston Takashi.
[SPEAKER_10]: Are you seeing a two player?
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I was just looking at that because the other video ran out, so I went and looked at some other matches.
[SPEAKER_10]: It was planned by Hiroshi Matsumoto, and the two of them actually went on to do a bunch of games for SNK, including Fatal Fury and Art of Fighting.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then they came back to work on Street Fighter IV.
[SPEAKER_10]: And we all know Inafune, Keiji, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Megaman.
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, he also designed the character portraits in Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_10]: and, uh, so we've got, like I said, there were two different versions in the arcade.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was the regular version, um, that had the six button and the deluxe one that had the pressure-sensitive pads.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you could basically hit the pad and you hit it as hard as the pad did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: version, well, I'd say in any non-Japanese version, I should say, Ken and Ryu were dubbed in English so that their moves were like Psycho Fire, Dragon Punch, and Hurricane Kick.
[SPEAKER_10]: And then later versions just left the voices in Japanese.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, basically, when you get into Street Fighter IV, it actually has both versions of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: So yeah, the home versions.
[SPEAKER_10]: There was, like I said, Fighting Street for the TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_10]: They had an arranged soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_10]: And...
[SPEAKER_10]: This was interesting, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because it didn't have a six-button controller, your strength of your moves were determined by how long you held the subsequent kick or punch button.
[SPEAKER_10]: They later did six-button controllers, though, when it's saved for TurboGrafx.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, did you know, Rob, that there was a Commodore 64 version?
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, I did.
[SPEAKER_14]: Isn't that sad?
[SPEAKER_14]: But yes, I did know about the Commodore 64 version.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I had it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, there was also one for the ZX Spectrum.
[SPEAKER_14]: It didn't play that great, by the way, because the Commodore 64 only has one button.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's MS-DOS, Amiga, and Atari ST that came out by U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gold.
[SPEAKER_10]: and, um, they were, uh, I believe published by Tiertex and they said that they actually came out with their, um, with an unofficial sequel called Human Killing Machines.
[SPEAKER_10]: Kind of interesting, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Of course, um, U.S.
[SPEAKER_10]: Gold also was the one that published by Commando in 1943, so.
[SPEAKER_10]: Now, um...
[SPEAKER_10]: The, uh, as far as this, I mean, it was considered to be one of the games of the year, as stated by Sinclair User.
[SPEAKER_10]: And C++VG said it had no lasting appeal whatsoever.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, how did that last?
[SPEAKER_14]: Lucky that somebody felt differently and gave it a sequel, huh?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and that's available for Windows PC and the Capcom Classics Collection Remix for PSP and Capcom Classics Volume 2 for PS2 and Xbox.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is that it?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your classic game of the week, Street Fighter or Fighting Street, I guess, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Depending on where you are.
[SPEAKER_14]: For a variety of systems.
[SPEAKER_10]: You could just be doing nothing apparently but shorty again over and over and over and over.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, we're going to move right into some rapid fire news tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: If things seem a little bit compressed, that's because we compressed our regular show because of the April Fool's thing we did at the beginning.
[SPEAKER_14]: So yes, it is moving at a different pace tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: So let's just go right into rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, let's talk a little bit about some Easter eggs.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this is kind of funny.
[SPEAKER_13]: There was actually an Easter egg that was found on the Nintendo 64 version of GoldenEye.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was actually an emulator for the ZX Spectrum.
[SPEAKER_13]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_13]: The company, well, Rare, they had also, I guess, developed games for the ZX Spectrum back in the day.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's kind of interesting that that was on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, and then this is kind of disappointing news.
[SPEAKER_13]: Uh, Kid Icarus Uprising actually began as a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, and it was being developed on PC as well.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, I would imagine it's the dev kits or PCs, but as a Wii game, I, yes, exactly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kind of think it should have stayed a Wii game too.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: It would have been fucking awesome as a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_13]: Not to say that they couldn't bring it to consoles later on, but it would have been fucking awesome as a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Now that I'm playing it and thinking about the controls too, I can see how it totally was a Wii game and it would have been because you could use the little thumb stick to move and you aim at the TV.
[SPEAKER_14]: It actually makes a lot more sense as a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Although the 3D is beautiful in it though.
[SPEAKER_13]: Here's the thing that's really disappointing though.
[SPEAKER_13]: They actually have video from the game running on the Wii version and
[SPEAKER_13]: It's gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_13]: It still looks gorgeous.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't see the video.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's just... Wait, is it on the story here?
[SPEAKER_13]: It's on the story.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, they actually show... It looks like... I mean, it's basically what you see in the 3DS version, just minus any enemies and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: But, I mean, wouldn't that have been awesome?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is the first level.
[SPEAKER_14]: This looks like it could just be the screen from the 3DS one, but... But, yeah, that's the prototype version that they had.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: So sad that it could have been... They should still do it as a PC game.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's still time to put it out as a Wii game.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wii U game.
[SPEAKER_13]: You never know.
[SPEAKER_14]: So yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Disappointing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Very disappointing.
[SPEAKER_14]: less disappointing is the success of Journey which is a PlayStation Network game I really didn't talk enough about because it came out at the time I was getting back into Mass Effect but this is a great experience on the PlayStation 3 and again I really suggest you guys check it out however it sounds like a lot of you already have Journey is now the fastest selling Sony Computer Entertainment America region PSN game in all of recorded history so check that out the honor before that was Infamous 2 Festival of Blood so
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyhow, so Journey has been doing very, very, very well online and April 10th is when the soundtrack is coming out.
[SPEAKER_14]: You can get that either on the PlayStation Store or you can do it in iTunes.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's going to be coming out on April 10th and it does have a gorgeous soundtrack with it too.
[SPEAKER_14]: So again, Journey on PlayStation Network is, it's a trip.
[SPEAKER_13]: I like it a lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they're going to be doing LittleBigPlanet stuff for Journey as well.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I did read about that.
[SPEAKER_09]: Someone needs to get it for me.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe for your birthday.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: If PC games are more your thing, Audiosurf, especially if you like music games, is probably one that you've checked out before.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, guess what?
[SPEAKER_14]: They're not going to stop there.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a website for a little something called Audiosurf Air.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who knows what that is?
[SPEAKER_14]: It could be a mobile version of the game, but it sounds like it's more likely a sequel to the original AudioSurf.
[SPEAKER_14]: There is some screenshots on the website.
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course, everything is subject to change, but it does look like, I don't know, the little machine looks a little more like a boat or something now.
[SPEAKER_14]: So it is definitely possible they've changed some things up.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they are recruiting for beta signups right now, so you can check that out on their website, which is...
[SPEAKER_14]: It's air.audio-surf.com air.audio-surf.com That's a lot of punctuation.
[SPEAKER_14]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Audio Surf Air.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_09]: Well, in other news, Rob, playing with your game.
[SPEAKER_14]: I got a swap note.
[SPEAKER_14]: I had to check it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Is it Kat?
[SPEAKER_14]: I sent a swap note earlier, and it's my little April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now, did you get the one from Reggie?
[SPEAKER_14]: I did get the one from Reggie, and you can use him as a level 5 guy in Find Me or whatever, but he got scared off by the monster, and I didn't get to use him at all, and that pissed me the fuck off.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fucking asshole.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: So, news.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had to give you a hard time, Rob.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mortal Kombat Vita has a release date.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's going to be coming out in Europe on May 4th.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I don't see what the American date is.
[SPEAKER_13]: U.S.
[SPEAKER_13]: is May 1st.
[SPEAKER_13]: May 1st, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, basically, it's going to have touchscreen-enabled fatalities and a challenge tower.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_10]: And 150 Vita-exclusive missions.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_14]: The Vita challenge tower could be neat.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, they're going to incorporate a lot of the Vita stuff into it, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: Awesome Knots
[SPEAKER_10]: It's a multiplayer arena beat-em-up that's going to be on PlayStation Network and Xbox Live Arcade on May 2nd, put out by Ranamo Games.
[SPEAKER_10]: So you basically beat people up in teams of three online or via split-screen locally, and there's no price tag on it yet.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ranamo is a Dutch developer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nice.
[SPEAKER_10]: They put out Swords and Soldiers.
[SPEAKER_14]: All righty.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're going to get into the Fugle Question of the Week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Actually, though, I think I want to do an unscripted break just because the recording is starting to get a little long.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I need to save the recording so we don't lose it so I get the temp space back.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we're going to do a little technical break.
[SPEAKER_14]: And when we come back, I'm going to do just a two-minute song here.
[SPEAKER_14]: When we come back, we will do more of Orange Launch Radio, including the Fugle Question of the Week, FUs of the Week, Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR, and...
[SPEAKER_14]: your phone calls at 1-877-GAME-OLR we'll get to those right after a quick impromptu break here
[SPEAKER_14]: Welcome back, everybody, to Orange Lounge Radio on this April Fool's Day edition, episode number 452 of our show.
[SPEAKER_14]: And if you tuned in late tonight, you missed a little bit of retro OLR at the top of the show, so check it out when it hits the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, it will all be in the... Somebody was asking if they could get a recording of the beginning of the show tonight, and I was like, it'll be in the podcast, so it'll be all there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Songs and all, because we very intentionally pick songs that were from the games themselves, so they're licensed a little differently, so we can...
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, anyhow, let's get back into the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Fugle Question of the Week!
[SPEAKER_14]: It's where we ask you guys a question on Facebook and Google+, and we call it Fugle.
[SPEAKER_14]: No Bites on Google this week, which has me convinced nobody is on Google+.
[SPEAKER_14]: and since I'm being forced to move to this stupid timeline thing on Facebook I like it Google Plus doesn't seem so bad and our page is now timeline you can get an ad for that by the way I think I will I hate the way timeline looks I hate it I hate the left and the right side stuff I love it well I hate it
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, here it is, the FUVO question of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: What is your favorite urban legend or April Fool's joke in the gaming community that turned out to be fake or perhaps even real years later?
[SPEAKER_14]: For example, Shang Long, Sonic and Super Smash Brothers, Melee, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_14]: Be sure to sign your comments.
[SPEAKER_14]: Obviously, if you wrote on Facebook, then you already did.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkTetsuya writes, honestly, I don't think anything could top Shang Long from EGM April 92.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, he even quoted the magazine and the date.
[SPEAKER_14]: Keep in mind that this was even before we had the internet, much less as big as it is today.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you have to give the editors credit for sticking the find the AFD joke contest right underneath it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I agree, that was a pretty epic troll on behalf of that magazine I remember they used to do these epic April Fool's jokes every year and they kind of set the benchmark but I loved when their jokes would become realities like Ermac in Mortal Kombat 1 ended up being a real thing that was kind of funny Cody T writes us and says one that happened just recently, Assassin's Creed Connect and there's a video trailer for it and everything it's actually pretty hilarious
[SPEAKER_14]: and he linked us to the video trailer there.
[SPEAKER_13]: I didn't see this.
[SPEAKER_13]: I watched it.
[SPEAKER_13]: It looks like the normal Kinect videos and you see this guy do this backflip in his living room and stuff.
[SPEAKER_13]: It just gets more and more ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_14]: Porkchop writes and says, how about the Final Fantasy VII tech demo for PlayStation 3 that had everybody lose their minds and assume there'd be a remake?
[SPEAKER_14]: Ultimate fanboy troll.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, to be fair, that wasn't an April Fool's joke, but we did say urban legend or April Fool's joke, so that was a huge troll on somebody's part.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have to wonder if they didn't consider it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Can I add mine in here real quick?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure, of course.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you get to answer two.
[SPEAKER_13]: Remember when they were going to do Mega Man Legends 3 and then they said they were going to put out a demo for it and that you'd have to pay for the demo?
[SPEAKER_13]: And then they said, fuck you, we're not going to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Ha ha.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that was a... That wasn't a troll.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was just fucking mean.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what that was.
[SPEAKER_13]: Which, by the way, and I do follow them on Facebook still, 100,000 strong for Mega Man Legends 3 to return or whatever that is.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're up to 80,000 likes.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's more than a million moms, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I mean, hey, if you haven't liked them yet, maybe you should.
[SPEAKER_14]: This just in, there are more Mega Man fans than moms, apparently.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go figure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_14]: I kid, I kid.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tyler M says, Goken in Street Fighter 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't remember that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: I do, because it was supposed to be Ryu and Ken's teacher, and now he's in Street Fighter 4.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, how funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: I forgot that one.
[SPEAKER_14]: That must have been a little later after the Shang Long ordeal.
[SPEAKER_14]: Phil G writes, I'm still not convinced the Diablo 3 release date is real.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a very valid concern, sir.
[SPEAKER_10]: But we have people who are already playing the beta.
[SPEAKER_14]: The beta's been out for a while now, though.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's got to be sometime soon.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was practically done in October.
[SPEAKER_13]: You know there are some people that are concerned that the Gran Turismo 5 release date isn't accurate either.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also a legitimate concern.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see, UnfoldedRaptor writes and says, when I was in third grade back in 2000, I feel so old.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Shush.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was a great troll from Unfolded Raptor right there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good job, sir.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: I used to tell my friend at school that if he threw flares in the corner of a certain room in Tomb Raider The Last Revelation, that it would skip him to the end of the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, he kept doing that, and it ticked him off that he had to restart the level again and again and waste his flares.
[SPEAKER_14]: So he comes back and tells me the next day that if I went through the whole game of Star Fox 64 without doing a barrel roll, that at the end, Andross would come out and shake his butt.
[SPEAKER_14]: I have to remember they're in third grade, so this is funny.
[SPEAKER_14]: I played Star Fox 64 over and over for about a week before I was convinced that no such thing existed.
[SPEAKER_14]: Years later, my friend told me he lied about Andross, and it served me right.
[SPEAKER_14]: But deep down in my heart, I want to believe that such a secret ending actually exists.
[SPEAKER_14]: This is an April Fool's prank that has stuck with me throughout the years.
[SPEAKER_14]: I feel like this needs an animated GIF file of Andross shaking his butt with, I want to believe.
[SPEAKER_14]: that's a good story what I like about that story is it really has nothing to do with gaming magazines or press but it's just like people trolling each other and that's that's great all right lastly uh Hunter R writes and says I remember last year this game that claimed to be Duke Nukem Forever came out except it was totally lame there are people who are still convinced that shit is real haha
[SPEAKER_14]: I see what you did there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, that's it for our Fugle question of the week.
[SPEAKER_13]: There's developers that think that the critics went too hard on them.
[SPEAKER_14]: By the way, those are like the 9-11 conspiracy theories.
[SPEAKER_13]: 100,000 strong for bringing back Mega Man Legends 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're up to 81,642.
[SPEAKER_13]: That's actually been going up quite a bit.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they keep that up.
[SPEAKER_13]: You may be able to hit that before June.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would go like the page, but I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's just where I'm at.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm over it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, let's get back into some more news, Loki.
[SPEAKER_13]: Alright, well, unfortunately something that may not be coming back quite as soon as Mega Man Legends 3.
[SPEAKER_13]: Two PSP games which had problems with their save files or they could be exploited to launch a homebrew emulator on the PlayStation Vita, basically through the PSP emulator on there.
[SPEAKER_13]: and allow them to run unsigned code.
[SPEAKER_13]: So before we knew about Motorstorm Arctic Rift that was taken off and now Hotshots Tennis or Everybody's Tennis in Europe has also been taken down because it was also being used in exploits to run homebrew on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_13]: So that's what happens is these people release a method that requires one of these games and then it goes away.
[SPEAKER_13]: PlayStation Vita Hacked
[SPEAKER_14]: I found that to be interesting, that they were using the old games to do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's only hacked within the emulator.
[SPEAKER_13]: But the emulator isn't as strapped as it was on the PSP.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can still do a little bit more.
[SPEAKER_13]: You have a little bit more memory and stuff to work with.
[SPEAKER_13]: But it's still within the emulator.
[SPEAKER_13]: You don't actually have access to the whole Vita stuff yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it allowed you to install Linux on the Vita?
[SPEAKER_13]: It would allow you to run emulators and maybe ISOs.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know about that, but at least emulators.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm surprised you didn't get in on this before it got shut down I don't download PSP games other than the ones I got for free and honestly I'm kind of over playing emulators on stuff right now if I want to play emulators I have my PSP still I have a Dingu that only plays emulators I don't really need another system to run homebrew stuff on right now
[SPEAKER_14]: Death Jam Rapstar Death Jam Rapstar Death Jam Rapstar Death Jam Rapstar
[SPEAKER_14]: I try not to.
[SPEAKER_14]: DJ Ranma S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_14]: EMI is suing 4mm Games and Terminal Reality saying that songs were used in the game that they weren't entitled to.
[SPEAKER_14]: Rapstar apparently got some songs from labels like Def Jam and so forth.
[SPEAKER_14]: EMI says though it owned small percentages of other tracks that were nominally owned by other labels.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's weird.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of the examples include DJ Khaled's I'm So Hood, Lil Wayne's Got Money, which EMI said they own 10% of one of them and 30% of the other.
[SPEAKER_14]: I know, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: This is just me that multiple publishers... The way these things get bought and who finances it and so forth, I can kind of see where this happens.
[SPEAKER_14]: But EMI says 54 tracks infringe on their rights.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going after $8 million in damages.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the weird thing to me is that this game is kind of old now.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it was 2010 or 9.
[SPEAKER_13]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was that same E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was October.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was in October.
[SPEAKER_14]: I remember seeing it at E3, and I want to say it was the same year that Game Room had come out.
[SPEAKER_14]: So what year was Game Room?
[SPEAKER_14]: Was that 2009?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think it was 2009.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was 2010, actually.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really?
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: 2010, and yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they shut down the community site in 2011.
[SPEAKER_13]: Dope.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's move on to the mailbag.
[SPEAKER_14]: Every week you guys send us e-mails.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_10]: They've always had free artistic reign, producing tons of exclusive comics and characters that never really gained traction elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_10]: At the end of the 90s, Disney Italy decided to launch a couple of experiments, some successful, some less so, but all quite surprising.
[SPEAKER_10]: These included P.K.N.A., a Marvel-slash-DC-style comic featuring Paper... Paper-y Nick?
[SPEAKER_10]: Donald Duck's superhero alter ego as he fought aliens, time travelers, and mutants, featured violence and actual character deaths.
[SPEAKER_10]: The most successful of the experiments.
[SPEAKER_10]: This even got its own video game although that was based on the shitty third series that fans like to forget ever happened.
[SPEAKER_14]: Can I say real quick?
[SPEAKER_14]: The whole Epic Mickey thing, since it's nowhere else in our show row, I don't think we've covered it here.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's that awesome new, I don't know if you heard, but with Epic Mickey 2, they're also doing the 3DS game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, the 3DS isn't a port of Epic Mickey 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: The 3DS game is a new Castle of Illusion game.
[SPEAKER_06]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_14]: Right?
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're doing stages like classic stages, but they're doing stuff like Tangled, and it's a bunch of new Disney movies in it too.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm like, sold!
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sounds better than the console one to me.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, to continue?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's Witch, a shoujo manga-style comic.
[SPEAKER_10]: This one also ran for quite a long time, also getting its own TV show and being turned into a real manga in Japan.
[SPEAKER_10]: Not to be confused with Winx Club, which was a cheap and nasty knockoff of this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ritty Topolino, which is what you get when you cross Disney with Monty Python.
[SPEAKER_10]: Short-lived but hilarious, things they did included publishing their Christmas issue in July, inserting deliberate mistakes into the comic strip, and one memorable feature celebrated the Olympics by having Mickey compete against a garden gnome.
[SPEAKER_10]: The inanimate gnome not only won, but the end of many also dumps Mickey for it.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's Mickey Mouse Mystery Magazine, the darkest of the bunch.
[SPEAKER_10]: Mickey is a hard-boiled detective in his own noir comic, solving mysteries and dealing with bad guys.
[SPEAKER_10]: This was so dark later, issues tried to soften the story by making it look like Mickey was just watching the episode as a film rather than him being the actual protagonist.
[SPEAKER_10]: Then in the early 2000s, Disney Italy got a new director who decided all this awesome teen-oriented stuff was too bold and basically killed off every one of these projects, which is a great shame.
[SPEAKER_10]: They all deserved a lot more recognition.
[SPEAKER_10]: Unfortunately, PQNA and MMMM never made it to the States, so your only chance of reading these fine series is to learn Italian or look for fan-translated scans on the net.
[SPEAKER_10]: But yeah, I would love to see some of the edgier characters in Epic Mickey, too, but since they're virtually unknown outside of Italy, not much chance of that, eh?
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway, late and take care, Picaruno.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for the email, Picaruno, and just for you, since you brought it up.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_10]: And this is actually from... There was a link from the Star Tribune.
[SPEAKER_10]: Last year, Best Buy lost a staggering $1.2 billion as it was deeply discounted merchandise to keep pace with rivals Amazon and Walmart.
[SPEAKER_10]: All in all, Best Buy hopes to shed $800 million over the next three years, saving the company plans to use...
[SPEAKER_10]: So, wow.
[SPEAKER_14]: Best Buy Best Buy Best Buy Best Buy Best Buy
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, Best Buy is going to have to be aggressive if they want to stay competitive.
[SPEAKER_14]: It will probably help that more states are forcing Amazon to charge sales tax because there's a lot of people that use Amazon simply because they don't have to pay tax when they buy on Amazon, but that's going to be changing, unfortunately or fortunately, depending on how you look at it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Next email I have a neighbor of mine who owns a fairly large pasture On this pasture he allows a number of animals to freely graze Horses, cows, sheep, whatever On the fence that lines the property is a series of signs that all say the same thing Free manure, inquire at the house
[SPEAKER_10]: By now manure, he means bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fresh new, high quality bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: My neighbor's bullshit is free to anyone.
[SPEAKER_10]: You just have to haul it away yourself.
[SPEAKER_10]: As I looked at my Twitter feed on Wednesday, I began to wonder why people aren't all a Twitter about my neighbor's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yum!
[SPEAKER_14]: Mainly because no one actually cares about actual bullshit Did you see the ad today for the Chick-fil-A steak sandwich?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, I did That was pretty funny Is that it for emails or we have one more?
[SPEAKER_10]: We have one more, but I wondered if you had a rebuttal for Why is real bullshit not as talked about as the bullshit people actually care about?
[SPEAKER_10]: Because your neighbor's not famous and doesn't make video game systems.
[SPEAKER_14]: The end.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot of game sites that run with bullshit or else they'd have nothing else to publish.
[SPEAKER_13]: Speaking of shit, EA is still up for grabs for Worst Company in America.
[SPEAKER_13]: So if you go to Consumerist.com and vote, I believe tomorrow is when they're having... I don't know if it's tomorrow or maybe the early part of next week that they're actually voting for the semifinals.
[SPEAKER_13]: So...
[SPEAKER_13]: They can do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: And this year, they're also giving away three different golden poos.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're going to have the golden poo, the silver poo, and the bronze poo this year.
[SPEAKER_13]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_13]: So they still have a chance as long as they win next round.
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, congratulations.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Two emails left.
[SPEAKER_10]: Excuse me?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, I had to burp.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh well.
[SPEAKER_10]: Good pick.
[SPEAKER_10]: After anxiously connecting all of the cables and the single controller, I was relieved to find the PS1 was still kicking.
[SPEAKER_10]: And better yet, I jammed to Don't Stop Me Now as a celebration anthem.
[SPEAKER_10]: That song is great.
[SPEAKER_10]: I love the scene in Shaun of the Dead where they're beating up the zombie to that song.
[SPEAKER_10]: That's the best.
[SPEAKER_10]: I haven't touched a PS1 since 2000, back when I was nine.
[SPEAKER_10]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: The nostalgia began to return to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm not enjoying all this age of our listeners this week.
[SPEAKER_10]: I remember being blown away by games like Einhander, Gran Turismo, and Twisted Metal My question to you guys is this With my first ever PS1, what game should I immediately own?
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, what were the seminal titles of the PS1 era?
[SPEAKER_10]: I like all types of games, RPGs, platformers, horror, sports, fighting rhythm, you name it Also, where can I even find PS1 games anymore?
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks in advance, love the show, keep up the good work, Randy from Texas
[SPEAKER_14]: Flea Markets, you can find a lot of PlayStation 1 games that still... Amazon.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_14]: They still sell PlayStation 1 games?
[SPEAKER_10]: People sell stuff on Amazon all the time.
[SPEAKER_10]: eBay.
[SPEAKER_10]: Half.
[SPEAKER_14]: Castlevania Symphony of the Night, you should own right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, you definitely should own that one.
[SPEAKER_10]: Jumping Flash.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you enjoy music games at all, Parappa the Rapper and its sequel, Um Jam Malami.
[SPEAKER_10]: I also... They changed the whole import thing on the PS Slim, didn't they?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: Because, yeah, that was the one that you had to use the memory card thing.
[SPEAKER_13]: I never had a Slim.
[SPEAKER_13]: I just had the old one that we had the... The thing that plugs in the back?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: You might as well get a Final Fantasy VII copy, too, because that was a must.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get Final Fantasy VII.
[SPEAKER_14]: Um...
[SPEAKER_10]: Einhander, of course, you mentioned it.
[SPEAKER_10]: Even Ergeis.
[SPEAKER_10]: I freaking loved Ergeis because of the RPG mode in Ergeis.
[SPEAKER_13]: R4.
[SPEAKER_10]: R4, yes.
[SPEAKER_10]: And get a JogCon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Don't get a JogCon.
[SPEAKER_13]: Really not worth it.
[SPEAKER_13]: I bought a JogCon and I was like, wow, this is crap.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know what you need?
[SPEAKER_10]: Wipe out with the NegCon.
[SPEAKER_13]: What if I have a JogCon still?
[SPEAKER_13]: I've got two of them.
[SPEAKER_14]: And of course, Ridge Racer.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was R4.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, Herp Derp.
[SPEAKER_10]: Ridge Racer Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: But Wipeout with an egg con is probably one of the best experiences.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's what I was thinking of was Ridge Racer Revolution.
[SPEAKER_10]: God, what else?
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I mean, I just picked up Bust a Move 2 Arcade Edition, which is literally the best version of Bust a Move you can find.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chrono Cross?
[SPEAKER_10]: Chrono Cross.
[SPEAKER_10]: Chrono Trigger re-release.
[SPEAKER_13]: You gotta get Bubsy because that was such a high quality game.
[SPEAKER_14]: Ah, don't troll.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't troll.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, so good luck finding your PlayStation game.
[SPEAKER_14]: And just for you, just for you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe you should just go get a PlayStation 3 and get a SingStar Queen or a rock band and all the Queen songs.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about The Last Demon?
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, how about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Greetings, OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's your friendly neighborhood turtle.
[SPEAKER_10]: Question of the week.
[SPEAKER_10]: What game are you looking forward to most this year, not including January through March?
[SPEAKER_10]: Also, a comment on Skyrim.
[SPEAKER_10]: I almost never buy games day one because of costs, which I believe are too high, but I did buy Skyrim, sunk 40 hours into it in two weeks, and haven't touched it until today.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks to Steam constantly advertising the latest mods, I decided to give it another go, but only after spending two hours respeccing my character.
[SPEAKER_10]: Being able to respec plus the sky UI has made the game playable again.
[SPEAKER_10]: By the way, the HD graphics pack made the game look that much better.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anywho, keep up the good work and I'll listen to your answer tomorrow, your loyal turtle in Philly, Serious Turtle.
[SPEAKER_13]: I kind of want to play it on my PC.
[SPEAKER_13]: So do I. I don't know if my PC can run it, though.
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it can.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm sure mine can.
[SPEAKER_14]: Games I'm looking forward to this year.
[SPEAKER_14]: Kingdom Heart, Dream Drop Distance.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes!
[SPEAKER_14]: Which is out in Japan, but it's not out here yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: The new Tomb Raider looks really good still.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm interested in that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I kind of think there's going to be stuff at E3 that we don't know about yet that will be very exciting, especially with the Wii U and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Also, it's looking very, very, very good that I'm going to be able to go to E3 this year, so I'm very excited about that because I didn't go last year, really.
[SPEAKER_14]: I sat in the lobby last year.
[SPEAKER_14]: But hopefully this year I'll get to get some hands on that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I miss E3.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do.
[SPEAKER_13]: It is fun.
[SPEAKER_13]: I do miss it, but I can't.
[SPEAKER_14]: You have a baby.
[SPEAKER_13]: He has separation anxiety.
[SPEAKER_14]: When the kid's 18, then he can go to E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably not that old.
[SPEAKER_14]: But you can't take kids under 18.
[SPEAKER_10]: You can take him.
[SPEAKER_10]: By four, hopefully he'll understand that daddy goes away sometimes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, he's just at the point now where it's just like, you know, he's very clingy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Understand, understand.
[SPEAKER_13]: I get to stay back at work and work while everybody goes and drives down to Monterey.
[SPEAKER_13]: Rough life.
[SPEAKER_13]: Who said I'm going to work though when they leave?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm kicking back.
[SPEAKER_14]: Internet all day, every day.
[SPEAKER_14]: So that's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Emails, mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com if you want to send us some emails in the future.
[SPEAKER_14]: Again, that's mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good emails this week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's get to the FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_09]: Making me work.
[SPEAKER_14]: The FUs of the week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_14]: And some special April Fool's FU music as picked by Loki tonight.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know I tried to find the whole video for that song just because I needed to hear it in context.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: This is actually really well looped.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just mesmerized for a second.
[SPEAKER_10]: Anyway.
[SPEAKER_10]: You need to stop that because that's too distracting.
[SPEAKER_14]: How about if I get the sax guy off the screen?
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura.com
[SPEAKER_10]: What sucks about it?
[SPEAKER_10]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_10]: What sucks is that I have a class that's on during my work shift.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I'm basically going to have to miss the rest of the semester of that class.
[SPEAKER_10]: But I've already told the teacher that if I got a job, job comes first.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki!
[SPEAKER_13]: Fuck you, McDonald's, for not being able to make food correctly.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, it's not that hard.
[SPEAKER_13]: Seriously.
[SPEAKER_10]: You're calling that food?
[SPEAKER_13]: Well, it's Harley food, but like I said, there's a few McDonald's on the way here and no Burger Kings that are right on the way here.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, it's like, well, I could drive way the fuck out of the way to go to Burger King or I could just be quick and get McDonald's.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I was quick.
[SPEAKER_13]: I was actually almost going to get their Fish McBites that they have now.
[SPEAKER_13]: Although, I think that would be poison.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, I'm not really sure if I should do that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm not.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_14]: F you to the people that keep wanting to compare Battle Royale to Hunger Games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Get over it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And F you to F you to Jelly Belly.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am so mad.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am no longer going to be able to eat Jelly Bellies anymore.
[SPEAKER_09]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm boycotting Jelly Bellies.
[SPEAKER_14]: What happened?
[SPEAKER_14]: They had Rick Santorum at their factory giving a speech and then did this whole thousand dollar a plate fundraiser dinner at Jelly Belly because I never knew this.
[SPEAKER_14]: They contribute to all these causes which I don't, you know, I'm not mad at, like I'm not the person to usually get up there and say F you to all Republicans and all this because I don't feel that way.
[SPEAKER_09]: But he's evil.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot of Republicans I do like and there's some progressive ideas that
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: He's the village idiot of this country and deserves to be pointed and laughed at wherever he goes.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm just sad that he has tainted the Jelly Belly Factory and I can no longer support that company.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I urge all of you to.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was hoping that maybe it was all like they were going to do a Bernie's Bots for Santorum flavored jelly beans.
[SPEAKER_14]: But...
[SPEAKER_14]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_13]: All right.
[SPEAKER_13]: So moving on, let's talk a little bit about changes.
[SPEAKER_13]: And Sega, unfortunately, changing for the worst.
[SPEAKER_13]: They are canceling games, cutting jobs, and restructuring.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, of course, their expected net income is down almost 50%.
[SPEAKER_13]: And, of course, they're going to make some changes regarding that.
[SPEAKER_13]: They're streamlining the operations of Sega, both in the United States and Europe.
[SPEAKER_13]: Um, they're gonna focus on key franchises, including Sonic, Football Manager, Total War, and Aliens.
[SPEAKER_13]: So, um...
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, it's interesting.
[SPEAKER_13]: Funny enough, though, they're actually still doing an Olympics game in June, so maybe they're restructuring after that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, no, that Sonic and Mario Olympic game did crazy good on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_13]: No, I'm not talking about that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I'm talking about the actual Olympic games, the sports game that's on PS3 and 360.
[SPEAKER_13]: But maybe for that same reason they're doing that.
[SPEAKER_13]: I mean, that'd be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_13]: but yeah I can understand they try a lot of experimental stuff and it doesn't always work out if only they'd release Shenmue 3 if only well I think they kind of do that stuff though a little bit more experimental stuff though on Xbox Live Arcade so I don't know necessarily we're going to see the end of that kind of stuff because after all they're going to be doing Jet Set Radio here so it's very possible that they'll still do Shenmue alright
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, I know you've got to be feeling a little sad about the changes at Sega.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, I'm also pissed off at my laptop, but that's another thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Did Sega build your laptop?
[SPEAKER_10]: No, it's a piece of shit.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Nietzsche in our chatroom is wondering the same thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's going to happen to my PlayStation Online 2 Sega?
[SPEAKER_14]: What about PSO2, you bastards?
[SPEAKER_14]: That's how I feel.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just stop putting out the crappy Sonic games and maybe it'll be better.
[SPEAKER_14]: Firefly the Arcade Game
[SPEAKER_14]: April Fools' Joke
[SPEAKER_10]: What time does it say?
[SPEAKER_14]: It doesn't say.
[SPEAKER_14]: It just says March 31st, 2012.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I'm going to take it with a grain of salt.
[SPEAKER_14]: This probably is a joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: But let's entertain the idea that it's real for a minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's entertain if it could be realistic or not.
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently, because of the 10th anniversary of the show Firefly, even though it had a short life on television, it's very cult.
[SPEAKER_14]: And now they're talking about a Firefly arcade game.
[SPEAKER_14]: See, the thing about this is the screenshot does look really fake to me.
[SPEAKER_14]: The whole thing looks very fake.
[SPEAKER_14]: It does.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's a whole first-person shooter and all this.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, and that cabinet, too, just doesn't look... No.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's assume it could be real, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Somebody was really thinking about this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Would this be something worth doing?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because it is a bit of a cultish franchise, but I...
[SPEAKER_14]: a lot of stuff from kind of back of the day ends up coming full circle again I don't even know necessarily it's an arcade game but like a pinball game I could totally see a Firefly pinball game I really don't think it would happen I mean then again I'm sure Joss would like the money
[SPEAKER_13]: they wouldn't make an arcade game based on a property that's niche like that especially since arcade games nowadays it's just like you've got to have some sort of gimmick to get people to come to the arcades to play the game they're not going to spend the money to make cabinets for an arcade game like that
[SPEAKER_13]: April Fools, haha April Fools, haha
[SPEAKER_13]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_10]: Oh, yeah, that would be me, wouldn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, ma'am.
[SPEAKER_10]: How about Tesco?
[SPEAKER_10]: Do you know what Tesco is?
[SPEAKER_14]: They are a big grocery store in Britain, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yes, did you know that they've opened markets in the United States?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yes, because they're fresh and easy.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's how I knew that.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_14]: And they're being protested, hella, the new stores that open here.
[SPEAKER_10]: Really?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because I guess Tesco is very anti-union.
[SPEAKER_14]: So some of the union grocers in the area are protesting.
[SPEAKER_10]: When I drove by, there was actually an ambulance in front of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe they started fighting each other, who knows?
[SPEAKER_10]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, at any rate, the supermarket has now said they are the home of gaming in the advertisement over in the UK.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I guess since Game UK went under, there's an opening.
[SPEAKER_10]: Actually, there's no more game store closures.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, there was an article on that on Eurogamer.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, I didn't hear that follow-up.
[SPEAKER_10]: They didn't close any more stores.
[SPEAKER_10]: Huh.
[SPEAKER_10]: so basically they're saying that they have more gaming stores in the UK than any other retailers so that's 393 open at midnight for new releases and that they will have over 10,000 titles available online free UK delivery and day one pre-order shipping
[SPEAKER_10]: So I have no idea what to say about that.
[SPEAKER_14]: This reminds me of when 7-Eleven got into gaming for a hot minute.
[SPEAKER_14]: They stopped doing that, right?
[SPEAKER_10]: Dan is friends with somebody who managed.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was a big flop.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, of course it was a big flop.
[SPEAKER_14]: What about this though?
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, I remember back in the day, a lot of grocery stores had like video rental shops in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: And you could also rent games there too.
[SPEAKER_14]: So like integrating, and a lot of them still sell DVDs.
[SPEAKER_13]: It's not a bad idea considering that
[SPEAKER_13]: The video rental market is coming back because blockbusters have closed down, Hollywood has closed down, most of your mom and pop shops have closed down.
[SPEAKER_13]: Now they're starting to reopen back up, although kiosks are popular nowadays.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I found the thing about game, by the way, that it was OpCapita, that's a parent company of Comet, is bidding for game again.
[SPEAKER_10]: And there's 333 stores still open, 211 of them being game and 122 being game station.
[SPEAKER_10]: and basically they were initially blocked by the lending syndicate that owned them including the Royal Bank of Scotland.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was what stopped them before.
[SPEAKER_14]: So could video games at the grocery store work?
[SPEAKER_14]: I think especially the cheaper market could work because you see a lot of that at Target.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, yes, Target sells new games and all that too, but they also like up by the registers usually have the $20 Wii games and those seem to do all right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Like they sell more there than they probably would at a GameStop or something.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, Tesco's pretty big too and I think they are like a wide, very broad in their services and markets, so...
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Probably like a Safeway here.
[SPEAKER_14]: You know, it's got a lot of stuff.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's not necessarily just the store, but usually the full-service deli in China, you know, a lot of places.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_14]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, as far as I understand it, it actually is a bit more like a Super Target.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_10]: You know.
[SPEAKER_10]: So Tesco is really big.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, but it was a big supermarket, but like you can get, or maybe like a, oh, what's that thing that they had in Washington that Fred Meyer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Fred Meyer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_10]: The sum of everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, well, Loki, if you don't have any comments, then let's go to the next story
[SPEAKER_13]: Let's talk about something, kind of a really cool piece of technology, BrowserQuest.
[SPEAKER_13]: It was an MMO tech demo built by Mozilla.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it's basically an MMO that works in browsers.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they've got this little, kind of almost looks like a 16-bit MMO that you can play.
[SPEAKER_13]: And it actually will kind of work in any browser, I guess, that supports HTML5.
[SPEAKER_13]: and they even have the full source available on github if you want to create your own MMO based off that which is pretty cool and if you want to check it out you can go to mozilla.org future of MMOs
[SPEAKER_14]: Possibly?
[SPEAKER_14]: Sounds like just another, like, oh, yay, free, MM, you know, type of thing.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, I mean... I mean, how many browser-based games do we have these days?
[SPEAKER_14]: There's a lot.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, but the Ultima one that EA had... But, I mean, something that runs in HTML5, though, that would be compatible with, you know, like, iOS and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: Oh, I get where you're going with that, then.
[SPEAKER_13]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, like, on mobile devices and stuff, it's not just... Or, like, All Games Radio is compatible with HTML5, and you can get it on your iDevice at allgames.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_13]: Yeah, so they're saying, yeah, it's written in HTML5 and JavaScript and can be played in Firefox, Chrome, Safari, with WebSockets enabled, also in Opera.
[SPEAKER_13]: And they're saying, of course, iOS devices and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_13]: If you want to play the game, it's browserquest.mozilla.org is the URL to go in.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: But there's also Zork Grand Inquisitor, Zork Nemesis, all these games came out.
[SPEAKER_14]: And then of course the text adventure games, Zork Anthology, Zork 1 through 3, Beyond Zork, Zork 0.
[SPEAKER_14]: All of these games are on sale right now at the website Good Old Games.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're half off right now along with some other games such as Caesar 3, Vampire the Masquerade, Redemption, and so forth.
[SPEAKER_14]: So yeah, pretty cool if you're a Zork fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh God, I remember the Commodore 64 text adventure really well.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's when games were hard.
[SPEAKER_14]: You had to know exactly what to type into that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't run out of matches or torches.
[SPEAKER_14]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_14]: You might get eaten by a Groo.
[SPEAKER_14]: So if you want to get your Groos half off, get your Groove on at GOG.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's a much better April Fool's thing than what they did a few years ago with the whole we're going to shut down unless you give... I don't remember what it was.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was really terrible.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Anyhow, let's get into some Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_14]: And we're going to open the Skype line right now because it's not open yet.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I should do that.
[SPEAKER_14]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio, all one word.
[SPEAKER_14]: And Skype is signing into the wrong account right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's really convenient, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_14]: You can call and talk about whatever.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to take it back to the Bimani stuff, that's fine too since that was part of our fun tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or again our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: All one word.
[SPEAKER_14]: While we wait for some calls, let's go to our Twitter, twitter.com slash OLR and see what tweets are in store for us.
[SPEAKER_14]: Gamer Girl tweets us saying, Is PlayStation Plus really worth the money?
[SPEAKER_14]: I was thinking about getting a subscription, but I want to know if it's worth the money.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think I'm the only one that actually has PlayStation Plus here I'll tell you this if you use your PlayStation a lot and especially if you buy from the store a lot then yes there's you know so many discounts and things and a lot of freebies that you get with PlayStation as well so if you think you'd kind of be into some of those freebies you want to get like one arcade game every couple weeks or so I think it's a pretty good deal and getting Journey early was really nice as well so I think there's a lot of good stuff there but um
[SPEAKER_14]: It really depends on how much you love your PlayStation.
[SPEAKER_14]: Meanwhile, the phones are ringing, so let's go to the phones.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Lawns Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, this is DS Lover.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, what's your name again?
[SPEAKER_14]: DS Lover.
[SPEAKER_14]: What's on your mind?
[SPEAKER_15]: Not much other than to talk about something that happened last night on the Cartoon Network.
[SPEAKER_15]: I don't know if the rest of you...
[SPEAKER_15]: and the rest of the anime community ever caught this, but Toonami was on instead of the usual Adult Swim bumpers.
[SPEAKER_14]: And hopefully this
[SPEAKER_15]: And I'm not just saying this, but you know how I sent you guys an email?
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, how you guys have risen above a podcast that just pretty much kicked us?
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I'm going to reveal that podcast name right here now.
[SPEAKER_15]: Games and More Entertainment Radio, like, they've just pretty much ceased.
[SPEAKER_15]: They're not doing anything anymore, and just, like, I need my gaming news fix on a weekly basis, or else I'm still left.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, is that another indie show, or is that a corporate-backed show?
[SPEAKER_15]: No, it's another indie show.
[SPEAKER_15]: Well, I don't like to throw shade at the other indie shows, because they all work hard at what they do, but everybody's got different preferences, so... Yeah, and I will say here, with the fact that 16th Empress beat Minya with the last one, the PS2...
[SPEAKER_15]: Has anyone heard any announcements for the PlayStation 3 versions at all?
[SPEAKER_14]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_14]: We kind of think that Konami may have just given up on the whole damn series, which is a darn shame because I think there's opportunity there for them to do a massive collection on the PlayStation 3, but that would require them investing in another controller or at least a converter for the old ones, which I would think would be easy to do, but they don't want to do it.
[SPEAKER_15]: There are controller converters for the PlayStation 2 controllers.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, they already work for the Guitar Hero stuff.
[SPEAKER_15]: I mean, it shouldn't be that hard.
[SPEAKER_15]: I think they should be able to work on the Beatmania controllers.
[SPEAKER_15]: If anyone in the crowd would like to test that out, I'd be willing to import.
[SPEAKER_14]: There could be lag, I don't know, especially with the music game, lag could kill it, but I mean, if they did it with the guitars and so forth, then I don't see why it isn't possible, but...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_14]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've got to see that the fans are there for 2DX to sell on the PlayStation 3, and then maybe they'll do it.
[SPEAKER_14]: But certainly in America, Beatmania didn't sell.
[SPEAKER_15]: Yeah, and I think it was because the set list was halfway the problem, and that's what I've heard from many Pumani fans, was the set list was one of the few problems on top of
[SPEAKER_15]: Oh, it's way too easy to get your place in this.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, which is why I'm currently on the search for something like BM98 for the Macintosh or some of the equivalent, because
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm thinking about getting one of those Joy-Cue keys or one of those PS2 to USB adapters for my computer just so I can play Beatmania.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or even a similar... You know what you need to do?
[SPEAKER_14]: You need to write a letter to Konami.
[SPEAKER_14]: You need to say, I am a concerned fan.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that's once Konami hears voices.
[SPEAKER_14]: But anything is possible at E3.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, wouldn't it be cool if maybe the Wii U could become a controller somehow?
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_15]: Hey, what about Twitter?
[SPEAKER_15]: I'm sure it's well, they have a Twitter.
[SPEAKER_15]: Tweet them!
[SPEAKER_15]: The body fans of the world, tweet Konami to bring Beatman to the PS3.
[SPEAKER_14]: It worked with President Kat, sort of.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, well, DS, what was, DS fan, I gotta let you go and take more calls, but thanks for the call.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, peace out and keep the shows rockin'.
[SPEAKER_14]: 1-877-GAME-OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: Username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Going to some Tweety Tweets here.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dartetsuya says, coming to the site this week, I've got something planned for the listeners to participate in.
[SPEAKER_14]: So stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_14]: That doesn't sound like an April Fool's joke.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Moving on.
[SPEAKER_14]: SSJ100Matt tweets us, I know it's a video game show, but I played Cards Against Humanity, the card game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's apples to apples, but M-rated.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, you've never heard of this now, Loki, have you?
[SPEAKER_14]: Of course not.
[SPEAKER_14]: So you're very familiar with Cards Against Humanity, right?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_13]: Cards Against Humanity is a very inappropriate apples to apples game.
[SPEAKER_14]: What makes it so great?
[SPEAKER_14]: Just its level of inappropriateness?
[SPEAKER_13]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Going to WatchDragon, who tweets us, Mr. Pandaria is great.
[SPEAKER_14]: Just finished the starting area.
[SPEAKER_14]: How did you get past all of those freaking pandas and some of those quests?
[SPEAKER_14]: That must have taken a lot of patience.
[SPEAKER_14]: Some of the art style is neat, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: I do like the way Pandaria looks.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's cute.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to see it later, DarkSakura, we can fire it up on the computer before you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: If you want to peek.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_14]: Be fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Going to some tweets from Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_14]: 1877 GameOLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Tigerclaw says, why Soul Calibur V only had one-fourth of a full story mode?
[SPEAKER_14]: I did feel like story mode in Soul Calibur V seemed to be lacking a little bit.
[SPEAKER_14]: But what happened with Soul Calibur V?
[SPEAKER_14]: Apparently it's an interview that was on Train to Game with the producer Daishi Odashima says the story mode shipped with the game was a fourth of what they had planned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Quote, our first plan on the storyboard was that we add every character's story, and actually we do have it in the studio, but time-wise, manpower-wise, we weren't able to do it, and only one-fourth of what we planned to do is in the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: That was a dumb thing for them to admit.
[SPEAKER_14]: We could do it if only we had the DLC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
[SPEAKER_14]: I just think that was a dumb thing for them to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think they should have kept those cards closer to their chest, sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it did feel to me that story mode in Soul Calibur 5 was a little bit lacking.
[SPEAKER_14]: So, Tigerclaw sends us another tweet.
[SPEAKER_14]: Warhammer 40k Dark Millennium.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's going single player because layoffs have hit Relic and Vigil.
[SPEAKER_14]: More layoffs, man, this is a bummer.
[SPEAKER_14]: So Warhammer 40K Dark Millennium, it's now a single-player action game.
[SPEAKER_14]: It will have multiplayer elements.
[SPEAKER_14]: The president and CEO of THQ, Brian Farrell, put out a press release saying, quote, as previously announced, we have been actively looking for a business partner for the game as MMO.
[SPEAKER_14]: However, based on changing market dynamics and the additional investment required to complete the game as an MMO, we believe the right direction for us is to shift the title from an MMO to a premium experience with single and multiplayer gameplay.
[SPEAKER_14]: Robust digital content and community features So, shit tons of DLC, y'all Actually
[SPEAKER_14]: As much as it sucks that these studios got closed and so forth, this makes sense.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think the MMO market is really volatile right now, and it's really tough to make a showing.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, look at where Star Wars is at.
[SPEAKER_14]: They've come the second best probably to getting wow, and even they're starting to lose some people who are getting kind of bored of the game.
[SPEAKER_14]: So MMOs are hard to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Phone calls are a lot easier to do.
[SPEAKER_14]: We have a phone call coming in now.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, it's Porkchop.
[SPEAKER_14]: Porkchop, what's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, it's good that you started talking about the whole Soul Calibur thing because I was really let down by that.
[SPEAKER_01]: That pissed me off, something serious.
[SPEAKER_14]: Porkchop, where are you from?
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm on Ireland, actually.
[SPEAKER_14]: I could tell.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hello.
[SPEAKER_14]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_14]: You guys stay up late to listen to the show over there.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, I do.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wasn't that a dumb thing for them to say, that they only finished a quarter of it?
[SPEAKER_01]: I was so pissed off I mean I remember playing through the story mode okay and it was it took me a day I played it in one fucking day and I played that I paid like it'd be about what 40 or 50 euros something like that'd be about 50 60 dollars something like that in the exchange I went and played that it took me like two maybe not even an hour I played it and I said fuck this I'm really disappointed so what I did was I brought it back I got Arkham City and I was much happier
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank God the creative character mode's at least still fun, and the fighting core game is still really fun.
[SPEAKER_14]: But yeah, the story mode was a little bit disappointing there, so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh Christ, I mean, if you finish it in an hour, it's not worth buying.
[SPEAKER_01]: For that price, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I don't even buy full-price games anymore, never mind anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, nowadays I just look in GameStop for games that are like two to three years old.
[SPEAKER_01]: Like, I just picked up Final Fantasy XIII for, what, six?
[SPEAKER_01]: Six euros?
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh God, it was cheap.
[SPEAKER_14]: I've been waiting 10 years for an angry Irishman rant on this show and it had to happen on April Fool's Day.
[SPEAKER_10]: You should really see the look on Rob's face right now.
[SPEAKER_10]: He just looks like he's won the lottery.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Well, I'm glad I can fulfill your fantasy or whatever the hell is going on.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was Rob's final fantasy.
[SPEAKER_01]: So there you go.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, full price games nowadays really aren't worth it.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's the fact of the matter.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wait like for...
[SPEAKER_01]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh God, why not?
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I'm never going to pay full price for a game again.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's pretty much how I'm looking at it at this stage.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, Porkchop, let me ask you this then, and maybe I'm baiting you for another rant here, but it certainly begs worth asking when you kind of are sick of only buying these new games that are so expensive and so forth.
[SPEAKER_14]: How do you feel about this story we were talking about earlier that by the time the PlayStation 4 and whatever's next on Xbox are out, or Orbis or whatever it's called, that used games aren't going to happen.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're going to block used games.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: Pain in the fucking ass.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, as I said, I said in chat that I always favorite hard copies over digital anyway.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I still buy CDs and I'm never going to use iTunes or any of that shit.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm still doing that to this day.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like CDs are my vinyl in a way.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm just going to keep doing that and pray to fuck that Sony kind of cop out.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Steam's really successful.
[SPEAKER_01]: I kind of favor those guys because they aren't kind of overcharging the fans or anything.
[SPEAKER_01]: Me and my best friend, he kind of works in the industry and he was telling me Steam are basically the daddy at this stage and they look to be like some sort of messiah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's looking good on their end, but Sony are overcharging people way too fucking much as far as I'm concerned.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, you know, and what's funny, what you made me think about while you were talking about Steam and the way that they're viewed in the industry, there was a rumor a couple weeks ago or maybe even last week on this show about the whole Steam box.
[SPEAKER_14]: And although Valve was quick to shoot that down that that's not actually happening, you can't help but think, holy shit, what if you have the PlayStation Orbis, which doesn't play used games, and you have the Xbox 360 or, excuse me, 720 or Lube or whatever it's called that doesn't play used games, and then you have the Steam box...
[SPEAKER_14]: All of the receipts he had for the past...
[SPEAKER_01]: a couple of months and I looked at it and I compared PlayStation Store and I was like what the fuck am I doing with a PS3 if I can get all these games all the same games nearly every single title I have he had a receipt for and it was like oh god the sales that were on he picked up like 50 games within the space of 3 months and he totted it up and he showed me the end total which would have been if they weren't on sale was around 400
[SPEAKER_01]: and I was like, wow.
[SPEAKER_01]: And he actually said, I never paid that much for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And I was like, holy shit, I want a Steam account.
[SPEAKER_14]: And that was me saying.
[SPEAKER_14]: Could that be a regional thing though?
[SPEAKER_14]: Because most of it here in the US, it seems like, especially when new games come out, it's about the same.
[SPEAKER_14]: You'd play on the PlayStation Network that you would on Steam or whatever, getting it on PC.
[SPEAKER_14]: Part of me wonders if PlayStation doesn't jack up the price even more overseas in other countries and maybe it's that price
[SPEAKER_14]: That pain of the, whatever you want to call it, translation of the cost or whatever is truly causing the difference.
[SPEAKER_01]: The truth is, it wouldn't surprise me.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, even he said games in America are way cheaper.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, as far as I know, I think they are anyway.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, it's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: I hate to sound like I'm bragging, but it's true.
[SPEAKER_14]: When we see how much you guys pay in euros or whatever currency we're looking at over there, it's pretty crazy how much you guys are paying for stuff over there than we are here.
[SPEAKER_10]: I think we're paying on average 10-15% less.
[SPEAKER_01]: Oh, I'm sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, when you look at the exchange rate, you can see that.
[SPEAKER_01]: But even the prices, I'm sure, like, you know, in terms of, you know, denominations of notes or money with bills, as you call them, you know, I'm sure you could pay, use two 20s to buy a good handful of games, whereas that wouldn't even get you, well, it gets you close to one, which is fucking ridiculous.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, Ireland, apparently, the capital of Ireland, Dublin, is one of the most expensive cities in Europe at this stage.
[SPEAKER_01]: so it's fucking ridiculous and that's why I have to go wait a couple of years for these games to come out and I have to go look and I'll be like okay I'm two or three I just finished Deus Ex and that's like year two years I finished Assassin's Creed a couple of days ago or a couple of months ago pardon me and you know I'm playing catch up at this stage but you know what I don't care I'm not paying full price it's fucking ridiculous as long as you've got fun stuff to play now anyway
[SPEAKER_01]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I have a good collection as it is, and I've kept some of the really old ones and hope to play through and buy the rest of the sequels in the next five years, something like that.
[SPEAKER_14]: You could spend your entire life playing classic games and be totally satisfied.
[SPEAKER_14]: I mean, look at the Classic Game of the Week segment we do here on OLR.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I was actually pleased you actually brought up Street Fighter because I'm a big fan, and I got the Capcom Classics collection.
[SPEAKER_01]: I played the shit out of that.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, thanks for bringing that up.
[SPEAKER_14]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: and that's not even all of it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Brag, brag, brag.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm just saying, I mean, it's one thing.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you actually got through most of them or are you waiting to play through them and kind of use one as game of the week at some stage?
[SPEAKER_10]: We've actually gone through most of them.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, a lot of the games that my husband and I picked up are games that we played when we were younger.
[SPEAKER_10]: He was a big Sega guy, and I was a big Nintendo girl.
[SPEAKER_10]: So when we got together, we both had the love of our systems and brought them together.
[SPEAKER_10]: So we go back, and now, though, we have staples that we play, but we'll pick up something every so often just because we've just had the biggest boner to play it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I went on a mad buzz about maybe two, three years ago and I decided, fuck this, I have a Dreamcast, I'm going to buy games for it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I got Jet Set Radio and Shenmue and I was like, okay, I don't regret this one.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, I thought it was going to be like, oh God, these games, why did I buy these?
[SPEAKER_01]: But I actually enjoyed them and I love playing.
[SPEAKER_01]: I play them again and again and again every time I visit my mum's house where she keeps my old room and I have all the Dreamcast games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I still have some PS2 games in there, so...
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like a little fucking hermit's cave where I go back and just play games for the weekend or whatever.
[SPEAKER_10]: I've been tempted to hook up the Dreamcast because I actually want to finish Grandia 2.
[SPEAKER_14]: Wow, that's an old... That's a fun RPG.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, Porkchop, I have absolutely loved having you on the show because I love accents, so I appreciate you calling in.
[SPEAKER_14]: But it's going over a little bit, so I've got to wrap up to get some more calls.
[SPEAKER_14]: Do you quickly have any other final thoughts?
[SPEAKER_01]: Just basically, I love the station.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love all games.
[SPEAKER_01]: I love Orange Lounge, Dead Picks, all that.
[SPEAKER_01]: Keep up the good work, and I'll be listening through the early hours all the time.
[SPEAKER_14]: We love you, and if Derek's listening, I know he's going to appreciate that shout-out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: All the best.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_14]: Love it.
[SPEAKER_14]: The International Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I'm even being asked in our chat room, I think I'm saying this name right, Delighter in our chat room says, Rob is very fond of the Irish, I take it.
[SPEAKER_14]: I get mistaken as Irish all the time.
[SPEAKER_14]: I can't even tell you.
[SPEAKER_14]: Because of that red hair.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, look at that little get up I wore to Umlaut with the hat and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: I did look kind of Irish, even I'll admit that.
[SPEAKER_14]: I am actually, by heritage, I am half Scottish.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I look very Scottish.
[SPEAKER_10]: That means that you greet people by headbutting them.
[SPEAKER_14]: My real name is Dutch, so I have a little more in common with Syl from Girls Gone Wild than I do with that color.
[SPEAKER_10]: I married a Dutch ancestry.
[SPEAKER_14]: You did.
[SPEAKER_14]: Your husband has a very Dutch... It's funny that... You have a Dutch name now, too.
[SPEAKER_10]: I have a Dutch name, but none of my blood kin are remotely Dutch.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, we got another call on the line, so let's go to it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_11]: Nobuo Amatsu
[SPEAKER_14]: A couple nights ago... Wait, wait, now, we don't need to hear about your romantic adventures.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, no, no, no, no.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, that's actually the name... Well, that was the name of the little concert that he had.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's kind of dirty.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hey, don't tell me to shut up.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's my show.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: No, but it was just this really small concert where it was just 150 people.
[SPEAKER_11]: It was Nobuo Matsu and Arnie Roth, who's this conductor in Chicago, and they had this string quartet playing...
[SPEAKER_11]: Dark World from Final Fantasy 6 and this new string quartet arrangement of Fight with Seymour from Final Fantasy 10 and it sounded really good and I was really excited about it so of course I had my phone on me and I tried sneaking my camera on and I recorded the whole concert and I tried putting it on YouTube actually that sounds awesome but you know what
[SPEAKER_11]: No, it was worth it.
[SPEAKER_11]: I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_11]: The piracy, the jail time is going to be worth it because it was so good.
[SPEAKER_11]: When the songs were done, I turned around to see people climbing and stuff.
[SPEAKER_11]: People had their camera right in front of their face.
[SPEAKER_11]: They were being very obvious about us.
[SPEAKER_11]: I was like, whatever.
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't feel bad anymore.
[SPEAKER_14]: I was going to say, an intimate evening in Cell Block 5 with Stan.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: How did you get into this concert if it's only 150 people?
[SPEAKER_11]: What?
[SPEAKER_11]: I don't remember where it was being advertised, but a friend of mine posted this link on Facebook, and I saw it.
[SPEAKER_11]: It said, intimate evening with Novo Matsun.
[SPEAKER_11]: I read the description.
[SPEAKER_11]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, I got my 3DS signed by Noble and Arnie.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's really cool.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes, hold on, wait.
[SPEAKER_14]: I asked Arnie Roth
[SPEAKER_11]: If he would ever consider having an amateur musician sit-down session reading the actual orchestral music, being able to experience the orchestra feel by being inside it, by paying like a small fee, and he was actually really interested in the idea.
[SPEAKER_11]: Well, that's what he told me, but it sounded really cool because I really wanted to play, you know, Final Fantasy music in an orchestral setting with Arnie Roth and Nobu playing, or
[SPEAKER_11]: I figured that'd be really, really cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: That sounds like a heck of an experience.
[SPEAKER_14]: And there's obviously lots of band nerds who are video game nerds.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I say that endearingly because I was a band nerd in high school.
[SPEAKER_14]: There's lots of band nerds and video game nerds that are kind of into both those worlds that I think would just get the ultimate kick out of that.
[SPEAKER_14]: But now I'm going to have to ask you, what do you play in the orchestra?
[SPEAKER_11]: Oh, actually nothing.
[SPEAKER_11]: I play saxophone.
[SPEAKER_11]: So I wouldn't even be able to do this.
[SPEAKER_11]: So does Dark Sakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: Dark Sakura is a saxophone.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'd probably have to...
[SPEAKER_14]: DarkSakura is a sax person too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Here's the thing though.
[SPEAKER_14]: Even if you couldn't play the Final Fantasy music as part of the jam, what you could do is when the time's right, you could just be there in the back and you can just bust out with this.
[SPEAKER_14]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_14]: Be the epic sax guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: Sweet, I'm the beatbox guy.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Stan, I'm going to have to let you go because the connection's a little bit shit, but that's not your fault.
[SPEAKER_14]: Don't worry about it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you for sharing your experience.
[SPEAKER_14]: Please share the pictures online on Twitters or something so we can see them.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah, you know what?
[SPEAKER_11]: I'll send you a link on Facebook or something because that's the only place I have it right now.
[SPEAKER_14]: And I would like to see the bootlegs.
[SPEAKER_14]: I would like to see the bootlegs very much.
[SPEAKER_11]: 13 minutes.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's long.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's all right.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay, cool.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right, send it on over.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Take care.
[SPEAKER_14]: I think we're breaking up.
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good one.
[SPEAKER_14]: Good night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you, too.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Bummer about the connection, but hey, it happens.
[SPEAKER_14]: What can you do?
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's see if I can wrap up these Twitter topics.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm going to go ahead and close Skype for the night.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you guys so much for calling in.
[SPEAKER_14]: I really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Sorry to those that didn't get through, but try again next week.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or, of course, you can always send us an email.
[SPEAKER_14]: Again, that's mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh shit, I was actually out of tweets.
[SPEAKER_14]: I guess I can do one more.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'll let Tigerclaw have one more because this is pretty good.
[SPEAKER_14]: So we'll do this other link from Tigerclaw here who sent us a link.
[SPEAKER_14]: Retired NFL players are getting the green light for a lawsuit against EA.
[SPEAKER_14]: Maybe you didn't hear, but retired NFL players actually filed a lawsuit against EA.
[SPEAKER_14]: A California judge rejected EA's case to have the whole thing dismissed.
[SPEAKER_14]: They want to turn this into a class action lawsuit, so $6,000.
[SPEAKER_14]: The alleged lawsuit here is that EA through EA Sports brand used the likenesses without consent in multiple Madden NFL games over the years.
[SPEAKER_14]: EA says it was basically fair use and real names were never used.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: EA is mad in games, though.
[SPEAKER_14]: They have a lot of historic teams that use stats, attributes, and other factors for fantasy players.
[SPEAKER_14]: They're close to the real-life counterparts, but not exact.
[SPEAKER_14]: Or so EA claims.
[SPEAKER_14]: So I don't play these games, so it's hard for me to take an opinion on this one way or the other.
[SPEAKER_14]: But the judge certainly felt they had a case, so it could be very interesting to see how this plays out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Hmm.
[SPEAKER_14]: That's it for our tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_14]: But that also brings us to the end of the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: But not before I ask for any last-minute stories from Loki or DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_14]: I'm good.
[SPEAKER_14]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_14]: All right.
[SPEAKER_14]: Well, shit, we're done then.
[SPEAKER_14]: We're out.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's do a last-minute... Let me do my last-minute kind of plea here.
[SPEAKER_14]: We are, of course, a free show, and we do this every week for nothing.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't charge you guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: We don't have ads in the show or ads on our website.
[SPEAKER_14]: All we ask is that you tell a friend or two or 50 about the show.
[SPEAKER_14]: Help us spread the word by leaving a nice review on a website such as iTunes or wherever you found this podcast or help tell people and spread the word about OLR because you'll help our little OLR army grow and we really appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_14]: Let's go around and get everybody's final thought tonight.
[SPEAKER_14]: Loki, why don't you start us off?
[SPEAKER_13]: I think it's ironic that Volition or THQ or Saints Row's April Fool's show was for a new thing, a DLC that actually sounded cooler than the DLC that they put out.
[SPEAKER_13]: Haha.
[SPEAKER_13]: Joke's on you.
[SPEAKER_13]: Your DLC sucked.
[SPEAKER_13]: And I didn't buy the last two bits of it.
[SPEAKER_13]: Also, read Ready Player One.
[SPEAKER_13]: You can do it.
[SPEAKER_13]: You won't be able to put it down.
[SPEAKER_14]: my final thought for tonight is I'm excited that it's taco night because it's sure to be better than that shit taco I had at Chevy's on Monday just saying that was a pretty who puts fucking mayonnaise on a taco what right it was cilantro mayonnaise is gross hated it DarkSakura how about your final thought
[SPEAKER_10]: Um, I really have to give, uh, the, uh, April Fool's award to, uh, Google for Google Quest.
[SPEAKER_14]: Yeah, we didn't even bring that up tonight, but that was amazing.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_10]: And I love the little commercial blowing in the cartridge and everything.
[SPEAKER_14]: I loved the Easter eggs of like the little landmarks being, and there's a whole list on Reddit of like all the different hidden landmarks.
[SPEAKER_14]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_14]: I loved it.
[SPEAKER_14]: They used all the Dragon Quest art in it.
[SPEAKER_14]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_10]: and the YouTube collection.
[SPEAKER_14]: Oh yes, I saw that.
[SPEAKER_10]: That was great.
[SPEAKER_14]: Alright, well that's it guys.
[SPEAKER_14]: Thank you so much for tuning in to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_14]: We'll be back another week and next week it won't be April Fools anymore so it'll be a little more serious but we can still be a little silly tonight, right?
[SPEAKER_14]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_16]: That does it for another episode of Orange Lounge Radio Live Orange Lounge Radio Live is an Orange Lounge Radio production For more information about our station, visit our website at www.orangeloungeradio.com And now, here is your fortune cookie message of the day
[SPEAKER_16]: God damn!
[SPEAKER_12]: Ow, my foot!
[SPEAKER_12]: Why did I shoot myself in my foot?
[SPEAKER_12]: Oh my god, it hurts so bad!
[SPEAKER_12]: No, my foot!
[SPEAKER_12]: I need that for walking!
[SPEAKER_12]: Somebody once told me what having a baby felt like.
[SPEAKER_10]: Giving birth sucks and I'm never going to do it.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's why they cut open your stomach and pull the damn kid out.
[SPEAKER_12]: It's just like, what the hell's the point?
[SPEAKER_12]: It's like trying to shove a piano through a door when there's a perfectly good window right there.
[SPEAKER_12]: I don't see the point.
[SPEAKER_10]: And that's why men will never have babies.
[SPEAKER_16]: The genius of Loki on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_16]: Thank you very much for listening and we'll see you next week.