Orange Lounge Radio
These are hosts, Dark Sakura, Sky and Lowkey
Tonight April 8th, 2012
Capcom responds to Better Business Bureau complaints
Sex offenders get booted from Xbox Live in one state
And our listeners sound off
Is EA really the worst company ever?
Orange Lounge Radio
Hello my friends out there on the internet
And welcome back to another week of the show
Where every gamer has a voice
Orange Lounge Radio
We are live for this April 8th of 2012
With episode number 453 of our show
My name is Rob Roberts
And I'll be joining you over the next few hours
Not with Dark Sakura
Or Jamie Summers, sadly
She is not here tonight
We had to make a last minute cancellation tonight
Because she's not feeling well
So we hope she feels better
She's got like a science fiction double feature
She has a sinus infection double feature
Her sinus infection could be science fictional
It could be
She sounded like hell
Let's just put it that way
She sounded like goddamn hell
And you did not want her on the show tonight
Also, Tech Master Lowkey
Is not here tonight
He's doing Easter stuff
With his Jewish wife
I don't know how that works
Jesus, Jesus, Jesus
No, I
It's obviously a holiday for the family
So they're doing stuff with their kid
And all that
So there's no Dark Sakura
There's no Lowkey
But there's me
Rob Roberts
And obviously you can hear over there
My loud ass
Interrupting
Excuse me, Alan
You dropped
I keep forgetting you dropped your handle
A couple weeks ago
It's too mouthy and wordy to say
Alright, well how you doing Alan?
I'm good
Alright
I haven't been on the show in a long time
You haven't
So I'm glad we have an opportunity
To have you on
Again tonight
Yes
For the listeners who haven't heard you
Why don't you give us a quick introduction
About yourself
And the types of games you like
And all that
Mid 30's
Been playing since the Atari 2600
Favorite console is the Super NES
Right now I'm playing a lot of PC games
Dragon Age, Orange
Dragon Age
Oranges
Not Oranges
Which would be weird
Mass Effect
And so on
Alright
And we live together
So
That's right
So you get to see me all the time
Yes
Alright
Um
We have to have a third co-host obviously
The Orange Country doesn't work without three co-hosts
Insert Ferret here
Alright
Say hello everybody
Welcome back
By the way to VX JasonXV
Or just Jason if you will
Is back with us tonight
Three weeks
Uh
Quite a better turnaround
Than the eight years that we were going on
About previously
I was gonna say
For somebody who lives in Denver
That's really good to be able to get to a show
Three weeks
It's like I got home on the train
Turned around
Took another one
And hey I'm back
Which is actually what happened
Pretty much
But now I don't know how much I can and can't say on the show
But I think I'm okay saying
You were trying to get like a job thing
Out here
And you got it
Yay
Congrats
So that's why you're back
Last time I was out here for my interview
And I'm still
I'm still kind of giving the company the chance to
Announce it because they make a pretty big deal out of it
But yeah I got the job offer
Monday night
I took Tuesday to pack and wrap up things at home
And tell my other job
Peace out guys
I'm on a train tomorrow
Love to give you two weeks
Two weeks notice
But that's not happening
So Monday
Monday night
Solidified everything
Tuesday night
Tuesday in general
Finished off everything that I needed to do
Wednesday morning on the train
And I've been here since
Just after business hours on Thursday
But there were no snakes on the train
So we're good
There were no snakes on the train
Alright that's good
That's good
Well welcome back
I'm glad you're able to be here
Especially on a week where we need a lot of people
But you have the
You have an awesome radio voice
So I'm happy you get to kind of step up and be a co-host tonight
So some folks might be wondering like
Well why
Okay Rob why would you do a show without Dark Sakura
And without Loki
And you know well
With no slight to Alan or Jason
Who are fine step in hosts tonight
But you know it is a little weird
That there's only one of the regular OLR hosts here
But remember guys
It is the show where every gamer has a voice
And it's not necessarily just about me
Or just about Jamie
Or just about Loki
It's about you guys
So we want to make sure that we would have a show here
And a place where you guys can interact
And still chat with us
I have to say I did take some inspiration
A little bit from what's going on over at Video Game Outsiders
Which is another show on the All Games Network that I listen to
And poor John's been holding down the fort over there for a while
Because his two co-hosts have had just other stuff going on
But they still do the show every week
So there's no reason we can't
We're actually not going to be here next week
That was a pre-planned thing
So we knew that Loki would be out tonight
But we thought Dark Sakura would be here
But of course people get sick
That happens
But we knew we would not be here next week
And we didn't want to go two weeks in a row with no show
So we have the show going tonight
And you guys can chat live with us
chat.orangeloungeradio.com
And AlphaKanandagram starts us off in the chatroom tonight saying
Yay weird show! Fuck yes!
Aww, but you guys
More like Brorange Lounge Radio, right?
I don't want you guys to feel like it's the weird show
I mean obviously Jason, you've been our webmaster for years and years
And you played Bamani games just like Dark Sakura, Loki and I did
Just at a different arcade
So I know you followed that scene probably longer than we did
But you were in all that stuff
And Alan, well Alan's cool too
Right
Alright, before we get into How Was Your Gaming Week and all that tonight
I thought we could talk a little bit about not just the weird oddities
Of having only one of the regular hosts here
But I mentioned next week we were going to not be here
Because I have a pre-planned trip
We're going to Disneyland, which I know shock and awe, dying of shock
Alan's coming with me of course because he does that
And we're going to the final ever electronica
But for those who didn't know, they turned California Adventure into
Like this whole, they turned a part of it, not the whole damn park
But they turned a little part of it into The Grid on like Friday and Saturday nights
And they did this back when the Tron Legacy movie first came out in theaters
And it got extended several times
I think it was only supposed to run for about 6 months the first time
It's been extended to like 18 months or even longer now
It's been about a year and a half since that movie came out
But one of the other cool things, and I know we've talked about it on the show before
Is that electronica also has a replica of Flynn's arcade from the movie
With classic 80's video games that are in great condition
Because you know it's Disneyland, they're not going to let shitty run down games into their park
And the one time I have seen a broken machine there
They had a dude out there fixing it in like 5 seconds
So we're going to go say goodbye to electronica
Because you know they made a business decision to get rid of it
Because Tron the movie again is a year and a half old now
We don't know if they're going to be doing a sequel
Although there is the anime that's supposed to be out in summer or fall
So it seems weird to me that they're not going to have awareness for that
But they're replacing it with the mad tea party
And that's tea as in just the letter T
Not as in a sippy drink that British people have at lunchtime
Where's failed trombone? Do you have it queued up?
I can get failed trombone queued up
It's too late
Why are you
And you're upset about the mad tea party
Like you're personally offended right
We saw that movie and I didn't think it was going to be very good
And you were very optimistic
It'll be okay it's Tim Burton and it was shitty
I didn't like it at all
I know some people were into it but no I didn't like it at all
But here's the thing and the reason why I bring it up
Is that unfortunately with electronica changing over to the mad tea party
They're going to close Flynn's arcade
Now supposedly the mad hatter is supposed to have some type of arcade
But I don't believe that means he's keeping the 80's retro games
From what I hear they're supposed to be like skee-ball
And it's what happened to every other arcade from the 80's
They're now birthday kid palace
Where the machines spit tickets and all that stuff
Although I heard the mad tea party won't even give you tickets
It's just playing skee-ball for the sake of playing skee-ball
Which is weird and absurd to me but whatever
Disney Imagineers if you want to listen to me for a very awesome idea
You should fix the bootsy run down arcade off of space mountain
And put Flynn's arcade there
And it will be super awesome
Exactly and tomorrow lands a great fit for it
Or just fucking bulldoze interventions
Cause who goes in the interventions building like ever
And just make a giant Tron grid
It would only cost like $11 billion and it would be amazing
But my hope is, here's my secret hope
I have a secret wish hope pie in the sky idea
And that is that maybe if we go to the last electronica
They're going to give away some of the arcade games
You get an arcade machine
Everybody gets an arcade machine
In reality that fucking won't happen
Because I think they're leasing them from a local company
That specializes in this shit
But hold on I want my idea
I want my pie in the sky idea
And that is that they're going to give away these machines
So I was thinking about if you could have a retro arcade machine in your house
What arcade machine would you want to have in your house
If you could have something from Flynn's Arcade in your house
What game would you want
This is a tough one
Cause there's a lot of like great games
And part of me wants to say Dig Dug
Cause I'm actually pretty good at that one
Part of me wants to say BurgerTime
Because I damn near bought a-
I came so fucking close to buying a BurgerTime machine
Like not even a couple months ago
And then I realized I live in an apartment
And that would be a really shitty idea
To bring an arcade machine into the apartment
But you saw when I saw that BurgerTime machine Alan right
I was like I could forego getting an iPad
Your BurgerTime machine
And you're just rolling your eyes in the back of your head
But I think the machine I would really really want to have
I don't know why it's just
Is a spy hunter machine
Any of the racing games from that era
Cause they all had different like variety of pedals
Switches, different steering wheels
Like All Points Bulletin was actually one of my favorites
From that time period
Or at least that's how my brain seems to relate it
I think I just have a lot of memories of Spy Hunter as a kid
Because that's what they had
Okay shut up
It was at the local roller rink
That's where all the arcade games from my youth came from too
It was that or the pizza parlor
Pizza parlor was like a sit down
Either like a joust or a galaga or something like that
One of the two sided top sitting
It's probably a name for that I don't know what it is
So I want a Spy Hunter machine
I want Oprah to give me a Spy Hunter machine at the last electronica
Jason what arcade machine would you want?
You know I had one in mind
And then my brain replaced it with Neo Geo
So I kind of forgot what it was entirely
Not just Light Cycle Tron
But one of the I think it was like the
Movie Tron arcade machines
There were two Tron machines
There was Tron
It was just called Tron
And then there was Discs of Tron
And did that have
I think there's even a third one
Because there should have been one that had like the assault on the MCP and tanks
Tron was made up of four mini games
And I think you're just thinking they're all separate games
Wasn't Tron originally just a Light Cycles game?
That's one of the mini games
It's just the most popular one
There was Light Cycle game
There's the MCP cone
There's the tanks
And there's
I would probably say Discs of Tron
Discs of Tron
I would not mind more time with that game
I've only played it like once or twice
And it looked really good
It was very engaging
It was really fun
Alan, if you could steal one machine out of Flynn's arcade
Or excuse me, have Oprah give you one
Gift you one
What would you want her to give you?
Well I don't think it's in Flynn's arcade
But if I had to have a vintage cabinet in my house
It would have to be multiplayer
And it would have to have large cabinets
To set drinks on
And I would go with Golden Axe
Because that game is amazing
I think Golden Axe is better left in my memory
Like every time I've played Golden Axe
Not to just take a crap on what Alan said
Not this shitty port that was on Genesis
And is currently on XBLA or whatever
But the original arcade Golden Axe
With three people
It was a good time
It was good memories
God damn that goblin
Attack faster, come on
Awesome comments from our chat room
Chat.orangelaungeradio.com
Because everybody's joining in in the chat room
Love this
DDRdollabill says
Robotron2084 would be his game
Hands bloody fucking down
Brad from Pod Culture
Love this answer
This is one I would want too
Fucking Star Wars the arcade game
Good call
I completely forgot about that
I'm not even like a Star Wars aficionado
And all that
I mean I like the movies
I don't like obsess over them
I'm more of a Trekkie than a Warsie
But the arcade game
Was so fucking good
Is that the Vectrex one?
Yes
Did you know there was an Empire Strikes Back of that?
There was
I don't remember how official it was
But a buddy of mine that has a bunch of arcade machines down in his basement
Has it on a little
Not a ROM switcher but a cart switcher
And I was completely unaware that there was essentially a second Star Wars arcade
There was
It was a little more complicated
But yes there was one
It was pretty awesome
Let's see
Tigerclaw on chat says
If they did that
Meaning handing out the arcade games
Rob would scream like a schoolgirl if he won an actual arcade
But then he'd be like
Wait a minute how am I supposed to get this thing out of here
I would tie it to the roof of my Honda
I don't even care
Go driving down by five
Catching all the bugs
Jim Sally says
Burger Time all the way
Burger Time for the win
Yeah I was almost there too
Stan says
Pac-Man but the small table version
Where both players sit at opposite ends of each other
A cocktail machine
Cocktail machine
Oh my god I'd love to have a cocktail machine
Those are hard to come by though
Cocktail machines are really sought after
Isn't that new Pac-Man game that came out that was incredibly expensive
That's the latest cocktail cabinet
It was definitely inspired by cocktail machines
Yeah I know it's not Pac-Man Championship Edition
But like an arcade
Pac-Man Battle Royale
I remember it had a funny name
And it's in Vegas and like New York and no where else or something
My Dave and Busters in Colorado had it
It was really fun
Rama says
Magic Sword
Oh good fucking call I love that one
That was the one they had at Round Table Pizza
That I would just play the shit out of
Pork Chop says
APB is awesome
Brad from Pod Culture also says
The original Gauntlet would be hella awesome
There's a good multiplayer game too
So good calls all around
Love the classic arcade game suggestions
We're going to be very sad when Electronica closes
But our plan
There's actually like a group of us going
Like I'm meeting up there with some of my friends from Warcraft
Nerd nerd
Some of my DDR friends from back in the day
Mel and Mel
Mr. Mel B who was a big DDR freestyler back in the day
Is going with us
It's going to be good
And our plan is to at the end of all of it
Yell end of line and then collapse into tears
Drunken tears
And I want to see Laser Man because I still haven't seen that shit
Laser Man will be there from what I understand
So there you go
Hey Dark Soccer joined our chat room
Hello Dark Soccer and said Dave and Busters in Roseville has it
So if you want to go play Pac-Man Battle Royale there you go
We haven't been there since
We haven't been there in a while
Yeah I think it's one of those things that's going to become a staple of Dave and Busters
Because it's not redemption but it kind of feels like it
And it's just a quick engaging game of Pac-Man
I'm thinking Dark Soccer should have a local birthday thingy thingy at Dave and Busters
Wink wink nudge nudge with her two gay besties
If nothing else
Should have a Dave and Busters night
That would be fun wouldn't it Alan?
Yes
Alright
Anyhow that's enough for our reminiscing and retro arcade games
And we will not be here again next week
Our pal Bobby Black Wolf who we are usually after
At All Games Radio where we do tape live every Sunday night right after his show
At 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern
He's been off for the past two weeks
He will be back next week
So at least live folks you have something to look forward to
Our 9 cast of course also live on Sunday nights
They will still be doing their thing
They've been constant over the past few weeks
So there will at least be those shows to look forward to but no OLR
We'll try to find a best up from the archives for you live folks
Maybe a rarity
I just came across a stockpile of episodes that aren't even up on the OLR archive
So maybe I'll dig one of those up and play that next week
It'll be fun
Meanwhile let's talk about our gaming weeks
And how was your gaming week?
I would usually say ladies first but there are no ladies
So Alan since you're within kicking range
Kick kick go
How was your gaming week?
I've been playing the Mass Effect trilogy
Inspired mostly in part by all of the wank
I got mad and bullshit over the ending of Mass Effect 3
I've had the first two games in my steam account thanks to those crazy sales
So I was like I'm gonna play these things and hopefully get to 3 at some point if I can buy it
So two or three weeks ago I beat Mass Effect 1 on both Paragon and Renegade
Which is sort of goody two shoes good guy and asshole good guy
And now I'm playing Mass Effect 2 and I'm ready to beat it
Like I just started the end game mission that's all very intense
The characters die and I had to save and quit to do the show
So we are literally taking you away from doing Mass Effect right now
Yes but that's all I've been playing for the last week
It's probably good to have a break once in a while
Microphone extension cords and headphones
No we need him to focus
He needs to be funny because we don't have Loki or Darth Sock tonight
So unless you want to be funny he has to bring the funny
Alright so that's it for you Mass Effect, Mass Effect and more Mass Effect
Now what are you going to do? Are you going to buy the third game or are you going to try to play the second one over again?
Well I'm doing my goody two shoes play through right now
So once I beat that then I'll load up my female femshep
And she's just like fuck you, fuck you, kill everybody and save the universe
And I don't give a shit because that's how she rolls
That's another 40 or 50 hours of gameplay
DarkSakura sent me her gaming week through proxy and she wants you all to know that she played a shitload of Portal 2 this past week
What a shock, yet has she touched that copy of Mass Effect I loaned her?
No
That's alright, Portal 2 is a pretty kickass game
Alright, Jason how was your gaming week?
Well as I kind of started to say at the top of the show
The first half of the week almost didn't exist for me with trying to get back out here
But I did load down my iPad for the train with games and I just kind of picked up some old favorites of mine
Death Rally has a modern iOS remake which is really fun
I picked that up again and started working through the missions again
Jetpack Joyride and then a couple of silly little things like Sudoku type games
Pickris type games
And I feel like I'm missing something significant but considering that consoles weren't really in the mix I don't think I was
Sometimes you have to game on the go
Yeah
And when you have 33 hours to do nothing but sit there and bounce to the left and to the right and back and forth and stumble through a narrow corridor
By which I just mean a train in real life
Yes, certainly
Go to our chatroom at chat.orangelandtrader.com
There's a lot of people talking about Mass Effect and lots of people getting into Mass Effect
AcidicVampire says everyone should play the Mass Effect series, end of story
A lot of folks saying they got the Steam deals going on there
Let's see, Dark Soccer is yelling at me saying girl I'm on my PC unless somebody wants to buy me Mass Effect 1 on Steam
Tigerclaw said I bought Mass Effect and Mass Effect 2 for $3.60 but you may want to wait until BioWare releases the patch that will fix the face import bug
Which is set to be released next week
Which is great because I won't get to Mass Effect 3 before next week so I will never have known that that was ever a problem
I just had someone on my Facebook a couple hours ago post that they finally beat Mass Effect 3
And of course they've already had the perspective of all the wank about the ending for the last two weeks
To I guess if they wanted to be pretentious and rise above that
And they said I have a lot of questions and it's not confusing at all and it's not really wrapped up into a neat little bow but they were satisfied with it
So they were like I don't get it, I don't get the rage
I heard it's one of those endings that makes you madder the more you think about it
So like maybe he's not mad today but next week he'll be like raging internet angry
Or 3am
WAIT WHAT
Waking up in a cold sweat DAMN YOU
I'm prepared to be let down by the ending of Mass Effect 3 but just the adventure from Mass Effect 1 and even I'm about halfway through Mass Effect 2 right now
Well I don't want to say 2 is so much better because 1 was awesome but if the last 20 minutes of the endgame rashetty for the whole trilogy
That franchise in my opinion has given me at least 100 hours of quality emotional rewarding gameplay
So it's not a waste of time
And of course there's going to be more DLC some of which obviously will come up a little later in the show when we get to news
So let's see my gaming week so Mass Effect for me as well just like Alan I got sucked into Mass Effect amongst all the chatter of Mass Effect 3
And Shane basically bullied me into playing Mass Effect like basically would threaten to kick me out of the WoW guild if I don't start playing Mass Effect or something like that
So I've been playing it, it's been amazing as I've talked about in previous weeks on the show
I'm just still cleaning up the loyalty missions and getting ready, I gotta catch up to where Alan's at
I have been playing a few other games though I want to tell you guys about, one of them is old and one of them is very new
The old one I want to talk about tonight is a game I got for $15 at Target it was on clearance
I might be partially responsible for this
Yes you were kind of an enabler you were like hey you should get this it's $15 and it has dance in it you'll like it
And I pick up the box and I'm like I think I heard about this game and I heard it was really basic
And I looked at the song list I'm like well if it's basic it still has a really great song list so I pick up a game called Dance Paradise
Which was $15 which was one of the early Kinect games
Is that THQ or Ubisoft?
I want to say it's THQ that did this one
Here's the thing Dance Paradise it has a really good song list
It's got like Lady Gaga it's kind of a euro infused song list it's like songs I think that were bigger a little bit bigger on the other side of the pond
Because you got things like Jerry Halliwell and nobody cared about the Spice Girls in America once they split up
But you know you got Lady Gaga you got a few Rihanna it's basically gay bar in a box right
And you know it's going to be good music because it's gay bar in a box and it's a great song list don't get me wrong
And it's also really cool because you get the little music videos actually play in the background while you're playing which not every game has
That was pretty cool but it's just it was so fucking basic like I don't know how else to describe this game
Like and the way you play it is really stupid like
Because you have to take a you start in the center and then to do a certain dance move you have to take a step to the left to do it
And then a step to the right and it's not the time warp
Yes exactly you jump to the left and step to the right but it's like Lady Gaga you're dancing to
Imagine it looks like rock band where you have like the four columns that notes fall down
Well you have to literally walk into each column in order to do the move and instead of falling notes you have falling dance moves
So maybe you're like doing a little disco or you're opening your arms back and forth or you know kind of a lot of the same stuff you see in Dance Central
But the fact that you move back for like who designed that that's just like that's not even that it's so weird
For those who play connect in a loft giant warehouse floor for all the room you need to play it
But here's the other thing that kind of disappointed me is that there was a good game in there somewhere
Because one of the things that was really cool about it was that some of the moves that you did mimicked the dance moves in the video
And I thought well that's that's a good thing to see in a music game is like learn to do the dance from the video that was really cool
Because Dance Central doesn't really even do that right and that's the king of the crop
You might see some like you'll definitely see like like for um oh
There's a little bit of booty and baby got back
Yeah there's that and then what the hell's that oh what's the goblin male dance what's that
Soulja Boy tell us
Soulja Boy okay thank you isn't it sad that that's how we communicate
We have problems
And unfortunately I know wow just enough to understand that too now
Okay Soulja Boy you do that dance in Dance Central so some of the big ones are there
But it doesn't like match the music video because Dance Central doesn't have the music videos
And Dance Central is still a lot of fun I mean it doesn't really matter
It kind of bothers me that like you have you have really good licenses and a really kick-ass song list in Dance Paradise
And then what was the other big competitor to Dance Central that came out
Dance Masters
Dance Masters the Konami game Dance Masters is actually beautifully put together if you think about it
It's just para para of Kinect right
Or even not not exactly there are three or four there are three or four
Wow
There are three or four songs on the list that are Eurobeat and do have para para routines
But everything else to the extent of my knowledge completely original
But it really is like fully fledged dance minus walking around a stage because Kinect is narrow tracking
A lot of them were like crossovers from DDR though they had a lot of DDR crossovers
Oh yeah everything was Konami original period
But the ones that weren't para para were very the routines were actually well they were fun to watch
Because I haven't exactly learned them yet but they were fun to watch
But there was some really weird weird crossovers though because like I remember one of the songs was Exotic Ethnic
Which I was trying to find in my my archive here but it's like it's not really a song you can dance to
I mean it's a DDR song it's a great DDR song because the way DDR structured
But now that we're kind of beyond the dance pad and in the whole like free movement
Exotic Ethnic doesn't make a very good dancey song
The routine from what I recall the little bits and pieces it like the song the song on DDR was like 200 beats per minute
I found it here we go so you can kind of see what this looks like here and hear this song and like see the routine
And realize it doesn't really work very well
What is up with the backup dancers this is like pg-13 here look at this
But anyway it's not a very like it's a good song like it was great back in the DDR days
But like to like freestyle move it's weird and it doesn't really like make sense
So here's the thing you've got a great interface and a great shell not even just dance masters
But say rhythm party right the game that just came out on Xbox Live Arcade
But not even the Bimani community seems to care about at this point
It's actually a really well put together game and I've said that for weeks on the show
There's a Bimani community
Yeah well you know what I mean I think there's a Bimani community
What's left of it? What's left of it?
So you've got that and then you have to it's like they need to learn something from each other
If you had rhythm party with Dance Paradise's song list you would have an amazing music game
Or if you had you know something that if Konami would just take the risk and license more than literally three licensed songs
Or if you know THQ would take the risk and spend a little more time designing a game that people actually want to play
And not just relying on the music to sell your game
If they would both take that risk there could be a legit competitor to Dance Central which kind of has both
But unfortunately both of them are looking to cash in a lot cheaper and don't want to take that financial risk which I can understand
Konami a lot of these a lot of these companies that are producing these are when it comes to music and rhythm
In my opinion they're mostly all on like the second tier
And Konami as far as American and European releases minus DDR has pretty much become that
Has gotten to that has driven themselves down to that point as well
Oh yeah
Notably starting with Rock Revolution
Harmonix is now the top tier
Harmonix is absolutely the top tier and Konami is now under them
Absolutely I would sign on to that
It's too bad but there you go
Anyhow so that was my big bloated Dance Paradise of a year and a half old game Dance Paradise there you go
And that was your gaming week
One other game I'm sorry I have to say it quickly quickly there's a new pinball game that came out on Xbox Live Arcade
And I don't even remember the name of it it's just called like pinball I think
Arcade pinball or something
Here's the thing though it's a bunch of classic tables it's it's the guys that made the like Williams pinball collection
And the Stern pinball collection like those games have already been out
They just basically ported it to Xbox Live Arcade but I see what they're doing they're piecemealing it
Because the game itself comes with four tables
It's four damn good tables it's Ripley's Believe It or Not which is a great table
Arabian Nights and Theater of Magic and Black Hole are all great tables
So it's like 800 Microsoft points for four like killer tables and then they're gonna do DLC later like Pinbot
The thing that they have that Pinball FX doesn't have is licenses
They're licensed with Stern and Williams so they're gonna get all those tables into their game
But if you already own the collections that came out on Xbox previously
I don't see the reason to get this whatsoever
But for those that missed it and want their game a little cheaper and more piecemeal
If you like pinball there's some great tables in there
And I don't remember Theater of Magic being in the collection so it's pretty cool that at least that game is there
Or if you're named Dark Soccer and just have all the tables in your house anyways
This may also not be for you as cheap as it as it is by comparison
Well I want to say Ripley's Believe It or Not was one of their like sought after tables that they wanted
So they can do a virtual version of it on the Xbox 360
Pinball Arcade says Zethur in the chatroom at chat.orangesauceradio.com
I knew it had a very very basic name to it so Pinball Arcade that's the name of it
Medieval Madness is DLC says Zethur and I know I saw Pinbot in the list which is one of my favorites
And you know they'll kind of do that so you know Pinball FX I like it a lot
It's got some great original tables
I'm glad to see there's a little healthy competition now with both of them being out there
And especially if you're a pinball fan it's a win-win situation
So you know if you somehow missed the collection last time this is definitely worth checking out
Alright now I'm done with my gaming week
Housekeeping check us out on Twitter twitter.com slash o-l-r
Of course always our website orangesauceradio.com
If you want to find more of the OL Army members check it out in the upper right hand corner
At orangesauceradio.com there's a box called Extended Play where you can find us on Steam
You can find us at Last.fm
Lots of places to play with other cool folks who are not going to be a jerk
Because you know the number one rule of the OL Army is don't be a dick
Because there's so many dicks ruining the game experience on Xbox Live Arcade and PlayStation Network
We want to be different than that
There you go
Alright let's get into some actual gaming news
Jason why don't you start us off tonight
Harmonix has come full circle once again and is returning to its roots of a frequency amplitude inspired type of game
Again taken from the Rock Band franchise that they've been so excellent with over the past 5 years? 6 years?
I actually don't even know what year they really started with it anymore
They're returning to a frequency style layout with some very notable differences
There was a very famous point in amplitude and frequencies history where you could learn the exact track that you have to make to get the absolute max score
And Harmonix has responded to this by making Rock Band Blitz a slightly simpler game
One track per instrument and it was either 2 or 3 targets per instrument
I forget which
But the power ups aren't as track specific, the video is talking about a multi-measure automatic note auto player
And then there was like a wrecking ball that kind of bounced around tracks in a diagonal manner picking up notes along the way
And there's also no concept of a combo that you have to continually go on one measure to the next to extend the combo
And you can actually just jump from instrument to instrument and apparently it'll go a long way towards making a slightly unique sound
A slightly unique emphasis or you could just sit on your favorite instrument and play it the whole night
It sounds like it's going to use your entire back catalog so if you've been playing since Rock Band and you've imported everything from game to game
Plus all the DLC that you bought, all the Rock Band Network and what was the indie version of Rock Band Network?
That is Rock Band Network, yeah
Rock Band Store is the license, you know all that stuff
It's sounding like you should be able to have all of your official and indie content
No specific pricing and no specific import restrictions due out just yet but the game looks fun and it's always nice coming back to this style
I had a lot of fun with Rock Band Unplugged as well
It's interesting like I was partially really excited by the news, I have to admit a hint of disappointment
Because knowing that like this is the big project Harmonics has been working on
I have to express a teeny bit of disappointment because I was like oh I was kind of hoping for something new
But okay I mean it's really fucking hard to be disappointed when this sounds like a real powerhouse of a game
And the fact that it imports everything that's already on your drive, that's huge
What other company even keeps all your stuff like that anymore?
Exactly, like seriously what other company is going to give you that type of value?
Does EA own Harmonics at this point? No they don't, Harmonics is independent
They bought themselves out from MTV
I was like surely this is not behavior coming out of EA
Well that just proves Harmonics is independent
So yeah they're truly independent because they came off the MTV games, that was where they were at when Rock Band started
But just the value they're giving you there, it's so amazing coming off the weeks of us talking about how developers want to lock you out of used games altogether
Now it's like here's a game that enhances the value of all the DLC you've already bought
Like well fucking done, applause
This is, I mean I feel like an asshole for saying that I even expressed a hint of disappointment at this game
I'll definitely be picking it up day one, I mean now that I see kind of all the pieces and I'm like okay
I did like amplitude and frequency a lot, people did say they wanted a new frequency and amplitude
Even though this isn't really it, it's what they could get away with doing and know that it's going to be profitable
And so I'm excited for it, I am
I mean the way that I look at it is that we had the simple arcade style band
I'm trying to avoid the word simulation because the point is we had the arcade style music experience
And that was literally with like Guitar Freaks Dramania, the early Konami games
And then Guitar Hero came around, put it solely on the guitar
And then Rock Band came around and gave us the whole band
And then Rock Band 3 came around which gave us the pro controllers and everything else
Where you can use a no kidding digital drum kit and have an actual performing gear that you can actually plug in and use with the game
What else are they going to add into the Rock Band franchise that isn't going to be tacky as hell
And so instead to kind of go off the beaten path, whether they do something new which is hit or miss
Or they use this engine that was really fun and have all of your content like you just said
That's not a bad decision
I mean fucking how many songs have I bought on Rock Band
It is disgusting how much DLC I have on my Xbox 360
You're going to buy either a $30 or $40 game and you're going to import what $200 in content automatically
Rock Band Blitz is on Xbox Live Arcade, it's at most going to be $20
So maybe even $10
Probably less than $20
Well with 25 licensed songs or whatever it is they're doing
That in turn are going to play in Rock Band 3
Amazing!
We love you Harmonix
Who else is doing this?
You remember?
Okay remember like three years ago before Rock Band 3 came out
And they were talking about the Rock Band store
They were talking about how they wanted Rock Band to be like iTunes
Like it's iTunes for your consoles
And a lot of us kind of laughed it off and said oh yeah you're doing music
You're not the same as iTunes
iTunes is for your iPod
And downloading a song into Rock Band is not the same as iTunes
But now here we are years later
That's what they were setting the seeds for
Because now they've enhanced
You didn't just buy Rock Band DLC
You bought a song that functions in multiple ways on your console
That is starting to feel a little more like iTunes for your console, that's amazing
So like I said it's hard to be that upset
And deep down inside I kind of think
Rock Band Blitz is more of probably a side project
To something that's you know
Something that's really going on
I bet there's something else
I mean there was the iPhone stuff too
They had the vid rhythm or whatever that was called
The sampler video plus audio
Yeah the experimental thing
And maybe there'll be something else at E3 this year
Because they've announced this in time for PAX obviously
And you know we're showing it on the floor there
Maybe they've got something else to show at E3
Maybe they're working on something for the next wave of consoles
Maybe it's something for the Wii U, who knows
So again my disappointment is like one grain of sand
In a oh my god I can't wait to eat this delicious cake
It's gonna be amazing
And actually if anybody's interested
I believe they're based out of Massachusetts
When I was job hunting a couple people pushed me in their direction
But I didn't really want to relocate
But if you are willing to and you're interested
They actually had a lot of positions available
Anything from creative to programming to design
I think even like program management that kind of stuff
If you're interested look them up
That's all I have to say
As Rob stuffs his face full of popcorn
Dead air
I thought I had a break to eat
Bad co-host
It's alright you're learning
Learning
You have to learn how to fill in those gaps
So I can be a fat ass
You'll get there
Alright anyhow
Well let me ask Alan you've been awfully quiet on that story
I mean I know you're not like as huge in the music games as the rest of us
But surely that whole enhanced value thing is kind of making you go hmm
Yeah I've kind of been abstaining because
Rock band and that whole genre
Guitar Hero
I never really
Was into it at all
But it sounds like what they're doing with this new Blitz game is amazing so
You don't like watching your friends get drunk and sing Lady Gaga and make asses out of themselves?
Eh
You could get that before there was rock band
I don't have a smart phone with a camera to put it on Facebook so
If I can't blackmail you then
Then where's the fun in that
Alright well another game was announced just this past week
It's a game
It's a reimagining of an old game
We've seen a few of these lately
WayForward the company that brought us
What the hell did they bring?
There was another
God dammit they did blood rain
I think blood rain betrayal was one of their games they did
There's another one I was trying to think of
They are now taking over the Double Dragon franchise
I had no idea that it was up for grabs
But it makes sense
Majesco was the ones that got the Double Dragon franchise
Who had it before?
I'm trying to remember
Trade West
Maybe Midway had it and it was one of the things that went under
When they went under
But Majesco got the Double Dragon franchise
So it's being reinvented as
Double Dragon Neon
Which is going to come out on Xbox Live
And Playstation Network
Why did they call it Double Dragon Neon?
Well because it is
80's-tastic
The colors
The colors are the best
around
Hopefully that can be in the game
But I don't know. There is a trailer
Let me play some of this for you
Because it does have some nice remix music
And you can notice
The way the characters move
Is very fluid and all that
You know it looks really nice
In HD
Yeah that is pretty
Beyond pastel-tastic
Yeah and everybody is very 80-infused
Like you see the afros
And the leather jackets
And the boots with the fur on them and all that stuff
You know call me crazy
Or call me stupid if this already happened
But you know what I'd love to see a
Very modern remake of in this style
Captain America and the Avengers
Well especially when there is the movie and everything
But I think they did another game for that
Here is my concern with Double Dragon Neon
Okay I bought Double Dragon
When it was available on Xbox Live Arcade
It is not available anymore obviously
But it was available on Xbox Live Arcade for a short time
When you know other people had the license
We played it together and we did
We did
And then Darkstakers Dan yelled at us for trashing it
I remember that
Yes because we played through it and we were like
This game isn't very good
What the hell were we smoking when we were 12
This game sucks
And now I'm looking at this going
It looks like it's a faithful port
Of the original Double Dragon game
But Double Dragon
Maybe I'm just old but it kind of gets old
After the first stage
You're like punch punch
Kick kick kick and I'm over it
What Double Dragon
Founded Final Fight made better
And I'd rather play that
But even playing Final Fight now
Playing any of those old fighting games just doesn't feel the same
Better dudes
They're all the same
It would be cool if they could incorporate some of what we see
In new fighting games a little bit
Maybe more like versus
And special moves and combo attacks
Oh god
Don't give them ideas
But I will
I'll at least check out the demo
So that's coming out this summer
So what you're saying is
You want them to bring back that mode from
Tekken Tag Tournament
Actually that mode kicked ass
So yes I want them to bring that back
It was a little bit more fun
Because there was the entire moveset
And a little bit more depth to a side scroller
And you could play it as panda
And the concept of a fighting game where a panda bear
Beats up everyone
Is pretty fucking awesome you have to admit
I think they brought that out it's just not a side scroller
Oh right!
Wow did
Panda kills everyone
Anyhow
Wow reference number 5 today
Keep that number going
Yeah sorry
Sorry guys
So for Pokemon fans and SRPG fans
Nintendo of America
Is bringing Pokemon
And Nobunaga's
Ambition
What?
Nobunaga's Ambition
Nobunaga
Cowabunga
Cowabunga?
They're bringing that to the US
Called Pokemon Conquest
And it's coming out on June 18th
And you play a warlord
Who has a Pokemon
PAL and you have to build up your army
And it's skirmish based and it's an SRPG
And if you follow import games
And
You're a fan of
Nobunaga's Ambition
This is great
You know I remember when I heard
That this game was coming out in Japan
Like what a weird fucking idea
And to hear that this game
Is actually coming out here
I have mixed emotions
Look I get it
Pokemon has it's rabid fan base
That will buy almost anything that ties into Pokemon
Like I'm totally
Like I understand that fine
But how on earth
Does the US get
Pokemon and Nobunaga's Ambition
Relatively close to the Japanese release
You know within a year yes I would call close
To this yet we had to pull
Out fucking teeth to get
Xenoblade
Is this an
Example of maybe
I mean I guess technically it wasn't
A Nintendo game because Tecmo designed it
Maybe that's the key difference
Because Pokemon just shits
Money and it's the Pokemon factor
I mean it's
Even if the whole feudal warlord fails
To grab onto people it can still be
Propped up and kept afloat
At least a little bit more with something like
Oh I don't know a Pokemon franchise
Which is insanely popular
As opposed to a
I'm not going to say an underground favorite
But definitely a less trafficked
Series in the Zen of Years
Zen of Sagas and of course
Why?
I understand why they changed the name
Because you don't exactly have your
Raving Nobunaga Ambition fans here
In the US I mean there was that
They had like a few of them on the NES
Like Nobunaga and Romance of the
Three Kingdoms and some of that but
That series has kind of been deader than dead here
For years or at least I think it exists on the
PC it definitely has like a cult
Following but nothing mainstream
So I get why they
Changed the name but you know there's going to be those purists
Though there's always some goddamn purist who's
Going to be like why couldn't they just call
It Pokemon Nobunaga
They think it's they dumbed it down for stupid Americans
Stupid Americans
Get off your goddamn horse
They changed it for Americans indeed
Yes they did change it for Americans
Because we don't have like two
New Nobunaga Ambition games coming
Out on consoles every year like they do
In Japan wake up
It's fucking amazing this game
Is coming out here in the first place that's basically my point
And it sounds like it has six on six
Battles and
Battle conditions can change on every turn
Keeping players on their toes in anticipation
Of what will happen next
Me me me me me me
Fancy pants reading of the quote
And this article from Scott Moffett
Nintendo of America's executive vice president
Of sales and marketing
Pokemon fans are always
Interested in playing in new
Environments and experiencing new
Adventures. Pokemon conquest
Gives them an entirely new way
To enjoy this beloved series
With exciting new settings
Fierce battles and nearly 200
Pokemon to team up with
Read that first phrase again in that quote
Real quick. In that voice or normally?
Whatever you want
Pokemon fans are always interested
In playing in new environments
And experiencing new adventures
Okay okay you know what that translates to?
Pokemon fans will open up their wallets
And give us all their- They will buy fucking everything
They will buy any fucking thing that we put
In front of them and they will like it
If this was something that we were
That we were you know head over heels
Interested in we have a quote
For this too
Shut up and take my money!
Exactly. As I screw up the quote the first time
I got it
But I know people like that
Shane's like that
He probably has his pre-order in already
Not that there's anything wrong with that
Alright let's go on to the next story
Was that mine? I'm keeping up
I swear. My computer isn't though
Um
Max Payne is being brought out
Again and being adapted to
IOS was this one
I think this one uh yeah an Android
Version is actually gonna come a couple of weeks later
The current rumor says that
Max Payne for IOS is going to
Come out on April 12th I believe that
Is Wednesday of this coming week
As to
Be expected it's gonna- The game is gonna be
Scaled down and adapted so that you can get your
Bullet time portable on
Purely on screen controls no talk
About any kind of a controller or anything to do
That but you can start diving around
And rolling around and uh
Falling off the- Oh what was that
Scene where you were going in like a drug
Crazed and you had that terrible
Walkway to navigate against that's gonna be
Really really bad with touch controls
Most ports are really really bad
With touch controls that's what
Makes the story interesting because like
I- That was the other game
I didn't mention in my gaming week is that um
Midway read
For the 200th time
Re-released their whole classic arcade game machine
Uh, classic arcade game compilation
And I picked it up in all the packs
So I have um
YARV, Gauntlet, um
The sequel to Smash TV, same characters
Uh, I completely
Forgot what it was called but then most specifically
Like my favorite game- Total carnage!
Thank you. My favorite game with a
Mouthful of popcorn again
Total popcorn!
Like I- Like I was
Just saying one of my favorite classic games in the arcade
Was All Points Bulletin and that is
In this collection but it uses
It uses the accelerometer
Or the dryer or one of the two and it uses
You have to tilt the phone to steer
And that-
That sucks! It's like
I would have been less torn up if there
Was an optional D-pad but the fact
That it's purely tilt is just a pain in the ass
Yeah that's the- I think I have that same one
It's the like Williams collection or something it's called
I thought it was Midway specifically
It's only on my iPad it's over in the other room
I have it it's called
Midway Arcade it looks just like that right?
Okay I have it too and Spy Hunter
Speaking of that game is in the- Playing that on the train too
And it fucking sucks
Yep
Like that's not how I want to play the game Hey look there's the fork in the road
Let me get off to the left. No why are you going to the right?
No, no I said to
Crash! There are- Okay there are
Two games that are actually
Three games that are tolerable in that collection
One of them is Joust
Because think about it
In Joust you didn't have up or down
You had left, right, and flap
So that works okay because
There's only so many buttons you can- You're not going to like
Accidentally screw up and hit up left when you meant to hit
Just left because you have a fat thumb
Or any of that right? There's left, right, and flap
So Joust works surprisingly alright
The other two are Ski Ball
And that- Basketball or- Dumb little
Basketball game
Which aren't even fucking Midway games they're just
But you still get tickets from them
Exactly! You can get the virtual
Prizes from the prize stand
You know what I've learned to do to get virtual tickets
Here's your players tip for Midway Arcade
Just fucking sit there and start Ski Ball
And go, just swipe your finger
Nine times really fast, restart
I managed to get a 900 game within about
Five or six times of trying
There you go. So Max Payne this week
Android about a week and a half later
And everything else
Touch world is okay, moving on
Can I ask this real quick before we get into the
Next story? Ridgey you wanna say something?
No. Oh okay. Um
Did you hear the news around the internet this week
About how Instagram came out for Android?
Mhmm
And was suddenly bashed by
All the iPhone users everywhere that was like
Ugh
I can't believe Instagram is slumming
It up on Android
Hipstergram is now Losergram
Ugh
They need to come out with something new on the iPhone
Because I refuse to use an
App that exists on Android
What the fuck is up with that attitude?
Like I don't, where does that come from?
All the same holy wars that divide
Them in the first place. The same brainwashing
That has them upgrade a personal appliance
Every fucking nine months for $500
And they see nothing wrong with that
Same attitude. I'm gonna club
You with my iPhone if you keep talking
I'll help
But I'm not like that
I think everybody, I love it
When Android users get the same apps
Because sometimes we can still like play together
And stuff. I'm totally fine with
Android users having the apps
All my Android buddies have all the same
Words with friends hanging with friends
I'm sorry I haven't joined the
Zynga must die petition completely yet
I haven't started draw something
For that reason but I still play words with friends
Hanging with friends and scramble with friends
It's alright I'll just judge you from back here
Exactly. All the way across the table give that
Evil glare for the rest of the show
He still gives money to Zynga
I would ask Jason to host the show again
But he fucking plays Zynga games
Like he's so not cool
And then there are some other games we've
Played like there was, I can't even
Recall the name of it but there was some pool simulator
That had like 8 ball 9 ball and
Different table arrangements and that kind of stuff
And yeah those are all cross platform
And since they're asynchronous
And just alternating they work
Very well. They're very nice and they get everybody
Involved. Okay going to our chatroom at
Cat.orangeslaungeradio.com. Tigerclaw says
Sky it's Apple fanboys
They are elitists. No they're not
I'm an Apple
Fanboy and I'm the guy that buys
The iPhone every time. And your desktop is a
Windows machine
I'm by
Alan I have to tell you something
I'm by. Computeral
By portable. And you have the sense to
Skip a release before you
Upgrade. Yeah alright
So dig yourself out of that hole
Although also recall
One of the first couple of words out of my mouth
After I walked in here last time
Wow I'm in Windows world. This feels
Weird. Okay then fanboy
Do you consider, you're worse than I am clearly
Do you consider yourself an elitist?
You have to think about this. I can't
I can talk like it. I don't mean it
I mean when I was
When I had my whole phone switching
debacle I actively looked at what Sprint
Had offerings for both Android and Windows
And because I had an iPad
I was more than willing to get a different
Phone because I still had something to let
Me get done with the tools that I wanted to use
But
Sprint's selection was fucking garbage
And they have the 4S so I was like okay I'm done
I figured it out
And that's the story of how I have the
Latest phone. There you go
Alright let's
Let's go. It's not the Apple
Show. Let's move on to this story. That's my
Other show that I do. Oh that's
Right. You really do have an Apple
Show. I do. I should let you guys plug your
Podcast because he has one too. I'll let you
Do that at the start of the next half of the
Show. Alright for now
Let's talk about the Wii U
And a rumor about the Wii U
And usually I don't like to talk about rumors
Like these but it was kind of a slow news week
Because everybody was in Boston with the PAX East
Thing. Which by the way we will have some phone calls
On that later. But for now
We better. Rumors. Yeah we better
Because I didn't go this year. I'm kind of sad
Some of the other all game shows had it
Covered but you know
I might go to West Coast
This year which is really exciting so
We'll hear from the folks
That were at PAX East a little later
For now let's talk about the Wii U
Launch date
Rumor spreading around the internet like wildfire
We're talking being picked up by Eurogamer
GameSpot and so on
The rumor is the Wii U
Is out November 18th
That day sounds awfully familiar
That's
Five years later isn't it?
Didn't the Wii U launch right around that day?
Did the Wii U launch? Or did the regular Wii U launch
November 18th? I don't remember
It was just before Thanksgiving
Because it was just before I moved out of Arizona
Apparently it's coming from
A Japanese retailer email
Or something like that is where this date is coming from
So you know take it or leave it
But November 18th is the day
So
Here's my honest reaction to that
I don't think Nintendo knows the day yet
I don't think Nintendo's picked the day yet
I think Nintendo in part is
Waiting to hear what Microsoft
And Sony are doing although I guess they have to
Release a date at E3
Maybe they don't have to
I want to say they didn't announce the Wii release date till after E3
That year
I don't even remember
The Wii
Came out on November
19th of 2006
Oh so close
Well okay at least that shows that
They're aiming for the same weekend essentially
So
I would not put it past a retailer
To stub a date based off
What they saw before
To have some record in their system
So they can start saying pre-order
Pre-order give us your money
Or at least some of it
So
Yep there you go
Another day Wii U
What else can you say?
Alright moving on
So there's been a lot
Of anger over
Street Fighter X Tekken that Capcom put out
A couple weeks ago
In regards to all of the
Launch day launch week DLC
Available
That is on the disc that you have to pay to
Unlock and I know if Loki were here
He would be pitching a fit right now
Because this is obviously a thorn in his side
There have been a lot of
Better business bureau complaints
About this and Capcom has finally released a statement
It's very
Professionally coded
And groomed
To say
We're sorry you feel that way
But
We didn't do anything wrong
Nanny nanny boo boo
The first draft of that said fuck you
You fucking fucks
But that got scrapped
Yeah they rubbed it through the PR machine
Some bubbles came out
Basically they're saying that
They make sure that the majority of
Content is on the disc
There's 38 fighters to play out of the box
It doesn't matter if the DLC is available
On the day after the release date
Or three weeks
You still have to pay whatever
Five, six bucks, PSN points
Xbox Live points
To access the content
So there's no difference between
Content that's on the disc that you have to pay to unlock
Versus stuff that's downloaded later
And they're saying
That the
Disc, the product of the game
When that has to go gold
When they actually say this game is done
And then the release date which comes a couple months later
Even if that
Extra content that comes later still makes it on the disc
It's
From their point of view
It was always
Intended to be something
Supplementary to the original product
And it's not wrong
Because Xbox and PSN lets them do this
And they're sorry but
You have to pay to unlock it either way
Whether it's day one or day 22
So
What do you think? You personally
You're a fighting game fan
I know that
Given what happened with Street Fighter 4
And Mortal Kombat
I basically learned to just say
Screw fighting games and wait until two years later
Which I know some people in chat are like
I don't know the name but
They're going to release a comprehensive
Game of the year full bullshitty DLC edition
I'd rather buy that
They have sworn they're not doing it this time
Unless you want to get the Vita version
Or whatever
Then sure, that's what Loki says
Get the Vita version
You have a Vita, we can get it
That was code for
Rob, buy it for your Vita
And let me play it
Let me play it when you're at work
I guess it's
It's sleazy but like they said
It's not wrong
You know, I'm playing Mass Effect 2
Which has a lot of
Several hour long DLC episode
Packs for it, missions with bonus weapons
And blah blah blah
But the game itself is already so long that you don't
You don't really need it
And it's just being a completionist and knowing that
I want to play Troll Mega Man so bad
But I don't have to but I want to
And it's on the disc
It's frustrating to know that
It's right there on the disc but they want you to pay
I mean that's the frustrating thing about it
At least the Mass Effect 2 stuff you actually download
And while there might be seeds of information
On the disc, you're still downloading
A good chunk of the dialogue and you know
All that you're actually downloading
You're not able to hack it off the disc
In my opinion
Capcom may think this is the more convenient
Way to do it or whatever but
The hacking community is kind of
Teaching them a lesson here
If you go that route
Here's the price you're going to pay for it
And it kind of sucks that legitimate users
Get screwed in the end
And that's where Capcom is starting to look like idiots
Like always
And on that note, there's actually related news reports
Coming out about this
About the fact that Capcom has posted
I believe it's on their own forums as well as also
The official Xbox Live boards
Is that they want people to enforce
To help enforce against the hackers
And report people who are using these
Hacked unlocked characters
And are using them on online matches
They can't do their own fucking job?
But if this is the more convenient way to do it
Then police it your goddamn self
I guess to save themselves a lot of wank
From their fans
Have it be available on launch day
Digitally
Do not put that shit on the disc
For any reason at all
And even if people want to make the argument that
Well, it's Tuesday morning and I have the disc
And now you're saying there's $40 worth of
DLC for me to get
Why wasn't it on the disc? They could just say
Well, because you have to download it
It's not on the disc
And that will remove a lot of the argument that the hackers have right now
AcidicVampire in our chat room says
Ultimately, it's their decision to make it pay to unlock
It sucks, but if you want to have it your way
You should wait until the final Ultimate Edition
Is eventually released
Yeah, exactly
The vote with your wallet statement
Which I think a lot of us are on board with
Yeah, I didn't buy it
And this is a big part of the reason I didn't buy it
Was because Capcom has historically shown
That even if they swear up and down
They're not going to do it this time
I don't believe them
I'm not going to buy it until there's the Ultimate Edition
Or I'm at least going to wait until the disc is down to like $20
Then I'll buy that
And then the $20 to unlock everything
That'll be about the game right there, right?
This story
The hackers, I guess, that have
Figured out how to play those
Pay to unlock characters online
Without having to actually
Get the DLC
Apparently Jill and Shumagoreth
From MVC3
Were on the disc launch day
As Pay to unlock characters
But they were incomplete assets
So to pull down that final 20%
That made them playable
That was a remote file package
That you could bring down to your console
Which is probably what they should have done here
I'm assuming
If they wanted to keep the hackers truly not playing it online
Or what have you
Let's see
Other comments in our chatroom at chat.orangenautry.com
Porkchop says
Capcom left characters on the disc
And the hackers saw it as a personal challenge
And they took it, they ran with it
And gee
What number of times is this that we've heard it?
Millionth and a half?
Absolutely, well you know the old saying
Hackers gonna hack
Right? Haters gonna hate and hackers
Gonna hack. So when you say
Your system is unhackable
That is like printing a wedding invitation
To all the hackers says you are cordially invited
To hack the fuck out of this box
Not only did they take the box, but they took the whole damn network
And almost the company
I mean, what set everybody off about
PlayStation when they removed Linux?
You wanna piss off a hacker?
Take their Linux away?
I mean for real
Take away their command line
Take away their way of exploring
And they'll make a new way
Brute or not
And for people that work in IT
That are hardcore crypto people
They don't even have to be gamers
They see this stuff as a Rubik's Cube
It's exactly like you said
It's a gauntlet thrown down, it's a challenge
Once they release into the crack community
Here's how you
Unlock this
They may not even be gamers, they're just really into crypto
And the community is there
And they're always gonna find a way around it
It is pretty surprising that they're
Not only hacking, but they're going activist
With it and actually playing these
And matches and using it as advertising
That's pretty ballsy
To go on Xbox Live with your gamer tag
And be all, look at me, bitch
I know a lot of people that have a lot of safeguards in place
That on a console that is hacked
Actively prevent them from going on
Xbox Live first
And nothing goes wrong
And then they have to knowingly unlock it
And undo any mods or however the process actually works
But yeah, this is
Probably attributable to the last six months
Or so of tech news
But they're not only hacking, they're going activist
On it as well
That's the more interesting story for me personally
Interesting
Because now people in our chat room are talking
About what is likely next
And Wylan says, I won't buy Darkstalkers 4
But Stan says, I'll totally
Buy Darkstalkers 4 even if there's stupid DLC
I've been waiting for that forever
Act F says, I'll buy Darkstalkers 4
When the Ultimate Edition comes out
This is interesting
Have the reputation of fighting games
Been tarnished due to not just the behavior
Of Capcom, but if you think about it, Mortal Kombat
And WB Games
Didn't really do anything different, granted they didn't leave it
On the disc, but they did release
Extra fighters just to turn around
This is February or March, they had the comprehensive
Freddy Krueger, Scarlet
You know, Kenji
DLC edition
So it's not just Capcom, if you think about it
I still stand by my argument
That EVO has something to do with the timing
And the extensive release
And all that kind of stuff
I really do feel that that factors in
Because fighting games have thankfully stepped back into the mainstream
And EVO, if there's something bigger than that
I don't know what it is
At least here in the States, of course
I don't have a specific point
That comes off that
Ties into all of this
Has Namco and Tekken and Soul Calibur
Done this shit? I don't think they have
They're still the one franchise that's relatively
Tarnished
Well, Soul Calibur
Well, if you had Yoda, you could pay to
Get Vader, and if you had Vader
Because of the version you bought, you could pay to unlock Yoda
But that was really it
It was one character, and everyone knew that was gonna happen
Well, you know what they're doing now
Is it's all the-
Yeah, because 5 just came out and I have no idea what they're doing with it
They're doing princess packs
If you want to dress up your pretty princess
In all the gear, you have to download the
Costume packs
But that's
That's still shitty
But it's cosmetic
Whereas in this, it's players, characters
Right, I mean, it's not
I think what they're doing is not
Nearly as bad as what's happening here
Over at Capcom
And if you're into the design character stuff
Which I know some of our listeners are
They sent a bunch of custom characters
He made, and a lot of them are just hilarious
Like, they're great
Real life interpretations made in the game
And with even more stuff
I can just imagine the additional
Opportunities that opens up
But that's totally different than
You know, a whole different character is here
On the disc, you know
But I don't think they really had
DLC characters, there might have been like
One that came with the collector's edition
I can't remember
The best buy, I want to say
The really over the top silly
Like vaudeville character
I would imagine that after a couple of months he would be made
Available for DLC, but there's a precedent
For that, that they did with Vader and Yoda
Right
Alright, let's move on
Let's talk about what games are coming out to a retailer
Near you that will require you to buy it in the store
And then buy all the DLC later
Okay, maybe not
What's coming out in the US, Jason?
Especially considering the selection that I have to work with
If these games have DLC that would scare
That would scare me to death
Pretty light week
As far as I see from the next week
Three games that
I don't know if I should even go on with them
But here they are
3DS, Spirit Camera, The Cursed Memoir
With bonus
Drops on the 13th
Oh, that's just a strategy guide
Why is that in a game?
You fail-tastic
Also for the Nintendo DS, Titanic Mystery
Maybe with DLC you can
Float the ship back up with ping pong balls
I solved the mystery
It sinks
It was Colonel Mustard in the ballroom
With the anchor
And lastly
With the iceberg
I don't even remember the blue character's name
So there's not even really a way to narrow that down anymore
Mrs. Peacock?
Yeah, that's not water related at all
Oh, okay
There was a tie in there somewhere, but I'm not witty enough
Speaking of boat sinking, I think that joke just sank
To the bottom of the Pacific
I'll never let go, Jack
I'll never let go
We were watching Titan AE last night
And the very ending had a very similar situation
I'll never let go
I'll save you
At any rate
Lastly, oh, so Titanic Mystery
Is...
That's not next week, that's two days ago
Okay, I apologize, this just failed a lot
Spirit camera for the DS
Titanic Mystery for the DS
4-in-1 action pack for the PS3
Drops on Tuesday
Quiet week
An unexciting week
Well, let's go to Japan and see if it's any different over there
On the 12th in Japan
On the Nintendo 3DS
Nintendo Sudoku 3D
Dai Ni Shu
Eitsuno Puzzle Day 1000mon
That is, for real, the name of the game
It's fucking Sudoku in 3D
Okay
Like
Can somebody explain to me
How Sudoku is fucking enhanced in three dimensions?
Because you can have a cube instead of just a flat surface
No, it's not even that
Well, it could be a cube
Your brain couldn't fucking handle the Sudoku coob
I could do that
The Sudoku
Sudoku Coos? What?
Sudoku
Moving on to others
That's all that's on the 3DS this week
With a title that long
I thought it was Sudoku with schoolgirl titties
Or whatever Japanese has
That would have been far more interesting
I would play a Sudoku game if
After you beat the puzzle
Sexy lady dance, titties in 3D
Maybe that's the hidden feature
Or you know
Guys in their underwear
Shaking it in 3D
Whatever it is you're into
You could have a switch
I think you just alienated 80% of the listeners
Look, it's like Mass Effect
You get a choice
You can point the thing up or down
If you were worried about tonight being a dry night
Dry night
How about the Vita?
How about it? In Japan this week
Rayman Origins
And, and ready?
Nikolai no Sudoku 5
Shugyoku number 12
Puzzle, that's right
It's a Sudoku game on the Vita
As well
Is that a swastika? What is that?
That's one of the puzzles
No, that is not a swastika
That is not Sudoku
It's rotated
Look at it diagonally
I need the chat
Oh, it kind of does look like a swastika
Don't buy that game you guys
That's not cool
It's in chat, tell us we're wrong
That is not a Sudoku puzzle, that's the other one
What's that? Kakoru?
There's the missing number crossword
Kakoru or something like that
I don't remember the name of it, god dammit
How about on the consoles?
Maybe there's something to save us on the
Playstation 3 this week in Japan
Dirt 3
You get Sudoku or Dirt
Also
Grand Slam Tennis 2
And Rayman Origins
On the Playstation 3
And lastly on the Xbox 360
Nothing, because no one owns
a 360 in Japan
No seriously, there's nothing on the 360
this week in Japan
How about Europe? UK
All those countries over there
Looks like
a light week over on the UK side
or the Europe side as well
On the 11th I have Football
Manager handheld for the Android
Legend of
Grimrock for the PC
Skullgirls for
Playstation 3 and 360
On the 12th we have
Max Payne Mobile, which we just covered
Tribes Ascend for the PC
On the 13th
Fez
Fez, not Rez
Fez, maybe your little Shriners in the little cars
Fez for the 360
On the 14th, Pandora's
Tower for the Wii
Which is kind of
a big deal
That's one of those Operation Rainfall games
Pandora's Tower?
So while we wait here in the US
everybody's going to be pirating it
Because that's what
people do
Alright, I'm just kidding kids, don't pirate
But seriously
Someone on my Facebook just mentioned getting
Center Blade Chronicles
Like they just bought it in the store this week
And I was like, what? Oh yeah
I guess we should only really be playing that
Starting this week
Oops
I would have loved to have bought Xenoblade
A year ago
Nintendo, you've made the bed
Now lie in it
Moving on, let's do one other
Quick story before we get to the classic game of the week
DarkSakura's not here tonight
I know she's in the chat and she can scream all she wants
But we're taking the
Classic game of the week car and driving it
In another direction tonight, so here we go
Jason, one more story though
By the way, the chat room
Oh there was, hey, look at the main intention
Well I'll say this real quick, the chat room is
Lighting up, saying there is
What we know as a swastika
In Japanese can be a manji
Which is actually a good luck
And some old video games had that
For instance there was some
Dungeons and Zelda, somebody was saying in our chat room
Kind of looked like that
I remember it was 1942 and 1943
Had those symbols
In the Japanese versions
And they were like extra life or something
So, and it's not controversial there
Because it has a different meaning
It looks mirrored to me
Yes, I believe it's the other direction
But obviously that's a pretty easy mistake
For commoners, so generally
Games that would have had it and come to America
Get it just changed to something else entirely
Or just stripped out
Was there another comment on that one?
No
Yes, one last story because I swear I am keeping up with things
New York has booted all of its registered sex offenders
Off online gaming networks
Microsoft, Sony, Blizzard, EA, and Apple
All cooperated with the purge
Which follows a court case
In the state of New York
In which a 19 year old pleaded guilty
To abusing a 10 year old
He met on Xbox Live
New York law demands all convicted sex offenders
To hand over any email addresses
And online aliases
To help limit their access on vulnerable web networks
However, this is the first time it's ever been invoked
In relation to online gaming
Pretty, pretty
Didn't, we
We never went through this
Six years ago with Uno
And yet we're finally here
Oh god, strip Uno, I remember that story
Look, here's the thing though
Obviously
People that would do that stuff to kids
Are not okay and they need to be dealt with
In ways like this, I get that
But, there's another side to this
That kind of bothers me
What parent was letting their 10 year old
Play on Xbox Live unsupervised?
Hello
Did they just not know
What happens on Xbox Live?
I'm like, ignorance is not an excuse
You know what I mean?
That should be a wake up call
To parents everywhere
You need to supervise children
That are going to play games online like that
Again, I'm not saying
What the 19 year old
19 year old did was right
That's no excuse, but I'm just saying
There's kind of a couple things wrong in this picture
Although, take it on the flip side
And I can say something from my youth
While I wasn't 10 years old
I was still really young
And my parents were divorced
And I was living with my mom
And on the times that she had custody of me
And even sometimes when my dad
Had custody of us
Sometimes it was just myself
And my sister who is 3 years older than me
But sometimes it was just straight up me
Often times, especially after my
Sister grew up and moved out
It was just myself in the house
All weekend
This is before the years of online gaming
Functionally
This is just a modern version of that
But these situations
And I completely understand
Where you're coming from
One, there are bad parents
Two, there are bad situations with good parents
And
It would be
Great if parental controls
Were a lot more perfect
If Microsoft could step in a lot better
And have some kind of a camera
Filter or if they were just kind of smarter about it
But these situations happen
And it's incredibly unfortunate
I can kind of meet you halfway there because
When I was probably about 12 or 13
On my Commodore 64
On my 300 baud modem
I was calling into BBS's
Local bulletin board systems
And posting on message boards and playing door games
I was fucking playing Legend of the Red Dragon and shit
At like 14 and 15 right
Which if you ever played those games back in the day
Nice games
And my mom just said oh he's on the computer
You know and I was posting on message boards and stuff
And there would be people on the message boards
It's like yeah you should like come out to this meetup
And all this stuff and it's like okay I'm 15
You know and
You know I can kind of see
That side of it
That sometimes the parents
If she knew what I was doing online though
She would have punched me in the face
She would have taken the cord
She would have burned the cord in front of my eyes
She knew what kind of stuff
I was doing on the computer
How does the outside world exist anymore?
Especially nowadays
With us I mean look at what we're doing here
Three nerds around the table and a lot of cords
That are just connecting us to the rest of everybody else
Did you have a comment on this Alan?
I feel that
A lot of people
Will pretend to be high and mighty by saying that
A TV or a console should not be a babysitter
But it's
A privilege for a kid to have
Two adults that are in the same household
As them invested in raising them
And sometimes if they have to work
Full time jobs you know
To do what's necessary to run that household
A console or a TV will be a babysitter
For four or five hours a day
And I don't really think that that's negligent to do so
And even if the parents
Had taken measures to lock down that kind of stuff
It doesn't necessarily mean the 10 year old
Doesn't know how to crack their parents
Password and lock it themselves
Like they're not
Idiots at 10
I guess that's true you know but
Don't fucking buy them an Xbox Live subscription
Do not buy a 10 year old an Xbox Live subscription
Ever
And if you're gonna get one for yourself
Password lock it if you know there's a kid in the house
It's dangerous
Yeah and if the kid still cracks the password
There shouldn't be icky
20 plus, 30 plus year old pedos
Creeping on them
Well that's still absolutely true and I'm still
But I'm just saying you know
Everybody needs to accept some responsibility here
Alright
Anyhow let's move on
Let's move on to a time when
Xbox Live didn't exist and we didn't have these
Complicated situations
Although the Nintendo
Did still babysit us a little bit
Or in the case of this week's Classic Game of the Week
An old computer would babysit
Okay so here's the deal Dark Soccer's not here tonight
So this is Dark Soccer's Classic Game of the Week
But we're taking over
It's my Classic Game of the Week tonight
Dark Soccer had picked a game for tonight
But I was like, it's a good game, but I'm like
She can, I wouldn't want to
I wouldn't want to do it without her here
Because then she might have things she wants to say about that game
So we'll let her roll it over to next week
And I'm gonna do a game tonight
That I know she would never pick
Why? Because I picked a game
From the Commodore 64
That's right, the game I've picked tonight
Is tonight's Classic Game of the Week is
Impossible Mission
I don't know if anybody ever remembers this game
But this game was awesome
Because it was one of the first games ever
To use a voice synthesizer
And so here you go
Here's what you would hear when you would start
Impossible Mission
Another visitor
Stay a while
Stay forever
That was the shit
When I was a kid
By the way, he's saying another visitor
Another visitor
Stay forever
The last Metroid
Is in captivity
The galaxy is at peace
It was kind of like that
So the original version was on the Commodore 64
And it was done by Epyx in 1984
Epyx was the company that made this game
Can we even hear the thing?
By the way, the sound effects
And stuff in this game is very
Ambient
There's no music
So you just have some very ambient noises
If you want to jump a little bit there
Alright, so anyway, here is the deal
In Impossible Mission
Not to be confused with Mission Impossible
Wink Wink Nudge Nudge
The big show from the 60s
Impossible Mission, you played a secret agent
Not to be confused with 007
That is trying to stop an evil genius
Elvin Atombender
Is tampering with
National security computers
So you go into the stronghold
And you race against the clock
Which in turn will make a password
While you avoid deadly
Electrocuting face eating robots
Ok, they don't eat your face
But they will electrocute you
And you will sometimes fall
Down bottomless pits and all you'll hear is
Ahhhh
Anyhow
We've got the chorus going on now
Once you finally put the password pieces together
You'll put the completed password in the main
Control room door, and that's where you
find the evil professor. Where do you find password pieces? In the furniture of
course. You search the furniture in the rooms you might find lift resets and
snoozes in the rooms as well. You also will have a room where you can get more
lift resets and snoozes from doing a musical puzzle. There you go.
Everything in this game was randomized which kind of made this a lot of fun
because you could play it over and over again. Sometimes you would have layouts
of the mansion or the stronghold that like were not winnable. But most of the
time you got winnable and sometimes you get really easy one too. Rogue apparently
was an early inspiration for the randomized room layouts. The designer
cited rogue. Do you remember the old old ass rogue game that was on like
terminals? I don't know that I've originally I've played an original rogue but I've played a
million roguelikes. Oh yeah well then you kind of know what the deal is there.
Here is the speech that is in the game. There is the death scream which can also
be heard in Beachhead 2. They recycled the death scream. There's another visitor
stay a while stay forever and then there's also destroy him my robots. Which
happens in the very first room you walk into a never again correct? It's a
randomized room. Really? And then there's also when the game is over there's a
laugh and then if you find him he'll say no no no and then there's a lady voice
that says mission accomplished congratulations and that's all the
speech in the game that's all you can fit on one of those freaking five and a
quarter floppy disks that is like bigger than terabyte hard drives these days.
There were only two types of enemies and impossible missions there were the laser
spout and robots and then there was also some some would move slow some would
move fast and then there's also other types of security guards that would kind
of just stay in place and then it would wake up when you got really close to it
there. You get six hours to beat the game 36 puzzle pieces every time you die
ten minutes are deducted from the total time. This game was ported like mad. It
was on the Apple 2, the Atari 7800, the ZX Spectrum, the Acorn Electron, the BBC
Micro, the Amstrad CPC, the NES, and the Sega Master System. Not all of them had
speech though. Get this the 7800 version on the NTSC platforms had a bug that
made the game impossible to win. So it really was impossible mission somebody
took the game name to literally there. Looks like level 30 syndrome started a
bit earlier than we thought. Aha there was a sequel called impossible mission
2 in 1988 with new traps and items and also a bigger stronghold. There was a 3d
sequel planned for Epyx's handy system. I don't know if you guys know but Epyx was
going to launch their own system. It eventually became the Atari Lynx so that
didn't happen. Impossible mission 2025 came out in 1994 for the Amiga which was
kind of the similar gameplay. Impossible mission did show up later in 2004 it was
on the Commodore 64 direct-to-tv and it was on the Nintendo Game Boy Advance in
2004 and the Sony PSP in 2008. Get that. This game is also available on the Wii
Virtual Console but only in Europe because the Commodore 64 was a fucking
huge deal in Europe. It was kind of big here but it was huge in Europe April 11
2008 is when it came out there. This is one of those games that this is the game
in my opinion and I'm obviously very age biased myself in that it's gotten better
with time because when I was young playing on a Commodore 64 I was just
like running jumping and collecting these random numbers and other things.
You had no idea what the fuck you were doing right? I can ride lifts up and down
inside the side and sometimes not even that couldn't always figure it out but
now that I've grown up and matured I actually understand what's going on and
what I have to do and this game is freaking hard but it's a good challenge
and it's worth revisiting and finally starting to finally starting to get
played again. I have actually I still have not beaten the game to this day but
knowing what I have to do going back and doing it with the original Commodore 64
version under emulation I've been making an active an active try to do it and
come up short so far but I've still had a lot of fun doing it.
Tigercall on our chat room says Sky do you think Impossible Mission could ever
get remade? Well I mean I mean we do have the Game Boy and the PSP ones but yeah
that the Wii the Wii version and all those modern consoles I I would call it
a remake because it's not it's not just like improved graphics a lot of a lot of
aspects of the game changed like you don't pick up numbers you pick up puzzle
pieces that you have to rotate and put into place that form like a map security
code something or other I got pissed off at the game and I stopped playing it
it's technically already happened but not in a significant way. I think there
would be a brilliant use on like let's say Xbox Live Arcade or PlayStation
Network of multiplayer can you imagine if you and three other people all
attacked the same Citadel at the same time and like you could maybe see the
shadows of the other players as they're exploring and then you know I think
this would be a great competitive game especially with the randomization
element in it and everything I think for like old-school fans I think there's
really something untapped here that the developers didn't do when they made
these other ports. For some very obvious reasons perhaps. You should be giving me
the rights to do this franchise even though I know nothing about game or
programming games I think that wouldn't that be a fantastic game on Xbox Live
you could like do multiplayer co-op and competitive you do co-op where you're
both collecting puzzle pieces I think this is a great franchise. One person
manning the computer and controlling some room elements and the other person
swiftly dodging the robots at a moment's notice and scanning scanning the
furniture and everything else a lot of potential absolutely. Well there it is
your classic game of the week for the Commodore 64 where it all started
although it's available in a shitload of systems after that impossible mission
Commodore 64 your classic game of the week
haha Dark Sakura haha took your other classic game and just threw it out the
window now she'll bring it back next week I know she will it's okay
considering what the game is it would just float to safety there's your hint
for next week all right that's gonna do it for part A of Orange Lounge Radio but
don't go anywhere we got plenty more to come in the second half of the show
we're gonna talk a little more about PAX East we're expecting to get a phone
call a little later in the show we're gonna talk about PAX East with some of
the OLR listeners that was there I'm not ignoring PAX East I just I live in
California and didn't fly out there this year so I'm sure there's lots that's
gonna be said about PAX East we do have more news your FUBU question of the
week more phone calls and plenty more when we come back with more of Orange
Lounge Radio right after this
welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio live on this April the 8th of
2012 with the 453rd episode of our show little weird tonight because we're not
missing just one but two co-hosts but we have two fantastic co-hosts sitting in
tonight we have Alan of course and Jason filling in that's me I promised you guys
could talk about some of your side projects because you guys don't just
co-host here but you both now have your own regular podcast that you do Jason
we'll start with you you mentioned you do an Apple related thing yeah there's a
there's a network of nerd topic goodness called a stack exchange and myself I'm
quite personally vested with a couple of others on their Apple topic site called
ask different and so myself and two others started up the ask different
podcast and we've been going since I want to say last summer but suddenly
that feels wrong for some reason but ask different podcast pretty easy to search
for ask different comm is the site and there's links to blog chat finding us
finding the site itself and all that content pretty simple I'm assuming
that's a little pun on the think different yeah and that that's that was
that was the name chosen for the site the highest voted name for to actually
to actually call this site there there's like I could rant for like 30 minutes on
how we came to that name but I'll spare all you guys because it's not the topic
and you really do have a great radio voice I'm not just saying that cuz you're
here but I mean it's convenient but you do have a great real voice I can only
imagine it's the ass different podcast is great so all right not as a exciting
and hilarious as the show is at least 99% of the time sometimes we get in a
good good pun that's okay this show can be pretty boring too now I'm kidding it
shows always amazing always Alan you you now in the time that you have been for
your last guest co-hosting on this program you now have your own podcast
right I've branched out of the olr network how very dare I how very dare
you I'm surprised I'm surprised you were banned from this program actually I just
sleep on the couch for a week so pretend you didn't make me do that I am on a
podcast called fabulous flames and it is a World of Warcraft podcast maybe I
guess a competitor of courthouse yeah I know it's my hair yeah I was invited to
be on it because the host was a fan of what I had to say on whorehouse so
there's three of us and it's just I guess World of Warcraft from a male
point of view I don't really know what the gimmick is but yeah we it's a gay
Wow podcast that's what the gimmick is fabulous flames is an actual spell from
an encounter from this latest expansion and it's the gay dragon that was
originally supposed to sound like Paul in from match game and Blizzard like cut
his voice our listeners are listeners are too young to get that reference
honey so Blizzard cut his voice acting going no this is not good so we're
joking that we're the gay dragons and don't just stand in the flames bask in
them so it's it's World of Warcraft discussion and you can find us at
fabulous flames on Twitter and fabulous flames calm or on iTunes how very dare
you work that tagline so one gay dragons two talking dragons is my lack of Wow
biting me somewhere here it's the Twilight dragon twins it's a brother and
sister and the brother is on fire so I I've often been obviously I have a side
project I do not just orange on studio but I have a podcast about the World of
Warcraft called the best little whorehouse in Azeroth and our tagline is
it's all things World of Warcraft but never too seriously so you know that's
what we've got and I often get asked the question is it weird that you and your
boyfriend are on competing podcasts and I'm like no because I support all
independent podcasts and that's what I've been preaching on orange launch
radio for years so I fucking love it that he's doing his own show it's great
I love it no it is it is fabulous flames is still very much on its sea legs we're
only on our fourth or fifth episode so we have we have a long way to grow
you're still basic bitches but you'll grow I've been I am so rude to the the
main host of their sunshine I'm I am such a bitch to him on Twitter but it's
fun because you know we're frenemies we're frenemy podcasts is what we call
each other and so I've said I I have all these names for fabulous wives I call
them the fabulous flops it's my favorite name them so anyhow alright so there you
go and honestly I really do I think it's great because it's not like most people
I know that listen to podcasts listen at work and they've got plenty of time to
listen to plenty of shows and I would rather somebody be listening to an
independent podcast then some of that crap that certain websites that won't be
named produce honey yeah you try I had to dig in one more come on come on
alright anyhow so there you go let's um also I would do shoutouts for PAX East
since we're giving other shows shoutouts I do want to say I heard little bits and
pieces of what the B team which is one of the other shows on the all games
network did they were live at PAX East and did some good shows so check that
out I also know electric sistahood which is also on the all games network did a
show while they were there I don't think it was live but I think maybe it was I
don't remember sorry girls but they did one and it will be on their podcast feed
and on the network this week for sure and I think I heard Ranma who calls in
this show all the time and we'll be on the show tonight guest it on it so I'm
glad to see the all games network big happy family getting together at PAX I
will say the one year we did the all games thing at PAX Prime was a great
year I mean oh man that was a that was like one of my favorite cons ever was
that PAX Prime 2008 when all the all games people were there we were
broadcasting it was a great year but I did go to PAX East the first year a
couple years ago and had a good time so I was sad I couldn't go this year but
you know there's only so much money and you know I I spent a lot of it going to
Disneyland what can you do but I am gonna try and go to a PAX Prime this
year if nothing else all right I'll advertise real far advertising the all
games network never saw that coming well what do you want me to advertise I have
no good response tonight I was gonna say something bitchy about one of the
corporate networks but I'm not gonna go there and I'm just gonna ask that we go
for some rapid-fire news so you know what's funny about that I'm on a loaner
laptop right now and I just pulled the power cord out so I can tell you the
first story purely from recollection is that Diablo 3 was finally dated for mid
May what's the next quest what's the next question for the great dungeon
crawl torchlight when is it they haven't said yet soon soon shortly after Diablo
3 which is still soon but not soon enough you want to give me the headlines
of the next two because I can hard angle oh what there you go
theater rhythm Final Fantasy finally dated for the what is that midsummer
July 3rd mm-hmm game was actually completely off my radar but looking at
the looking at the screenshots looks fun I did get a particular amount of
amusement of the fact that cloud stripes face was completely obscured in the one
screenshot I did see by the target exceeding the the the note exceeding the
target zone whatever the particular vocabulary is for that and finally Sega
says rhythm thief is still happening and that article unfortunately I don't have
on the top of my head so while my computer starts back up can somebody
saved my poor dead-air ass there was they were on the paxi Sega was at PAX
East and there was confirmation that rhythm thief is still happening this is
despite all the Sega bad news we had last week
rhythm thief was not canceled so it is still happening it's a 3ds rhythm action
game featuring people in top hats and ties I guess they're like tap dancing on
disco floors there you go all right some other rapid-fire news for you guys
fallout the original not the fallout 3 which was still really good but the
original original game way back in the day was free I say was because you
missed it it was on good old games or gog.com it was earlier this week
unfortunately if you're hearing this now though it is no longer free so why am I
reporting it because I just wanted you to know what you missed out on free
fallout which is a great great PC get your PC gaming fan I know you know yes
all serious also it's worth mentioning since we brought up gog they throw a
little shade at steam this week they were kind of like you know when you give
these games away for such low cost it doesn't really help anyone which I
thought was an interesting little dig it helps me I can't imagine I mean EA
fucked off and did their origin store because they just want to be elitist and
only sell things through their own platform but if a game developer is
letting steam sell a five-year-old game for $2.99 I don't think valve is
twisting their arm zithers in our chat room talking about the Sega stuff saying
I hope to God we get Phantasy Star online to hear if that gets canned I
will explode I hear ya that character creator came out this week overseas it's
not you know that the game has been announced for the US cross your fingers
and your toes we get any three announcement because if you don't hear
it at e3 it's probably not happening you know what is happening though a sieve
5 expansion civilization 5 gods and kings it is going to be coming out on
June 19 is the release date for that 22nd if you're international there was
more information announced about this a game developers conference but in case
you forgot 27 new units 13 new buildings 9 new wonders and civilization they're
also going to add religion and espionage into the game and some tweaks to
diplomacy so hopefully they'll fix some of the balancing issues that they borked
in the game to begin with but if any of my sieve friends are listening we're
gonna need to get a match going in late June after this comes out because I'm
I'm eager to revisit the game again but God you know how the sieve 5 matches
will go you started at six o'clock in the evening and then suddenly oh shit
it's 2 a.m. and we just discovered railroads another story this week epic
games you know epic games they make well you know epic games including unreal and
you know the Gears of War here's the deal they have announced sort of that
they're doing a PC exclusive project it was mentioned during a PAX East panel
the unannounced PC project is under development the plans are to keep the
game exclusive to the PC so if you were worried that epic was all about the
consoles and I don't know iOS games now because that's the other big thing they
did right infinity blade don't worry a PC exclusive title is in the works hmm
could be interesting Alan there has been an online petition for the game Dark
Souls the sequel to Demon's Souls otherwise known as one of the hardest
console games ever this generation the petitions been to bring it on to the PC
platform and Atlas has come out and said yes there will be a PC edition of Dark
Souls and it's called the Dark Souls prepare to die edition to which anyone
that's played the game would say very much yes you will die there was a lot of
hype in last few weeks about the game journey I believe it is that sort of has
an online element if that's correct Demon's Souls was similar in that when
you were fighting in these labyrinths you would fight these ghouls that were
actually other players and Demon's Souls has a similar mechanic or sorry Dark
Souls has a similar mechanic so yeah it's a very difficult game and it's
coming to PC it's one of the few examples of where an online petition was
a success it has over 92,000 signatures and it has exclusive bosses to the PC
Edition which I'm sure will be just as impossibly hard or even more so so Dark
Souls fans on PC you're in luck Skyrim 1.5 patch which I was surprised when I
read this story because I've been playing on PC Skyrim 1.5 patch for a
couple weeks now is hitting 360 and ps3 this week and it's mostly bug fixes at
least two dozen or so bug fixes that were blocking progress on certain quests
the big deal though about patch 1.5 Skyrim is that it's it's adding kill
moves and kill cinematic like awesome slow-mo bullet cam for projectile
weapons like arrows and spells which Skyrim didn't have before and also new
kill moves for melee weapons so now not only can you behead people you can fry
them you can shoot arrows through their necks and all that other stuff you saw
in shaky cam Hunger Games yes they fixed what it looks like when you go underwater
and it also looks like they finally fixed the Lydia bug Lydia is the first
guard woman that you get and you when you buy a house she if you're wearing an
omelet amulet of Mara you should be able to propose to her she's been bugged this
whole time since November or whatever so finally they fixed the Lydia bug yes I
look for that on Xbox and ps3 this week finally Sonic 4 episode 2 the big 2d
HD resurgence of the sonic franchise that kind of came off like a fart in an
elevator is getting its episode 2 like everyone's like it sounds so awesome and
then it came out and it's no one Kerr it is finally getting its episode 2 and it
will likely be the last episode so they are wrapping this up really fast
episodic content is the way of the future like we'll give you a part 2
because no one like this shit and we don't want to make it anymore so thanks
Gabe Newell PSN version will be released on a May 15th XBL a version of Sonic 4
episode 2 will be the next day May 16th and PC and mobile versions are I guess
confirmed but to be announced later all right that's all let's go to the
frugal question of the week oh no we won't go to the frugal question of the
week well one quick thing I missed in the theater them story if you're at PAX
East you can go check out the oh sorry nevermind it's over yeah it was joke may
I do the frugal now absolutely every week we ask you guys a question over at
Facebook or Google Plus Facebook put together that's Google that's our concern
facebook.com slash orange lounge radio if you want to like us over there and
Google Plus slash search for orange lounge radio because we don't get short
URLs there I'll start with Google Plus tonight because the very first answer on
Google Plus I need to read this because it has something very important in it oh
I should tell you guys what the question was just like I forgot to tell you what
the question was just then I forgot to give a good question earlier in the week
so I made it really easy this week I said how was your gaming week shit we
all have to say every night how our gaming weeks were the host of the show
so why shouldn't the listeners get a shot so how was your gaming week
listeners I especially said what game are you into right now that everybody
else should be playing so Derek H starts us off on Google Plus and this is worth
mentioning he's playing pinball arcade on Xbox Live arcade but everyone should
be playing joust on maim as part of the hunt and I totally forgot to mention
this I'm so bad and I had like notes to myself to mention this partly because I
had no idea this was happening until Monday of last week after last week
show but dark Tetsuya who pretty much writes most of the articles in orange
launch radio.com at this point it's either him or act after me me
publishing episodes of the show and that's it at this point dark Tetsuya is
doing a little contest and it's called the hunt and it's based off of the book
ready player one where they kind of do something very similar I don't want to
go into all the details but he's doing kind of his own spin of the competition
called the hunt and it involves classic video games and being able to get
scores that are better than what dark Tetsuya gets and he doesn't really try
super hard because he makes it you know beatable so right now the contest he's
running is joust and if you can beat a score of 39,000 something so I mean
39,800 you take a screen cap of it and either email it to dark Tetsuya or you
post it on Twitter and you're gonna get a little copper key and some points that
let you into the next round of the competition so joust is the game that
they're doing right now I don't know how much longer you have to do it I'm hoping
dark Tetsuya will allow a little bit of an extension because if you weren't
reading the website you may have missed or seen the Twitter you may have missed
this so I'm telling you guys now if you have joust be it in MAME or Xbox Live or
whatever fire it up get the score and go on to the next round of the competition
because as I understand it right now Derek H is in the lead and well we just
we can't we we have to give us a competition you guys Derek H is the guy
behind like the big battle and all that stuff so we have to we have to give him
a challenge here we don't let him just walk away with everything so I submitted
my entry today and I'm gonna try to play in future weeks as well so more
information is available on orange lounge radio calm now Derek H also wants
to plug you will die on Xbox Live indie games because I get money when people
buy it well played well I see what you did there actually you will die is a fun
game though like if you like you know your retro shooters he did a good job I
did buy it I bought it like two years ago when it first came out so he's
probably long spent the money but I did buy it all right uh pwk responded and
said I was at my first packs this weekend congratulations I hope you had
fun I want to hear more about it Tony M responded and said this is an oldie but
after Atlas recently cut the prices of their PSN downloads I've been playing
persona 3 portable it's pretty awesome if you're into JRPGs you know persona is
one of the series I hear nothing but good things about but I just I personally
haven't sat down and played it myself but like I said the same thing about
Mass Effect a few months ago on the show I haven't really played it myself but I
hear a lot of people are really into it so persona one of these days I'm gonna
sit down and play it maybe that's something you could do after Mass Effect
play persona is that a serious interest you at all no you did play it before
though didn't I have you don't know three and four for ps2 I think might
still be shrink-wrapped on this show all right let's go to Facebook read some of
the answers there um lots of replies on Facebook I can't possibly read these all
but I do want to thank you guys for taking the time to actually answer these
let's see another persona Austin W says right now I'm really into persona 4 on
PlayStation 2 anyone who is a fan of JRPGs dungeon crawlers and the social
character interaction aspect of games should check it out let's see going to
Stan says splitting my time between draw something angry bird space push mo on
3ds and more Soulcalibur 5 online trying to show off my creative souls Chad C
responds and says been playing realm of the mad god it's an MMORPG shooter with
85 player groups what free to play on your browser also on steam 35 make
download 8-bit graphics perma death kind of sucks when your guy you log 30 plus
hours on dies but it's so easy to get into that it won't stop you from playing
more what perma death and an MMO that's crazy once you hit level 20 you start
gaming gaining fame which allows you to buy keys to unlock more dungeons the
final boss is onyx everyone gets teleported to his lair when all quests
are completed on your realm and someone kills 2500 mobs the game isn't over when
he dies however because you can keep getting gaining fame to unlock harder
dungeons and get better loots I don't know this game but it sounds crazy
thank you I keep bumping into it but I haven't really taken the plunge myself
huh now you knew there were gonna be some people talking about Xenoblade this
week so we have Barry M Xenoblade Chronicles on the Wii is an amazing JRPG
game much in the vein of Final Fantasy 12 meets my White Knight Chronicles I
think that's exactly how I described it when I first reviewed it actually also
playing Ragnarok Odyssey on Vita Kid Icarus uprising on 3ds and Tales of
Graces F on PlayStation 3 this is a great year for RPG fans Carlos M says
I'm halfway through Dragon Age 2 on my 360 and 56 coins and to draw something
I'd like that those two games are like on the same level there it's awesome
zether simply responds Xenoblade everyone probably knows why and dark
soccer would kick me if I didn't say I randomly started playing Portal 2 again
I know I know I should be playing Mass Effect yes you should I'm gonna read
this comment from unfolded Raptor it's a long one but it's good this past week
the blockbuster video in the city I live in was going out of business and had a
liquidation sale and had to sell everything so I found a whole bunch of
really good PlayStation 3 games for $8 each I ended up buying 15 that I never
played yet and probably won't for a while I'm not gonna read all these but
like Twisted Metal Demon Souls Deus Ex Bulletstorm there's a ton in here grand
total of a hundred and seventy three dollars for those games it's a steal
considering at Walmart and even at the evil G the lowest some of these get is
around 20 bucks I highly suggest people play Borderlands that they haven't yet
it's a ton of fun other than that I've been dedicating myself to Ninja Gaiden
3 and have almost finished it I'm loving that as well and I don't see why all the
hate for it sometimes I think that people forget how to have fun pretty
similar situation in my neck of the woods and I'm sure many other places
people people around work were saying you what if there's any movie you've
been wanting for a long time go check out the blockbuster right down the hill
cuz uh it'll be gone soon I want a blockbuster to go out of business here
California props it up a lot better than some of these more sparse well they all
went under already years ago red box took over years ago here there's like
only I can only think of like where one blockbuster even is there's one over on
Folsom below are that I know I'll keep your eye on it for it to go under well
okay I will do that it's right next door to Papa Murphy's so we it's like the
only pizza chain I'll eat so anymore so all right there you go that was our
frugal question of the week thank you guys for responding sorry I didn't read
them all but like that was more that since it was such an easy question there
was more there than like ever before so let's move on Jason more news electronic
arts has been voted the worst American company ever okay not ever but just in
2012 so I guess it's actually for 2011 considering the year just started
whatever beyond that the consumerist holds an annual tournament to determine
the most despised American companies nominations are put to a vote and the
ultimate winner is crowned the worst company of this of the year electronic
arts congratulations in a poll that took over 250,000 votes EA beat out the Bank
of America for its greed and treatment of consumers with a comfortable 64% lead
hell hath no fury like a pack of scorned gamers I don't think EA has ever double
withdrawn someone's mortgage payment and I know people can be evaded have had
that happen so I'm a little skeptical I know the study has been going on for a
while but with the timing to the Mass Effect 3 ending wank this seems I timed
poorly for the story for me I ate all the popcorn I'd saved for this story
because I have not seen such internet lulls like I've seen this week on this
story from all facets I mean there's obviously the people that you know voted
for this and allowed it to win that just their seething hatred for EA that mostly
comes down to everything that happened in Mass Effect and you granted there's
the DLC stuff there's I mean I'm not letting an EA off easy here but you know
it's not like they're Capcom there's I think EA's kind of taken the burden for
everything that everything hey everybody hates with the gaming industry right now
I think it's kind of said in that statement but then what also cracks me
up is like the people on the consumerist that are like fucking gamers fucking
gamers ruining this poll fucking Bank of America is the fucking evilest company
in the world what the fuck is wrong with gamers obviously gamers are too poor to
own a house and it's like you guys internet polls are really fucking
serious business everybody look at your lives look at your choices you are all
rabble-rabble ing over an internet poll on some website that is owned by the
same people that don't go talk to I think I know no they sold it off years
ago but then one time you know what I'm saying it's just who cares it's an
internet poll it is not that serious you know what your worst company is and who
you're gonna give money to and not and so forth it's it's kind of an individual
decision so and meanwhile Activision Blizzard is going to dodge that bullet
girl we ain't done shit the rest of this article is a pretty good read I'll leave
it verbatim to those who might sneer at something as non-essential as a video
game company winning the worst company in American vote it's that exact kind of
attitude that allows people to ignore the complaints as companies like EA to
nickel-and-dime consumers to death argues the site for years while movies
and music became more affordable and publishers piled on bonus content or
multiple modes of delivery or multiple modes of delivery is added value to
entice customers to buy video games have continued to be priced like premium
goods for its exploitation of the downloadable content model the
consumerist will be sending EA a little golden poo as a trophy the poo is
usually presented on a red pillow but this year the company is sending a
choice of colors mocking the controversial Mass Effect 3 ending haha
like the Razzies sorry it's okay as gratuitous as EA's deals he is I can't
help feeling that it's not quite as bad as illegal foreclosures of or some of
the other scummy things the companies in the running did there you go though the
internet hath spoken also hath was my addition it said has but there you go
and I loved EA put out some response that was very like we don't give a fuck
like it was very much like all this money on our naked bodies we don't care
it's so amazing no it was very like well I guess Halliburton and Exxon and all of
them are really happy that they didn't win the award this year and then pop cap
put out a statement that was like you fucking design quality games for 30
years I'm paraphrasing clearly you fuck his healthy pop cap would put it that
way but it was basically you fucking design games for 30 years that are
quality games and try to make the internet happy and see where it gets you
but in my opinion that statement as much as I love pop cap I love them a lot but
that statement they need to step away from the Borg hive mind that they're
starting to become a part of because that's not the reason why EA won this
award look at the reason that look at the trends that EA has been starting
look at the things that people don't like EA invented the online pass EA you
know obviously this whole Mass Effect thing they're taking some of the brunt
on that EA sports games every year with no discernible difference is probably
the exclusive contract is probably the driving force between behind trying to
lock out used gamers in the next gaming cycle you know they want that to happen
look at origin Oh God an origin yeah not wanting to play nice with other gaming
companies they they refuse basically to play by the normal rules of Xbox Live
and we're like either we get to build our own infrastructure or we're not
putting our games out on your system and the kind of using that muscle Mass Effect
3 isn't on Steam and you know that would sell there exactly so anyway enjoy your
golden poo yeah internet polls are very serious business clearly now there's an
interesting follow-up to the all this stuff it isn't directly a follow-up to
the same same story but there's always going to be that guy that asks what
about all the good things EA did and to be fair EA had a couple big stories this
week that were some good news so let's cover them one of them which I think all
of you have got to be aware of by now but it is out there they have announced
that there will be Mass Effect 3 extended cut Mass Effect 3 DLC extended
cut is coming out it's going to be coming out this summer it is going to be
providing a more fleshed out experience for their fans it's going to bring
closure to the ending is there nice PC way of saying we're gonna fix the
goddamn ending then fine here's the big thing about it that I got a mid even
caught me is my surprise it's gonna be free it's gonna be free through April of
2014 or something like that and even then they said they buy aware said they
only end dated it because EA has a policy on free DLC has to be end dated
and they won't ever charge for it if they can get away with it and it's free
because it is not an addition of playable content or missions it is
literally you restore a save before the final encounter before all of the
expositor expository narrative ending cinematic crap and that visually that
you watch is expanded upon so it's free because it's not it's it's additional
content but it's not playable some rumors going around that the voice
actors for femshep and male Shep have not been asked to come back yet which
implies that you know and again I got a I got a tread lightly around the ending
here but if they're not in it then how could they really do much of an ending
that perhaps it's just gonna be text on the screen all a text I think that's a
little bit silly there could be some type of like third-person narration or
something going on I could see that happening but or maybe it's gonna be
told from somebody else's point of view like years later or something I don't
know I think there's still a lot they could do with it that even though they
don't have the voice actors back but it sounds like again the Internet's already
not happy with it well it's it's not a new ending which is what people are
demanding they're like throw this shit that you put in the game out give us
something completely different but they wear that there I was like no this is
our artistic you know point of view so it's not a different ending and it's not
any new ending choices they are just fleshing out what's already there yeah
trying to explain it more or what have you so in a way it's kind of like saying
well it's very metaphorical and up to your imagination and you didn't get it
so if you didn't get it then here's we're gonna throw you a bone so what do
you think about the fact that the internet got their way well they didn't
they didn't I mean they're getting something else I'm actually I'm legit
surprised they're doing it for free and I said a few weeks ago on the show I
said if they don't put it out for free then they're just assholes and to my
surprise they're doing it for free so I have to stand by what I said and that is
that it's hard to complain about this I feel that they only really did this
because their analysts or whatever saw evidence of an actual fist fiscal impact
with the fact that Amazon was accepting Mass Effect 3 returns as a defective
product I know that's really cynical and pessimistic it's nice that they're
throwing the Phantom of fandom a bone but you know if EA has the final say
this is just damage control to say that they they attempted something even if
fandom still hates it and I think that their hands were forced because they
could possibly lose money off of the degree of butthurt that the Phantom was
showing so as far as the fact that them them getting getting their way but they
kind of didn't get their way they didn't they didn't I mean it's gonna be really
hard to say until it comes out but I just I think there's gonna be a lot of
people that still aren't happy with it imagine if the internet it was what it
is today with Final Fantasy 7 right oh no game will ever be as hyped up or as
anticipated as Final Fantasy 7 was but we kind of just had to eat shit and deal
with it was kind of a jank ending we didn't really have the outlet or
resources to freak out on a company like this but what happened to you fee who
feet visit what do you mean what happened they weren't even there exactly all right
I think a lot of people probably already made up their mind on this DLC though
did you have anything to say Jason I'm just effect so I I will probably get
around to the series eventually but yeah not yet completely missed it well here's
something that impacts Mass Effect and it's and some other Bioware games it's
something Bioware is kind of known for and Bioware obviously tells these very
deep stories and sometimes romance is an option in these stories and Bioware has
been in many ways a pioneer for any type of relationship you want meaning if you
want to be in a straight relationship or if you want to be in a gay relationship
and they're starting to get some pushback for that and EA is EA who owns
Bioware is kind of the target of all this there is an anti gay letter writing
campaign going on right now EA's received several thousand letters
objecting to same-sex relationships in their games the letters are being sent
to a variety of senior leaders at EA threatening to boycott EA games until it
changes its policy EA is standing by it say standing by their games saying they
will continue to include LGBT characters in their games as options every one of
EA's games includes ESRB content descriptors so it's hard to believe
anyone is surprised by the content this isn't about protecting children it's
about political harassment that's from EA's chief spokesperson Jeff Brown
obviously Mass Effect 3 allows you to do man woman man man woman woman woman
alien shit you can do whatever you want in Mass Effect and Mass Effect 1 was
originally going to have same gendered pairings but with Dragon Age Origins
coming out on the horizon which had a more involved relationship system they
cut that content out and let Dragon Age Origins set that precedent mm-hmm and
Mass Effect 1 sorry to interrupt took a lot of heat from conservative funding
groups for having sex at all and many people having a sexual machine which
isn't like it's not that much more than you'd see on an episode of like nip tuck
or something I mean for real anyhow Star Wars the Old Republic is going to be
having same-sex relationships it's been reported and some people are not happy
with that because they don't they only see it as Star Wars like oh that movie I
loved in 1978 it's gonna get the homos we can't have that
later ain't no homo of course it almost had incest slightly so although that is
completely right although that is completely incest is a okay but heaven
forbid Vader be a homo which isn't even how it works Star Wars the Old Republic
takes place thousands of years before the movies and all that it's completely
different and saying it should be noted same-sex relationships aren't in the
game yet it's been noted for a future patch it will be in the game the letters
are coming from Florida the where the Florida Family Association is at and
again EA is standing by it but I mean they're doing these it's clearly a form
letter and if you look at the form letters like people will hand write
messages on them that say like remembers like look at this one there's a
handwritten message here you'll get a kick out of this thank you remember
Sodom and then it's signed I had a friend who turned into salt last week so
that shit is real and you will not minimize that that still happens can I
read can I read the hate mail here dear mr. Riccitello it was troubling to learn
that Bioware and Electronic Arts were pressured into committing to add
LGBT content to Star Wars video games pressured by who they always announced
it was going to be there I am also concerned that Bioware employees state
in postings at SWTOR.com that they have been censoring deleting and banning
forum members for expressing opposing views about including homosexual content
in the games children play guess what on a person's private forum the First
Amendment does not exist for example if you're a guest in my home and you start
talking like you know imagine if we invite somebody over let's say Jason's
our guest and we invite Jason over in our house and Jason says you know I
really hate faggots and I don't know how you and Alan can be faggots together
what's gonna happen we're gonna throw him out right we're gonna we're gonna
ban him right we're gonna kick him out of our house and he's not allowed to
come here anymore obviously he wouldn't do that but I'm just he's sitting right
there and he's an example this is the same analogy here if you come into
somebody's house and say something they don't like they have every right to
remove you you don't get a First Amendment yeah the overwhelming number
of players on Star Wars games is children who do not need to be forced as
a captured audience to participate in homosexual content thirty-year-old
children living in their parents basement whoa whoa whoa again if you're
letting your child play an MMO unsupervised they're not getting that
$14.99 a month themselves someone's credit card uh-huh we ask that you
please adhere to your long-term policy of omitting and steering clear of this
type of advocacy representation in your games what EA had a policy no please do
not include LGBT content in Star Wars video games that will impact so many
children thank you remember Sodom there it I mean the facts are just being
distorted terribly I mean that this is here's the thing about this though is
that you know these people don't fucking play video games because video games all
together are the goddamn devil yep so there's no there's no real boycott
happening here this is all for show it's all for press it's all for show it's
just like those idiots that get out there at the funerals that say God hates
fags and you're burning in hell because America embraces fat mr. Rogers is
burning in hell because you know America's a fag-loving country and all
this I hate that I'm using that word so much tonight but unfortunately I see it
in these you know protests and things like that and it's just they do it what
for attention for those that remember I know this isn't all that similar but
when nipplegate happened with Janet Jackson at the Super Bowl the FCC came
out and said that for all the thousands of complaints that they got it was some
random group that was made up of 20 icky old creepy old white dudes that just had
a form letter and they spammed the shit out of the FCC so the the fact that
they're getting as many complaints isn't really representative of how the public
feels because these these are just really isolated groups telling that
they're following to send this form letter dozens of times and that adds up
that makes it's just people making a fuss because they have nothing better to
do with their lives they this is what they choose to do instead of going out
into their community and choosing to do some good because what Alan and I have
is so threatening there is no gay agenda because we're either at the bar or the
gym we don't have time stop you Amy stop it anyway so it's even I love that they
scan this in its signed I can't read that name is that homa Johnson home no
homa Jay Lorne homa Jay Lorne dear homa Jay Lorne shut the fuck up anyhow prop
CEA at least for standing by this whole thing because you know what I gotta say
this even though I haven't played Mass Effect 3 myself yet I spoiled myself and
looked at some of the stuff on YouTube I've looked at all the different romance
scenes I've looked at the female female I've looked at the male female I've
looked at the male-male relationships and I got to tell you the male-male
relationship that they do one of the one in particular they do in the game is so
well done it's it's kind of refreshing to see that it's a relationship that's
not about the bar or the gym or any of that stuff it's it's really touching and
they do it so well and so tastefully like I just can't believe people are so
offended by it they want to take it out of the game stupid if this is what
earned EA a big golden poo hold it up high right let's move on I'm all huffy
now after that story well let's do the mailbag let's follow that up with some
listener emails you know what the people I like to hear from let's do some
listener emails every week you guys send us emails you mailbag at orange lounge
radio.com and dark soccer opens up the email bag and read some of her favorites
but she's not here tonight we took a poo in the bag and detrimental to ourselves
isn't it here all right no there are there are some good emails tonight and
Alan's gonna read them tonight will writes us and asks can't remember if
this has been brought up on olr yet or not but have any of you checked out the
web series titled cron tendo it's one dude playing every single Famicom slash
nest game release in chronological order oh my god he plays them enough to give a
basic review and some history of the title needless to say it's a massive
undertaking and worth checking out he has a YouTube channel but much more
content is posted on the archive org site he also started a cron Sega series
which is going through all of the master system titles in order the humor is
pretty dry but fun to watch anyone wanting to know more retro gaming history
or looking for some old games to play will want to give it a look man some
people have a lot of time I think it's great it's a great endeavor though I saw
similar linked me to it might have been dark Sakura actually a group of let's
play people on YouTube there's four of them they did a simultaneous battle
toads the original that game is hard as hell it's it's on YouTube but it's quad
screen just a competition to see who could get reach the end of the game the
fastest and it's filled with swears because that game is hard now is very
fun so look up about battle toads competition for that second email is
from Stan who writes hi olr I have a question for you and anyone listening or
this could be a future fool question what video game franchise would you like
to see reimagined or translated into another genre for example the morrows
the Mario for example the Mario series was fantastic as an RPG yes my answer
would be seen the Kingdom Hearts and Final Fantasy characters be introduced
in a Soul Calibur game so like Kingdom Hearts and Final Fantasy well there was
our guys you want to kind of stretch it a little bit I also think it'd be funny
to see Grand Theft Auto reimagined as a Japanese dating sim game now that's just
silly signed Stan sent from his iPhone and he's very upset about the Instagram
news this week no um gosh that's that's a tough one what would I like to see
cross genres and persona 4 is getting a fighting game and I saw that email from
Alice and I was like what how about an 8-bit version of demon souls like the
platforming game where it dials up on a modem it's just basic online no it's
just asshole Mario is all you guys have heard of the the the portal mod for the
original Mario one haven't you oh yeah the Mario with the stylized oh yeah have
you heard what the latest update is gonna be I think I heard something about
soundtrack six player co-op now that sounds fun yeah not exactly cross genre
unless you want to say it's portal being ported to 8-bit sidescroller that that
yeah that question is really insanely difficult yeah my mind is just stuck in
the fact that Super Mario RPG was freaking gorgeous and that was like the
first RPG that ever really meant something to me and I actually I think
it might be my very first RPG I ever actually beat Superstar Saga was not
half-bad partners in time I didn't get far enough into but was still pretty fun
I mean a Disney RPG Kingdom Hearts was grand I don't I don't know that there's
one specific series that would mean something to me in a different genre
though that I could really pick yeah this is a hard one especially because I
didn't really think about it beforehand like I'm trying to look through my game
collection right now and see if anything jumps out of my eye is like something
I'd want different Alan did anything come to mind for you at all I'm still
thinking about it I have some great comments from chat oh let's hear some of
those chat that orange laundry new calm god of war in the style of Mario Party
Kratos is mad cuz he got max stars but someone else got a star cuz they didn't
get any stars how about okay I got one I got one I got one Saints Row as a
Pokemon game but it's hose gotta catch them all I catch them all and it's so
many different ways or it's diseases cuz Saints Row is a fucking hilarious game
and I would like to I'd like to see it as kind of like a silly RPG call me call
me crazy any other comments from chat or was that it I'm looking people are
talking about Mario franchises Call of Duty Oh a first for our head shot
against Princess Peach how about Mass Effect as a more fantasy RPG like with
hit points and shit instead of the whole like first person although I gotta say I
do I don't know shows Shepard arrives on this hit L and pulls out a gun blade not
that crazy but I don't know that I gotta admit I'm not much of a first-person
shooter type person but the map the combat Mass Effect is pretty darn good I
guess I really wouldn't change it I did hear though they were doing that legit
first-person shooter out of Mass Effect and that would've been kind of fun to
play I think yeah us to move the music game as an RPG kind of dance summit
style yeah cuz you got kitty Ann and then you know she could cast spells
disco spells disco spells that would be the name of the game disco spells well
all right ah all right there you go that's it for the emails tonight send
us emails mailbag at orange lounge radio.com again that's mailbag at orange
lounge radio.com my answer to that question also is Ridge Racer but as a
puzzle bobble slash puzzle you're dropping cars down they just trying to
fill blocks like poll poll here weird all right let's do the F use of the week
it's the part of the show where we get angsty
I'll start tonight fu to that people that are sending those letters to EA
there's so many reasons to hate EA but that's not one of them that's one of the
reasons to appreciate what they're doing so F you to all of them F you to sheep
F you to people that are sheep because that's who those type of people are are
sheep so think for yourselves F you to sheep Alan I guess F you to the fact
that I had a job interview two weeks ago and I didn't get it you know shit happens
it's good to have an interview but also while I was trekking home from that
interview for the job I didn't get I was completely done up in a suit dress shoes
you know interview attire rolled my ankle on uneven pavement and completely
ate shit on the sidewalk hilarious I'm sure should be on YouTube if anyone had
a camera going out so yeah F you to I guess not getting a job and being a
klutz in the middle public F you did not having a job and needing a new pair of
pants now yeah nobody to buy it throw the pants out because the road roush was
so bad it ripped all in it do you have anything Jason F you to myself for
forgetting how to get out of a door of a car I have this really nasty gash on the
right side of my head because I apparently when I grabbed my bag in turn
to get out of the backseat of a car I leaned forward and just completely
knocked the corner of the door it hurt a whole hell of a lot and it looks pretty
nasty and it feels kind of nasty but anti F you to immune systems and the
ability to recover from that and I think there was another thing something about
keys and doors and where I'm staying while I'm out here but I think I think
the injury made me forget it so I guess I don't have it right now if anyone asks
story though if anyone asks someone tried to mug you and you beat the shit
out of them and that's the little mark or tell him it's a sex injury let him
try to figure it out I think I was coming up with some kind of I I tried to
participate I was a casted for the role of something and face-off and that was
the suspicion mark they tested to see how how good my face bar fight bar fight
yeah bar fight go with that cuz that coat you'd like a beer bottle could have
hit you right there oh yeah easily I bar fight right position mm-hmm all right
there it is your F use the week all right a few more news stories for you
guys and then we're gonna open up the skype line actually we're gonna hear
from some people from PAX East first I'm gonna bump their call in first night so
we can talk to them about PAX East because we all ignorant because we
weren't there so we need the ol army to help us out especially the New Yorkers
and and surrounding areas who did go so we'll talk to them in a little bit but
for now a few more stories for you guys Jason miss explosion man is finally
making it to iOS more specifically explosion man of any form is finally
making it to iOS which will arrive this summer you may remember a couple months
ago Capcom decided to make a very similar game by the name of Max explosion
that came out on iOS and there was a little a little a little kerfuffle
between the two studios Capcom and twisted pixel twisted pixel says well
you know Capcom made Megaman so I guess it's not all that bad and drama ceased
very quickly miss explosion man was obviously the hit sequel to the original
explosion man both Xbox Live arcade titles miss explosion man is heading to
the App Store with a version for steam on the PC games for Windows Live another
PC gaming service and Windows Phone 7 as well no specific pricing or specific
release date just sometime this summer if you were at PAX East maybe you played
it and if the game differs in any way call in let us know I am legit excited
about this game that I'm about to talk about and it's kind of sad when you get
more excited about the portable version of a game then the console version of a
game but you I have legit reason for this guy's epic Mickey of course is
getting epic Mickey 2 on the consoles which you know is all fine and dandy
whatever still we right we Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 okay so good for them
stepping it up but on the 3ds Disney epic Mickey power of illusion oh yes
it's what it sounds like it's a basic I don't want to say a sequel to but
heavily inspired by castle of illusion oh my god that game was gorgeous for its
day and a really amazing platformer oh my god and now it's gonna be on the 3ds
and it's going to incorporate yet you get to draw objects that magically
transform into Disney style 2d illustrations and then they're gonna be
3d on the 3ds is top screen blah blah blah but it gets its influence from a
lot of modern-day Disney movies like Tangled is gonna have a level and yeah
I'm so excited about this Beauty and the Beast from the screenshots here you can
see I mean it's just got that right mix of like retro look to it no Tron no sale
you never know you never know Peter Pan Tron is in that Kingdom Hearts game
coming out dreamed up distance so it just looks gorgeous I'm so excited like
I could care less now about the console one just bring me that 3ds game you guys
is a 3ds game I'm excited about yeah it's not just a port a 3d port of a
client of a good classic game like Zelda Rama in the chat room put it best I
can't say it any better myself shut up and take my money
amen Allen so this story is a doozy wow I'm not sure how to report this I guess
I wanted you to do this for a reason I guess the state of Arizona just looked
at Florida is the worst state of in the country and was like no we have to do
better and and for the last seven or eight years they have been okay so this
story is about a bill that has passed the both sides of the state legislature
so it's ready to be signed by the governor and it's the anti trolling
cyberbullying bill is it just me or does the governor of Arizona kind of reminds
you a Cruella de Vil like I'm not sure he's the one who put her finger in the
face of Obama yeah yeah just like don't doesn't she remind you of Cruella de
Vil a little bit like I'm not trying to get political or whatever and I'm not
it's it's just she's kind of nasty anyway sorry didn't mean to derail you
yeah so it passed both houses it's waiting for the governor to sign it a
governor Brewer and basically if let me read exactly what the the statute
dictates it is unlawful for any person with intent to terrify intimidate
threaten harass annoy or offend to use any electronic or digital device digital
device and use any obscene lewd or profane language or suggest any lewd or
lascivious act or threaten to inflict personal harm to the person or property
of any person so you cannot be shitty to people on the internet if the recipient
is in Arizona because if they try to prosecute you it could be a class one I
think misdemeanor which I want to say the maximum fine for that is $2,500 and
up to six months in jail is that the right direction that the receiver has to
be in Arizona I kind of figured it would have been the cinder the origin oh that
that is actually addressed here let me find it sorry yeah come arrest me
Arizona sucks what are you gonna do about it there are already exceptions to
the First Amendment which is freedom of speech which is which is obscene and
obscenity is very vague and also inciting violence site like saying this
person should get beat up let's all meet at the place in time that's inciting
violence but just being an asshole on the internet you know think of the penny
arcade greater internet theory have you ever read the comments to a story on
yahoo news oh my god they would fill the jails in Arizona overnight I'm fucking
serious go read the comments to any story on yahoo news story any of them or
the answers on yahoo answers it could be a story about like fluffy kitties and
dogs and it'll be like that dog is fucking ugly and it looks like an Obama
dog because Obama's ugly and all like this this is what oh my god I gotta go
to yahoo news right now and give you an idea what I mean here a whole new level
of quality for the show huh this is important because yes and this is this
is how it ties into the gaming world because of course what did gamers love
to do more than anything troll be shitty to each other with no consequences which
I guess this bill is trying to fix and if this bill does get signed it's like
many bills that California itself has had where it's effective as law for like
a minute and then it immediately gets shoved into the courts and it's
unenforceable and it gets juggled around in the courts to decide if it's
constitutional not for years and eventually goes away so already you know
people are saying that this is way too vague and there's no way this is
enforceable and blah blah blah and call me a grammar Nazi unless that's illegal
in this state but the text of the the text of this bill is it's one of those
things like for some reason there have been these weird weird quirk grammar
stories in the news lately notably talking about the the talking about a
the new iPad because they only referred to it during the keynote as the new
iPad so if anybody says I want the iPad 3 no you want a the new iPad but you you
read you read the text of the particular statute and what jumped out to me
immediately was it is unlawful for any for any person with intent intimidate
blah blah blah to use a any electronic or digital device it is unlawful for any
person to use a any electric or digital device is one little letter I don't I
don't mean to like narrow in on this but it's just kind of like the language
already sucks but to throw something in there that just doesn't make any damn
sense come on guys so if I write something rude on the side of a toaster
incentive trolling here's I just fucking arrest you in Arizona because you're
trolling you are now a wanted criminal in Arizona since the bill stipulates
that the offense only has to occur on Arizona soil that basically puts the
entire internet on notice according to this article so if the infraction
allegedly is it is viewable within Arizona which of course Facebook last I
check doesn't filter themselves out of Arizona maybe they should now that'll
make the people in Arizona really happy Google already block YouTube in Arizona
yet yeah that'll probably be in next week's stories we out so if the
infraction is you can view it from an Arizona network then you I guess
according to this bill have the right to try and prosecute the narrow mindedness
of something that in their dream little world could affect to the whole freaking
world another addition to this is that if the trolling is contributing proof
if you're able to prove that it's attributing to actual stalking of a
person then that would bring it up to a class 3 felony and there's a whole
additional cache of stalking laws that would then be brought into this I guess
it's supposed to be a countermeasure to cyberbullying which I do believe kids
have killed kids have killed themselves because of hate pages made like this
page that someone is you know a fat slut on Facebook that's shitty and parents
and teachers should get involved so cyberbullying sucks but an anti trolling
bill is not the way to go about it at least not the way it's written so some
sections of Yahoo News have apparently switched to requiring Facebook logins
which I guess a lot but here let me give you an example here's a story on
President Obama wishes Jews Christians happy Passover Easter so what's the harm
in the president wishing people a happy holiday for whatever it is they believe
it right nothing wrong with that right let's see
Jack Haynes says Obama stop lying we know you're a secret Muslim Bob Harvey
says Muslim use a fabric Bob Harvey says I'd vote for Reagan's corpse before I
vote for this egotistical clueless inept narcissist there actually is a story
about a dead politician beating an alive one Jack Van Valen says did he get the
okay from the Muslim Brotherhood like and the thing if you if you are
Republican Democrat whatever I don't I don't care you Romney Obama just don't
fucking vote for Rick Santorum seriously oh my god like that I draw the fucking
line at that asshole but I mean he is the president scroll up what's the
headline again Obama wishes President Obama wishes Jews Christians happy
Passover Easter the White House Christmas card from this most recent
December was I think their cat or their dog I don't remember what fucking pet
they have it just said happy holidays that's it no Merry Christmas or Hanukkah
or anything happy holidays with no Christmas tree and no nativity and the
Christians flipped their shit now he's wishing Christians and Jews a Passover
some Christian sorry flip their shit yes so it's yeah can't win for losing any
how it's okay if you're Muslim all right now that Christian or at you can't we
all just get along holidays of advertising past all right now only if
you're in Arizona all right look less politics more gaming stories Jason help
with well I guess it's not exactly politics but cute childish I owe cute
iOS app childhoods end back online after pedo bear mix-up Apple was worried it
might be a recruiting tool for pedophiles essentially what this boils
down to is that there was a tower defense game called childhoods end which
featured large bears converging on the point where you would die in a tower
defense scenario and the developer submitted an update and the one
particular Apple the one particular App Store reviewer got a hold of it and said
why is pedal bear advancing on a childhood game and they they sent the
developer a notice that they will need to take extended time they will be they
will need additional time for an extended review and immediately followed
that up with direct contact with the developer and expressing their concern
and caution over the subject matter I've never heard of this app before and I
looked at a I looked at a lot of stuff about it but perhaps one of the things
that doesn't exactly help why were you so interested in a pedo bear app I'm
just researching the story the description of the app says use your
wits and tactics to guide big Phil along his quest in this engrossing defense
game with towers join big Phil now and help him navigate his adolescence as he
fights off the evil teddy bears of his childhood your tactical skills and with
a little bit of luck is all big Phil needs to see him through his teenage
years not exactly the childish that you would expect but you know you know
what's in a name there's a couple things coming out about the this article I
haven't exactly understood what exactly this is but they put a there's a
screenshot of the in-game bears versus a picture of pedo bear and saying of
course the image is broken now so I can't recite it off but it's it's it's
drawing a contrast that this is a teddy bear you will see it in almost any
American child's home that has stuffed animals why is this a big deal I mean we
know why it's a big deal but this particular version just makes no sense
the the game was subtly changed the art for the bear was changed a little bit
at the update resubmitted and I believe it's been approved at this point now
Peter bear free yeah if one of those things said it's a silly situation for
something that probably didn't need to happen but it did so man you know one
more news story for you guys before we get to the calls and as if this show
couldn't go any further down the toilet I think this news story is kind of like
it's trolling that somehow is traveling across the game blogosphere because this
guy can't be fucking serious I'll go governor Brewer well the arrest this
man it is who did this it was Camille german pres I'm sorry if I butchered
that name but Camille german pres talked about studio are kato's they made the
game hell yeah for Sega it's one of their first games to come out they're
taking a month off and then they're gonna come back and do some more games
but saying it's a guess packs East booth the comment was quote we're gonna make
two games one game on P and one game on poo yes that's right one game on P one
game about P and one game about poo it's going to be a steam game I think okay
and yeah it's on I swear to God it's on every game blog go go look at any of them
and this to peepee poo-poo presented with no comment is that what I just heard
do I need to comment on this story about what is there possibly I mean can we set
the bar we already had news stories about the the urinal games where they
were installing games on the urinals for men to play or you know women if they
want an extra challenge while they relieve themselves women get the metal
gear solid version where no one catches them in the bathroom cuz that might be
kind of awkward for my birthday will you get me the pea and poo plush dolls that
are in chat if that's what you really want is this for real yeah they were on
sale in the cast are actually a couple years ago you would know that I just I
have an idea what a poo plush doll looks like but I want it oh god they're so
cute
maybe they got license to this game or something I don't know you need a
license okay nevermind maybe pee and poo have been licensed they're the actual
characters Rama can you post salacious pops linked to the tumbler so the
podcast listeners have an idea or talking about cuz I I can't how much do
they want for this Oh sorry particular all this item is discontinued no pee and
poo for you I'll make you a poo for your birthday oh if you go on eBay you'll
find that pee and poo plushies are a collector's item how much do they go for
and on that note we're gonna go to the Skype line we're gonna open it up right
now and take your calls at one eight seven seven game OLR or our username on
Skype is orange lounge radio actually I do want to make sure our PAX East people
get through so I'm gonna kind of wait and let them call in first here cuz I
want to hear from people who went to PAX East against one eight seven seven game
OLR our username on Skype is orange lounge radio and here they come
hi you're an orange launch radio who's this it's Rama what's up everyone what a
surprise hi Rama how are you I'll do it good how about you I I don't know what
to think after I've seen the pee and poo plush dolls but yeah my thoughts
exactly all right so you literally just got back in the door from PAX East right
yeah about an hour ago give or take and you've been listening to OLR the whole
time I'm sure yes yes yes behold the power of all of smartphones so how was
how was PAX East I had fun I really enjoyed it all right there's your PAX
East wrap up have a go have you been to PAX East before yeah this is my third
PAX East this is your third PAX East where does this rank because I was
reading some negative negativities on Twitter the negativities are probably
coming from the people that were complaining about the fact it was the
same weekend as anime Boston hey look people if you gone to more than five to
six anime conventions in a year it wouldn't kill you to go to a gaming
convention which was a hell of a lot better just just please shower while
you're at the convention that's all we ask I actually at the game you can at
this one there was a lot of showering there was very little confunk laughing
because act-deaf in the chat room the pee and poo dolls might be out of stock
but now there's an HIV plushie so oh geez and the habit there it's in a
family with a hepatitis C and a tuberculosis and polio I love the
internet I love it so much oh yeah PAX East so what was on the show floor what
were they showing we didn't hear a lot of news news come out of PAX East no no
it was just from like there's a lot of independent developers especially from
the Boston area I mean there was a big all this big Microsoft display really
then really pushing the Kinect games over in the corner was Nintendo over the
same place they were last year pimping out the 3ds with one new game spirit
camera it was a nice mention of MMOs you had League of Legends all the way towards
the back of the expo hall but packed all the damn time there were people
wandering around checking out lotro and D&D online and one other thing that
packs does a lot of too is that they just have like it's not just about the
new games or whatever this on the show floor but there's like like people
sitting in the hallways playing card games and people playing D&D in rooms
and people playing Magic the Gathering and classic games and you I mean how
many freaking games did you see people playing too many I mean there was like
Catan I mean there was one booth I think I forget the name of it but you could
pick up a game and play like borrow and just learn to play it I remember early
yesterday afternoon I was coming back from expo hall I ran into a daisy
cosplayer we were started talking next to you know I'm sitting there with her
husband a couple or two other people were sitting there playing a round of
Cards Against Humanity good times oh yes yes indeed um did you go to any of the
panels because I know there's a lot of great panels and things that come out of
them packs a lot of announcements come out of the panels I went to one panel
the whole weekend it was the nerdcore hip-hop panel which is something I look
forward to every year nice how was that it was great it was a little bit
different from last year's where it was front a lot mega Rana came Murdoch they
pretty much discussed the history of hip-hop nerdcore how it came together
last year mega had discussed more about how he got into it his backstory this
year it was a little bit more about front a lot it was pretty cool um who
did the concert this year was there any concert yeah there was a lot of concerts
Friday night was more was um Metroid metal and the proto men I forgot who was
on I think was storm runner I think that was the first one I caught a part of
Metroid metal and this was my first time listening to them and I was like wow the
best way I can describe Metroid metal is this take Metallica India prime at plus
one I love Metroid metal we've played some of their stuff on the show it's
good stuff I picked up both their albums will be listen to it on the way back
very nice Saturday night was a Colton Paul and storm front a lot and mega ran
okay wait look what I found look what I found Metroid metal
I can't wait for Metroid scream oh oh Rob here's a quick story that you'll
greatly appreciate hmm as we were as me and Jovian walking into the eye this is
a convention center I had said to her that I saw somebody with a x-plate a pin
on their back I'm like I threw mine in the garbage he's like why I'm like
because I don't support you for the person at least six feet in front of me
over her he's like yeah I can't stand them either next you know it is about 20
to 30 people going into convention to complain about how much g4 sucks well
done Boston well done yes yes indeed all right so before I let you go what else
do we need to know about PAX East anything else you got to share with us I
did check out a couple of games um Final Fantasy theater rhythm it's a fun game
Oh only Square Enix can take a music rhythm game and make it into an RPG 40
bucks worth is it worth it yeah I said that's definitely a day one purchase
hmm interesting okay all right I also checked out Sonic the Hedgehog for
episode 2 and is it as shitty as the first one I love the graphics the
controlling not so much I'd wait but I but this was something funny because we
were talking to one of the people at the booth sorry I had a cry for Sonic talk
to one the guys at the booth and you say it's only going to be on 360 and ps3
because this is a wheeze hardware limitations they won't be able to port
it and I said to my sister uh but yet I have Sonic 4 episode 1 on my Android
phone and the guys like yeah what does that tell you very nice well Rama I'm
glad to hear you had a good time at PAX East I wish I could have joined you guys
out there but now looks like off to do Seattle this year and maybe maybe Boston
next year if money let's say 2013 bro 2013 oh well our sweet um a fond of me
for your birthday hello that's gonna have to have well the way I see otherwise
tell me go to finally I might have to go west young man oh good cuz all I was
about to hear was excuses and I'm not having any of that so we hope to see you
I don't need an angry Rob I don't I don't need that
rar all right I better let you go Rama one more thing for you I got one more
thing um Assassin's Creed go to go to their Facebook fan page you're having a
contest for the best cosplay please vote for my sister Lady Ava she made the
the Heliquin costume from scratch and it's fucking phenomenal please vote for
her that's what that's it you got it take everybody bye bye I gotta make a
quick call here sorry I see other calls coming in but I've got to make a quick
call here because somebody very special wants to be on the show and I need to
oblige here if I can find them because they said they were on Skype but I don't
see them this is amazing radio we're gonna call them right now try to get
them on the phone I'm gonna hope it works this is live radio boys and girls
making a call right now trying anyway hi hi dark Sakura hi how are you I'm the
voiceless lender ah see you do sound like hell I told the blisters at the
top of the show that you sound like hell but I'm sorry to hear that it's alright
I'm feeling better that's good listening to olr with Jason and Alan is making you
feel better well that and exceeding amounts of Robitussin and Sudafed she's
high as hell right now no way I can take all this stuff with no if you want to
see me high as hell you should have seen me when I had pneumonia a few years ago
and was on Vicodin encoding all the time dark soccer is there anything you
wanted to say on tonight's news or anything we talked about oh yeah one
comment and this that clearly is a comment on pee and poo games well sure
me farted too with all the Capcom stuff oh that's that's good to have the
comment from Jeremy appreciate that especially so we're not doing the show
at your house anymore but you has a birthday coming up yes I do so when we
come back in two weeks cuz we're not gonna be here next week we come back in
two weeks it'll be like your birthday show weekend so what are we gonna do
for your birthday cake and pinkberry that sounds doable I think we could do
that yeah because well I mean I'm doing a something this Friday but I you know
me when I have my birthday I like to let the party go you know for a couple weeks
exactly make it last you only get one a year so make it last for a month exactly
and you remember the the the beer and pay and cake potluck I do well I'm
thinking about having a pie party I'm thinking about it pie is awesome so I
think you should definitely look into doing that yes or either that or just
Dave & Buster's and I drink until I bar for something I don't know I hope you
feel better in time for that to come around I hope this doesn't like stick
around for a week no it's all allergies I on Thursday I played over I was over
at Becky's house playing with her son in the backyard that was very grassy very
allergic to grass and I started stuffing up like right after that and Friday I
was just sniffy got a sniffy over and then started hacking so that's why I
have no voice better huh I hope you feel better thank you I am all right and I
hope you're not too mad I changed the classic game of the week no bitch all
right I kind of expected it cuz honestly I you know I would have been
disappointed if I didn't get to do the one I wanted exactly so we'll hear that
in two weeks when we come back with OLR anything else you want to let the
listeners know before we let you go pass out from Robitussin I'm not gonna pass
out from Robitussin not for another hour anyway all right then before I hang up
on you um no bye bye bye bye dar Sakura thanks for calling it's always good to
hear you know check in say hello the phone's ringing off the hook tonight hi
you're on orange on radio who's this so Shane hi Shane what's up I'm playing
World of Warcraft that's what's up did you go to PAX East this weekend I
totally didn't so why are you calling I don't know why are you calling you you
called us what do you want what's on what's on your mind um I wanted to
respond to the EA getting the worst company of the year thing or whatever
uh-huh I totally after reading EA statement that they put out I felt
really bad for them and I kind of feel like the internet won and lost because
they were just way too loud and they should not have you know beaten Bank of
America of all people you do realize in their statement they need like they said
well at least it wasn't Halliburton or did it and yeah they named like three of
the prior winners of the contest I didn't know their prior winners but
still I don't I don't think they should have even come close to winning I think
there were a lot of other companies up there that I saw and they're like half a
picture I would see on Kotaku when I'd sadly go to their site like I think I
saw a Best Buy up there which they deserve to be up there I think I saw I
think I saw AT&T which deserved to be up there here's the thing though here's the
thing does it really matter it's just the internet it's a poll on the internet
no honestly I guess it's publicity and you know the whole saying about
publicity and stuff and it's never bad blah blah blah well right after we
reported on that we turned around and talked about a couple good things that
EA is doing and I'm sure you have opinions on these so first yes the Mass
Effect 3 ending um I'm torn I appreciate what they're doing it's still not what I
would like but one of the writers clarified some things this week on
Twitter and it sounds like a lot of the doom and gloom that people inferred from
the endings were because the writers thought we were smarter than that but
you know that's a stupid thing to think when you're basing it off of things
you've seen in the game for the past however many years the series has been
going so I'm excited to see the extended cut I know it's not going to satisfy me
though because it's not what I exactly want which you know that's an impossible
request anyway I kind of I mean can they do anything to make you happy though um
yes what they could do is make a Mass Effect 4 with all my same characters and
just make a new story and keep it going cuz I am not done with Shepard or any of
my crew members even the ones that may or may not have died in 3 and so you're
trying to sleep with and continuing your relationship with yes especially Caden
and you want a more explicit Mass Effect 4 no no but better romance scenes would
be nice because it's it's like you know maybe a ten-year-old came up with them
and they didn't have any concept of what a relationship is besides like kissing
and holding hands and maybe like hitting the other person every so often well
wait a minute though okay let's get into the other story which is about the whole
target of the EA is a target of the anti-gay campaign so you've you've
obviously romanced Kaidan with your with your man Shep so your benefits yeah
you're benefiting from the content that they've put in the game a do you think
this campaign means anything no it's just something for that stupid
organization to do this week cuz they pick something new every week and B well
you kind of like showed me these scenes that you know the the man-on-man with
Kaidan and all that and how well done they were well they're well done well
okay wait wait let me back up the romance scene is not well done once you
get into the romance part but like the date scene and the conversations they
have brilliant because I aware for the most part can write amazingly well but
they need to learn a thing or two about romance scenes cuz Dragon Age that was
laughable I didn't see Mass Effect 1 I didn't do anything in two because you
know saving myself for Kaidan and in three it's like let me get pushed down
on the bed and then we're gonna roll around for like half a second and oh
we're under covers now and we're sleeping okay but it's not like they're
gonna get porno on you you know but it was also more like can't spoil things it
was like a shirtless scene of something that you do earlier in the game with
another crew member that isn't romantic at all wrestling well there's like a
like a little sparring match that's kind of what it reminded me of except we had
no pants all right pants in the sparring match all right but but otherwise I
mean it's certainly more interesting than what we've probably seen in any
other video game wouldn't you say probably more interesting you know the
male male or female female stuff we've seen in other games which has been
remarkably little but I'm sure in other games there have been better male female
romance scenes because I assume that the developers are probably straight and
have more experience with that like they couldn't just load up like a porn
website okay that is pretty blanket statement to make though I mean there's
probably hundreds of people that work at Bioware I'm sure there's a couple people
there that have some you know first-hand experience well I'm saying the ones that
that designed the scene not that worked there period gotcha sure they're like
three all right uh Shane I gotta let you go to get some more calls you have
anything else you want to say mmm oh you should go download the rest of your
download content for Mass Effect 2 because the shadow brokers what I did
today that $10 one and it was amazing it was so so good right now except I spent
all my points on that pinball arcade game well go buy more points one more
problem solved holy crap I gotta let you go bye now bye bye all right one eight
seven seven game olr excuse me or username on skype is orange lounge radio
acidic vampire in our chat room says the actual romance scene is kind of dorky in
Mass Effect 3 but the after romance scene is quite touching bonds double o
six says enchanted arms for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3 that has tons of guy on
guy action I vaguely remember that but I don't remember having tons I just
remember being one of the first but anyway we have more calls coming in so
let's get to them hi you're on orange launch radio who's this hello you're on
orange launch radio we can't hear you hello oh no I heard it it's click hello
wait did you hear me yes we do now hi yes damn mic switch gotta love those
zenocore from the OKC how you guys doing hey how you doing zenocore see I knew
you knew how to work your Skype it's had to be something like that all right
what's on your mind buddy and not much of it I purchased Arkham City finally
because I said screw it I'm not gonna get any DLC anyway and it's ruined
gaming for me now I can't play half the other games because it's not as
satisfying but I'm sitting knocked everything out of Barbara I can't play
Skyrim now because the combat sucks I can't play dragon aids I can't play half
the RPGs I got anymore because the combat just does nothing whatsoever
Arkham City is just that fucking good like it raised the bar that high that
now everything else sucks asylum is better than that I mean the only thing
that holds a candle to it as far as a RPG like environment I'm not counting
Mass Effect because it's a first-person shooter is mountain blade of all the
things that's the guts they got the most visceral hand-to-hand combat that I know
of in an RPG like setting and that's a conquest game so technically doesn't
even count and it's very disappointing to me is it just the combat that you
love about Arkham City or what is it about this game that makes it so great
it well I guess just the way it goes you actually feel like you're really whooping
ass I mean everybody knows this about Arkham City in Arkham Asylum anyway this
isn't new news but the fact that nobody else has done this in any other game yet
is freaking annoying to me I mean I finally upgraded my POS computer to
something that's near top of the line I play Arkham City and I can't play half
the other action action or RPG games on it because they all suck as far as that
it's all I'm doing is clicking the mouse at least in Batman you're somewhat
managing things and using multiple weapons all at once I mean you hell when
they did added that stuff with Catwoman's like holy shit this is fun as
hell just beating people to death little whip but it is it is really it's just
it's funny to hear you say how much it's just ruined everything else because it's
so good I know it man I never thought I'd be in this position so I just blew
almost a thousand bucks on this machine and I've gone back to playing like Space
Harrier 2 on the on the Sega emulator I got off of Steve and everything else
just because nothing after I start after about 10-15 minutes I got to put it down
because it's not as good as Arkham City or I look oh my god so what about the
rumors of Arkham world I'm not paying attention to those we'll see but that
combat engine is unique it's not gonna work in anything that's that large
because it's tied to together like the combat from like a way back when from
the game Oh knee when that first came out of ps2 that combat system was
amazing but the way they built it you couldn't do anything else with it there
is no multiplayer ready thing because the way they glued it together so I
think Arkham City and Arkham asylum that style of gameplay is gonna be stuck in
that have you checked out any of the DLC yet I'm not going to Robin Nightwing
whatever all I need is a big bad cat woman and I'm good that's interesting I
don't know why but I find that very interesting that even though you love
the game so much you're like man don't really need to do the DLC cuz like for
me like I I probably will have to play all that Mass Effect DLC at some point
just because I'm getting so into this you know Mass Effect DLC Jesus man what
a what a racket that was have you played the Mass Effect DLC and no because my
roomy he bought the game run it released and he was gonna ruin it for me so after
seeing what actually were rewards you get it's like beating Rygar but not
doing it in an old-school way the old-school Rygar ending was something
you got because you fucking earned it everybody can get to the ending in this
game and it's gonna be a piece of shit so why bother oh my god pay for it
that's a classic 8-bit game I really need to try and do start to finish like
your event yeah my car was two screens and one of them has some animation on
that's it but that game was so freaking hard you're glad to see that screen
because you do not not many people get to see it but seriously yes but uh and
then they're just gonna slap a patch top of Mass Effect 3 to explain the
explaining the ending apparently so they're not gonna actually make it to
where you actually steer the character in one of three directions without
making a single choice at the end which ruins the whole experience for me so
now they're not getting any my money for that series anyway all right any last
thoughts before we let you go tonight Xenocore yeah the dark Sakura let that
tussin soak in there girl remember put some water in it shake it up more
tussin tough it out all right now hopefully she's listening I hope she
heard that all right take care buddy later all right bye
1877 game olr username on Skype is orange lounge radio I guess we can try
and squeeze in one more call we're getting a lot of calls tonight so I'm
gonna really try and fit in one more call here before we say goodnight
meanwhile I need to read tweets I have I have been totally ignoring the
Twitter's at twitter.com slash olr but let me read some tweets for you right
now no I'll take a call then we'll do tweets be the last call tonight hi who's
this yeah hey Zaku what's up yeah me and uh Adam your Ron was you after the
column we all went to packs together hell we even room together nice how was
it how'd you enjoy PAX East it was uh was it was almost a almost the same as
um last year in terms of crowds like like Friday was just like the heaviest
day like just trying to try my luck in in watching these trailers or playing
some of these games there were like at least two two hours plus in line it
wasn't even worth it what I did do was just hit up most of the panel though
stuff like the harmonics panel on Saturday when they actually explained
the whole process is to how rock band blitz became actually got it gone about
like it actually started off as a prototype and you know within this was a
prototype that was done within the course of a at least three years even
though it didn't pick up full steam until that last summer so it basically
went through several iterations where you know it for example the they
actually they did a lot in terms of trying to figure out the proper controls
seeing that they they propose so many so many ideas and solutions that most of
them ended up failing until they found the one that worked which is basically
either the joystick using the the D pads and the buttons or the shoulders just to
just to hit both notes and then the whole notion of having whether or not to
make it just like like frequency and amplitude in terms of a shifting you
from one instrument to another automatically so it deviates from that
in the sense that you can just play any you could stick with one completely like
I tried it today and I was I was pretty much bouncing from one one track to the
other within the song so you know coupled with the fact that you could
just do mostly power-ups that you gain as you as you obviously hit more notes
then it just basically it's almost like audio surf but in the sense that
everything's structured more importantly everything is um it just said it's just
binary in the sense wait did they have to have audio surf too on the floor no
no no that wasn't there I'm pretty certain prime will probably that depends
if they the developers of get get themselves a booth for prime but back to
the point it's like like back in the days of amplitude it was pretty much the
same way but it's the fact that the songs themselves of rock are like a rock
nature where it's not like techno and this is one of the questions that was
brought up in the panel I guess they're there the rationale was in the it's
easier to just you know release a product in which on day one people who
have existing rock band users and consumers could just you know start
playing right away with their with their current with their current collection
whereas if they added things that normally wouldn't fit into a into that
rock band caliber like a techno trance on that was made you know that and made
frequency and amplitude pretty much a you know called classic then it would
just like folks have to start over from scratch let me let me try to get away
from the rock band stuff for a minute we've seen so much about it on the
internet what other panels did you get to all right the other all right other
ones I like let me see the Kotaku panel that was on Friday where everyone
everyone in that panel was taking it over for an hour so I just threw out one
little question in terms of a sort of like an inside thing in Kotaku if you
were like really in the in the site you would actually know like all their
sections like how they how they have their own blocks of stories they let
anyone have a panel they clearly are letting anyone have a panel so I want to
know our panel at PAX Prime yeah but that was that folks writing stories
within the hour and actually you know they actually they had a little work
actually air their grievances in terms of banning people or or or actually
taking pictures and so forth it was even live blogging that's productive open the
floor back up to the people dance on a website yeah I mean did they suck their
own dick in front of all you guys too no it's like they were just alright they
what happened was like the the editors or actually the former editor of Kotaku
was was spearheading the panel so the idea was that folks who just like pitch
their their story ideas and the audience the the audience would actually pick the
ones that that they would want to they would want to hear about and within that
hour they would have to actually produce it you know write an article for it did
they have a big on the site and did somebody judge people yeah the editors
obviously the editing team was pretty much making sure everything was there
all right no no disrespect but I could give two shits about the Kotaku panels
tell me about our other one all right the other one was caught the tail end of
the epic panel where cliffy be basically we're just going off on sir you know for
questions in the audience one of which was a you know a girl actually trolled
the whole panel is in saying that you know she wants to see Gears of War on
PlayStation 3 and to which cliffy replied he will if they fix the you know
they fix that god that weak rumble the ps3 controller and then she was promptly
arrested in the state of Arizona for trolling the panel all right but the
last one I caught was a was basically a classic arcade panel like you have no
interest in penny art you know packs they have they have an actual classic
arcade room like nothing but old arcade machines good I love that were the folks
from the from a cam the American classic arcade museum actually they ran the
panel with with a couple of developers who actually worked on the original like
the original older arcade titles one of which was a food fight and miss pac-man
and then the other the third one was he was a developer for a crew for the
cruising series as they were going through how back in the day they were
like they basically started off from their dorm dorm rooms at MIT to the
point where they they made they made mod kits for their for existing arcade
arcade cabs like one like one for missile command that actually extended
the gameplay but in the sense that you know you would get more revenue because
the the challenges would be harder you wouldn't be playing the same thing and
with your guy with a with a single quarter and sheer sheer skill could just
like stay there for hours on end so you know it gets to the point where they get
to buy Atari and then they get picked up and then they start creating this pac-man
and to the point where it leads up to the the crash we're running long here
Zaku let me let me just quickly ask you your favorite thing about the whole con
certain prizes swag it's just like a free shit I mean I think I played
battlefield 3 and a cop you know in a mini tournament and all I got was a 4
gig USB drive but it was just like not only that is the after party the the
curse party the curse is like a service site that hosts like all these forms
like including ones for Minecraft they had a killer party with like open bar
and everything and the whole works and that was yesterday and they're saying
me and Adam had had ourselves a kick-ass time all right Zaku I gotta let you go
but I'm glad you had a great time actually I'm a little jealous but I
guess I'm happy all right take care Zaku all right have a good one later some
things haven't changed all this coming out of people's MIT dorm rooms I I love
hearing the stories about the old game design though my god those guys really
loved what they did and it's just folks that were younger than you or I am now
you have designed these classic classic games all right I have to close up Skype
you guys we were running long now and I'm really sorry to those didn't get
through it was lit up tonight I still haven't even touched Twitter I've got to
quickly say we're running like so long so let me just read a few tweets here
Rhetortainment tweeted us saying Bank of America tried to foreclose on homes in
a state that they don't have the right to operate in how did EA win worst
company because it's the internet lol lol lol lol dark to see you says the
hunt at olr is heating up your next challenge starts this week it might be a
little different from what you're expecting go play the hunt go get your
score in joust he said he'll extend it to like Tuesday or Wednesday I know what
I'm doing on the bus tonight there you go you can you can you can work it on
your iPhone you exactly it's not restricted it's kind of like an on your
honor thing like if you go and Photoshop something you're just a dick and don't
don't play in our competition just to be a dick but if you're gonna play on
different platforms I think that's cool like I saw act def screenshot and
because he's from Mexico all the Xbox stuff was in Spanish and I thought that
was cool because I don't usually get to see that it's different let me read one
of Tiger Claus tweets here he always sends us some great tweets I need to cut
it a little short tonight but I will read this one because this is about a
company that we talked about a lot about here on the show Activision Blizzard has
been sued for patent infringement of virtual worlds usage due to World of
Warcraft and Call of Duty they're being sued by worlds Inc worlds Inc claims
that World of Warcraft and Call of Duty are violating the patent quote
technologies created by worlds have helped the business of virtual worlds
and gaming and the sale of virtual goods to grow into a multi-billion dollar
industry that was from worlds Inc CEO Tom Kidron while we are pleased to see
the gaming industry and is rapidly growing customer base of enthusiastically
embraced our patented technologies we deserve fair compensation for their use
this is the second time they've done this they filed suit against NC soft in
2008 for city of heroes it was dismissed after a undisclosed settlement was
obtained worlds Inc has been in business since either 99 or 2000 you know what I
don't know of them but to say they invented I've heard the name too but to
say they they're responsible for World of Warcraft and Call of Duty it's kind
of like dude I think copyright law online especially needs to be updated
because it's things have changed since the Revolutionary War just slightly ah
all right we got we gonna wrap it up we're running long tonight who knew that
it would be a long episode when we have guest hosts tonight but I'm so thankful
to you guys for stepping in tonight I really appreciate it Jason thanks for
being here do you have any final thoughts for listeners tonight I guess I
will say that actually as a result of this new job there's a chance I can make
these visits a little bit more regular they actually bring all of their out of
town folks in twice a year and so uh perhaps they'll start being a better
occasions for me to be able to get back on this show again for more than what is
this the fourth episode I've been on I believe I think so you come by anytime
you're welcome the door is always open for you even when we like move or
something and thanks for all you do once again for orange on trader calm again
and superly more importantly pee and poo plush 65 bucks that's it all right Alan
thank you for sitting in I know you live here and you sometimes don't have
another choice because I'll threaten to make you sleep on the couch but thank
you for filling in you're welcome do it for a while even though this happens you
know the apartment every week um good luck with a flop cast yeah bitch do you
have any final thoughts for listeners tonight I'm gonna beat Mass Effect 2
tonight I think maybe good luck with that yeah all right my final thought is
BRB Disneyland see you guys in two weeks thank you guys for listening to orange
launch radio thank you for subscribing to our show thank you for supporting our
show if you like what you heard here at orange lounge radio please tell a friend
or two about the show help spread the word that's all we ask you know we don't
have big advertising dollars behind this we don't have giant packs panels where
we can sit there and suck our dicks on stage for an hour to help spread the
word about the show so please tell a friend or two and then maybe we can get
that panel someday although honestly I would much rather have a panel let some
of those guys who founded the way from the classic arcade games of the past sit
in I just want to hear them talk so um have a great night everybody have a
great week have a great two weeks we'll be back in two weeks hopefully with Dark
Sakura and Loki all over again have a good one we'll see you then good night
you've been listening to orange lounge radio orange lounge radio is an orange
lounge production to join us for a live show visit www.allgames.com Sunday
nights at 6 p.m. Pacific time the views and opinions expressed on orange lounge
radio do not necessarily reflect those of the entire staff of orange lounge radio
or all games calm but we're probably right anyway see you next week