[SPEAKER_08]: You're listening to the podcast Orange Lounge Radio, episode number 454.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before we get to tonight's show, we would like to start with an important announcement that occurred during the taping of the Bobby Blackwolf show the night of the recording.
[SPEAKER_08]: Up first is that clip, courtesy of the Bobby Blackwolf show.
[SPEAKER_10]: But right now, it is 6 p.m.
[SPEAKER_10]: on the West Coast, 9 p.m.
[SPEAKER_10]: On the East Coast, and I want to say hello to all the OLR listeners that are coming in for OLR.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm Bobby Blackwolf.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm typically the opening act here on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_10]: We typically don't talk meta that much about where we broadcast all that often.
[SPEAKER_10]: We feel that those type of conversations are best kept off the airwaves and in private, but indulge us for a few moments as we discuss some things here.
[SPEAKER_10]: AllGamesRadio.com
[SPEAKER_10]: We've had a lot of great experiences here with this network from E3 Outpost to the Xbox Live Gamer Picks to PAX 08 and E4 All and the live broadcast.
[SPEAKER_10]: Lots of great things have happened that I know I personally will cherish for the rest of my life.
[SPEAKER_10]: And even though I was removed as station manager and site admin several years ago, I've enjoyed the community and the stage that has been here.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's been my home for one hour a week here on Sunday nights.
[SPEAKER_10]: There are changes coming to All Games Radio and they're changes I don't personally endorse.
[SPEAKER_10]: They're not necessarily bad, but they're not ones I personally want to be a part of.
[SPEAKER_10]: And one of the other show hosts here on the network stated that if all you wanted to do was just have a stage to do your own show and not attempt to help move forward to make the network a better place, then you needed to get out of the way.
[SPEAKER_10]: so even though I don't personally endorse the proposed changes I don't wish to stand in the way of them so tonight right now I'm announcing that this right here is my final broadcast on All Games Radio well
[SPEAKER_08]: This might be a good time to mention that there is a reason we haven't hung up just yet.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, Orange Launch Radio started as its own fully-fleshed radio station in 2002 on Live 365, and after five years, we made a business decision in light of escalating costs to move to the All Games Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: This arrangement, as Bobby mentioned, it was really initiated and championed for by Bobby.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been absolutely honored to have Bobby as he puts it in his words as an opening act for the past five years.
[SPEAKER_08]: We view it a little differently.
[SPEAKER_08]: But without Bobby's efforts, it's very possible that OLR, as we know it, would have ended several years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, change to All Games Radio is going to be a great thing for the station.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's time to let you all know that a plan was drafted some time ago that will require us in order to take Orange Lounge Radio to the next level to leave the network as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tonight's upcoming episode, episode number 454, will be the last Orange Lounge Radio on the All Games Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've been fierce supporters of independent podcasting and podcasters and this is not and will not change.
[SPEAKER_08]: We remain supporters and fans of the All Games Network even though the future for Orange Lounge Radio will involve our show being elsewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Out of respect to the other hosts and community at All Games Radio we will not be unveiling those plans here on their bandwidth.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know where to find us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, the show will go on next week and yes, Bobby is still the co-headliner.
[SPEAKER_10]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_10]: the community here at All Games we've had some good days and we've had some bad days people that are probably in the community more often than just Sunday nights know what I'm talking about but ultimately I will remember a lot of the good stuff the hardest part of this is that I will probably be leaving the chat room where I've idled for almost a decade sometime this week and it's going to be kind of hard to say goodbye to that but sometimes it's time to move on Tigerclaw
[SPEAKER_10]: You guys probably don't realize this.
[SPEAKER_10]: If it was not for Tiger Claw, this stage that we have been on probably would have collapsed a year ago.
[SPEAKER_10]: He is the man that has been keeping the light on for the rest of us because he's been kind of acting as station manager.
[SPEAKER_10]: He has championed bringing in other people, other podcasts to the community.
[SPEAKER_10]: I'm sure that he's going to help keep the light on for much, much longer.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thank you very much to Tiger Claw for everything.
[SPEAKER_10]: And also, lastly, Scott Rubin.
[SPEAKER_10]: And while Scott and I did not see eye to eye on everything, and I might have actually felt that there were some unfair characterizations made of me back on the All Games Interactive days, off the air, he has been very supportive of me and wanted me to succeed in everything that I wanted to accomplish.
[SPEAKER_10]: I am here to do this tonight because of him, because of his advice, because of his support.
[SPEAKER_10]: Without Scott Rubin...
[SPEAKER_10]: There would be no Bobby Blackwolf, literally, as in he actually picked out that name.
[SPEAKER_10]: I didn't come up with that name, Scott did.
[SPEAKER_10]: Just as Scott has moved on from all games, he's doing high-profile live streams for mainstream TV networks.
[SPEAKER_10]: It is time for me to move on from all games, but I thank Scott for every single opportunity that he has given me.
[SPEAKER_08]: We want to thank some people too, but our lists are probably very similar.
[SPEAKER_08]: First, Bobby Blackwolf, obviously, for all the obvious things we've already stated.
[SPEAKER_08]: The other hosts at All Games Radio that work their asses off to produce quality content for this network and promote the independent gaming community.
[SPEAKER_08]: I personally have loved meeting all of you at the various events.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Paxes, The E3s, The Outpost, so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Unfortunately, not every show is really in the All Games Network to promote the community, but I'm not going to dwell on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot that are very passionate about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've been noticed, you've been appreciated, and I hope we can work with you in the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: Although we don't want to name everyone specifically for fear of leaving someone out, if there's one host we need to tip our hat to besides Bobby...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's our own personal podfather and the man that taught us a lot about internet radio, Travis Donovan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Specifically to the OL Army, if you're hearing this, you've stuck by us through every tough decision we've made.
[SPEAKER_08]: You've supported us when we said we are no longer exclusively a Bomani show.
[SPEAKER_08]: You supported our creative decision to end the live afterbirth segment of our show because it just wasn't striking our creative spark anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: You supported us when we left Live 365 to take our show to the next level and we know you will support us as we leave All Games Radio to take it to Stage 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think this is a good time to reiterate, we will be back next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you will be able to listen to us just as easy as you do now but out of respect towards the network we're keeping that under our hat as to exactly how that's going to happen for a few more days.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tigerclaw gets our thanks as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: All games would not be able to function right now without Tigerclaw.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's passionate about this network and every host on this network owes you a lot of thanks.
[SPEAKER_08]: of course Scott Rubin although certainly we've mentioned Bobby a bit in how we ended up at all games Scott was a crucial piece of this as well although we give the mainstream gaming press a lot of shit on this show Scott is someone who lived it left it and built an online network that fit in his independent vision and we all have so much respect for that
[SPEAKER_08]: So, I know I've been monopolizing the conversation.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like the first time in probably five years I've read from a script.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I want to allow DarkSakura and Loki, because their OLR is just as much as me, to say anything they want to say about this as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like to thank myself for being awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, really, you said everything that I could say.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Jesus has nothing to do with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for letting us know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, anything?
[SPEAKER_07]: And I will still not be updating the radio app on PSP.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, our PSP.com will still stay out of date.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some things shouldn't change.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some things have to stay the same.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby, it's all you.
[SPEAKER_10]: Well, I think that this is the part where I'll be letting you guys go.
[SPEAKER_10]: I had to write my stuff to a script too.
[SPEAKER_10]: So any last words here before I send everybody off?
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't cry.
[SPEAKER_08]: That goes for you and it goes for the listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: It ain't over.
[SPEAKER_08]: We still have a show left.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stay tuned.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're still having a show tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know this is shocking.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is how you have to start the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: and good luck to everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I really, really wish all games the best of luck.
[SPEAKER_08]: And thank you so much for having us for the past five years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_10]: All right.
[SPEAKER_10]: Orange Lounge Radio is up next.
[SPEAKER_10]: Thanks so much, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Tonight, April 22, 2012, Halo 4 has a release date, Nintendo announces new games for the 3DS, and the upcoming enhanced Baldur's Gate won't be coming out for one particular system.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, Jamie Summers, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: It's always some fad diet with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not a fad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not fad diet, but it is always some diet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was really happy as a vegan.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you're purdy just the way you are.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not doing this for purdy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm doing it for healthy.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also say hello to Tech Master Loki.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's still on his pizza diet, clearly.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a diet.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, because that implies that I'm eating pizza all the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Loki, don't worry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think you're purdy just the way you are.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really not.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so anyhow, we're here.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're live.
[SPEAKER_08]: Live, as you'll hear on the podcast, as our live listeners heard for the last time, at All Games Radio, www.allgames.com, right after the Bobby Blackwell Show at 6 o'clock Pacific, 9 o'clock Eastern.
[SPEAKER_08]: Join our chat room at chat.orangeloungeradio.com if you want to chat live with us on this lovely evening.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the date today?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know.
[SPEAKER_08]: April 22nd, 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's right, because my birthday was last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Happy darn birthday.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before we get into our gaming weeks, let's talk about we were gone last week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We didn't have a show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know this was a whopper of a night to come back to, but hey, it's just how it went down.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, how was your birthday?
[SPEAKER_08]: What'd you end up doing?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not really a whole bunch of stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: I went to get delicious Indian food with you and Alan and Pinkberry.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan took me to Claim Jumper where we split an ID clear for dinner.
[SPEAKER_02]: I felt so sick that night.
[SPEAKER_02]: He got me a really neat art book from 1944 that I've had my eye on.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's very cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was very old museum-y when I saw the pics.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, on top of that, it was a lot of... Because keep in mind, this particular edition was fresh right after World War II.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it had some of the really cool art movements that had occurred just like 10 years before that.
[SPEAKER_02]: So for me as a designer, it was a real treat.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you and Alan got me a sailor suit for my Duffy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can look at your Duffy bear and say, Hey, Thaler.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, well, I love Duffy, you all know that.
[SPEAKER_02]: You two are the only people who got me presents.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have everything else that I pretty much want, so it's all good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Plus, once you get to a certain age, it's kind of hard to buy presents anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Outro Music
[SPEAKER_08]: and video games cost $60.
$60.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know that's how much I paid for Killer Instinct on the SNES?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I was going to say, I guess to be fair, video games have always been kind of expensive.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, Street Fighter 2 as a cartridge was, what, $80?
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't it one of those, or Mortal Kombat 2 or one of those?
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know what the most I've ever paid for a video game is?
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I probably do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was it your Castlevania Symphony of the Night on Saturn?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I've paid more.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, actually, the Saturn one was like $20.
[SPEAKER_07]: Your game with the dish.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would probably be a Neo Geo game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is a Neo Geo game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was $280 for King of Fighters 2000.
[SPEAKER_02]: But Dan and I thought it was going to be the last one to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: Little did we know the Summer Showdown 5 would be the last one to come out.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, we wanted to buy a brand new Neo Geo game just to say we had.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we were in a different place then.
[SPEAKER_02]: but um but no um I pretty much you know if there were the like the only thing that I actually had on my want list you know if you could call it that is an iPad and I'm waiting on that one because I'm going to Disneyland next month hello
[SPEAKER_02]: So, you know, I can wait on that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have my netbook.
[SPEAKER_02]: It works.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, it's sort of like, like I'd said, you know, back during Hanukkah, Christmas-ka, Kwanza-ka, whatever holiday was going on.
[SPEAKER_07]: Insert politically correct statement here.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Christmas, I can't remember how.
[SPEAKER_02]: Festivus.
[SPEAKER_02]: so it's like I've got tons of stuff I don't really need anything and I've got tons of stuff to do you know it's like it's not like I can't just go and play Mass Effect that Rob loaned me I have no problem just going and playing Mass Effect that I bought myself but anyway but you know I've got I have great friends and I have a wonderful hubby who sometimes can be a jerk face but for the most part is really cool
[SPEAKER_08]: You're going to make me sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's too much emotion on this fucking network tonight.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for the most part, like I said, I've got everything I pretty much need.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not all gimme gimme anymore.
[SPEAKER_02]: Although I do like the ABBA song.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was off last week because I went to Disneyland for Jamie's birthday I went to the final electronica that was the whole reason because I am such a nerd I had to go to the final electronica I've talked about it a million times on the show I don't want to re-explain it but you know it was really great to be there for the last show and everybody booing when they pulled the plug
[SPEAKER_08]: A little disappointed that they just literally shut the lights off on everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, grid's down.
[SPEAKER_08]: LOL, bye, get out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got to see the Tron pinball machine, but Flynn's Arcade was so crowded because people knew it was the last night it would be operating.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Dan's friend has one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_08]: has the deluxe edition too I need his address yeah I'm gonna go play uh supposedly they're keeping the Tron pinball machine at Disneyland it'll be like the one Tron thing still left in the parks um but it was it was kind of a crowded day um so we didn't get to do a whole whole lot but electronica but that's what we went for and I was happy um I did the driving so I didn't get to play a lot of games in the car sadly Loki you you guys have actually been out because you I
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys weren't on the last show before the vacation, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because that was the Jason and Alan show, right?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, because it was Easter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, how was your Easter?
[SPEAKER_08]: What have you been up to, Loki, personally?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not much, just hanging around the house and took Josh over to my mom's house and did the egg hunt and stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: He didn't really care about that stuff, though.
[SPEAKER_08]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, what video games have been in your world this week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, not so much actually playing, but we've been doing playthrough watching lately, Dan and I have.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's fair.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we watched a playthrough of Samurai Shodown because my friend Gary had never, he didn't even know about the game.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we're like, what planet are you on?
[SPEAKER_02]: And how are we letting you in our house?
[SPEAKER_08]: We're fixing this right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: Exactly.
[SPEAKER_02]: And we were even explaining some of the bad translation in it, some of the English, which was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Like how we were calling Amoksa a happy funster.
[SPEAKER_02]: And just showing, even talking about, because a lot of the characters in the game are based on historical and cultural fictional characters.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we were trying to explain.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then today we're actually watching a playthrough of Klonoa.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's why I said my next cat's name is going to be Klonoa.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh yeah, I saw that on Facebook.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm going to get a rat named Hupow.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because it's fun to say Hupow.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I actually, you know, I've got a new job so I've, and since I'm also in school full time and still have all of the graphic design projects that I took on while I wasn't working.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have been a busy bee, so I haven't really had that much time to sit and really play through anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't even had time to play much WoW, which... Oh my gosh!
[SPEAKER_02]: I've done like two dungeons all week, and then one of them was so fail that I quit halfway through.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate that.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then it just derails your spirit for the game for a whole week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just like, ugh, screw these people.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why are Horde players so stupid?
[SPEAKER_08]: One of my friends was telling me today about how Final Fantasy XIII too did that to him.
[SPEAKER_08]: He was running around for literally three hours trying to figure out what to do and realized he was in the wrong time thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: They went to the wrong part of the story and he was supposed to be in a chocobo that jumps.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now you know how I feel when my Kingdom Hearts 2 game glitched when I skipped a planet.
[SPEAKER_02]: and couldn't go back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I actually skipped all of Agrabah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Going to our chat room at chat.orangelongeradio.com, Breakman is in there saying, Sky doesn't have children or pets for their safety.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, I am the wicked stepfather to two kitties.
[SPEAKER_08]: My other half, Alan, when we moved in together, he brought old kitties.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're 12 years old this month, I believe.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're getting old.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're Medicare kitties, but they're still cute as hell.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and sometimes Sanrio will let me pet her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, Maruko is really an attention whore.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, all I have to do, like, I go into bed, lie down, get my DS open, like, I'm going to play DS or B on my iPhone, and, like, within minutes, and he jumps up on the bed, and he doesn't just, like, get on my feet like some cats do or get on my chest or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: He gets up in my face.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I am here, bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pet me right now.
[SPEAKER_02]: I told you what Shermie used to do when we had our bed on the floor.
[SPEAKER_02]: She used to crawl in under the sheets in the middle of it because Dan and I use, we have separate blankets because we're both sheet hogs.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we just use our own blankets.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Shermie would crawl under and then put her head on my shoulder and just start purring away and sleep on my shoulder in the morning.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's cute.
[SPEAKER_02]: And usually just get up, bitch, and feed me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything else for your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright.
[SPEAKER_08]: My gaming week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actually, not a whole lot because I've been focused on one game.
[SPEAKER_08]: What did you want to say, Jamie?
[SPEAKER_08]: You thought of something, didn't you?
[SPEAKER_02]: Damn stupid panda shit not installing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you, Blizzard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, you got in the WoW beta and it won't work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, and I left my hard drive at home and I was going to copy your files.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would say something about, well, this is why they call it a beta, but I don't want to get hit.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I have a 4 gig flash drive on me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can use that guy.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can borrow that guy over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a 1 terabyte hard drive just sitting there.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've got a flash drive on me.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow.
[SPEAKER_02]: But my thought is because I've moved my WoW folder in full before, I figured what I might be able to do is copy your installs and have them update on my computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: I just kept fast forwarding through the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did the guy say nanu nanu?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: The very last thing, you know, after he does his splooge business is you hear nanu nanu and then it fades to the credits.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, my childhood has just been raped.
[SPEAKER_08]: This porn wasn't from the 70s.
[SPEAKER_08]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was from like last year.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was done this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: and it's called Mork and Mindy the Dream Zone Parody and it's like hideous and awful but the girl does look a lot like Pam Dauber and the guy that played Mork actually does a very good cracked out Robin Williams impression I realize there's change in all we've been talking about tonight but last I checked we weren't going to become a porn show
[SPEAKER_02]: I just had to get that out because it was funny.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let me talk about my game of the week.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really been one game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's still Mass Effect 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I did go through all the DLC this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: I said, because I realize I am right at the very end and if I do the next mission, I set off a sequel of events where I won't get the best ending unless I play it to completion.
[SPEAKER_08]: People who have played the game will know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: And Alan's like a step ahead of me and he said, whoa, whoa, whoa, don't do that mission until you are absolutely ready to finish the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I said, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I did every side quest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did Overlord.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did Arrival.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did Shadowbroker.
[SPEAKER_08]: I played all of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Did Arrival enjoy it?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kind of mad at myself for giving EA that much money, but damn, it was good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially of note, I think my favorite out of all the DLC was Arrival.
[SPEAKER_08]: and the reason why I think I preferred that one I mean Shadow Broker had a lot of cool stuff to it and there was a lot of great scenes I realize that's kind of commonly people's favorites the reason why I really loved Arrival was Arrival really felt like an episode of a freaking science fiction show like Battlestar Galactica or something like I am playing an episode of a show watching it play out it has its very cliche twists part way through a good beginning middle end I mean it plays out like an episode of a TV show and
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of wish, as much as I'm kind of eh on DLC, like this is something I really like seeing in games, is this like really true episodic content.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, I can support DLC when it's pretty awesome like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was my favorite by far was Arrival.
[SPEAKER_08]: and Shadow Broker kind of felt the same way too I realize it kind of plays in a lot more to the greater story and I think Arrival in some regards is supposed to tie it's kind of to bridge two and three together which I get but it still felt a lot like a standalone to me I will have beaten that game by this time tomorrow I'm pretty close and then
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks to the sale on Mass Effect 3 this week, I have my copy of Mass Effect 3 sitting in the screen craft ready to go.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I can be really disappointed at the ending just like everybody else.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the experience and the, what, probably 25 hours of Mass Effect 1 and 35 so far of Mass Effect 2 plus whatever I spend there will at least be worth it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, how about your gaming week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I started playing some more stuff on my PS3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, Infamous, I finally played a little bit of that, and it's okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Not even that old, but it's just...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's alright, I may finish it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Unfortunately, all my time is being taken up by Call of Duty Modern Warfare 3.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, finally jumped on that bandwagon.
[SPEAKER_07]: After playing Modern Warfare 1 for a long time, well, it seems like a long time, but a few months, we decided to go ahead and make the shift to Modern Warfare 3, and it's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I enjoy it, playing...
[SPEAKER_07]: Pretty much just all multiplayer, because the campaign, I can never really sit down and play that for long enough.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm enjoying it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like the fact that, first off, the game still supports System Link, which is great, because our internet kind of sucks at my work.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ironically enough, it fixed itself when we had a power outage.
[SPEAKER_07]: All it took was shutting something off and turning it back on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the old IT standby, and yet someone... Calling Comcast tech support.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dude, dude, dude.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, did you try power cycling?
[SPEAKER_08]: I love how it's called power cycling.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you power cycle?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like it's fucking something out of Tron.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did you power cycle the cable modem?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, just hit that big switch that says power.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, now count to ten slowly with me.
[SPEAKER_08]: One.
[SPEAKER_08]: One, two, three.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, now turn it back.
[SPEAKER_07]: So instead of us having no connection to Xbox Live, we still have a shitty connection to Xbox Live.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess a shitty connection is better than no connection.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we're playing System Link, so it doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I like the fact that not only do they have System Link, but they have...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: um so I like the fact that they added that because they really didn't have to do that um which is nice I wish Grand Theft Auto 5 did that because I I just wish that that has system link because that'll be you know worth it but actually I picked up the game on um on PS3 and on 360 so I have it on both platforms I actually play with some of my co-workers on PS3 I'm actually for well I play online um on PS3 I haven't played online with my 360 yet but um
[SPEAKER_07]: I may, you know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess that means I have to create an elite clan, so we'll do the OLR army.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, get the OLR army.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, I guess that wraps it up for our gaming weeks, so we will get into some news here shortly.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, we usually do housekeeping.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think we said the pretty big part that we were waiting to say, so we'll...
[SPEAKER_08]: Ask Orange Lounge
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, I do want to say, of course, as always, since we are on Facebook, we are on Google+, add us.
[SPEAKER_08]: Facebook.com slash Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: And also, Google+, just look for Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's get into some gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, why don't you start us off with the news this week?
[SPEAKER_07]: Nintendo, Nintendo, Nintendo
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: with Miis Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: with Miis
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't know, is that really a step up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Do I really need a Wii U for that?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, because you're just giving me the game that you had last year, or was it last year?
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Recently, on the Wii, but now you're adding, you know, Mii support.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, something that...
[SPEAKER_07]: On a modern console, ones that have updates to their games, you could just patch in instead of releasing a whole new game for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought for some reason you could already do the Miis in the Wii game that was out.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why I thought that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I mean, okay, at least it'll be HD and native widescreen support or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's got to be another catch.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's got to be something they're not saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I cannot believe...
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially if this ends up being a launch title, which we don't really know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm assuming it's a launch window title.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a lot of 3DS stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it could be a launch title, especially if it's based off New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: They've got to be rushing something.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think they're going to learn from the mistake of the 3DS, and they're going to have a AAA something out.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're probably right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's probably Mario.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I'm curious what the little gimmick is going to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: How could Nintendo put out a launch title for the Wii U and not somehow integrate the whole screen in your lap concept?
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be something derpy like when you go in a pipe, you're on your screen and your other partners are still out there in the world.
[SPEAKER_08]: Watch.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be something silly like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have an idea what this is already, but we're not covering that until later.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think it's a port of a game that's coming to another platform that they're going to do some things.
[SPEAKER_07]: That other game may integrate with the Wii U since it has two screens.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see where you're going with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anybody who's been paying attention to the news this week knows.
[SPEAKER_08]: Otherwise, we'll get to it in a minute.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: Besides Wii U, Mario, they're promising that they're going to reveal Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I'm assuming...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't really know what... I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess we'll find out what it's about.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm not excited about Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_07]: I couldn't really care about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's one of those series I just kind of missed because I was never really... You know, I didn't get into the... Wasn't the first one on the 64?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or was it a GameCube?
[SPEAKER_06]: I think they were both GameCube ones.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just missed the boat on Pikmin.
[SPEAKER_08]: I understand people really love it, but it's one of the series I never got to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was too busy with F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's put it that way.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be cool if they announced an F-Zero game for the Wii U. Don't tease me.
[SPEAKER_08]: These things are going to happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: Microsoft did announce that Halo 4 is going to launch worldwide Tuesday, November 6th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Funny that they did the whole integration with Conan O'Brien.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a long segment on the Conan show on TBS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nine minutes about Halo and some funny voice like they were the background guys doing moving or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a little silly.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hope it's in the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was very red versus blue to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it was cool because it was Conan and Andy Richter who are both awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, of course, there's the whole little corporate speak of with Halo 4 leading the charge, we're confident 2012 will be the most successful year in Xbox history.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are beginning a new saga with Halo 4 and embarking on a journey that will encompass the next decade of Halo games and experiences.
[SPEAKER_08]: Confirmed, Halo 4, 5, and 6.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Confirmed.
[SPEAKER_07]: and 7 and 8 and 9.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course, to be fair, they already said in a while this Halo 4 would be the first game in a new trilogy.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it really, as much as I'm being sarcastic, it really isn't new news.
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, I don't see a problem with a new Halo game coming out without Bungie.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I understand that Bungie was kind of the driving force behind the last...
[SPEAKER_07]: and so on.
[SPEAKER_07]: um it hasn't hurt sales at all so I don't think that the fact that Halo 4 is going to come from a different studio that there's going to be any less quality in the game I think if anything it could be just like kind of fresh eyes on it I guess
[SPEAKER_07]: It looks cool, just like the brief little snippets of things that they have on there
[SPEAKER_08]: Um, uh, some of our chatters, Actdeft at chat.orange.radio.com says, I'm an Xbox person and I'm not excited about Halo at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Gamer Girl says, Halo is overplayed, just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Porkchop says, Halo needs a kick to the crotch, one way to kill Master Chef, and Chef is not a typo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, surely he meant to say Chief.
[SPEAKER_08]: Uh, Technus says, I like Halo.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not the shit everybody wants to believe it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, it's not...
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not the shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that means like, yeah, you're the shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not the shit as everybody wants to believe it is, but I won't knock it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think that's kind of how I feel about Halo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I'm not gonna like, oh my god, melt fanboy Halo, but it's a decent series.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a reason why it propelled the Xbox the way it did.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a great first-person shooter, especially on the original Xbox.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it still is.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, in what...
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, I don't think that they're doing another Gears of War game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I'm sure they'll find a way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Nah, they'll find a way.
[SPEAKER_08]: But supposedly, Gears of War is really, really dead and ain't coming back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, here's one other thing I want to say about this before we go on to the next story.
[SPEAKER_08]: November 6th is the day that the game is coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first Tuesday in November.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there anything else really big every four years especially?
[SPEAKER_08]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_08]: that people might kind of be caring about this year.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of passion around it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It has nothing to do with video games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think Call of Duty comes out that day.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, no.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Election Day here in the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Election Day.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, we have this guy, the president.
[SPEAKER_08]: You ever heard the name Barack Obama?
[SPEAKER_07]: Barack Obama.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't listen to that hip-hop music, okay?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's the leader of our country.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a pretty amazing title for a hip-hop artist.
[SPEAKER_08]: He has to run for office again because there's somebody else named Mitt Romney that thinks he shouldn't be president anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's a terrible hip-hop name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look, it's not a politics show and it's not a porn show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just an interesting observation, but I guess Microsoft got called on it and it was very like, you know, the statement they kind of released was like, well, we think a lot of people will be excited about both, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, let us hold our release of our game so you can have your little election.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or we can just move on like, you know, the rest of the world is...
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's be real.
[SPEAKER_08]: In this day and age, you can vote absentee and Amazon delivers to your door.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: You don't have to leave the house to participate in democracy or fragging online.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've been absentee.
[SPEAKER_07]: Voting takes like a few minutes.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like to vote in person.
[SPEAKER_08]: I personally don't vote absentee.
[SPEAKER_07]: How about putting those voting booths inside GameStop?
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or another retailer.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would actually be a really good idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: Get more young voters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to Claire's, then go vote?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_02]: They should have them at the mall.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jamba Juice, free smoothie with your vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could get a Cinnabon while I vote.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that's a lot better than going to the Lutheran church around the corner from my house.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is true.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do feel like I have to go to the grade school to vote here, and I don't have kids, so I feel really awkward going to the grade school.
[SPEAKER_08]: They're going to make you sit down at the really small desk.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you have to go in the library, and I'm like, I'm a big person.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm hitting my head on the ceiling.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's going on here?
[SPEAKER_08]: It feels awkward.
[SPEAKER_08]: Guys like me aren't supposed to be hanging around elementary schools unless I have kids, and I don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: So what's my excuse?
[SPEAKER_02]: And again, I have to go to the Lutheran church to drop mine off.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think I'm going to burst into flames or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get to vote, then you get some Kool-Aid.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura, take us to a new story.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, for those of us who are blessed with iPhones, we have a great game coming up for iOS, although I have no idea how the fuck we're going to play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry, can I read some great chat comments real quick?
[SPEAKER_08]: Lord, what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Infanel, I love this comment in chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: If corporations are people, can I vote Valve for president?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: GameGuru says, can I vote for Master Chief as my president?
[SPEAKER_08]: Good way to tie the stories together.
[SPEAKER_08]: Appreciate that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, you know who I usually write in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bill the Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, Bill the Cat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've been doing this show with you for 10 years.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know Bill the Cat very well.
[SPEAKER_07]: Why don't they just call Obama Master Chief?
[SPEAKER_08]: I would call him my Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_08]: He is Master Chief.
[SPEAKER_07]: Here's how you win this.
[SPEAKER_07]: You put Obama in your fucking campaign.
[SPEAKER_07]: Obama comes in, dressed up like Master Chief, kicks down a door, pulls off his helmet and says, go vote.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that'll get people in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's kind of how the Bin Laden speech went down.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, let's...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't remember him being in Master Chiefs.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh wait, that was when they made fun of him on late night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, no politics, moving on.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway, this awesome game I'm referring to is Marvel vs. Capcom 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's going to be on iOS on April 25th.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've only got the British price, which is 2.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm assuming it's going to be a $5 game over in the US.
[SPEAKER_02]: It said there's nothing yet announced as an upgraded version for iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it doesn't show the virtual D-pad on the screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: So who knows exactly how it's going to control.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey...
[SPEAKER_07]: The virtual d-pad is paid to unlock content.
[SPEAKER_02]: On top of that, it has all 56 fighters from the original.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was nice of Capcom to do for a change.
[SPEAKER_08]: You fucking know they thought about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know there was that guy in the boardroom.
[SPEAKER_08]: We could have, you know, eight characters that come with it.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then for 99 cents, do eight more and eight more.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Meh.
[SPEAKER_08]: But for real, Marvel vs. Capcom 2 on the iPhone If I had an iCade for the iPad If I had, which I don't think is on tonight's show roll, so I'll say it That Midway game on the iOS devices, that Midway Arcade Treasures Got support for the iCade this week
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, very yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: That helped that game immensely.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, IK'd support for Marvel vs. Capcom 2 would make it, you know, for those that don't own anything else, I guess, would make it desirable.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I want IK'd to make?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hmm?
[SPEAKER_02]: I want them to make those little miniature arcade cabinets like they had in the 80s.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, so yeah, with the LEDs and everything?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want them to make, like, little cabinets like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I should make one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a friend of mine that had a Donkey Kong little LED game like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had a friend that had the Pac-Man.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I actually have a Frogger cabinet like that, like one of the really small LED ones, that I actually was going to convert into a MAME cabinet.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember when you bought that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was your whole $100 project, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I didn't buy that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually got that free from a co-worker.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, but I have the internals for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have a Pico ITX board and a tiny little LCD screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be awesome-tastic.
[SPEAKER_07]: The only problem is there's no room to put the controls on there because you realize you're all yeah, I can't really fit buttons on this thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, that's what I was thinking Dan should do with his Transformer tablet, because it's an Android, and you can get MAME for Android, is to set that up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, that's another story.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just don't buy an iPad, I mean, for arcade games.
[SPEAKER_07]: Buy an arcade cabinet for arcade games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously, you're going to be spending about the same amount of money.
[SPEAKER_07]: You might as well have the authentic...
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: That BurgerTime I was looking at was $500.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how much an iPad would cost.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I wanted an iPad for stuff other than games.
[SPEAKER_02]: This isn't coming out on iPad.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not like I don't already have three other copies of it anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: But still.
[SPEAKER_02]: Gonna take you for a ride.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: um so it is coming out in Japan no word on US but probably coming out around the same time I know you're very cynical about Animal Crossing and you could give two shits about the improved park bench sitting or whatever features they're actually adding into this one however I have a friend a real person that I know that said holy shit Animal Crossing is coming out time to get a 3DS shit you not Animal Crossing has its fans
[SPEAKER_07]: I understand, it's just like Apple product fans where they're like, holy shit, Apple has a new thing coming out, I gotta go get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's just like this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was just glad that she spoke to me in that language for a change and didn't say... Well, I hope that when she plays it, she discovers a whole... It really makes a lot more sense in the Japanese version.
[SPEAKER_07]: A wholly unique experience and not the same damn game again.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you know I found my Japanese Animal Crossing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so she brought up porn.
[SPEAKER_08]: A long time ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's what the little animals say.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really fun to put in dirty words and hear how the little animals interpret them.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, sorry for dumbing down the show.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: They also announced that they're going to be doing a Kirby 20th Anniversary Edition on the Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, if you're even mildly interested in it, I would recommend picking it up, because if anything, remember those Mario... What?
[SPEAKER_08]: You're recommending this?
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't be... Look...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, hey, I'm recommending this because of the resale value of the last Mario game.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the last Mario game was a stupid ROM conversion.
[SPEAKER_07]: It literally was a ROM from the SNES.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like, hey, we're going to just snap, you know, put this virtual console ROM on that disc.
[SPEAKER_07]: Done!
[SPEAKER_08]: No disrespect to the Kirby fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a great franchise.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, you know, they did this with Mario.
[SPEAKER_08]: They did it with Zelda back on the GameCube.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was a pre-order bonus only thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it was basically a virtual console on a disc.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, if they get some ones that we haven't seen elsewhere out on there, it'll be kind of awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it'd be neat if they were, I don't know, redone, but I think it's just a bunch of virtual console games.
[SPEAKER_07]: At least this time, it's not going to be just one ROM.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that'd be kind of neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: No word on when that's coming out, but sometime this year.
[SPEAKER_07]: And...
[SPEAKER_07]: Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2 is now coming this August.
[SPEAKER_07]: Both Japan and the US.
[SPEAKER_07]: And looks exactly like New Super Mario Bros.
1.
[SPEAKER_07]: But with now Raccoon Mario.
[SPEAKER_07]: Hooray.
[SPEAKER_02]: Raccoon's awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Raccoon or Tanooki?
[SPEAKER_02]: Raccoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe Tanooki.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who knows?
[SPEAKER_02]: I thought the Tanooki suit was the most awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, my favorite was the Hammer Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: suit.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm just glad, though, that they have stuck with the same backgrounds from the first game so that, you know, Josh's room is still current.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, actually, that looks like Josh's room, except different patterns in the mountains.
[SPEAKER_08]: is it sad that it seriously took me a minute because my first reaction when they announced the sequel was I was like holy shit already we just had Mario 3D Land last year and then I was like oh wait it's not a sequel to the 3D game this is a sequel on the 3DS to the Wii game
[SPEAKER_08]: My brain actually had to go through those motions.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually to the DS game that was on the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: What the hell was the Wii game then?
[SPEAKER_07]: The Wii game was kind of the same damn thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: Wii.
[SPEAKER_07]: Notice the Wii at the end.
[SPEAKER_02]: That was actually the first game that made Dan think about getting a 3DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Confirmed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't understand Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, all you have to understand is they took the game and they made some new levels.
[SPEAKER_07]: And made some blinged out characters because there's a level with all gold characters for some reason.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, and spider webs.
[SPEAKER_07]: That must be new.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: by the way I want to point out Alan has paraded out here just to hand me to do nothing but he hasn't even been sitting here he's been sitting in the back room playing Mass Effect he walked out here specifically just to hand me the DS cartridge of New Super Mario Brothers as if to say here dumbass thank you honey thank you thank you I learned so much being with you I'm putting this up on our on our page
[SPEAKER_07]: New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's kind of weird that it's coming out in August.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that means that Nintendo does have something else that they're going to be releasing for the fourth quarter.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I know!
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a new console!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's it!
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what they're releasing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That and probably Animal Crossing because Animal Crossing is somewhat cracky.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, anyways, as I was alluding to earlier, I believe that the Wii Mario game that we're going to be putting out is going to be New Super Mario Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: 2 for the Wii U. And that you're going to be able to integrate, or not integrate, but play the game on your 3DS and on your console because the 3DS, they will probably announce, will actually be able to link up with your Wii U to...
[SPEAKER_07]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_07]: Except the new 3DS that they probably will announce that will have two analog sticks and not just one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's hope and no attachment later on, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would kind of piss me off.
[SPEAKER_08]: Especially if it's exclusive to GameStop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Quickie poll.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Kuriboh's shoe or Hammer Brothers suit?
[SPEAKER_08]: Kuriboh's shoe all the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was like the raddest power-up ever.
[SPEAKER_07]: The Hammer Brothers suit sucks.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Frog Mario.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, Frog Mario sucks too.
[SPEAKER_07]: Frog Mario sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: FrogMario is balls unless you're in an underwater level.
[SPEAKER_08]: I will say that it is a challenge.
[SPEAKER_08]: If somebody can beat the game with FrogMario through the level 8 worlds, color me impressed.
[SPEAKER_02]: FrogMario actually is very good in one of the level 8 ones, the battleships.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Why hasn't that made it into Mario Kart as a power-up?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just a big shoe that stomps on enemies?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, exactly.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just like your cart turns into the shoe.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah, your cart.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's an awesome power-up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Your cart turns into the shoe, and it just flies ahead and stomps on whoever's in front of you, and you just take off from there.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nintendo.
[SPEAKER_08]: Patent pending.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can't do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nintendo, hire us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hire us.
[SPEAKER_08]: It would be a cool idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Confirm next week OLR on the Nintendo Network.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Kidding.
[SPEAKER_08]: Put the hate mail down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, and then last thing, the 3DS is finally getting with iOS and everybody else.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, hey, they've figured out, you know, you might like to sort your icons that you have.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're going to have a new addition to the home menu where you can create folders and store up to 60 icons within each folder.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that is awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can actually kind of sort your games and whatnot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like that idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's needed.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll become an April 25th.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Things I Don't Play folder.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's have that for all the little NES games and the Game Boy Advance games I downloaded because they were free and I don't play them.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some I do play, but some I don't.
[SPEAKER_08]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, let's move on with some more news.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, there's a lot of great Nintendo happy-go-lucky news this week, but somebody's not so happy-go-lucky about what's going on in Nintendo, and that would be Trent Oster.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who is he?
[SPEAKER_08]: He's with BeamDog.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he went to Twitter this week to say, Baldur's Gate Enhanced Edition?
[SPEAKER_08]: Not coming to the Wii U. Ironically, I never would have thought that game was coming to the Wii U. Yeah, I'm like, I never would have put it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, you know, for whatever reason, he was asked, and he said, We don't do Nintendo development.
[SPEAKER_08]: Previous experience with Nintendo was enough to ensure there will not be another Nintendo project.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, no, he didn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: He just basically said, worked with Nintendo before, not going to happen again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently it has to do with MDK2.
[SPEAKER_08]: You remember MDK from back in the day?
[SPEAKER_08]: There was MDK2.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was supposed to be WiiWare.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a 6,000 unit sales requirement before the developer gets payment.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see where that's kind of crappy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also had to do with trying to get a 400 meg game down to 40 megs with WiiWare, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see where, you know, if you don't like the rules, then I'm going to take my ball and go somewhere else.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: They honestly need to, like, you know, rethink their whole strategy with their online games because they are a little bit restrictive and, you know, the exposure on WiiWare isn't very good.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, this whole Nintendo Direct before E3 is very interesting to me, because E3 is only, what, about six weeks away at this point?
[SPEAKER_08]: And for Nintendo to have this kind of a major press conference before E3 is very interesting, because these are games they very easily could have kept in their hat until E3, with the exception of the firmware update.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really the only thing that's happening now.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Zelda in 2013, maybe
[SPEAKER_08]: well also one thing I wanted to say is that one thing that Nintendo didn't detail here that they're going to have to detail at E3 is the Nintendo Network we still don't really know I mean we've heard some little things about it we don't really know what that entails and I think E3 is going to be a big reveal for that and they don't know either I wouldn't put it past them
[SPEAKER_07]: So hey guys, we have this poll on our website.
[SPEAKER_07]: We want you to vote on what exactly you want the Nintendo Network to be.
[SPEAKER_08]: Breakman in chat makes a pretty good point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Spoiler alert, Gears of War 4 also not going to be on the Wii U. Sorry everyone.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true, and you probably won't see God of War coming to the Wii U anytime soon either.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just the way these things work.
[SPEAKER_08]: Halo 4, not on the Wii U. That's right, not on the Wii U. Not on the Wii U. Until there's... Someday, one of them's going to gobble the other up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just like Sega.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who would have thought Sega would be publishing on a Nintendo platform?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Minds were blown when Sonic showed up on the NES system.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was crazy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I cried.
[SPEAKER_08]: Aww.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not really.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, Final Fantasy XIV, they're desperate.
[SPEAKER_02]: They really, really, really, really want everyone to come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're just crying over it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, anyone who has an inactive Final Fantasy XIV account can come back for a 10-day free trial next month, according to Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_02]: I said it's going to be free of charge between the 10th and 21st of May with a new job system, 7th Umbral Era content and new gameplay that has a new update.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then for the people that are still playing, they're getting some goodies.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyone who's been subscribed for 90 days between January 6th and the 2.0 beta testing gets their subscription released to, well, this is in pounds because I'm reading off a British article, to 6.89 down from 8.99.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they are legacy subscribers and they get a new Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ooh.
[SPEAKER_02]: But they're also still cutting down on their servers, so they're desperate.
[SPEAKER_02]: Desperate!
[SPEAKER_07]: The problem is, though, who cares that they're offering a free comeback and try us for 10 days?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because it's not the 2.0 update yet!
[SPEAKER_07]: That doesn't happen until the fall!
[SPEAKER_07]: So why do I want to play your half-finished game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, to be fair, I mean, I give Final Fantasy XIV its fair share of shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I did play it for a while, so I can speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: as a former player, as someone who would be directly impacted by this.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have put some things into the game already that were needed, and that was Final Fantasy classes that people understand, to put it lightly.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like now instead of Thaumaturge and Conjurer, you can path to Black Mage and White Mage, and some of those changes are actually pretty exciting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Not enough to get me back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I should say...
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, if it's going to be free for 10 days, if I'm not... What weekend is this happening again?
[SPEAKER_08]: I kind of shut my brain off for a minute.
[SPEAKER_02]: Crap.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me look back at it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It says it is the 10th and 21st of May.
[SPEAKER_08]: See, here's the problem.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's happening on the 15th of May?
[SPEAKER_08]: Disneyland?
[SPEAKER_08]: For you.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's happening on the 15th of May for everybody else?
[SPEAKER_08]: Max Payne 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Diablo 3, people.
[SPEAKER_08]: Diablo 3 is on May 15th.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think I give a shit about Final Fantasy 14 while I'm in the middle of Diablo 3?
[SPEAKER_07]: Why does this make me think of Cabela's and the Halo 3 launch?
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's be real.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's really a four-day window to play Final Fantasy 14.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just keeping it real, folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: And so maybe if it's not because, you know...
[SPEAKER_08]: If the patch is 7 gigs, I have to think about, oh, I have a 250 gig through Comcast, and I gotta download Diablo.
[SPEAKER_08]: I hate that I have to fucking think about that, but I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, if it's reasonable, I'll check it out.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: If it's free.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I kind of don't think it's gonna sway my opinion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Porkchop in our chatroom asks, does Final Fantasy XIV have much of a soundtrack?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's decent.
[SPEAKER_08]: I believe Nobuo Imatsu did a large chunk of the tracks, which is strange because he didn't really do XI's soundtrack at all except the theme.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just bring XI free-to-play.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all you need to do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_07]: All you need is XI free-to-play, I'd be there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would be there today.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know why XI can't go free-to-play?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's the Japanese user base on PlayStation 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: How can you have a free-to-play game on the PlayStation 2 at this point?
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cut him out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: How long is the PlayStation?
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_07]: The PlayStation 2 still has some game coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: To be fair, there's like five people on Xbox 360 too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's not forget that.
[SPEAKER_08]: That was a pretty big deal.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's keep them up for the five people that play on Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, but all those people that play EA Sports MMA, fuck them.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or Need for Speed, ah, fuck them too.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: All those five people that are playing Final Fantasy, who gives a shit?
[SPEAKER_07]: Tell them, listen, go download the PC client for free because it's free to fucking play!
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: Some people, though, do like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, like, we have Ikuma right now saying that it's good now.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, okay, if you have a PlayStation 2 and you're still playing on that game, get a new PC!
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, come on, a PC from, like, a few years... Shit, you could probably get a PC from, like... What is it?
[SPEAKER_07]: How long has it been since I've been playing Final Fantasy XI?
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, ten years?
[SPEAKER_07]: Ten years?
[SPEAKER_07]: It's been a while.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, come on.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you can't afford a PC from like 10 years ago, what the... It hasn't been 10 years because the show is 10 years old and the Final Fantasy XI thing started.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like a couple years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: Five to seven years ago, okay?
[SPEAKER_07]: Five to seven years ago.
[SPEAKER_07]: I literally am throwing away computers from that time.
[SPEAKER_07]: I will give you a computer for free.
[SPEAKER_08]: The computer that the show is broadcast from could play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, I mean, fuck.
[SPEAKER_07]: Probably this Vita could play Final Fantasy XI.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a rumor.
[SPEAKER_07]: Remember?
[SPEAKER_07]: They really knew to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was a rumor.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would buy that.
[SPEAKER_07]: I would buy that shit.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, maybe not on the Vita, because I mean...
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'd still buy that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'm telling you, Final Fantasy XI would be awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who cares about XIV?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just listen.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, it didn't work out.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're going to make it free to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: To make it up, we're going to maybe revamp a little bit of Final Fantasy XI and make it free to play.
[SPEAKER_08]: There is too much pride for Square Enix, the makers of Kingdom Hearts and Final Fantasy to say, we're going to open this up free to play and have to take that big old slice of humble pie.
[SPEAKER_08]: It ain't happening anytime soon.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's necessarily a bad thing for your MMO to take that path.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why can't Final Fantasy go down the path of Guild Wars?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, forget it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because they're Squeenix.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_02]: They don't do that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's talk about games that are really existing in a store near you very soon as we travel around the world and look at some release dates.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so this week it's Prototype 2, PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, and on 360, Phantom Breaker Special Edition.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shinsengoku Musou Versus
[SPEAKER_08]: Vita, Seal No Surge, Ushinarwatiya
[SPEAKER_08]: Wareta, sorry, Hoshi i Sasagushi comes out this week in normal and agent packs, as well as Next Revolution comes out for Media 5 this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: Those are both on the Vita.
[SPEAKER_08]: And checking out the consoles real quick, going to the PlayStation 3, Biohazard, Operation Raccoon City.
[SPEAKER_08]: You get a special headset bundle for Operation Raccoon City, the game itself.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's coming out.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Loki's saying, don't fall for it, it sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, what's very interesting, Elder Scrolls IV Oblivion, Game of the Year Edition, finally coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fallout 3, Game of the Year Edition, finally coming out on PlayStation 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that a new Idolmaster?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think those are price reductions.
[SPEAKER_08]: And yes, the Idolmaster Graveur for You, Volume 7.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think this is more an expansion for Idolmaster.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think it's like an actual full...
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm guessing that those are getting a price reduction because there was just recently a combo pack with Fallout 3 and Oblivion for like $29.99 or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: That could be here in the States?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: That could be.
[SPEAKER_07]: That was on 360, but I can see them dropping prices.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oddly enough, 360 is pretty busy this week in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Operation Raccoon City Biohazard is out there as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Cybertroopers Virtual On Force gets the Platinum reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Who knew Virtual On was still going?
[SPEAKER_07]: I think that's the arcade game plus they're throwing in the tournament stick or that arcade stick that goes with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Need.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dodonpachi Resurrection Black Label and it's a cave game is out this week.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's probably a price reduction.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's going to be a double pack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, because it's called Cave Selection.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fallout 3 Game of the Year Edition also on the Xbox 360.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's Dodonpachi.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Dodonpachi Resurrection came out like what, six months ago?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: You saw that Akai Katana is coming out next month.
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I missed that.
[SPEAKER_07]: The new shmup.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, it's a new shmup.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's actually one that's actually formatted for widescreen.
[SPEAKER_07]: The first cave game for widescreen, HD TVs, all done in HD.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well done.
[SPEAKER_07]: About time.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's coming out in the States.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually a game that's in talks with Square.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if we have it in anything in the show, but actually one thing I am interested that's coming out, hopefully, that Square is doing is a sequel to The World Ends With You.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I heard about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're supposed to be doing that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_07]: Comes out December.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, really?
[SPEAKER_07]: No, I'm just saying, wouldn't that be funny because of the Mayan calendar?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I thought that was one of your little, like, Loki tips slipping in there.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's just funny because I don't think that our December on the Gregorian calendar would have been the end of their year.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, a little bit of trivia.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the lunar calendar for the Jewish calendar, we actually don't have a leap year.
[SPEAKER_02]: We have a leap month every, I think, 13 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a whole month.
[SPEAKER_08]: We have a whole extra month.
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you have to work in that month?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good times.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I mean, it's normal stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: You don't work on Shabbat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Who would run the world then if we didn't work for a whole month?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, the Jew... Anarchy!
[SPEAKER_08]: Moving on, UK...
[SPEAKER_02]: 24th of April we have FIFA 12, UFA Euro 12 The Walking Dead and Prototype 2 there's a game that actually came out on my birthday that I think has a funny name and I have no idea what it's about but it makes me think of Benicula as Botanicula
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know if anyone ever remembers a book about the vegetarian vampire rabbit.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 26th of April is Deus Ex Human Revolution.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the 27th, Binary Domain, Blazing Souls, Accolade, or is it Accelate?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Risen 2, Dark Waters.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be it.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Saw.
[SPEAKER_07]: Alright, so I don't know if I should be happy about this, but I guess a company doing well, great.
[SPEAKER_07]: THQ, their forecast for their earnings has improved.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're saying that now they're reporting a net sales from $160 million to $170 million.
[SPEAKER_07]: And of course the previous update was from 130 to 150.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what can this be attributed to?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it's due to the fact that people have been dumb enough to buy the fucking DLC for Saints Row the Third.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I am proud to say that I am not one of those people.
[SPEAKER_07]: I made the mistake once purchasing one of their content packs or expansions, whatever you want to call it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it sucked.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was 30 minutes of content for $8.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm sorry, $7.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I just said fuck it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's cheaper than a hooker.
[SPEAKER_07]: 30 minutes, yeah, that is cheaper than a hooker.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's definitely not as satisfying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not as much payoff.
[SPEAKER_07]: When did you start pricing hookers?
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't get me started.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is there something for your birthday I didn't hear about?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, I actually... Nothing.
[SPEAKER_02]: This comes from the episode last week's Supernatural.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was a fancy lady.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, a hooker?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dot, dot, dot.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, I mean, come on.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to know that you have to factor in the HMV into everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, everything's based off the HME, which is the hooker market value.
[SPEAKER_07]: And if you don't know what the hooker market value is, how are you going to know how to price your other goods that are based off the HMV?
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm telling you, this is just street smarts.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, seriously.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yes, it's really unfortunate that people were dumb enough to buy this.
[SPEAKER_07]: And most of which was paid unlocked content, by the way.
[SPEAKER_07]: In fact, they're still putting out little costumes and bullshit that was in the game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sadly, though, if they put out a sequel to this game, I'm probably not going to have to buy it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because I do remember earlier...
[SPEAKER_07]: Um, well, a couple weeks ago while we were out, or while I was out, a certain idiot from, um, I'm not really sure if he works for THQ or Volition, I believe he works for THQ, was complaining about, you know, I'm not getting enough money from use games, and so, of course, he had to be the first person to enter my list of, hey, I'm
[SPEAKER_07]: If you complain about used game sales and not making anything off of it, I'm going to boycott your game.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, Richard Brown, the first inductee into that list, who had worked on many things, including Saints Row III, unfortunately, I am now going to have to be forced not to purchase any more games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you seriously boycotting Saints Row IV?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do not believe it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not buying the game new.
[SPEAKER_07]: They will not get any of my new money.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll wait until that first trailer is out and I'll ask you again.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yes, he has worked on many games, including Homefront, Ren Faction, Armageddon, Saints for the Third, Stacking, Warhammer 40k, WWE All-Stars.
[SPEAKER_07]: He's basically, I think he's like a producer or something like that over at THQ.
[SPEAKER_07]: He backs the money for this stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So yes, and of course he came out bitching about how, you know, oh, they need used game sales because all these excuses.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even really want to go into detail about it, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it's annoying.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh, he talked about the real cost of used games and smuggle bastard.
[SPEAKER_08]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, everybody has Kickstarter fever in the States anyway because, you know, they don't really have anything like it overseas.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because, you know, by the way, I got to say this.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was a great Penny Arcade article on Kickstarter this week about how
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, there is a little bit of the financial end.
[SPEAKER_07]: You have to have people that manage your money, your marketing, and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can't just go make game, make money.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it's a little bit more complex than that.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a quick note for the podcast folks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, our live listeners lost us, but we show we're still connected and uploading data to the feed.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're going to just keep right on moving.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, so anyhow, Kickstarter, yes, there is an alternative to Kickstarter called Gambitious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, this is how the folks overseas are going to get into this.
[SPEAKER_08]: European indie developers will get this opportunity to use this.
[SPEAKER_08]: There are some differences.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a Dutch company.
[SPEAKER_08]: They will be filling the crowdfunding void by using their own service.
[SPEAKER_08]: You won't be donating funds to receive gifts.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're actually going to purchase shares of a game's development.
[SPEAKER_08]: So it's almost like a little mini stock market or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: When the game is completed, the user gets dividends like a traditional investor rather than a copy of a game or a lunch date or whatever it is that you're doing.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a very smart British way of thinking about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I like it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I wish they would do something like that over here.
[SPEAKER_07]: That'd be kind of cool.
[SPEAKER_07]: Very strange.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's move on to a segment we like to do every week here on the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know we're not live.
[SPEAKER_08]: We still have a big group that listens to us on the podcast.
[SPEAKER_02]: And for the record, they say that the play button's got to slash through it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just went to the site and it looks fine to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, what is the classic game of the week?
[SPEAKER_02]: The game is Kid Icarus, also known in Japan as Hikari Shinwa Palutena no Kagami, which is Light Mythology Palutena's Mirror.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is an action platform game that came out on the Famicom Disk System in Japan and cartridge in US and North America and in Europe.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, that's what I meant.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was the very first Kid Icarus game, and it came out in Japan in December 1986, and in Europe and North America in February and July 1987 respectively.
[SPEAKER_02]: We had a GBA version in 2004, a Wii Virtual Console version in 2007,
[SPEAKER_02]: and the sequel that came out on Game Boy in 1991 and of course the third version that came out on Nintendo 3DS in March 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which, having played a little bit of it, loved it, won it, oh my god.
[SPEAKER_02]: So anyway.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically, you are Pit, who is a cute little angel, trying to find the three sacred treasures, which he has to use to rescue their goddess of angel land, Palutena.
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically go through different areas where you can scroll up, and you've got your little...
[SPEAKER_02]: Dungeon levels where you have to go on kind of like a grid map type thing and it's really a neat little game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You basically have to reach the end of the levels, defeat the monster that guards the three treasures and it actually was done by Nintendo's Research and Development 1 division that meant it was designed by Toru Asawa and Yoshio Sakamoto and directed by Satoru Okada.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know who produced it?
[SPEAKER_02]: Gunpei Yokoi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Who is the man?
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, it actually had kind of mixed reception when it came out.
[SPEAKER_02]: There were people that did not like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's, you know, been a classic to everyone since.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Game Boy version that came out was Kid Icarus of Myths and Monsters in 1991.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then we had to wait for 20 years.
[SPEAKER_02]: So now we have Kid Icarus Uprising and everything's cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: But hey, we still have Pit in Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ball.
[SPEAKER_02]: So basically with this one, like I said, it is a platformer.
[SPEAKER_02]: You go through different levels and you collect health, you collect hearts, which you can use to buy stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you also have a score.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, as you go through that, you can go through different chambers that sometimes they're a market.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sometimes you have to defeat certain monsters.
[SPEAKER_02]: You have a god's chamber where your bow and arrow can be increased in strength by different factors.
[SPEAKER_02]: And sometimes it depends on how many enemies you've defeated or how much damage you've taken in battle.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then you also have a training chamber where
[SPEAKER_02]: where you can get one of three power items if you pass the test.
[SPEAKER_02]: So then you have, basically you've got the three stages, the underworld, the surface, and the sky world.
[SPEAKER_02]: And they have the different levels and the fortress.
[SPEAKER_02]: And all the first levels are, the underworld and sky stages are basically ones where you're going bottom to top.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then the last one is a side-scrolling level.
[SPEAKER_02]: The surface world.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry, it's side-scrolling.
[SPEAKER_02]: The fortresses are non-scrolling rooms, and you have to find and defeat the gatekeeper.
[SPEAKER_02]: So you can buy a check sheet, a pencil, and a torch so that you can basically track yourself on your map.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you can get a hammer that destroys statues, which will free a flying soldier called a centurion that will aid you in boss battles.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then when each of the bosses are destroyed, you get one of the sacred treasures.
[SPEAKER_02]: Blah, blah, blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and the last portion are kind of like a scrolling shooter.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it's pretty interesting.
[SPEAKER_02]: So the game, like I said, was done by a Nintendo's R&D1 division which was actually the programming was done by an outside company called Intelligent Systems.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was meant for the disc system because with the disc card you could have three times the storage capacity than the NES cartridges.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then it also could save your progress, given that it was on a floppy disk.
[SPEAKER_02]: Of course, when it came out on the Nintendo in the US, it was on a cartridge with a password system.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, uh...
[SPEAKER_02]: This, a lot went into the creation of this game, actually.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was even said that, um, all of the, uh, the pixel art was drawn by, um, Otsawa himself.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, um, it was re-released in, um, 19, uh, sorry, in 2004 in Japan as the Famicom Mini Disk System Selection for the GBA.
[SPEAKER_02]: And, of course, we got it on the Virtual Console in 2007.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, remember the cheat codes, Rob?
[SPEAKER_08]: I do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't there like Medusa fights Icarus angels or vice versa?
[SPEAKER_08]: Icarus fights Medusa angels.
[SPEAKER_02]: And there was terror, danger, horror.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: They took that out of the 3DS remake, if you can believe it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, they did.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I was leading up to.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, my bad.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, um, there were, uh, when, uh, there was, uh, the eShop version of the download code that was given to those who registered two 3DS games, um, with Nintendo in Japan and Europe, or pre-ordered Kid Icarus Uprisings.
[SPEAKER_02]: So, that was pretty neat.
[SPEAKER_02]: Boo to them!
[SPEAKER_02]: Part of it had to do with their rather dated graphics.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it was said in Retro Gamer, which is a magazine that Dan and I pick up sometimes, that it was the unsung hero of the NES, looks and sounds pretty, and said that the music is sublime and the enemy characters are brilliantly drawn.
[SPEAKER_02]: Which I have to agree with every single last bit of that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, um...
[SPEAKER_02]: JeremyParishWithOneUp.com said that it was a fairly forgotten masterpiece and that it was underwhelming, buggy, and annoying.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_02]: I say shut up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Agreed.
[SPEAKER_02]: It really is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Now, I will say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: That game is freaking hard as fuck.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_02]: and we've even seen Pit in Tetris, remember when you win on the harder levels?
[SPEAKER_02]: He pops up on the little win screen.
[SPEAKER_02]: F1 Race and Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Melee and he was a playable character in Super Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: Brawl and they completely redesigned his appearance for that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I liked?
[SPEAKER_02]: What I used to do in this one when you get turned into an eggplant?
[SPEAKER_02]: Is I would hold down and then slide across the floor as an eggplant.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: You couldn't see his little legs.
[SPEAKER_02]: Ah, that was the best.
[SPEAKER_02]: But basically, they revealed Kid Icarus Uprising in E3 2010 and sent me a 3D shooter that was developed by Project Sora.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the same company that the Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_02]: designer Masahiro Sakurai is from.
[SPEAKER_02]: It kind of does go back to that.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: and had a reverse difficulty curve.
[SPEAKER_02]: Basically, you can play it 16-bit on your web browser.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know what became of that, because honestly, that's the first I had ever heard of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: But now I kind of want to find it and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's our game, Kid Icarus.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, there it is, your classic game of the week, Kid Icarus on the NES.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just think that the original name is pretty cool, though.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do, I like that too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Light Mythology.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't know what's going on with the live feed.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're still showing that we're sending data.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently, the server itself is down.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we don't know what's up.
[SPEAKER_08]: According to folks in chat, this seems to be like a legit server crash that's happening, what have you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to need to take a little bit of a break here.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to go ahead and play music anyway, even though the podcasters won't hear it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But at least it's a chance for us to take a break and figure out how we're going to broadcast Part B. We'll be right back.
[SPEAKER_08]: Welcome back everybody to Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are live, sorta, on this Sunday evening, April the 22nd of 2012.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just what's going on for the live folks real quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: We flipped it to Ustream, which obviously you're figuring this out if you're connecting to the feed right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: And if you see, yes, that video really is live.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's my little hand waving in front of it.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're shy, so you get to look at Mr. Chocobo.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I don't know what's going on with All Games.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am still streaming to the All Games server.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm streaming to both right now, so this is going to be interesting to see if we can have the bandwidth for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the All Games server crashed, or something happened, so we don't know what's up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And guys, we suspect it's not... I realize there was a big announcement this week, and people are coming up with conspiracy theories, but we think if it was that, which would be...
[SPEAKER_08]: Silly if it was that.
[SPEAKER_08]: We would just have the access to stream to the feed taken away altogether because they know the IP we broadcast from.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we don't think it's that.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's just how ironic.
[SPEAKER_08]: How ironic.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like rain on your wedding day.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't change anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: You'll still get next week's show at the same time and all that good stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, let's try to move on with the show best we can.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to move into some rapid fire news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess DarkSakura's computer just crashed on top of everything else.
[SPEAKER_08]: Won't anything work?
[SPEAKER_02]: Why is technology... Because this is a piece of shit and my husband won't buy me an iPad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why is technology revolting against us?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like the fucking Terminator.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_07]: Paint Park is basically a basic paint program.
[SPEAKER_07]: You can take pictures of crap and draw and share it with your friends and do all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Plus, I believe you can actually draw with friends, maybe?
[SPEAKER_07]: And you can also use the rear touchpad and the front touchpad and all that fun stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: So that's neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: Then later this summer, they're going to be introducing Treasure Park and Wake Up Call.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess Treasure Park is an app that lets you create your own puzzles and send them out to your friends using Near and I guess 3G.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then also Wake Up Call is an alarm clock app that syncs with your alarm or syncs your alarm with other PlayStation Vita users.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't understand why you would want to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it says there's also a competitive element where players can set goals and are awarded for meeting or exceeding... I don't get it.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: Set your alarm.
[SPEAKER_07]: Goal!
[SPEAKER_07]: What's the point of that?
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't make any sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: Turning alarm clocks into a video game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not sure.
[SPEAKER_08]: How quickly you answer the alarm, I don't understand.
[SPEAKER_08]: I could use something like that, actually.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm the type of person that will hit the damn snooze for an hour.
[SPEAKER_08]: So something to motivate me.
[SPEAKER_09]: I set four alarms.
[SPEAKER_08]: and actually get out of bed.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ooh, a shiny sticker for my alarm clock park or whatever it's called.
[SPEAKER_07]: But yeah, Paint Park is available right now.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is free so you can check it out and play around with that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Actually, I haven't turned my Vita on in a few weeks so I missed a lot of stuff on there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I downloaded the Wipeout demo.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want to check that out because people keep saying that's a good game to get.
[SPEAKER_07]: and then also there's like some AR thing with resistance that you can play with and then there's that other free like puzzle game that they've got where I guess it's limited plays per day or something like that hey but it's free so you can try it and if it sucks you can delete it I still have to have an 8 gig card I still have to move everything over to but I haven't gotten a chance to do that yet so fun fun
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something else that's kind of cool DLC-wise, you know, LittleBigPlanet had a lot of cool DLC when it came out, and of course they're going to kind of continue on doing it with that LittleBigPlanet carting.
[SPEAKER_07]: With pre-order, I'm assuming at major retailers, Amazon GameStop they're mentioning, you get free Kevin Butler DLC.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's right, the fake VP himself.
[SPEAKER_07]: You get the Sackboy costume and his golf cart to play.
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Anyways, last but not least, there's a rumor, or I should say a campaign, sort of, to bring Archer, the FX animated series, to Pinball FX as a table.
[SPEAKER_07]: And apparently this is...
[SPEAKER_07]: came to fruition via some tweets from the Archer production designer.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess someone tweeted the Archer production designer and art director.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then he's like, well, yeah, hey, that sounds like a cool idea.
[SPEAKER_07]: If Zen Studios wants to do it, then I guess we can send the idea to FX and see if they're game for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then Zen Studios is like, hell yeah, we'll do it.
[SPEAKER_07]: And so now it's kind of in FX's hands to whether or not they were going to
[SPEAKER_07]: Put the wheels in motion, I guess, and they're going to swap contact information and maybe we'll have an Archer table someday.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'd be neat.
[SPEAKER_08]: That would actually be all kinds of awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: I so support this idea.
[SPEAKER_08]: Even though, if I recall correctly, Pinball FX has a spy table.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who cares?
[SPEAKER_08]: Archer's like ten times better than that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's sad.
[SPEAKER_07]: I really wanted to like Archer, but I hate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Archer's hilarious.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hate it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Oh my god, I hate you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing, though.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hated The Office when I first watched it, too.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's one of those things that you gotta go back later on and you're like, oh, this is funny.
[SPEAKER_07]: Or like It's Always Sunny in Fel- No, actually, It's Always Sunny in Fel-
[SPEAKER_07]: But it looks stupid.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's Always Sunny looked terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's true.
[SPEAKER_08]: The first time I watched It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia, I hated it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But now I think it's one of the most hilarious shows on TV.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm willing to go back and try it again.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it's just right now, I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't have time.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I'll eventually go back and watch Archer and hopefully enjoy it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me just quickly plug our chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if any stragglers are finding us through Ustream.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is our backup right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: The all-game server stopped responding, so we're continuing on with the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: You can't stop us that easily, Internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we're continuing on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com if you want to chat with us.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't even know if the Ustream TV chat room is there, but if it is, we're not looking at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you need to go to Chat.OrangeLawnTrader.com to chat with us live as we're doing our little radio show on this Sunday evening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Also, I want to open up the Ask Orange Lounge line.
[SPEAKER_08]: Send a private message to Sky, S-K-I-E, in the chat room at chat.orangelounge.com if you have a question for Ask Orange Lounge.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're going to get to that shortly after a few more stories.
[SPEAKER_08]: Quickly...
[SPEAKER_08]: This is really sad, and this is something I think it happened on the week we were off, but we need to say it and tip our hat to this.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jack Tramiel, he founded the company that created the Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_08]: He died at the age of 83, according to Forbes magazine, and if you grew up on the Commodore family of computers like I did, then Jack Tramiel was obviously somebody important to you, so rest in peace.
[SPEAKER_07]: um going to a completely different topic here on Nintendo uh real quick I'm sorry I don't I didn't have a 64 but uh wasn't it like the command to like start a program or something like 80 something or load quote star quote comma eight comma one uh that would be ironic if it was four you know what there were um that was actually the same uh command on the Apple IIe wasn't no Apple for some of the games that I played it was
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought Apple did something different.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was similar, but it wasn't the star.
[SPEAKER_08]: The star was unique to Commodore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Comma 8, Comma 1.
[SPEAKER_08]: Because Comma 8 is what called out the disk drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think if you had a tape drive, it was Comma 7.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember doing the Comma 8, Comma 1 on the Apple.
[SPEAKER_08]: Are you sure you weren't playing the Comma?
[SPEAKER_02]: For Lode Runner.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Lode Runner was multi-platform.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway, let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm talking about Miyamoto being a damn tease.
[SPEAKER_08]: Miyamoto had a conversation with Edge at edgeonline.com and yeah, he was talking about some first party stuff because that
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, you know, this has led to rampant speculation and internet wank about the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But, I mean, I love the idea of a new Link to the Past, but, hold on, wasn't Zelda Four Swords on the GameCube kind of a redo of the Link to the Past?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not like that idea hasn't been touched since the Super Nintendo days.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's not true.
[SPEAKER_08]: The Game Boy Advance games and the portable games were really like that until it went all Wind Waker.
[SPEAKER_02]: I do have to make a rebuttal real quick.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: I was thinking of my cousin's Commodore 64.
[SPEAKER_07]: Ah, okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's alright.
[SPEAKER_07]: It would mean, to me, I think he's looking at kind of like doing the new Super Mario approach to it where basically they kind of do an updated engine but kind of old school play style.
[SPEAKER_07]: So you would have like an updated engine but it would be a top down Zelda game kind of like it was.
[SPEAKER_07]: But my god, put an editor in there, put a community feature where people can create their own quests and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: You're talking like money in the bank right there.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, it would be epic.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it would be really something that Nintendo would kind of say, Hey, look, we understand the internet and community features and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Instead of pretending that you do or saying, Hey, now we can do updates.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, if our games are buggy.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're with it.
[SPEAKER_07]: We're cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, this is the other big part of this is that he was asked about F-Zero.
[SPEAKER_08]: So excited.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he did say this, quote, maybe with future hardware with Wii U coming up, maybe we could create something that does make sense either as a smaller game or a fully fledged title.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, please.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's an interesting way for him to phrase it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Either as a smaller game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Could this be talking about like a Wii U-ware type of game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that what we're talking about?
[SPEAKER_08]: Or small as in portable?
[SPEAKER_08]: There's a lot you can read into that and probably way more than Miyamoto intended anybody, but you will not calm the fanboy wank down.
[SPEAKER_07]: Riddle me this.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I'm assuming that this little tablet controller thing that they're going to put out is probably going to have some sort of ARM processor in there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something that can, you know, obviously render some video and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, a lot of these tablet devices are based off of certain ARM processors.
[SPEAKER_07]: Could you, for example, and there are some other patents, which I don't know if we have a story on, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, could you, for example, imagine that...
[SPEAKER_07]: Hey, guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Just like, you know, the Pocket Station or even like the Vita or something like that, you know, hey, you can take a version of your gaming experience on the road with you.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, for example, like, hey, we're going to create like a virtual console app that runs on this tablet.
[SPEAKER_07]: And guess what?
[SPEAKER_07]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Not only does a tablet stream your gameplay from the TV, but you can take that tablet with you and play on the road.
[SPEAKER_07]: These, like, games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, but there's the whole like streaming.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, it doesn't have to stream the content.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm saying that the processor would be able to render its own content.
[SPEAKER_07]: And yes, you could do this also with the 3DS where you would have just a virtual console game or, you know, 3DS app or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But it would be kind of a neat way to get people interested because, well, then again, they would also kind of cut themselves in the knee by, you know,
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically offering a portable system with a console system, but it might get people to buy the system.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very true.
[SPEAKER_08]: One more story for you guys before I turn it over to DarkSakura, and that is for you Bomani fans.
[SPEAKER_08]: Where are you at?
[SPEAKER_08]: Holla.
[SPEAKER_08]: Beatmania2DX20.
[SPEAKER_08]: or as I like to call it 20th style even though that pisses the hardcore off because this is really called Beatmania 2DX20 Tricoro is the name of the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Konami has confirmed it exists.
[SPEAKER_08]: It exists.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's called Tricoro.
[SPEAKER_08]: The three color scheme is kind of what they're going with with the whole red, yellow, blue and location testing is underway April 19th through the 24th in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Happy birthday to me in Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right?
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be honest.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't followed the Beatmania 2DX series since about... What style was like DJ Troopers?
[SPEAKER_08]: Probably even before that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Happy Sky.
12, 13.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the last one I actually touched was an Empress.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't even play an Empress ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, but they did have the PS2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I keep forgetting.
[SPEAKER_08]: They cranked out those PS2 games, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Empress was the last one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I keep forgetting that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there you go, anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: 2DX 20th is happening and it's location testing right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: But Monty's not dead.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not in Japan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there's a few other things.
[SPEAKER_02]: How about some new Kinect games that are for kids?
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, I kind of want to get one of these.
[SPEAKER_02]: Kinect Sesame Street TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got Cookie Monster and Groover!
[SPEAKER_02]: There's no Elmo to be seen!
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But that's going to launch autumn 2012.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's according to Argonaut CEO James Bustall.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then there is Connect National Geographic, like NatGeoTV it says.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's being put up by C21 Media.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would get the Sesame Street one.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: and then there is a leaked trailer that if it's to be believed then Resident Evil 6 will come out on October 2nd I'm sure there's a few people who are still into that series a few
[SPEAKER_08]: Resident Evil 6 looks hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: A lot of people are very excited about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's not a side story, which is a good thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: According to this trailer, the protagonist is Wesker's son.
[SPEAKER_02]: The man who's told to save the world.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then, last but not least, Brink has sold more than 2.5 million copies worldwide.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good job, Brink.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay, Brink!
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, that's a lot better than I thought that game did because I thought that game tanked.
[SPEAKER_07]: But that warrants a sequel, I would say.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's very true.
[SPEAKER_07]: I hope they're smart enough not to do one.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, well, since tonight was supposed to be kind of a special show at All Games Radio, although the server issues are holding us back, we're still going on Ustream.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, it's a different type of special now.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a different type of special.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's fooper now.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fooper, fooper.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we thought we would do, instead of the foogle question of the week, we would do Ask Orange Lounge tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We don't do this segment very often, but it's when we open it up.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is the show where every gamer has a voice.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to ask us anything, especially...
[SPEAKER_08]: with what's going on tonight, you can send a private message.
[SPEAKER_08]: You want to ask us about life or anything?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, you can send that over private message to Sky.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's cue up the music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's Ask Orange Lounge some stupid question.
[SPEAKER_08]: What will we find out tonight on Orange Lounge Radio?
[SPEAKER_08]: One thing I'd like to know is why can't we stream on all games anymore?
[SPEAKER_08]: It was supposed to be a special show, but leave it to us to get fucked.
[SPEAKER_08]: First question tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loco Poco, I love that name.
[SPEAKER_08]: Reminds me of like Poco Roco.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loco Poco wants to know, if RuPaul's Drag Race was a fighting game, thank God for serious questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank God for serious questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: If RuPaul's Drag Race was a fighting game, how bad would RuPaul be as a final boss if he had SNK boss syndrome?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, you know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you've seen the video for Glamazon, but it's on the internet.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, the big video that features the three finalists?
[SPEAKER_08]: It has, like, a video game theme, funny enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it's, you know, the three queens that beat all the other ones, like, being big Glamazon robots stepping up.
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's a lot of, like, video game graphics in it and stuff, so it was clearly inspired by games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You want to know something funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: Like, in the early 90s, my friend had an avatar online called Glamazon who was a large, buxom, overweight Wonder Woman.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, how bad would RuPaul be as a final boss?
[SPEAKER_08]: you would sashay all over your face but seriously what would a dream fighting game crossover that has yet to be done be a dream fighting game crossover that hasn't happened yet
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know about fighting game, but I do know what I would like as a survival horror game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'd like a supernatural game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want a new goddamn Killer Instinct game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that too much to ask?
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll say Killer Instinct versus Mortal Kombat.
[SPEAKER_08]: That works in my head.
[SPEAKER_02]: That would be pretty epic.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to say that for my answer.
[SPEAKER_02]: I want Pretty Fighter versus Asuka 120%, who only Sega, Saturn fighting game people know what I'm talking about.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tiger Claw thinks RuPaul's Drag Race would be more of a kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Geovidea says RuPaul would be a fierce final boss.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fierce, fierce.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, moving on to a question from Actdeft.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here we go with a serious question, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the thing or are the things you have regretted doing in the show and why?
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything you think or know you did wrong or shouldn't have done at all?
[SPEAKER_08]: Regret's a strong word.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think I know what Loki's is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: Karaoke.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sure there's things I've said.
[SPEAKER_08]: In fact, I know there's things I've said where I've kind of gone back and changed my mind later on.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think, boy, I sounded kind of stupid and ignorant saying that.
[SPEAKER_08]: My opinion on some games ends up changing.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that's part of this process.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's kind of the risk that we take doing this show every week and having done it for so long is that sometimes we're going to grow up in front of you.
[SPEAKER_08]: And in a lot of ways, that's kind of happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: When we started this show...
[SPEAKER_08]: We were 10 years younger than we are now.
[SPEAKER_08]: We went from being in our early 20s to being our early 30s.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think there's just a lot of like kind of growing up that happens.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to be honest, although I think the old shows for OLR are great, and I'm really proud of a lot that we accomplished in the old shows.
[SPEAKER_08]: When I go back and listen to old episodes, like anything before episode like 150, really, I go back and listen to the old stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really hard for me to listen to because I'm like, oh God, oh God, there's so much technically wrong with this.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it just sounds like a hot fucking mess everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: so I mean I wouldn't call that a regret but it's definitely something we've really like learned a lot uh from so I mean otherwise as far as specific instances I I can't maybe when I had my diva fit I'm not really proud of that moment um that was you know back when the show ironically when the show died halfway through and uh something just set me off and I think it was on Justin TV I don't know the place where we used to stream so I don't know um
[SPEAKER_08]: That wasn't a highlight of my career, certainly.
[SPEAKER_08]: But regret's a strong word because you learn from every little fuck up, you know?
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Rama asks, what game you played was so bad you said, fuck this shit, dropped the controller, and left?
[SPEAKER_08]: What game was so bad you said, fuck this shit, drop the controller and left?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, I'm sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: You weren't jumping in.
[SPEAKER_08]: I assumed you... What would you like to say for regrets?
[SPEAKER_02]: Nothing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I haven't rod rolled you enough.
[SPEAKER_08]: Game where you drop the controller and said, fuck this shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: Fusion Frenzy 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: So fucking terrible.
[SPEAKER_08]: That game.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like, what the hell is this garbage that I'm playing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yaris would be a good one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sonic 4 Episode 1.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Bullet Witch.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oof.
[SPEAKER_07]: and actually Oni Chambara because it was pretty annoying the whole having to have your sword get dirty and get stuck in zombies is stupid a sword would not get stuck in zombies a sword chops zombies in half
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to try to burn through the rest of these questions here pretty quick.
[SPEAKER_08]: Randy says, Have you guys ever looked through your game collections only to find a sealed game?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_02]: All the time.
[SPEAKER_08]: This happened to my cousin and a shrink-wrapped copy of NBA 2K10 yesterday.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, Randy.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found the Blue Seed RPG about a month ago for Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a copy right over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pilotwings Resort on the 3DS still sitting in the shrink wrap.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stupid me.
[SPEAKER_07]: Might as well sell that stuff for new on eBay.
[SPEAKER_07]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Matt, anything that you've had?
[SPEAKER_07]: I just have copies, but nothing that I didn't know I have because I normally don't leave that stuff shrunk.
[SPEAKER_07]: I have still a shrunk copy of Earth Defense Force, the original one, because I bought five copies of it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, I bought three copies when we were selling my work for five bucks each.
[SPEAKER_07]: I'm like, I can't pass that up.
[SPEAKER_07]: I am buying all the copies of those games.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I kept them.
[SPEAKER_07]: And funny enough, I actually broke a couple copies of mine.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it's still worth actually a pretty good amount of money, I think, because it's hard to find now.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, I'm going to close.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which, by the way, Sandbox Games is working on a new version of Earth Defense Force.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Rob, there is another game that we have that's still shrink-wrapped.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: That's...
[SPEAKER_02]: Gunstar Heroes for the Game Gear.
[SPEAKER_02]: Serious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why when you got the Genesis one?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I bought it for Dan as a treat.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to end.
[SPEAKER_08]: No more questions because I got five questions in queue.
[SPEAKER_08]: So question time is up.
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to read my question.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not reading your question.
[SPEAKER_02]: My question is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura asks, why are you so fly?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because I'm hot.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, moving on.
[SPEAKER_08]: GZDR4EV wants to know, according to Wiki, this is a deep question, according to Wiki, 68% of the population believes in some type of religion.
[SPEAKER_08]: So why aren't there more video games with a religious theme?
[SPEAKER_02]: controversy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi, people.
[SPEAKER_02]: You get one little thing about someone's religion wrong and they want to just go, it's sacrilegious.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it is part that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, even though the stat is 68% believe, the problem is that split up into how many different types of religions.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, you know, and like DarkSakura says, you get something wrong.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think
[SPEAKER_08]: You may not kind of put the two in the same category, but I think there's a lot of games where spirituality is a theme, especially a lot of modern RPGs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think especially a lot of the newer Final Fantasy games.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mass Effect, to some extent, has a little bit of those themes in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's not really in your face, but there definitely is questions about the big picture, which is what religion's about.
[SPEAKER_02]: All these different, especially in RPGs, like you were saying, all these different worlds have their own mythologies.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, for example, I'm just, you know, I'm going to use World of Warcraft.
[SPEAKER_08]: DR4F forgot about Battle of Olympus.
[SPEAKER_08]: He did.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I'm going to use World of Warcraft as an example just because it's fresh in my mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just finished that Thrall book today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was really good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's got elements of shamanism, which we have in pagan religions today.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have their light, which I'm assuming is... The way they've lined it up is close to an equivalent of Christianity and Judeo-Christian religions.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, they've got, you know, the devil worshippers.
[SPEAKER_02]: They have all kinds of different cults.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, but, you know, even apocalyptic cults, which we've got apocalyptic cults here.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, how many of those people poisoned themselves to get on the giant spaceship on Halley's Comet, you know, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, that wasn't.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was Hail Bop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hail Bop.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That whole thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: The freaky guy on the TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: I blame Oom Bop for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: but I mean my point is just using that I mean clearly a lot of the religions in that game are parallels for types of religions you have those archetypes you know and then you've got like say Final Fantasy 7 here's an example you've got the Cetra and their earth religion you know the soul of the planet that type of thing
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's just an example.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's not so much that they're mimicking real religions, it's so much that they've created their own mythology based off of what each culture that's made this game understands of other religions.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean, the same goes into, you know, different anime, TV shows, you name it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Weiland has an interesting point.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tekken has an angel and a devil in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, that's also supposed to be genetic, too.
[SPEAKER_08]: Xenocore says half the Final Fantasies have that theme, almost anything from Japan.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, like the whole spirituality.
[SPEAKER_02]: And here's another idea.
[SPEAKER_02]: For anyone who was an old Saturn gamer like me, there was Black Matrix that was based off of Hell mythology.
[SPEAKER_02]: So...
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt says if you had the money to buy three arcade machines for yourself what would they be?
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought this question came up last week but it was the show that Jason and Alan were on so let's hear it from you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: What three arcade machines would you buy?
[SPEAKER_08]: For me, BurgerTime, Magic Sword, Spy Hunter.
[SPEAKER_02]: For me, an Ultra Kade, a Mame, and no.
[SPEAKER_03]: Cheater.
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: Since I'm going to lump Pinball into Arcade, I'm going to say that I would get probably a Tekken 5, just because I really liked that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I would get a Strider, and then I would probably get maybe a Theater of Magic, Pinball, or Black Rose.
[SPEAKER_08]: and DarkSakura.
[SPEAKER_07]: Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, this is easy because I already have an arcade machine at home.
[SPEAKER_07]: The three that I can't get right now, we'll do... Let's see.
[SPEAKER_07]: Fourth Mix Plus, a Max 2, and whatever the newest DDR game they have out there.
[SPEAKER_07]: Was it something versus Dance Ice Revolution Second Mix or something?
[SPEAKER_07]: One of those.
[SPEAKER_07]: So three DDR machines.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: You won three DDR machines in your house.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, they're all different.
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, you know, Max 2 is pretty awesome in its own right.
[SPEAKER_07]: And, you know, 4th Mix Plus is pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: And the new game, I haven't played the new DDR game, but that might be pretty cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, Tiger Call, the ferret is actually at my house.
[SPEAKER_07]: X3 vs. Second Mix, says the chatroom.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, X3 vs. Second Mix.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's what I'll be getting.
[SPEAKER_08]: Three questions left.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku says, looking back, if Konami quickly and directly followed up with a successor to DDR Extreme 10 years ago instead of Supernova...
[SPEAKER_08]: Do you think it would have created a different rhythm game community than what it turned out due to ITG taking that place?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a loaded question.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think ITG ever truly took its place.
[SPEAKER_08]: ITG caused controversy and kind of splintered the community into a couple kind of different sects, if you will.
[SPEAKER_08]: I said sects.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was the pro-ITG crowd and the anti-ITG crowd, the DDR loyalists.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is how I feel about it in regards to the ITG thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's like, if you were at a restaurant and then a dog took a shit on the sidewalk, would that make a decision about which place you would go to eat?
[SPEAKER_08]: I think what needed to happen is, yes, Konami needed to put something out a lot sooner than they did.
[SPEAKER_08]: Konami failed because Konami of Japan refused to take risks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Jason Enos forced them to take a risk here in America.
[SPEAKER_08]: I shouldn't say force, but you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_08]: He pestered and pestered and did the professional version of that for years and years until Konami finally released something over here.
[SPEAKER_08]: When he left Konami...
[SPEAKER_08]: and they shut down Konami Hawaii who was doing a great job with the Xbox games when they shut down Konami in the Bay Area where the fans were making steps and you know all that stuff I think it lost a lot too much to recover from so honestly a little weird now seeing like some of these step mania artists and stuff like that or people that would make music for step mania and DWI and stuff like that actually as artists in the game it's a little odd neat but a little odd
[SPEAKER_08]: Two questions left.
[SPEAKER_08]: I do have to give another shout out here because I noticed our Ustream count is increasing.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is not a usual thing for us.
[SPEAKER_08]: We are using this as a backup.
[SPEAKER_08]: Our main feed at All Games Radio, which ironically it was to be our last night on All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: It died partway through.
[SPEAKER_08]: I am still showing feeding to All Games Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: So their server's down or something.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyhow, that's beside the point.
[SPEAKER_08]: you can't shut us up that easy so here we are on Ustream if you want to join us in the chat room chat.orangeloungeradio.com it's a radio show that's why you're looking at my Tron figurine on the camera alright moving on two questions remain Xenocore
[SPEAKER_08]: What game have you resisted playing the most but been the most pleasantly surprised by?
[SPEAKER_08]: Xenocore, you couldn't have given me an easier question because it's going on right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wrote it off originally as, oh, this isn't my type of game.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is like a first-person shooter.
[SPEAKER_08]: I watched a friend play it, and I saw the most boring parts of the game driving the Mako around, and I was like, eh, not the game for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Finally, Shane basically threatened to kill me if I didn't play it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm like, fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: He's very good at bullying me.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I said, fine, I'll play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, Rob, you should play Mass Effect.
[SPEAKER_08]: Pretty much.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just like that, too.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's my Shane impression.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't know, because he'll do that and tell you to do something, but then when he fights with you, when he fights with you, no, Rob, you gotta play the... He'll totally do the little boyfriend.
[SPEAKER_02]: See, I see this, fine, I don't care if you play it or not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stare.
[SPEAKER_08]: so regardless of you know the catalyst Mass Effect I started playing and I absolutely love it and I think it's a fantastic series Jamie anything for you here?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cave Story oh that's true it was out for years and years and we just kind of go oh little well I had known about Cave Story like forever and I even actually played some of the old version of it when it was you know like a flash download or something
[SPEAKER_02]: or I play different incarnations of Cave Story and then just starting to play it again and Dan though, he was really into it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So he's like, I'm going to play your Cave Story when you're not here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fine, play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll get the points.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, anything you can think of?
[SPEAKER_08]: A series you wrote off originally?
[SPEAKER_07]: Call of Duty Modern Warfare I knew it Honestly, because I played it once I was like, eh, I don't really like this as much as I like the World War 2 ones I'm not going to really play this and then went back and it was awesome so, you know, gung-ho into that I don't know Yeah, that's pretty much it I guess Alright, last question from Derek H
[SPEAKER_08]: Question, when women say the good ones are always taken, does that mean if you're still single you're not a good one?
[SPEAKER_08]: I always heard the good ones are always gay.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I always heard.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I'm always like, that's right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was never really in that opinion, you know, because I was like, fuck, I don't want anybody.
[SPEAKER_02]: And then I met Dan and I was like, well, fine, I guess you'll do.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, my husband is the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have you ever caught yourself saying that?
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, you're the woman on this show.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, honestly, I haven't because I mean, I've never had a trouble getting a date.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know why, I guess, you know, because I've always, I mean, I always thought that I was kind of this undateable geek chick, you know, but I've never really had a problem getting, you know, getting anyone to date me, I guess.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, what?
[SPEAKER_07]: Can't, never mind.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, but, you know... Can't say anything inappropriate to that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, well, I'm going to go ahead and say this out loud in public.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan was my first and only.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, not that I haven't made out with a bunch of people, but still.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, you know, Dan happened to be the right person at the right time, and he's always been the right person, so I've never...
[SPEAKER_02]: It's never been a case of why are all the good ones taken.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's been, why do all these guys suck?
[SPEAKER_02]: And oh, someone who doesn't suck.
[SPEAKER_02]: So that's what my experience is.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know if you find this to be the case or not, but I think a lot of times when somebody finds the one, you're kind of surprised a little bit at it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, I never thought it would be this or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think a lot of times women or anybody, I mean, I've heard gay guys that say that too.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's not just women that say it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard a lot of people say that, that the good ones are always taken.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think, you know, it just means...
[SPEAKER_08]: my radar isn't pinging off because I'm very tunnel vision to what I'm looking for and I have written all over my notepad what I want my dream boy to be like and everything that's shoved at me in the media I'm very tunnel vision and then it's like oh shit I just fucking fell in love
[SPEAKER_08]: And even though it's not a woman-man situation, Alan I knew for years online never would have thought I'd end up with him, moving in with him and all that stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it just happened.
[SPEAKER_08]: And when it happened, it was kind of one of those things.
[SPEAKER_02]: I knew Dan online for years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is, you know, when I was in Alabama and had no, I was actually saving up my money to go to Anime Expo, which is the money that I use for my plane ticket to fly out here in the first place.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, I mean, I had known Dan forever online and it just happened.
[SPEAKER_02]: I mean.
[SPEAKER_08]: Techness says, it's because the women who say that are usually dating assholes in our chat room at chat.orangeonradio.com I was always dating nice guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: I had broken up with every guy that I had gone out with because he was too nice
[SPEAKER_02]: I went as someone who would argue with me and not treat me like I was, you know, made of fragile eggshell and porcelain.
[SPEAKER_02]: And Dan doesn't treat me like that.
[SPEAKER_02]: He treats me like I'm an equal and like I'm his partner, not just, you know, his woman.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_02]: So.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_07]: Also, I was going to say, because you're in the friend zone, that's why they say that.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's why you hear that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, the friend zone.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because they can discuss these woman to woman things with you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say something else.
[SPEAKER_02]: I have had guys come back and say they were interested and I'll flat out evaluate would I have dated this person and for the most part I can safely say no like I'm not going to name names but there was someone who said he was interested in me until he found out I was married and I just flat out said well not to be a bitch about this but I wouldn't have gone out with you and this is why I wouldn't have gone out with you so if I'm the kind of person that you're looking for this is why I wouldn't have gone out with you you know what I'm saying
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah, I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that's very helpful for those guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop being neurotic.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you for the questions, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to move on with some video game news.
[SPEAKER_08]: Before we do, I have to notice, one other thing I just noted was still in the shrink wrap, going back to that earlier question.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at this.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have the PlayStation Vita little ARG cards, the AR play cards.
[SPEAKER_08]: Haven't taken them out.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good, because you haven't figured out that the AR is broken.
[SPEAKER_07]: Is it really?
[SPEAKER_07]: It sucks.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well here, I have a use for them now.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll put them on the Ustream cam since we suddenly have a video feed tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: There you go.
[SPEAKER_07]: Good job.
[SPEAKER_07]: Look at the cards.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should put Loki's kind of dried out looking pizza up there next.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like, it's terrible.
[SPEAKER_07]: I tried playing the soccer game and I spent like 15 minutes trying to get that damn thing to work.
[SPEAKER_07]: No.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I played the fireworks game and I was like, nope, don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just, it's a waste of time.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's neat, but you know, I need like an actual AR game that doesn't require cards.
[SPEAKER_07]: And that works, you know, that'd be nice if it worked.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, let's move on with some more gaming news.
[SPEAKER_08]: The mailbag coming up shortly here in a moment.
[SPEAKER_08]: First off, Loki.
[SPEAKER_07]: All right, let's talk a little bit about Sony.
[SPEAKER_07]: And I mean, I guess they kind of need to have like a,
[SPEAKER_07]: and their own Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: type game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, hey, why not?
[SPEAKER_07]: Everyone else is doing it.
[SPEAKER_07]: So, yes, there was a rumor, of course, that they were putting out some sort of game that was going to feature all the PlayStation All-Stars and that kind of stuff.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, now they've actually registered a domain called PlayStation All-Stars Battle Royale.
[SPEAKER_07]: And it is looking to be like that game.
[SPEAKER_07]: Something with maybe all their first-party franchise characters from Heavenly Sword to God of War.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although, Heavenly Sword, is anyone really going to remember that game?
[SPEAKER_02]: I do.
[SPEAKER_07]: So they're going to have all these different characters fighting each other.
[SPEAKER_07]: Maybe in some sort of Smash Brothers type way.
[SPEAKER_07]: Originally, I guess it was on the working title, Title Fight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Rumored to be announced actually this week on Spike TV's The Game Trailers TV show.
[SPEAKER_07]: When's that show on?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thursday.
[SPEAKER_07]: so uh i guess we'll find out this week if that's the case most likely probably going to be the case um so neat i guess um i i don't know it's just cool we'll see how this really kind of works well i mean obviously they're gonna kind of take the successful super smash brothers format and put their own spin on it i mean it's
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I don't know if they have quite the recognizable lineup of characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, I don't even think I can really throw that kind of shade at it because, you know, there are some big, big characters there.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like I don't see how... I mean, like, there's no... At least it's not a kart racing game.
[SPEAKER_07]: They have a little big planet for that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, Nintendo, you know, Smash Bros.
[SPEAKER_07]: makes sense because there's really no M-rated characters in Nintendo's kind of lineup there.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're all kind of that...
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you for watching!
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they need to have first off Kevin Butler needs to be a playable character as is also the creepy baby from their commercials needs to be a character as well that would be awesome but yes I wonder if they'll get any crossover things you know kind of like how they finally got like Snake and Smash Brothers and Sonic and some of that you think any of that will happen
[SPEAKER_08]: SSJ100 Matt says, can we kill that Marcus PSP kid?
[SPEAKER_07]: Psst.
[SPEAKER_07]: That would be hilarious, but no, it's probably not going to be the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, EA story.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very controversial company these days.
[SPEAKER_08]: Eurogamer had a report this week that in the UK, EA person Keith Ramsdale, one of the executives at EA, announced that EA is going to develop an online universe for all its franchises.
[SPEAKER_08]: He didn't say multiplayer necessarily, but a cross-platform major tie-in approach to games.
[SPEAKER_08]: And basically pulling in any gadget you can think of.
[SPEAKER_08]: iPhone, Xbox, whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: Flipo grenade!
[SPEAKER_08]: Quote, Imagine a player gets up in the morning, plays an online match on his 360 before going to work.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the bus on his way to work, he practices his free kicks on his tablet.
[SPEAKER_08]: At lunch, he looks on the transfer window on his PC.
[SPEAKER_08]: On the way home, he chooses his kit on the smartphone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing, when he gets home to play again on his 360 that evening...
[SPEAKER_07]: He finds out his account's been hacked and the people have charged FIFA DLC points to them.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: All those achievements and upgrade will be alive in his game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Here's the thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, so as much as EA's talking about this unified network, you know, I kind of thought this was already happening.
[SPEAKER_08]: And EA had a very our way or the highway mentality and that's how they got away with a lot of stuff on the Xbox.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean...
[SPEAKER_08]: Even the way I bought Mass Effect 2 DLC, you kind of had to go online and tie in the Cerberus account online, and then that opens up the DLC.
[SPEAKER_08]: I thought it was ridiculous, but EA is being very possessive about it.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, they want it that way so that you have to buy your fucking online passes for every game because they're like, shit, this offline game, how are we going to sell an online pass for it?
[SPEAKER_07]: Because, yeah, that may have worked once with Kingdoms of Amal or Reckoning, but people are going to start...
[SPEAKER_07]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_07]: Ghost Recon Future Soldier, Call of Duty Elite,
[SPEAKER_07]: Honestly, honestly, is it really going to take, what, like five seconds to configure your fucking soccer player or whatever when you get home?
[SPEAKER_07]: I mean, do you really have to bring... Well, of course, I guess if you're this type of guy that brings your fucking tablet and phone to work with you and shit, then I guess you want to get shit done right away, but...
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a little excessive.
[SPEAKER_07]: Cool if they're going to do that, but once again, I think it's just to sell those online passes.
[SPEAKER_07]: If it adds value, then neat.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think they've done that also with Need for Speed.
[SPEAKER_07]: They had their auto log or something like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're kind of already doing this.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's the way everything's going.
[SPEAKER_07]: They need to have some way to drive people to keep playing their games.
[SPEAKER_07]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, so you get to hear the same music, theme music again because it doubles for the mailbag music.
[SPEAKER_08]: Every week you guys send us emails at mailbag at orangeloungeradio.com and DarkSakura dives into the email bag head first and pulls out some emails she thinks she ought to share with the rest of us.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, now this is from April 12th, so disclaimers and everything, blah blah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, I haven't heard a lot about Assassin's Creed on the show, and I was wondering why it isn't a big subject on here.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a stellar series, and I really think the story is underestimated by its gameplay being the main attraction.
[SPEAKER_02]: What do you guys think?
[SPEAKER_07]: There's another game series that I play, and I'm like, fuck this, I'm not playing this anymore.
[SPEAKER_07]: Really?
[SPEAKER_07]: You didn't like it?
[SPEAKER_07]: I didn't like Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard a lot of good things about it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of Mass Effect to me, where I saw it really quickly and I was like, ooh, I'm playing too much WoW right now to get into Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a lot of friends that are really into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It is on my list to get to at some point, but, you know, we can't play everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: Next email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, that was from Danny.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey guys, Sterlach here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Welcome back.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was listening to some random video game soundtracks the other day and had an interesting thought for a possible topic to talk about.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm curious what your answer will be.
[SPEAKER_02]: It seems that sometimes that random game will come along that completely sucks but can defy all logic by having a kickass soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_02]: The two that jumped to my mind right away are Unlimited Saga for PS2 and Spider-Man and the X-Men Arcade's Revenge on the SNES.
[SPEAKER_02]: What games do you think of that will fit this criteria?
[SPEAKER_02]: Obviously opinion-based, but curious what you guys come up with.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why, but my mind goes very, very old school, and one of the first games I think of was Goonies 2.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know why, and the NES had a stellar soundtrack for the 8-bit days.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Actually, Dan really loves that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but the game itself was, eh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it takes some getting into, but then once you really do get into it, you're like, wow, this game, I don't give this game enough credit.
[SPEAKER_08]: But that was really where the soundtrack was so good, I had to play more of it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I liked, even, I'm not going to say it was a bad game, but it just wasn't that in-depth.
[SPEAKER_02]: It wasn't that hard.
[SPEAKER_02]: Strider 2 had a fantastic soundtrack, but really easy gameplay.
[SPEAKER_02]: But for me, a lot of it was just how awesome the music was.
[SPEAKER_02]: And oh my gosh, Strider, here are you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got a great answer for this.
[SPEAKER_02]: What?
[SPEAKER_08]: Final Fantasy Mystic Quest.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of a crap RPG.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, it's all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's got a decent story.
[SPEAKER_08]: But the soundtrack was so good.
[SPEAKER_08]: And it wasn't no buimatsu either.
[SPEAKER_08]: People are going to poop on me for this.
[SPEAKER_08]: But?
[SPEAKER_08]: Paperboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Paperboy.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't like Paperboy, but I love the music in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can see that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I just thought it was funny.
[SPEAKER_02]: I really am not any good at Paperboy.
[SPEAKER_08]: Paperboy is a weird-ass game.
[SPEAKER_02]: It is, but I love watching other people play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's the thing, but I hate playing it myself.
[SPEAKER_08]: Actdeft in our chatroom says, Sonic games.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, Sonic Adventure 2 had a good soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anything you can think of, Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: A stall on the Sega Saturn.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a random pick.
[SPEAKER_07]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: It was a great soundtrack.
[SPEAKER_07]: I actually recorded on my cassette tape because I played the music on the Saturn when I rented the console to play the game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hell yeah!
[SPEAKER_02]: but Crazy Taxi was kind of a crappy game but it's that song or the combination of Offspring and Bad Religion it just wasn't the same which were two bands I was so into when that game came out I freaking love Bad Religion there was another game that just popped into my head and then it popped out the moment you said Crazy Taxi so you know
[SPEAKER_02]: I would say the PlayStation version of Grandia.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was playing it on the Genesis because the Genesis version is so much better.
[SPEAKER_02]: But I still tried to play it on the PlayStation just so I could hear the good music.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, come on over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Have some fun with Crazy Taxi.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's run over some bitches.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hey, you're driving too fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_03]: I know what I'm doing.
[SPEAKER_08]: I mean, that song was already big before Crazy Taxi.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember that song in high school and stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: And then when that game came out, that song will forever be associated with Crazy Taxi.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay, I know another game.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I liked the music in it, believe it or not, was that stupid Avatar game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you're on your own there.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was going back and watching the cutscenes from Tron Evolution, and that was good music.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'll give you that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because, I mean, it was pretty much the Daft Punk stuff.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: More emails?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Let me go ahead and close the one from our friend Sterlok.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hi gang!
[SPEAKER_02]: Hope you had an awesome time at Electronica last week.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bitch.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you for my Duffy outfit.
[SPEAKER_08]: You're welcome.
[SPEAKER_02]: While you lot were having fun, I didn't get to go, so it was just while Rob was having fun, I was forced to help my parents decide which of my childhood memories I wanted to destroy for all time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hint none.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good lord, this sounds like a terrible reality show.
[SPEAKER_02]: While sorting through all my stuff, I found my old Master System 2.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe because all the episodes of Game Center CX I've been watching, maybe it's the fact that you mentioned Castle of Illusion last time, but I felt like I had to plug it in and get me a fix of retro gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was surprised that it still works perfectly and that I still remembered how to plug it in and tune the TV.
[SPEAKER_02]: Flicking through channels and suddenly I saw the Lo-Fi Sega appear.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a heartwarming experience.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wait a minute, is Master System 2 what they call the Genesis overseas?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: The Genesis was called the Mega Drive.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like Castle of Illusion.
[SPEAKER_08]: Was that on the Master System?
[SPEAKER_02]: They did it in Brazil.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, all right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I've never really been one for retro gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: I got MS2 pretty late and missed the 16-bit era entirely.
[SPEAKER_02]: I never really grew up on video games in that way.
[SPEAKER_02]: But picking a game, blowing into the cartridge, and inserting it while imitating Arino's Game Center CX Ka-chow on was fun.
[SPEAKER_02]: I, of course, never seen that show.
[SPEAKER_02]: The games I used to play were pretty much exactly as I remembered them.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fun, uncomplicated, and pretty tough.
[SPEAKER_02]: They just all seemed charming.
[SPEAKER_02]: The old school graphics, the 8-bit music, all real undeniable charm.
[SPEAKER_02]: The only thing I found surprising was how slow the games felt, Sonic especially.
[SPEAKER_02]: Maybe just a case of badly ported PAL games?
[SPEAKER_02]: Unfortunately, I didn't get to spend too much time playing it, but I'd like to say it's thanks to you guys and GCCX that I really had a renewed interest in the pleasure of retro gaming.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thanks, OLR, and that's from the OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: When it comes to retro gaming, do you prefer playing old games on a modern console is better than playing them on their original consoles?
[SPEAKER_02]: P.P.S.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bonus images for you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, this is Piccarino.
[SPEAKER_08]: I like to play retro games on newer consoles just because you know there we go getting it on my new TV and everything it's really hard to hook up an Atari 2600 to a modern HD TV you kind of can't do it without a lot of converters you know I saw his Twitter this week with all the Sonic Chaos R-Type oh I fucking love R-Type good times no I fucking love R-Type you want to talk about good video game music R-Type
[SPEAKER_02]: You need to find the opening music for R-Type for me right now, Rob, or I will cry.
[SPEAKER_07]: You know, I forgot to mention in my games that I played the last two weeks, but I actually played through both Sexy Parodius and Parodius Da.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, I love Parodius too.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have you ever played Chatting Parodius?
[SPEAKER_02]: No.
[SPEAKER_02]: You should play Chatting Parodius.
[SPEAKER_02]: Excuse me.
[SPEAKER_08]: This may or may not be the song you were looking for.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know this game as well as you do.
[SPEAKER_02]: Nope, that's not.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yep, that's his.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, bitch, let it start before you make a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, I gotta watch how much... Here we go, here's the part.
[SPEAKER_02]: This is like my favorite piece of video game music ever.
[SPEAKER_08]: We gotta watch how much of this we play on Ustream.
[SPEAKER_08]: They have a zero tolerance on piracy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, it's on YouTube, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: Um...
[SPEAKER_02]: I would actually have to say, and this is why Dan and I have such a big classic game console collection, is because we really do like playing them on their intended consoles.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sometimes I like going back and playing a few things on a newer console, if that happens to be what I have hooked up, and say that the Neo Geo is at Dan's mom's house, because we have a bunch of our game stuff in storage at her place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I can't very well go grab the Neo Geo and play anything.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I guess I can play King of Fighters on the Dreamcast or something.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I'm just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: So it depends on convenience.
[SPEAKER_02]: But if I've got it there, I will hook up the old stuff and play it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hell to the fuck yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Is that it for the mailbag?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, we have two more.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, my God.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: We've been gone for two freaking weeks.
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's true.
[SPEAKER_02]: Hey, OLR.
[SPEAKER_02]: Defective Candy here.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just emailing to announce my boyfriend and I are the new proud parents of our own arcade cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I picked it up on Craigslist for $70.
[SPEAKER_02]: It needed a little work, but the wood alone to build one from scratch would have run us over $100.
[SPEAKER_02]: We were thinking of turning it into a main cabinet, a PC-based system that uses emulators.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, we know.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because the game card is shot.
[SPEAKER_02]: The original cabinet was from Datapro, although I am unsure what game originally came with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It had WWF WrestleFest in it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I remember that game.
[SPEAKER_02]: I found out Datapro was a large manufacturer of mostly pinball machines and I was wondering if DarkSakura was familiar with the brand.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am familiar with them, but I don't think that they put out much that was good.
[SPEAKER_02]: I can double check that.
[SPEAKER_02]: I know it was Gottlieb that put out that TMNT table.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll have to check.
[SPEAKER_02]: Anyway, I wanted to thank you guys for keeping me in the gaming world all these years and inspiring me to follow my dreams of buying my own cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think the bug has really bitten us and we already went out to make a bar top cabinet next.
[SPEAKER_02]: Keep you updated on the status of our work.
[SPEAKER_02]: Cheers, Defective Candy.
[SPEAKER_08]: I want a bar top cabinet.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're more expensive than you think.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here's the machine.
[SPEAKER_08]: WWF WrestleFest.
[SPEAKER_08]: What a cheap piece of crap.
[SPEAKER_08]: But it's your piece of crap, and congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: And you know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll be great for the meme, exactly what Defective Candy's talking about in the email.
[SPEAKER_08]: It'll be a great thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: We built ours out of an old stand-up pole position.
[SPEAKER_02]: Our last one.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just be careful with what you're building your system out of because you need to have the right graphics card for it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I think there's... You can find the specs online.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, yeah, you can get special drivers.
[SPEAKER_07]: Like, I have...
[SPEAKER_07]: I ended up, before I was using an arcade VGA card, I recommend not going through that route because the arcade VGA cards are usually a little bit old.
[SPEAKER_07]: Although the newer ones are newer models.
[SPEAKER_07]: But I ended up going with an ATI card and then they have special drivers that you can get that will do the low res scaling for you.
[SPEAKER_07]: And then also...
[SPEAKER_07]: You want to get the JAMA adapter for the J-Pack.
[SPEAKER_07]: J-Packs are awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: You need to get that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Also be careful that you buy good buttons that won't wear out quickly.
[SPEAKER_07]: For a cabinet like that, you don't need good buttons.
[SPEAKER_07]: It doesn't matter.
[SPEAKER_07]: The buttons are so damn cheap.
[SPEAKER_07]: They're like 50 cents.
[SPEAKER_02]: The last email.
[SPEAKER_02]: Have any of you played Pure Solar?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's an RPG created for the Sega Genesis but was originally released in 2008.
[SPEAKER_02]: A reprint of the game recently sold out and they will probably release it again at some point.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's a really well made game and does something no other Genesis game has done before that I know of.
[SPEAKER_02]: If you purchase the companion CD soundtrack you can play the Genesis cart using the CD soundtrack in the Sega CD drive for the in-game music.
[SPEAKER_02]: The developer of Watermelon Games is currently working on a new Genesis Mega Drive game, so check out their website if you are interested.
[SPEAKER_02]: Do you have any Genesis RPG recommendations?
[SPEAKER_08]: Any of the fantasy stars really, although that's kind of an obvious answer.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember this one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I remember some of the Genesis games that came out later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby had had one of the folks on his show a few years ago.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't remember that one though.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome that people are still making games though for Genesis, but they still do it for like Atari 2600 and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Genesis RPGs.
[SPEAKER_08]: I didn't own a Genesis growing up.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a website for it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is a really hard question for me because I didn't own a Genesis growing up.
[SPEAKER_08]: And my friends, you know, the games we would play would be Mortal Kombat because I had the Blood and Street Fighter Championship Edition.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're all playing games on Genesis that weren't Phantasy Star.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dark Sakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, I was a SNES person growing up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bobby reminded me.
[SPEAKER_08]: It was called Beggar Prince.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: I knew.
[SPEAKER_08]: I was like.
[SPEAKER_02]: I grew up playing Chrono Trigger in the Final Fantasies so but I mean I've gone back we picked up the Sega Ages 2500 a copy of a Phantasy Star which we had our friend Krista translate for us while we were playing through it so I mean
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't have a Genesis.
[SPEAKER_02]: Not until long after Genesis was done.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: and even then it was just Sonic and Vector Man and... Vector Man's pretty awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't even remember what else we had.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was that a big booger?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a chisel.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm trying to entertain.
[SPEAKER_08]: Since we're forced to use a, well, we're not really forced to use a webcam on Ustream, but, you know, it's weird to not have one.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've just been putting random objects in front of the camera because we're shy.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a radio show.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I didn't do my hair.
[SPEAKER_02]: One more paragraph.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck with the move to a new station.
[SPEAKER_02]: Your fans will follow you, so don't worry about that.
[SPEAKER_02]: Looking on the bright side, it sounds like Bobby will update his podcast feed, which hasn't been done in a couple of years.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, this is a great opportunity for Bobby to turn over a new leaf.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: And that's by Will.
[SPEAKER_02]: He sent a link, which I'm going to post in the chat room.
[SPEAKER_08]: He must have just written that in the past hour.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, it was there as of part A. Oh, there you go.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's a link to Pure Solar.
[SPEAKER_02]: Awesome.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I might have to give this a try.
[SPEAKER_02]: Is that a pelican?
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a pelican.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's move on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, Mailbag, of course, at OrangeLoungeRadio.com is the website if you want to send us your question for next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: We had a lot of questions tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now it's not time for questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's time for angst and destruction.
[SPEAKER_02]: FUs of the week, DarkSakura FU to being tired and having people not really understand the way that good design works Committees, just committees, they should just let me do everything and take it Also one on behalf of Becky, because I'm pissed off for her
[SPEAKER_02]: Um, fuck those little things that try to put you into a category and then hurt teacher for making her write about it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because I'm pissed off that she has to do it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I've come up with interesting titles for her papers, including Fuck Your Yankee Blue Jeans.
[SPEAKER_02]: And my suggestion to her for the summary of her essay is, in summary, fuck you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki?
[SPEAKER_07]: Thank you to myself for letting my backyard get so overgrown that I can only, not even really mow, I'd say hack through with a mower, a weed whacker, and various other tools.
[SPEAKER_07]: I can only get about most of my side yard done before I filled up two trash cans full of grass and vines.
[SPEAKER_07]: It is a jungle out there.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm going to give an FU to the fact that here we are trying to do our last show on all games.
[SPEAKER_08]: There isn't an all-game server tonight, but whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: These things happen.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just always seems to happen at key times.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will say a thank you.
[SPEAKER_08]: For the listener that says we don't do enough thank yous during the FUs, I'm going to say a thank you to all of the folks, live listeners, listeners.
[SPEAKER_08]: for being really understanding in light of the difficult announcement we made tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: I feel a lot of love and a lot of support.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that wasn't an easy thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've had to keep it under our wraps for a long time, and there's a sense of guilt that comes with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But thank you guys for understanding.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's awesome.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are great.
[SPEAKER_08]: And next week, hopefully, our new server won't go down.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, that's it for FUZE.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's get into a few more stories and then Twitter topics at twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: Just a few of those.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sky Flying.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to do Sky Flying as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: So let's try to run through these last few stories so we have time for a couple Skype calls because I know people want to get in tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: Okay, so Nintendo has made a patent for game emulation on low-capacity systems.
[SPEAKER_07]: Basically, some sort of device that they have, it looks like in an airplane or something like that, where somebody is playing some sort of game or something on the back of a chair.
[SPEAKER_07]: So basically, like an arm device or something like that, that would emulate Game Boy, Game Boy Color, Game Boy Advance games, systems like cell phones and stuff like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: Funny, because that already exists, you know, as emulators on, said, pretty much every platform known man.
[SPEAKER_07]: But now they're making it official, I guess, that they're going to do some sort of emulators.
[SPEAKER_07]: Which points more towards, you know, having some sort of software that runs on those, you know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Buy all the old shit all over again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_07]: Played in...
[SPEAKER_07]: I like how you can play them on the back of airplane seats or on my phone that I have or my game device or my tablet or whatever else because they have emulators for everything.
[SPEAKER_07]: Computer.
[SPEAKER_08]: LOL lawsuits Ubisoft and game trailers were sued this week over Assassin's Creed for that email earlier and Assassin's Creed copyright apparently Assassin's Creed stole core ideas from John Besswinger's novel Link Link was published in 2002 Assassin's Creed first came out in 2007 now yes that's right I said he's suing Ubisoft and game trailers
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_08]: His novel discusses assassinations and has spiritual and biblical tones similar to those in Assassin's Creed.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's also a battle between good and evil that was stolen right out of Link.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yours and every other book.
[SPEAKER_08]: Apparently the Link device is where users access ancestral memories and relive specific moments in history much as the Animus in Assassin's Creed does.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've never heard that plot device ever before.
[SPEAKER_07]: I came out with a book with fantasy characters and there's elves in it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want my money.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this is great.
[SPEAKER_08]: The estate of Tolkien will sue you.
[SPEAKER_08]: The guy is suing game trailers because of the trailers that infringe on the copyright.
[SPEAKER_08]: So just for hosting the trailer to Ubisoft's game, game trailers has been looped in.
[SPEAKER_08]: And that's where this thing went from okay, well maybe, to fucking absurd.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, there is going to be Silent Hill Revelation 3D.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yay!
[SPEAKER_02]: And it's going to be in the theaters.
[SPEAKER_02]: October 26th, which is my brother's birthday.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just saying.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am so excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it will have Sean Bean and Carrie Ann Moss.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it will sort of follow Silent Hill 3.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just that it's got Heather Mason in it and their stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: I find it fascinating it's most of the same cast from the first movie.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's great that they were able to get them all to come back.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I think that's cool.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will Sean Bean die?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because he dies in everything.
[SPEAKER_02]: I was just going to say that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, sorry.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't sue me.
[SPEAKER_02]: But apparently it's going to have Akira Yamaoka's music again.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: I am super, super excited.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it doesn't say who... It means I'm going to have to go on the wiki now to see who actually directed it because I don't think it's Gans this time.
[SPEAKER_08]: DJ Morpheus in the chat room Anne Rice came up with overly gay vampires first but no suit against Twilight okay I'm on I should be offended but I'm totally not that's great okay I'm on the IMDB and it said no it won't load okay does this mean does this mean OLR field trip to the movies OLR night at the movies movie date Michael J Bassett will DarkSakura and I share a popcorn I don't need popcorn
[SPEAKER_02]: Allergy to corn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Will Loki and I share popcorn?
[SPEAKER_02]: You and I, we can share.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I'm not sharing.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob.
[SPEAKER_02]: Share.
[SPEAKER_02]: Rob, Junior Mints.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, we'll share Junior Mints.
[SPEAKER_02]: We'll show Junior Mints.
[SPEAKER_08]: I just want an excuse to put my hand in the box at the same time we hold hands.
[SPEAKER_02]: Aw.
[SPEAKER_02]: But it's directed and written by Michael J. Bassett.
[SPEAKER_02]: And another person, this is Kit Harrington, who I have no idea who that is.
[SPEAKER_02]: Some dude whose mom's name is Debra.
[SPEAKER_02]: Oh, he's in Game of Thrones, no wonder, because I don't watch that stupid show
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm not going to go into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: I happen to know a lot of people really love that show.
[SPEAKER_08]: I haven't watched it.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm going to say what I've told lots of people.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't give a shit if you like it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't tell me how good it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's a really good series.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fuck off.
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan likes it.
[SPEAKER_02]: And this is what I have to say.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just because I don't like something that you like doesn't mean I'm making a statement about you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Don't take it personally.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or that it's bad necessarily.
[SPEAKER_02]: yeah it's just not something I'm into and it has nothing to do with my opinion of you if I know that you like it then I will be quiet and not you know shit talk it in front of you out of respect for my friendship with you but if I don't like it I'm not gonna hide that I don't like it a lot of people might think supernatural is the dumbest thing on TV and they're entitled to that don't tell me I don't care all right moving on
[SPEAKER_02]: You know how it is when you say, oh, I kind of don't like this, and everyone jumps on you.
[SPEAKER_02]: Why don't you like it?
[SPEAKER_02]: It's the best thing ever.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm offended that you don't like it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's how I feel when people tell me they don't like RuPaul's Drag Race.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's like, okay, hate on Ru all you want because Fifi O'Hara's in the final three, but seriously, it's the best fucking show on TV.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shut up.
[SPEAKER_02]: But you know what I mean.
[SPEAKER_02]: When people take their shit personally and it's not something they say personally.
[SPEAKER_08]: Black Wolf says, I take it personally.
[SPEAKER_08]: Legend of Zaku says, King Joffrey will have Jaime's head.
[SPEAKER_02]: What, after he gets stabbed sitting on his chair of swords?
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_02]: That's what I call it behind everyone's back is chair of swords.
[SPEAKER_02]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Right.
[SPEAKER_08]: S, Actdeft, Drew, Carameldansen
[SPEAKER_07]: It is featuring bikini model Yuki Kamamura and well, you have to roll over her breasts that protrude all over the place on the map.
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes, it's like those wonderful mouse pads that you can buy.
[SPEAKER_07]: You must navigate your monkey ball over a field of breasts.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well played.
[SPEAKER_08]: Boobies!
[SPEAKER_08]: I just worry this is going to start a new fetish of some type, and I worry.
[SPEAKER_08]: I worry for the future.
[SPEAKER_08]: I think it's awesome.
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, actually, if you remember, Super Monkey Ball was supposed to have it where you can actually create maps based off a picture.
[SPEAKER_07]: So if you took a picture of a banana, it would create a banana-shaped map.
[SPEAKER_07]: So what is the TTP for that game?
[SPEAKER_07]: How long before we have penis-shaped maps?
[SPEAKER_07]: Half a second?
[SPEAKER_07]: Two seconds?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_08]: um a millisecond a millisecond all right instance or instantaneous one Toa Gak in the chat room says so you move your balls over the boobs yes just like that
[SPEAKER_08]: All right, one more story for you guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: And guys, we have to end on a good note tonight because this is like the hero of the gaming industry this week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we have to end.
[SPEAKER_08]: We talk a lot of shit.
[SPEAKER_08]: We commentate a lot on this and sometimes have a very cynical attitude.
[SPEAKER_08]: But this guy deserves a fucking round of applause.
[SPEAKER_08]: And we're going to end by tipping our hats to this man tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Katsuhiro Harada Do you know that name?
[SPEAKER_08]: You would if you're a fan of Tekken He's the Tekken series producer Totally love
[SPEAKER_08]: And why is he our hero this week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because he's a pimp.
[SPEAKER_08]: He talked to Edge Online, who apparently has been getting a lot of people this week in interviews.
[SPEAKER_08]: And he says, well, he didn't say if you are worried about what Capcom's doing, then don't worry about this.
[SPEAKER_08]: But he did basically say no tech and game will ever have DLC characters at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: I tip my hat.
[SPEAKER_08]: No Tekken game will ever have DLC characters at all.
[SPEAKER_08]: Too bad Tekken 6 was shit, but we forgive you.
[SPEAKER_08]: We forgive you and stand by your amazing statement.
[SPEAKER_08]: Now, before you get too excited, he did say vanity items might be added to the game after the fact and would have a charge.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, you know, alternate costumes and pre-order bonuses for that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no DLC characters, which is good enough for me.
[SPEAKER_08]: If people want to play Barbie with their characters and that costs money, then fine.
[SPEAKER_08]: But no DLC characters.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what?
[SPEAKER_08]: Now make sure Tekken 7 is a good game.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know what's funny?
[SPEAKER_02]: You talking about playing Barbies with the characters?
[SPEAKER_02]: Dan was really into Dead or Alive Beach Volleyball.
[SPEAKER_02]: And he'd be like, look at this outfit!
[SPEAKER_02]: And I'm like, oh, you're being such a girl.
[SPEAKER_02]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_07]: I don't think that's what he was referring to as far as look at this outfit.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's more like, look at how small this outfit is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It would just be funny to think about how he got these different outfits.
[SPEAKER_02]: And I was like, oh.
[SPEAKER_08]: Skype line's open!
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype is Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Give us a call.
[SPEAKER_08]: We got time for a couple quick calls tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're running a little long due to the earlier announcement that caused Bobby to run long.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we will try to squeeze in a few calls here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again, 1-877-GAME-OLR or our username on Skype, Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, let me try to get to some tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have a whole lot of time, but I'm going to get to these as fast as I can here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTetsuya wants to remind everybody about The Hunt.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you, DarkTetsuya, for putting that on at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: I apologize that things have been kind of going to the back burner in spite of everything else going on with the announcements and things like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: But if you haven't checked it out, it's a fun little competition.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkTetsuya is trying to get the little scoreboard and get people into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's really cute.
[SPEAKER_08]: Check that out at OrangeLoungeRadio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Piece of advice, don't get eaten by a Gru.
[SPEAKER_08]: So you can guess where the next challenge is probably going.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, let's go to some calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Launch Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey, hey, it's Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, hey, hey, what's up?
[SPEAKER_06]: Not a lot.
[SPEAKER_06]: A couple things I wanted to discuss in regards to PAX East because I didn't get a chance to last time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: But before that, I just have one thing to say to you, Rob.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_06]: In the time I've listened to the show,
[SPEAKER_06]: You've worked your ass off.
[SPEAKER_06]: You've delivered so much.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I don't care what you say.
[SPEAKER_06]: You earned that diva fit you made.
[SPEAKER_06]: You earned that.
[SPEAKER_06]: I mean, for what you give back and for that one person to say something for you to fly off the handle like that, you earned it.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is four-year-old news, Ranma.
[SPEAKER_08]: This is... We're over.
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll probably... You know what's funny in light of all the news tonight about All Games and everything?
[SPEAKER_08]: That'll probably end up being the big highlight of OLR on the All Games Network.
[SPEAKER_06]: And between me and Misty, one of us has that episode on our hard drives.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, great.
[SPEAKER_08]: Misty's getting a present when she comes out here for the 10-year show, by the way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_08]: Shit, was I supposed to say that on air?
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, oops, I did.
[SPEAKER_08]: I found some old episodes.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, what did you really want to tell us tonight, Ranma, about PAX East?
[SPEAKER_06]: Just a couple of quick things.
[SPEAKER_06]: One thing was, you know the portable console lounge?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: And a lounge full of 3DSs, the Vita stands alone.
[SPEAKER_08]: Really?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like nobody brought Vitas or what happened?
[SPEAKER_06]: There was like one or two people with Vitas.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was like for every 10 3DSs you saw, you probably saw maybe one person with a Vita.
[SPEAKER_08]: you know what though it's everybody's trying to street pass and everybody's trying to clear their queue for find me and everything I gotta say I got a shit ton of street passes at Disneyland this week when I was there and um yeah I was able to get all the way to the second to last boss and find me too and let me tell you there's some real bullshit that happens in find me too can I just say who you trying to kid anyway
[SPEAKER_06]: No, no, I agree with you about Finding Me 2.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm like, who are you trying to kid?
[SPEAKER_08]: I know, it's kind of getting to the point where it's bullshit.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I will say this, I did also finish the Kid Icarus puzzle and the little swap puzzle thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's a pretty sweet little 3D image that it's like in motion.
[SPEAKER_06]: I finished that one.
[SPEAKER_06]: I'm still trying to finish up the rest of the puzzles as I continue to street pass every single day to and from work.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's actually something I was wondering about.
[SPEAKER_02]: What's that?
[SPEAKER_02]: With the lenticular photos that the 3DS takes, Dan's phone takes lenticular photos as well.
[SPEAKER_02]: I wonder if they would be readable by each other's... You might.
[SPEAKER_08]: See what kind of file format it does.
[SPEAKER_08]: See if you can put it on the web especially.
[SPEAKER_08]: If it can go on the web and then you can see it in the 3DS browser, it might work.
[SPEAKER_08]: It probably would.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just depends on the full frame.
[SPEAKER_02]: It just occurred to me.
[SPEAKER_08]: Play around with that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, anything else, Ranma?
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I was telling Jamie this last night, but as you know, the big thing about PAX is the Omegathon, right?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I am proud to say that one of my very good friends, Tina Lam, if I'm not mistaken, first female gamer to make it to the finals of the Omegathon.
[SPEAKER_08]: Good for her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Did she win?
[SPEAKER_06]: No, she came in second place.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had a feeling because you would have said the first female winner of the Omegathon if that was the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, that's too bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wasn't the last game some type of old school board game with the pucks?
[SPEAKER_08]: That's what I thought I heard somewhere.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, and on the ride back from PAX, my Twitter feed was blowing up because she goes by the name of Pork Bun.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we were like, go team Pork Buns.
[SPEAKER_06]: You can do it, Pork Buns.
[SPEAKER_06]: We were just going nuts, just rooting for her because we want her to win.
[SPEAKER_06]: But since she came in second, from what I was told, her and her partner are coming back next year to compete again.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: The runner-up always gets to compete again.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_08]: I've heard that before.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, good.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I told Jamie last night, I figured she would love to hear an awesome story like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: I totally think that we should interview her.
[SPEAKER_08]: One day, maybe DarkSakura should be in the final.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, we'd love to interview her.
[SPEAKER_08]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: It'd be fun.
[SPEAKER_06]: Well, I'll see what I can do.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it'd be great.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'd love that.
[SPEAKER_06]: Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Ranma, I've got to let you go because we've got a lot of calls trying to come in.
[SPEAKER_08]: So I'll talk to you later.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay, buddy?
[SPEAKER_06]: All right.
[SPEAKER_06]: Take care, bro.
[SPEAKER_06]: Stay fabulous.
[SPEAKER_08]: Of course.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: 1-877-GAME-OLR or I use your name on Skype as Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Getting you some tweets real quick here.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tiger Claw sends us a couple tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sony wants MMO players to meet each other in real life.
[SPEAKER_08]: What?
[SPEAKER_02]: Final Fantasy XI Fan Appreciation Events
[SPEAKER_08]: I guess that's kind of what you do with like the DS.
[SPEAKER_08]: Go to a Starbucks and get the Nintendo Zone or whatever.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's just like with Nier.
[SPEAKER_07]: That's all they're doing is Nier stuff.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that makes sense.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, that is.
[SPEAKER_08]: That is kind of like the same thing as Nier.
[SPEAKER_08]: I wonder if the Vita could facilitate that transfer.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe I'm thinking a little highbrow.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let's go to another call.
[SPEAKER_08]: Hi, you're on Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: Who's this?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Legend of Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's Zaku.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can see Zaku tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is up with this?
[SPEAKER_01]: Hi.
[SPEAKER_01]: Because I'm on my Mac, my monitor died tonight.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, yeah, I have a backup.
[SPEAKER_08]: I would put you on the Ustream if I knew how, but I wasn't prepared to go video tonight, so whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's on your mind, buddy?
[SPEAKER_01]: Nothing much, just like catching up on gaming and the...
[SPEAKER_01]: HBO Go and 360 for non-gaming stuff.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, mostly League of Legends and Battlefield.
[SPEAKER_01]: But yeah, it's been either of those two games.
[SPEAKER_01]: And going on what I've seen in packs, like in the Portable Gaming Lounge, I'm pretty certain, I think Adam was right, well, Ranma was right in the sense that, yeah, there probably was a little bit more of a lopsided towards 3DSs.
[SPEAKER_01]: Don't get me wrong, the beat is pretty good, especially for Lumines.
[SPEAKER_01]: But I would also imagine that not only 3DS would have to...
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, compete against the same space as folks with iPhones that I saw over there.
[SPEAKER_08]: Nier isn't also quite the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, Nier isn't the same as that 3DS StreetPass.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I seriously think a lot of those people were just trying to, like, I never get to StreetPass with people.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have never, ever played Find Me.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know, like, because, you know, a lot of people don't take their DSs with them everywhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: But a convention like PAX is a great place to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Even then, there were still folks on their iPads playing all the other types of iPad games, not limited to Angry Birds.
[SPEAKER_08]: They were just showing off that they had the fancy new ones.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, they had their iPads or their tablets, but it was pretty much like, obviously the 3DS was the only traditional portable game console that was represented, but everything else was still mobile.
[SPEAKER_01]: I even had the chance to break out my
[SPEAKER_01]: You know, my phone for a bit, but, you know, battery was getting there.
[SPEAKER_01]: But you get the idea that it's not just 3DS anymore when you have, like, when you have mobile, especially... I'm trying to remember.
[SPEAKER_01]: Ah!
[SPEAKER_01]: I think it was... I forgot which one from Nintendo actually said that he actually liked Angry Birds...
[SPEAKER_08]: I do remember reading that same quote, something about, you know, like kind of tipping the hats of the competition.
[SPEAKER_08]: Angry Birds ain't that bad.
[SPEAKER_01]: And yet he goes against the wishes of his boss, who basically chides Angry Birds for basically going after their bread and butter.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, but you know he's played it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, but I guess Nintendo didn't keep these... I don't know if they're keeping their guys on a PR leash, but that's kind of damaging if the official company line is like, we hate casual gamers.
[SPEAKER_01]: Anything outside of, we hate casual developers.
[SPEAKER_01]: The guys who create Angry Birds or any other...
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't think Nintendo hates casual gamers.
[SPEAKER_08]: Look at what we just talked about tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Mario 2, who's that really aimed at?
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a hodgepodge of the casual and the hardcore market.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's like that whole platform where people could just buy a developer license for an iPhone developer account.
[SPEAKER_01]: for $200 and make an app that they sell for $2 a pop and make hundreds of thousands in profits.
[SPEAKER_01]: Meanwhile, folks who are doing the same for 3DS have to go through the licensing fees and they're lucky to break even.
[SPEAKER_01]: I guess my point is that with these platforms that have very little overhead, it's a lot easier to create breakout hits for audiences that Nintendo may or may not pick up due to them not taking that many risks.
[SPEAKER_01]: It goes back to the fact that, I hate to say this, but most of the Japanese developers are not that much of a risk takers.
[SPEAKER_01]: What did we just talk about with Konami?
[SPEAKER_01]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, whereas the Western counterparts, at least they understand that if they don't innovate or they don't take risks, they're pretty much dead in the water.
[SPEAKER_08]: And some have lost big, unfortunately, and that's why we hear about these studio closures and so on.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sako, I've got to let you go so we can get some more calls, but I'm glad you had a good time at PAX East.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll hopefully see you next year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Definitely Later buddy Bye
[SPEAKER_00]: Oh, thank God.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's Porkchop.
[SPEAKER_00]: How you doing?
[SPEAKER_08]: Hey, Porkchop.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is up?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, I've been trying to get through all night.
[SPEAKER_00]: I lost the shoutcast feed, so I have to switch between Ustream.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm doing everything on my Android, so it's good to finally actually get through and start talking.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, what happened wasn't ideal, unfortunately, but it is what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, I know.
[SPEAKER_00]: You guys are having the night from hell, and it's supposed to be really nice as you're kind of moving on and that kind of thing, so it's got to be a pain in the ass.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thanks for watching!
[SPEAKER_08]: Our listeners are so awesome that they would just follow us to, oh shit, go to Ustream?
[SPEAKER_08]: Alright, we're there.
[SPEAKER_08]: And look at you, you're juggling your Android and you're trying to go to Ustream back and forth just so you can call.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's great.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's not the case at night, it's the morning.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's like 5 o'clock here.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have a lot to do tomorrow, but I decided to dedicate it at this stage.
[SPEAKER_00]: I really enjoy the station.
[SPEAKER_08]: You guys are dedicated.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, why not?
[SPEAKER_08]: I wish I could tell you that the show was going to be on earlier in the future, but that's not the case.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry to say.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't care.
[SPEAKER_00]: I love it.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll still listen in.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I actually wanted to say that, you know, I was going to ask what was so bad about Tekken 6?
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it wasn't all that bad of a game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Apart from the whole it's been chopped and changed a bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: I can understand that you don't have, you know, go get your characters anymore.
[SPEAKER_00]: DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura, DarkSakura,
[SPEAKER_08]: But we were just kind of playing it going, eh, this game's kind of, we're not, like, we're just not into it.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I don't know what it is.
[SPEAKER_08]: Alan, can you explain?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yeah, we did story mode or whatever with a few characters.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's like, we didn't really recognize the roster.
[SPEAKER_05]: And there were a lot of characters, but no one felt interesting.
[SPEAKER_05]: And we played story mode a few times and beat the end boss.
[SPEAKER_05]: And it's like, this isn't really compelling us.
[SPEAKER_05]: It wasn't.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's kind of, I don't know, average.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's that... Yeah, I can kind of see where you're coming from.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, it's more than Soul Calibur, to be honest, because you play that and in a few hours you're done.
[SPEAKER_00]: But, I mean, the Arena mode was very lacking.
[SPEAKER_00]: You just go in the scenario, you play through with these guys, and even though they're already in the fucking other modes, you can just play straight away.
[SPEAKER_00]: It still gives you the option to go get them and then you can play through or you can get the random movie.
[SPEAKER_00]: But again, you can just play a load of matches until you actually get those.
[SPEAKER_00]: Like every 10 matches you got like an ending or a scenario, movie, whatever.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think you make some good points but as a big Tekken fan, I mean graphically it was great and they kind of introduced some weird characters.
[SPEAKER_00]: but I mean I think they did okay with it and Tekken 7 yeah I mean and I'm a fan of Capcom don't get me wrong I like their games a lot of their games but you know let's hope they get better and as for the DLC that's great news as well I will say this I am super curious especially in light of the DLC news you know we did get Street Fighter X Tekken but remember they're supposed to be a Tekken X Street Fighter as a part of this Namco is going to get their chance too so I'm
[SPEAKER_08]: Really freaking curious.
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, I kind of hope that's one of the things that's coming out at E3 this year, you know, to get the first look at is the Tekken Cross Street Fighter.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the other half going to look like?
[SPEAKER_08]: Because remember... Yeah, I lost.
[SPEAKER_00]: Sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_08]: No, I was just going to say there was always Capcom versus SNK was a huge, huge, huge game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, there was also SNK versus Capcom that wasn't bad.
[SPEAKER_08]: It just didn't quite get that same, you know, didn't catch on.
[SPEAKER_00]: I wasn't a big fan.
[SPEAKER_00]: I liked the Capcom SNK games, but the other one, that's 3CKS, wasn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh yeah, SVC Chaos, that's right.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, that was, I didn't really like the look of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: It looked very, you know, I was kind of like, you know, let's push the envelope a little bit.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah, but it didn't look great.
[SPEAKER_00]: I didn't really, you know, fall into that side of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: Again, I had a point to make, I can't remember.
[SPEAKER_00]: Anyway, yeah, well, let's hope that, I mean, I saw the box art for Tekken X Street Fighter, whatever it was.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think it's going to be a pretty cool game.
[SPEAKER_00]: Let's hope they don't fuck up like Capcom did.
[SPEAKER_00]: Leave the shit on the disc.
[SPEAKER_00]: Hackers gonna hack and all that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yes, sir.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wyland in our chatroom says Tekken X Street Fighter is 10% complete.
[SPEAKER_08]: Wow.
[SPEAKER_02]: By the way, I would like to point out that my personal favorite in the Tekken series was Tekken 3.
[SPEAKER_08]: Me too, absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: Absolutely, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yoshimitsu never looked cooler, so he stuck through there to the next game, Street Fighter X Tekken.
[SPEAKER_00]: I think he looks the same as far as I remember.
[SPEAKER_07]: I used... I'm sorry, go ahead.
[SPEAKER_02]: I used Jin, and they changed his moves as of Tekken 4, which he had, like, my favorite Jun moves, and all the rest were Kazuya moves, and I was in love.
[SPEAKER_02]: But, yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: I actually like both.
[SPEAKER_00]: I mean, I think it's cool that, you know, because Kazuya was, in quotation marks, dead.
[SPEAKER_00]: you know that they actually stuck Jim in and said okay well here's his illegitimate son or whatever but the whole I hate my dad thing then in Tekken 4 um yeah why not I think I think the karate kind of looks cool when he does it but again you know you don't want too many characters with the same moves you got Heihachi and Kazooie are pretty much the same um yeah so it's fresh it's new it worked I think it worked for me anyway so I mean up to you if you like it or not
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, Porkchop, I got to let you go so we can wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: But I appreciate you sharing your perspective.
[SPEAKER_08]: There's nothing wrong with a friendly little talk about what games we do and don't like.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, Porkchop, take care, buddy, and thanks again for staying up late.
[SPEAKER_08]: Absolutely.
[SPEAKER_00]: Keep the dream alive, guys.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the best.
[SPEAKER_08]: Take care, buddy.
[SPEAKER_07]: I was going to say that the reason why it's only 10% done is because they're working on Tag 2 right now.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's supposed to be a big one.
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, it's going to come up on multiple consoles this year, isn't it?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: So, all right.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me burn through.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to close the Skype line.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm sorry to those that didn't get through.
[SPEAKER_08]: Very sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Please consider sending us an email, mailbag at orangelawntrader.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: Again...
[SPEAKER_08]: The show isn't ending.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's a very important point.
[SPEAKER_08]: So we'll have a show just like always next week, especially podcasties.
[SPEAKER_08]: If you're listening on the podcast feed, you're going to be like, oh, next week?
[SPEAKER_08]: Like, same show, but I'm just hearing some slightly different websites given and some different things that will slowly unravel itself throughout the coming year.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyway, back to some tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Tigerclaw also tweeted us, New Facebook lawsuit highlights trouble with kids and virtual currency.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, God.
[SPEAKER_08]: I can only imagine how the kids can just rack up all this money so easily.
[SPEAKER_08]: It's kind of sick.
[SPEAKER_08]: But yeah, another complaint was filed against Facebook with the U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: District Court.
[SPEAKER_08]: According to this link, the Tiger Claw sent us at Gamasutra.
[SPEAKER_08]: This isn't the only instance of companies getting in trouble over minors purchasing credits for social games.
[SPEAKER_08]: A U.S.
[SPEAKER_08]: District Judge upheld a handful of claims that Apple distributed free iOS apps that trick children into money in-app purchases.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: Children are allowed to do Facebook accounts from the age of 13.
[SPEAKER_08]: However, if you're under the age of 18, you're supposed to ask for your parents' permission before buying Facebook credits.
[SPEAKER_08]: I'm surprised it's just not shut off altogether.
[SPEAKER_07]: Considering that you have to put your credit card information in, I believe that if you're 13, you don't have a credit card.
[SPEAKER_08]: How hard is it to open mom's wallet?
[SPEAKER_07]: Well, then that's a problem with fraud, and they should throw that kid in jail.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_08]: Throw the kids in jail.
[SPEAKER_08]: SJ100Matt says, Hey, remember Para Para Paradise?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, fuck yeah, I love that game.
[SPEAKER_08]: Well, a new Para-style arcade machine is coming out soon, and yes, it has Gaga.
[SPEAKER_08]: Oh, because every freaking music game these days has to have Gaga.
[SPEAKER_08]: Don't get me wrong, I love Lady Gaga, but damn.
[SPEAKER_08]: Dance Core is the game, I guess, that's coming out.
[SPEAKER_08]: He links us to a little YouTube of somebody playing it.
Yeah!
[SPEAKER_09]: What is it?
[SPEAKER_08]: It just looks like something.
[SPEAKER_08]: K-pop!
[SPEAKER_08]: It's going to be on Kinect.
[SPEAKER_08]: Maybe not in this country, but it'll be Kinect.
[SPEAKER_08]: But they say, yeah, they say in the article it's more closer to Power, Power, Paradise than it is like DDR or Dance Central or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Or maybe Dance Masters because that kind of had a lot of power in it.
[SPEAKER_08]: But anyway.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's really... I think that's going to do it for tweets tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys for sending us tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: Twitter.com slash OLR.
[SPEAKER_08]: But we've got to wrap up the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: We've got to wrap it... Oh, wait.
[SPEAKER_08]: I got one last tweet that came in.
[SPEAKER_08]: Let me read this one from GamerGirl.
[SPEAKER_08]: I have a question regarding GLBT.
[SPEAKER_08]: I know someone who is bi and they want to come out, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_08]: What is the best way to do so?
[SPEAKER_02]: Woo!
[SPEAKER_02]: You turn the knob, open the door.
[SPEAKER_02]: Here we go.
[SPEAKER_08]: Um...
[SPEAKER_08]: I know there's a lot of you know obviously I'm speaking as the gay guy on the show I know there's a lot of society pressures that come with like coming out and all that stuff and sometimes it's one of those things people kind of feel like they kind of have to do to get it off their chest I really truly believe a shirt person should not feel like they're forced to do it until they're ready because taking that first step to really like come out to yourself can be one of the hardest things you have to do in that whole process
[SPEAKER_08]: so, you know, don't ever feel any pressure that you do or you don't have to do anything you know, for your friend, whoever your friend wants to love is their choice whoever your friend wants to have a relationship with is ultimately their choice you know, that's a private matter that is public when you want it to be public, your friend
[SPEAKER_08]: So they want to come out or whatever.
[SPEAKER_08]: What's the best way to do so?
[SPEAKER_08]: You need to tell the people that are closest to you.
[SPEAKER_08]: True friends are not going to turn the other way.
[SPEAKER_08]: Some may kind of say, you know, I'm always kind of suspected, but it doesn't really change anything.
[SPEAKER_08]: I had the really good fortune that when I came out, everybody was supportive.
[SPEAKER_08]: There was very few people that I got into shit with.
[SPEAKER_08]: And anybody that was a problem, ain't in my life anymore.
[SPEAKER_08]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_08]: You know?
[SPEAKER_08]: But there's been a lot of great people that most people I know just don't really care.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I think that's fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: I will say this.
[SPEAKER_02]: Most of my friends that came out and told me, I was usually like, duh.
[SPEAKER_08]: The fact that it's bi and not gay can be a really tricky line to walk as well.
[SPEAKER_08]: and you know that could be a lot you know this could be somebody who's still questioning in a lot of ways and says maybe I'm having these type of tendencies you know or whatever all I'm saying don't ever don't ever feel like whoever you are you have to pigeonhole yourself into one bucket or another or whatever just love somebody
[SPEAKER_08]: and you know my best preferably yourself first yeah oh yeah absolutely starting with yourself accept yourself and everybody else will come easy that's the best advice I can give love yourself first then those closest to you and your true friends will show their colors now can I say the witty thing yes
[SPEAKER_02]: For the ones that come easy, some people are easy.
[SPEAKER_02]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: Stop.
[SPEAKER_08]: All right.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it for tweets.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it for Skype calls.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's it for the show.
[SPEAKER_08]: Thank you guys for staying up late with us on what has been a very interesting episode of Orange Lounge Radio.
[SPEAKER_08]: and a new chapter starts next week.
[SPEAKER_08]: And can't wait to tell you all the details a little later.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll stay tuned to our Twitter feed, twitter.com slash OLR, our Facebook, facebook.com slash Orange Launch Radio, our website, of course, orangelaunchradio.com.
[SPEAKER_08]: All the details in the coming days will be on the website.
[SPEAKER_08]: That's all I have to say for now on that.
[SPEAKER_08]: Anyhow, everything else about the whole situation will be in the podcast feed.
[SPEAKER_08]: We're going to replay the call that happened with Bobby and I think everything else we had to say on it is all contained in there.
[SPEAKER_08]: In the meantime, let's go around and get everybody's final thoughts.
[SPEAKER_08]: Loki, your final thoughts tonight.
[SPEAKER_07]: This is really strange, but there was this kid, because I took Josh to the park today, practicing his unicycle, which begged the question, if a bicycle can be shortened to a bike, would a unicycle be a eunuch?
[SPEAKER_09]: My final thought is...
[SPEAKER_08]: I felt this weekend that I have a lot of drama in my life right now, but I feel really good tonight.
[SPEAKER_08]: And I want to thank all of you for being a part of that.
[SPEAKER_08]: DarkSakura?
[SPEAKER_02]: Because people will shoot me if I don't say it.
[SPEAKER_02]: Reject false icons.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a wonderful night, everybody.
[SPEAKER_08]: We'll see you next week somewhere.
[SPEAKER_08]: Have a good night.
[SPEAKER_08]: Until then.
[SPEAKER_04]: or allgames.com, but we're probably right anyway.
[SPEAKER_04]: See you next week!